Chapter 324: An Approaching Conspiracy

If the route that Leylin had taken had been filled with hordes of darkness creatures on the way to the eastern capital, the journey would not have been so quiet.

Even if Leylin were to survive, Baelin, Jenny, and James definitely would have died in the mouths of these dark elemental beasts.

It was obvious that within the icy caves, in the places that these beasts convened, they hated light; they would attack with all they had the moment that they detected any.

“Even I would need to spend a lot of time and magic to deal with all of those bats every day. It’s not worth it.”

Leylin sighed.

While the groups of bats were running amok, he had used a concealment spell. Hence, he had naturally not been pursued or attacked by the bats.

After doing some experiments, Leylin made up his mind.

“Night Vision!” He used this spell on himself.

This was an essential spell for many Magi in the subterranean world. With this spell, they could see things in the dark as if it were day without giving off any light that would attract aggressive beasts.

“A.I. Chip, display the map in your records!”

After he casted the spell, Leylin gave an order to the A.I. Chip.

Immediately after, a 3D image appeared in front of his eyes.

This was the simulated model the A.I. Chip had formed after analysing the map Celine had given him.

Nearby Leylin, there were red dots that constantly moved nearby Leylin, indicating the activity of high-energy beings. Compared to the previous inflexible map, this was even more detailed and reliable.

In a cave like this that was as complicated as a maze, Leylin had a definite advantage with his A.I. Chip. At the very least, with the A.I. Chip recording down everything, he would not get lost.

The icy cave could easily cause people to get lost. Every year, there were acolytes or even Magi in the guild who got completely lost in the cave. According to other Magi, if they had been enticed to enter deeper areas, they would have likely died in the mouths of the dark elemental beasts.

“Show me the best route to where the Icy Jade Scorpions are the most active!”

Leylin ordered once again.

Then, on the surface of the 3D map, a red line extended from the marker for Leylin’s current location. It led to the deeper levels of the icy cave, even marking a few important areas.

“Let’s go!”

Leylin looked around him and then disappeared into the crevasse.

Within the fort, in a concealed room.

Skrill saw the scene of Celine sending Leylin into the icy caves through a crystal ball, a grim expression on his face.

“Did that bitch Celine think that I wouldn’t dare do anything to her if she found a peak rank 1 Magus to depend on?”

Skrill’s facial muscles began to contort as he stared at the shapely body in the image, his expression especially insatiable and passionate.

“You’re mine, and I will get you and make you my most beautiful treasure!”

Skrill moaned in an abnormal way.

“How is it? Have you made your decision?” Meanwhile, in a corner of the world, black mist rose and constantly changed shape, eventually turning into a human figure with vague features.

“There’s a large issue with your plan. Celine has already recruited a peak rank 1 Magus into her Nature’s Alliance. Our original plan will not work.”

In front of others, Skrill concealed his previous expression and seemed cold.

“Peak rank 1?!” A startled gasp was heard from the mist. “Is your information accurate? Why would a peak rank 1 Magus be willing to join a small guild?”

“How would I know?” Skrill’s face darkened. Being scared away by Leylin like that was the ultimate humiliation for him.

“He could easily repel the elemental particles around me, and his elemental conversion was at a very high level. Even if he’s not a peak rank 1 Magus, he can’t be too far from that… I wonder if that whore, Celine, tempted him…”

At the mention of Celine, Skrill’s mood worsened again, leaving him feeling frustrated and unresigned, as if a delicacy meant for him had been robbed by someone else.

“Jeje, a peak rank 1 Magus is a little troublesome, but you should also believe in the guild backing us. A peak rank 1 Magus is definitely not enough to hinder our plan!”

The person shrouded in the mist was very confident.

“What do you plan to do? A peak rank 1 Magus isn’t so easily dealt with. Besides, two peak rank fighting would definitely lead to a huge commotion. Aren’t you afraid of being exposed?” A curious look appeared on Skrill’s face.

“Jeje! It’s not as if we don’t have a peak rank 1 Magus in our organisation. Did you forget about that good opportunity we have? He will definitely accept!”

“Do you mean…” Skrill’s eyes brightened.

……

“Hah…”

Leylin breathed out white mist.

The moment water vapour reached the outside air, it immediately condensed into tiny crystals that fell to the ground and produced slight sounds.

“A.I. Chip, what’s the current temperature?” Leylin casually asked.

[The temperature is now -75 degrees Celsius!” The A.I. Chip immediately answered.

This temperature was more than deadly for regular humans, but in Leylin’s eyes, this was a mere chill.

As he advanced deeper, he reached the very borders where Celine’s map indicated.

It was at this place that he entered the territory where the Icy Jade Scorpions were active.

“The Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath!” Fire burned in Leylin’s eyes. This material was extremely effective in suppressing the issues he had from his bloodline, and so he definitely needed to get his hands on it!

As the overall data and gene composition was different between Magi, this was as good as hitting the jackpot for Leylin. If he missed this opportunity, he really had no clue where he would find this material again.

[Discovered being that matches Host’s description. Distance: 621 metres.] The A.I. Chip prompted, causing Leylin to perk up.

He followed in the direction the A.I. Chip indicated, and not long after, he saw the actual body of the being.

At the end of the tunnels of the icy caves, there was a huge cave, on the surface of which were mosses and little bushes, forming a rather infertile area where food was produced.

Here, two groups of beings were having an intense confrontation.

On one end was a large, transparent, green scorpion that looked as if its entire body was made of green ice.

The two large pincers in front constantly danced back and forth, and its venomous sting curved behind it, moving erratically and looking ready to strike.

Blue, chilly air was produced occasionally, from the mouth of this Icy Jade Scorpion, and spat towards its opponent.

With just a look, Leylin knew that this large Icy Jade Scorpion was what he was looking for.

Facing the Icy Jade Scorpion was a group of blue ants.

These ants were the size of a mature adult’s finger. Their two large and sharp saw teeth kept opening and closing, producing terrifying, ear-piercing sounds.

It was a pity that in the face of the hard shell of the Icy Jade Scorpion, their attacks were futile.

Even if they crawled all over the body of the Icy Jade Scorpion, they could not affect its movements. On the contrary, every time the Icy Jade Scorpion raised its large pincers, numerous ants were sent flying.

The chilly air puffed out by the Icy Jade Scorpion also froze many of the ants into little crystals, which it then swallowed.

This was a battle where the Icy Jade Scorpion was foraging for food. It was the absolute winner here.

“A.I. Chip, scan the data of the Icy Jade Scorpion in front of me!”

Leylin immediately ordered. After advancing to become a rank 2 Warlock, the A.I. Chip that was spiritually bonded to him had also gained many benefits. Besides a power up in its simulation abilities, beings like this that had force-field related innate skills could have their data taken down as long as they were below rank 2.

Of course, for beings above rank 2, the A.I. Chip would be discovered and counterattack.

[Icy Jade Scorpion’s Strength: 15.9, Agility: 10.3, Vitality: 25, Spiritual force: 45, Special attacks: 1. Icy Breath: An attack where the Icy Jade Scorpion spits out large amounts of extreme icy air. Power: 30-45 degrees. 2. Freeze: When heavily injured, the Icy Jade Scorpion can seal itself in ice and lower its bodily needs to the minimum until its body completely heals. 3. Icy Armour: The icy layer on the surface of the Icy Jade Scorpion’s body can effectively defend against physical and magical attacks, and also has a slight rebound effect on light magic.]

The A.I. Chip quickly sent out a row of data, and displayed a projection of that Icy Jade Scorpion in front of him.

“Even amongst rank 1 Magi, this is quite powerful!”

Leylin judged.

A Magus’s strength could generally be decided based on their spiritual force. Acolytes were definitely below 20, while rank 1 Magi, which were otherwise known as official Magi, had a spiritual force between 20 and 80. As for rank 2 Magi, it was above 80. Based on Leylin’s conjectures and the simulations from the A.I. Chip, the spiritual force of peak rank 2 Magi could reach 200!

The strength of most rank 1 Magi’s spells was between 20 and 80 degrees.

Not only were its various stats were extremely high, the strength of its breath could even reach past a degree of 30. With its innate defensive spell-like icy armour, even a regular rank 1 Magus was not its opponent.

“This strength is almost that of a semi-converted Magus. I wonder what the elites or even emperors of the Icy Jade Scorpions are like?”

At this point, the battle had also reached an end.

Chapter 329: The Headquarters’ Location

”I…I…”

Mully hesitated. Although he doubted the other party’s strength, Magi were a rational bunch. If it wasn’t for Celine, he would not even dare to provoke the other party.

Now, he was somewhat uncertain.

If Leylin really possessed such huge power and he decided to challenge him, wouldn’t he be courting death?

Immediately, Mully opened his mouth wide, “ This… this is…”

In this moment, Leylin had already thrown the ice mountain on the floor, producing a loud sound.

Within the ice mountain stood a thin bodied Icy Jade Scorpion that was unmoving, as if it were a statue.

“Celine! Get some people here and move these items!” Leylin contacted Celine through the secret imprint, and from the other end came a surprised squeal.

“Oh? Previously, Magus Leylin went down with the purpose to do research on the Icy Jade Scorpion. It looks like his gains were pretty good! Unexpectedly, he even caught a smaller one. It seems like it’s a young one!”

Old Madre smiled and explained.

While in its frozen state, the Icy Jade Scorpion’s breath was suppressed to its lowest and Old Madre did not see it.

“No, damn it! This isn’t some young Icy Jade Scorpion! It’s the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor! A peak rank 1 Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor!” Mully retreated while stammering.

“I have seen it before. This is absolutely the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor! Look at the terrifying markings on its back!”

Mully retreated to the edge of the site, afraid that the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor would go wild at any time.

“Raurghhh… Seriously!”

Madre picked up what seemed like a pair of glasses and placed it on his nose, taking a good look at the Icy Jade Scorpion. This was then followed by a squeal as she took a few steps back.

“Mag… Magus Leylin! Di- Did you catch this?”

Old Madre started to stammer as well.

“Of course!” Leylin smiled and nodded.

After having suppressed the emotional instability from his bloodline, Leylin massacred all of the regular Icy Jade Scorpions and collected their materials. As for the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor, he could not bear to kill it.

After all, its value while still alive was much greater than the value of the materials on its body.

He still had many simulations that he needed to complete on the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor, and Leylin was also extremely interested in the waning of the Icy Jade Scorpion’s life once it were to leave the radiation from the icy cave.

Hence, he had to wrap the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor and bring it out.

Leylin could only gather all the materials from the regular Icy Jade Scorpions inside the spatial pouch, and since it could not hold living beings, he had to carry an ice mountain all the way out.

However, the look of disbelief on the faces of these two Magi that turned into one of respect was rather amusing to Leylin.

He did not intentionally try to conceal his powers, but there was the underlying intent of showing his might.

After all, the might of a peak rank 1 Magus was not unfounded, and an Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor with a strength comparable to a peak rank 1 Magus was enough to intimidate everyone.

Although Celine had been actively disseminating the information of her guild, she had not acquired the acknowledgment from the other guilds as Leylin had been keeping a low profile. Most Magi had even thought of this as an elaborate scam and were here merely to look for trouble.

But now, these small guilds would think twice before coming forward.

Though he wasn’t afraid of trouble, he hated having to personally involve himself in these small matters. It wasn’t a bad idea to scare them away with this Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor.

Even between peak rank 1 Magi, their battle abilities were varied. Since Leylin was able to catch a Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor that was similar to a peak rank 1 Magus, didn’t that mean that he was at the top of the peak rank 1 Magi?

Old Madre and Mully exchanged glances, and their gazes towards Leylin was filled with reverence.

“Lord Leylin, it’s great that you could come back safely!”

At this point, Celine was excited as she brought back the two acolytes from before.

Leylin looked at them and nodded. It seemed like Celine had been waiting here with these two acolytes after he had left, which was rather considerate of her.

“An Icy Jade Scorpion is a creature with the might of an official Magus and they lived in clusters. Initially, I had my worries, but thankfully we were under the blessing of Gaia!”

Celine patted herself on her chest and was hesitant at the start, as she was worried for Leylin.

Hearing that, Old Madre and Mully surreptitiously rolled their eyes.

The one who should be worried should be the Icy Jade Scorpions. This Lord had already captured the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor and the remaining Icy Jade Scorpions had either disbanded or sought refuge with the other cyclones.

At this moment, Celine found the ice mountain beside Leylin, “ Do we need to move this?”

“En! Send two people to follow me to shift it to the Eastern capital before we look for a lab to analyse it further.” Leylin patted on the ice mountain behind him.

“ If you wish to find a lab, the headquarters of the Nature’s Alliance is just nearby for your Lordship’s usage.”

Celine’s eyes sparkled and suggested, “Furthermore, I would like to discuss in detail with your Lordship regarding the previous matter.”

“Your headquarters is nearby? Great, let’s go!” Leylin nodded in agreement. There wasn’t anything important in the basement he used in the eastern capital. All valuable equipment was carried on his person at all times.

As for the overall facilities, Nature’s Alliance’s lab was definitely better than his own established lab.

“Hop on and call another carriage to move this ice mountain back to the headquarters!”

Celine commanded. She went forward to take a good look at the Icy Jade Scorpion.

Through the translucent ice, a rune that closely resembled a face could be seen at the back of the Icy Jade Scorpion.

“This is… the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor!!!” Celine covered her mouth with her eyes wide opened.

……

Whoosh!

A huge waterfall which seemed to fall from the sky like a white curtain, created huge splashes in the underground pond. A constant rumbling sound of the water echoed in the surroundings.

After passing the waterfall, there was a small canyon.

Scattered around the canyon was a variety of plantations and some historical structures.

The landmarks and road signs were covered in vines, with constant rays of light shining from above.

This was where the Nature’s Alliance headquarters resided.

Leylin looked around with curiosity at the whimsical constructions.

Although these buildings appeared slightly run-down, there were slight glints of magical glows which indicated the existence of a powerful spell that had been cast on the wooden walls.

Nature’s Alliance, albeit being a small guild, had accumulated their high-level meditation techniques over multiple generations in the past hundreds and thousands of years, proving their might.

Periodically, a few Magi acolytes, dressed in grey gowns, would come out of the building to greet Celine.

“Oh Celine, it has been so long since you last visited!”

At the same time, a grey mole jumped out from a human-sized mushroom and lifted its claw, greeting Celine.

The grey mole was the size of a boy and had sparkling bright eyes brimming with liveliness. It had a spotlessly white moustache that dropped down from the bottom of its mouth to the floor.

“Nice to meet you, Grandpa Cedric!”

Celine expressed with respect, “I brought your favourite berries!”

Celine carefully placed the two strange fruits that looked like green dates on the ground.

“En! Not bad! That’s my favourite!” The gigantic mole used its agile claws to pick up the fruits and threw them into its mouth, crunching noisily,

“This is my newly recruited famous professor, Leylin Farlier! He will be having the same level of authority as me!” Celine introduced, after the mole finished eating.

“Leylin what?” The mole took a good look at Leylin with beaming eyes. “En! Deep and immeasurable power! Looks like you have pinned all your hopes on him…:”

Leylin looked at the mole, “ A guard animal? It has the strength of a rank 1 Magus. Not bad.”

At this time, Celine introduced to Leylin, “ Grandpa Cedric was Nature’s Alliance’s guardian during my great great grandmother’s time. He is usually very gentle, just don’t disturb his sleep…”

After introducing the two to each other, Celine brought Leylin to a hall.

There were tens of acolytes waiting in there. Seated at the front were Obo and Ilya whom Leylin previously met.

“To think that a Magus guild will end up with only a rank 1 Magus, an animal as a gatekeeper and a few apprentices. What a failure!”

Leylin became speechless as he followed Celine in.

Celine went forward and introduced Leylin to the acolytes, “This is Professor Leylin whom I’ve invited over! From now, all of you need to respect him like how you respect me. No, you all should treat him with even more respect, do you all hear me?”

“Professor Leylin!” The acolyte greeted with their beaming eyes.

Leylin’s past achievements slowly spread around through Obo and Ilya. The apprentices felt extremely happy and elated knowing that they have a rank 1 Magus taking charge.

“Nice to meet all of you! A Magus is a follower of the truth. I hope to see all of you in the hall in the future!”

Leylin spoke a few words and indicated Celine to let the students leave.

All along, Leylin did not like such situations and furthermore, he was not interested in the group of acolytes.

The sole purpose of gathering the students was to introduce Leylin. The introduction ended within minutes, leaving Celine and Leylin in the hall after the students left.

“Can we talk now? Seems like something was wrong before I left the icy cave.”

Leylin took a glance at Celine as he asked with a smile.

“I can’t seem to hide anything from you!” Celine bit her lips and finally made up her mind.

Chapter 331: Remodeling By Freezing

In the Nature’s Alliance’s laboratory.

Leylin stared at the large ice mountain, his expression revealing his regret.

Around the ice mountain were numerous crystals that were emitting blue light that constantly swept across the ice mountain. They formed a spell formation, and the blue light.

[Failure of simulating icy radiation. Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor’s life force is gradually weakening.]

The A.I. Chip intoned with no emotion.

*Bang!* All of a sudden, the crystals emitting blue light exploded, and the rays from the spell formation dimmed.

“Is it still a failure?” Leylin sighed.

This was the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor that he had taken captive. Ever since he had brought it from the icy caves, it had been constantly weakening. This was even happening while it was in its frozen state, or else it would have long since died.

Leylin had no other ideas. After multiple failures while trying to simulate the special radiation from the icy world, he had already given up on this idea and was preparing to make use of this Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor as much as he could.

“It’s impossible to extract an ancient bloodline from it, and I’ve already recorded all the information I’ve obtained from its blood. So…”

Leylin shifted his gaze to the back of the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor. The rune of a distorted woman’s face seemed to be alive.

Through the memories in its bloodline, Leylin knew that this type of Icy Jade Scorpion originated from the Scorpion Man that had the might of a Morning Star Magus.

The moment Scorpion Man had been drawn into the spatial crack, a drop of the female giant’s blood landed on his back.

From then on, the Scorpion Man’s bloodline was tainted by the blood of a higher ranking being.

The descendants of the Scorpion Man all had this rune on their backs.

Strictly speaking, the rune on the back of the Icy Jade Scorpion was just a projection of the power of the female giant’s bloodline.

However, just a projection and the wail it let out was enough to almost catch Leylin in an illusion.

In addition, the bloodlines of these higher ranked creatures all possessed incredible might even if there was just an aura of it left.

“A.I. Chip, how’s the analysis on this fear-inducing rune?”

Leylin asked.

[Analysis complete. Obtained freezing and healing runes that are incomplete at 45%. Able to make a cross reference with 31% of the information with the wailing banshee] The A.I. Chip intoned.

“Huh?” Leylin was surprised. “Looks like the innate ability of the Icy Jade Scorpion to freeze and heal itself was affected by and formed from the blood of the female giant.”

He suddenly had a thought that would exploit the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor to the fullest.

“If I combine that information about the technique to mend my sea of consciousness with the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor’s innate skill, burning through its bloodline and stimulating the abilities of the runes on its back to form a bloodline imprint that can be used once…”

Leylin’s eyes shone blue as he calculated, “In that case, I can also use this freezing ability once, and its effects will even be amplified. The power of the bloodline inside would be enough to mend the damage to my sea of consciousness.”

Using solidified spiritual force could do this as well, but it took far too long. In addition to this, Leylin wanted to regain his strength as a rank 2 Warlock as soon as possible.

“Freezing” was a unique innate talent of the Icy Jade Scorpions. While heavily injured, they could protect themselves in a thick layer of ice. Not only was it an ultimate defence, it could also help heal injuries.

Now, Leylin wanted to use this ability on himself.

“A.I. Chip, what is the feasibility of this idea?” Leylin immediately asked in his mind.

Large amounts of information and graphics flashed, and the A.I. Chip gave an answer. [Feasibility is at 87%. Host body first needs to undergo changes in order to be able to tolerate icy radiation.]

“As expected, it’s possible!” Leylin’s eyes exhibited his joy.

The innate freezing ability of the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor, as well as the slight projection of the power from an ancient bloodline, was definitely able to repair the sea of consciousness of a rank 2 Warlock.

This was the optimal method to make use of the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor.

After all, Leylin already had a lot of materials from the Icy Jade Scorpions. Besides, how could materials from another world be more important than his own strength?

“En! In that case, I should start making some preparations.”

Leylin glanced at the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor in the ice mountain. Covered in a block of ice, this Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor looked more fantastical, the green on its body looked almost alive.

Only the weakening of its life force and breath showed that it did not have long to live.

“A.I. Chip, prepare the Bloodline Ignition Potion. It’s essential to make some preparations.”

Leylin’s eyes glinted coldly.

To completely make use of the freezing innate ability of the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor, it was necessary to burn up all its blood completely and stimulate the fear-inducing rune on its back. Then, one needed to model it into a freezing bloodline rune, which involved a very complicated process.

However, all these preparations needed to start from somewhere. This was to ensure that this Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor could live through this, and secondly that Leylin himself could adapt to the harsh cold while in the frozen state.

……

Three days later, in the laboratory.

“Leylin, may I enter?” Celine’s voice could be heard from outside.

“I’ve already undone the alarm spell formation. Come in.” She promptly heard Leylin’s answer and did not hesitate as she pushed the door to enter.

“This…” The moment she entered, Celine instinctively wrapped her clothes tightly around her.

Within the laboratory, large amounts of mist was everywhere. There was even a thick layer of frost on the surrounding walls and some instruments.

Meanwhile, Leylin was naked in a giant glass tank.

He was soaking in a blue icy liquid that seemed to be seeping into his body bit by bit, turning him a little blue.

“What are you doing?”

Celine had long since gotten used to Leylin’s naked body, and she naturally approached him without flushing red. She judged the trough and was puzzled.

She found this icy aura very familiar.

“Isn’t this the unique radiation of the icy caves?” All of a sudden, Celine thought of its origins.

“No, this is just an imitation. It isn’t even 50% of the original, and can’t keep an Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor alive.”

Leylin breathed in deeply, and the icy blue colour in the tank faded, turning from a dark blue to a lighter one, to the point that it was slightly translucent.

Over ten seconds passed, and the icy liquid in the trough had turned translucent.

Leylin stood up and walked out at this point.

Celine had prepared a towel and began to dry the droplets of water on his body like a caring wife.

“What do you plan to do to the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor?” Celine enquired.

“We’re both going to go to the joint conference of the guilds in the east capital. When that happens, only Grandpa Cedric will be here, and it can’t deal with an Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor with the strength of a peak rank 1 Magus!”

“Don’t worry, I’ll take care of it by then.”

Leylin was overjoyed.

Through the tempering of his body with the icy radiation over these few days, he had gradually gotten used to such a chilly temperature. With a few more remodelling attempts, he would be able to make use of the freezing innate ability of the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor without any residual effects on himself to treat his injuries.

Of course, he would not mention this to Celine. She was an intelligent woman who knew what could and couldn’t be asked.

“Do you need clothes?”

After dressing Leylin, Celine rested her head on Leylin’s shoulder, her nimble little tongue licking at Leylin’s earlobes and silently hinting at something.

“Of course not!”

Leylin laughed and pressed her down…

A warm breeze blew, causing one to have the urge to take a nap.

In the subterranean world, the humans of Twilight Zone could not divide the year into four seasons. They had only two ways of detecting the current season. One was based on the activity of the planet’s crust, and dividing the year into the cold and warm season. Another way was through specific crops, and dividing it into the planting and harvesting seasons.

Such a warm breeze was the most obvious indication that it was the warm season.

Leylin sat on the back of a horse carriage with Celine by his side. An aromatic, crisp smell travelled over from Celine’s hair, causing Leylin to feel slightly restless.

The people driving the carriage were the two level 3 acolytes, Obo and Ilya.

Within all of Nature’s Alliance, these two were the ones who were somewhat able to do this.

The animals used to pull the carriage were obviously not horses, but an animal found underground—Wildebeests!

These animals were a lot larger than normal horses. They also had bony armour, and what was most obvious was the single horn on its head.

These animals were more patient than horses, they could also withstand some amount of radiation, and were the first choice for light Magi of the Twilight Zone when they went out on expeditions.

Of course, they was only useful for ordinary acolytes and Magi.

As for even more powerful Magi, they were naturally able to tame even more ferocious, mystical creatures, or even top-grade pets while they went on their journeys.

For a small guild like Nature’s Alliance, using a Wildebeests showed how hard pressed they were.

However, they had no choice. After Celine took over, Nature’s Alliance had not been in a good state and had been pressured in many areas. Based on the intel she received, there was a large possibility that the Nature’s Alliance would be demoted from its rating in the joint conference.

In this situation, Celine had no choice but to look for external help. She could only turn to Leylin.

Though Leylin had been said to be a famed professor in name only, Celine had been tactful and given most of the authority in Nature’s Alliance to him. Leylin wouldn’t turn down such a large gift as well.

He also needed help from the other organisations for his upcoming plans. He had wanted to help Nature’s Alliance expand and assist them based on the agreement they had.

However, it was also not a bad idea to take over this organisation.

Leylin thought to himself as he eyed Celine, who looked calm.

Chapter 333: Killing Intent

The only high-grade meditation technique in the Nature’s Alliance, the Crystal Mask, had been recorded by Leylin. It was a technique based on illusions that used energy from plants as supplements. There were merely two levels to it.

As specific materials required to advance to the second level were only able to be acquired from another world, there had never been another rank 2 Magus in the entire history of Nature’s Alliance.

Leylin possessed the Kemoyin’s Pupil, and had already confirmed his path as a Warlock. Naturally, he wouldn’t change his meditation technique.

As a result, with one glance, outsiders would be able to tell that he was not a Magus trained by Nature’s Alliance.

Based on the rules at the joint conference, Magi like himself were able to make an appearance, but small-scaled guilds could only choose one such Magus, and the chosen Magus could not be be changed.

“Dont worry, I have faith in Leylin!” Celine said confidently.

Leylin appeared to be a peak rank 1 Magus. This kind of strength was a equivalent to a medium-scaled guild’s trump card. Naturally, Celine wasn’t very worried.

“Is that so? That’s great!” Mistress Sache covered her lips with a black foldable fan, and smiled coquettishly.

“What? Did you receive some information too?” Upon seeing her reaction, Celine immediately set up a soundproof barrier around the three of them.

“Yes! I received intelligence from my boy toys. Skrill of the Eight-Clawed Spider Guild seems to harbour unkind intentions towards you. Moreover, he has the support of a medium-scaled guild called the Dense Fog Forest!”

After saying that, Mistress Sache looked at Leylin and said, “And they seem to have made preparations against you, an external support.”

“Medium-scaled guild! Dense Fog Forest!” Sure enough, Celine’s face registered a slight change.

These medium-scaled guilds possessed at least one peak rank 1 Magus as their trump card. The number of official Magi and their knowledge greatly surpassed that of Nature’s Alliance. How could this not worry Celine?

“Is there anything valuable enough inside Nature’s Alliance that the Dense Fog Forest guild is coveting?”

Leylin immediately wondered.

Being a medium-scaled guild, Dense Fog Forest guild possessed resources and minerals that Nature’s Alliance could not compare with. Furthermore, even if the Nature’s Alliance were to fall to an unrated guild, the Dense Fog Forest guild might not be the one that would gain control of their territory and resources.

“So the Dense Fog Forest has to be allies with the Eight-Clawed Spider. Once the Nature’s Alliance falls and loses its seat within the guild alliance, Eight-Clawed Spider would be able to take over its resources. With a little more edging from the Dense Fog Forest, the council of the alliance would not hesitate to hand the empty seat over to them.

“What resources do the Nature’s Alliance and Eight-Clawed Spider have in common? Only one! The icy cave!”

Leylin needed just a bit of time to understand the nature of this power struggle.

As long as one found out who the beneficiaries, or those indirectly gaining benefits were, the situation would then be made clear.

After all, nobody would be willing to do thankless jobs.

During this period of time, Leylin had somewhat gotten familiar with the resources Nature’s Alliance possessed. Honestly speaking, these resources weren’t valuable enough for Dense Fog Forest to be interested in.

The only possibility for this was that the secrets within the depths of the icy cave had been exposed!

“In the past, the icy cave had only been an area rich in production of frozen materials, with the Icy Jade Scorpion as a specialty. It isn’t that valuable, which is why it was allocated to Nature’s Alliance. However, within the cave’s depths actually lies an icy world of a larger scale. The icy world even has the remains of a creature with the strength of a Morning Star Magus and a drop of blood from an even more powerful bloodline!”

After obtaining the information held within the Icy Jade Scorpion’s bloodline, nobody could be more knowledgeable about the icy cave than Leylin. Bluntly speaking, this was a big treasure trove, especially for a bloodline Warlock!

Leylin’s eyes sparkled, with a tinge of chilliness within.

“Only benefits like this would be valuable enough for Dense Fog Forest to act secretly. Looking at the situation, information about these benefits has not been spread. If it was, the entire Twilight Zone would have been in an uproar, and numerous Magi would have formed groups to explore it.”

“Celine, Please ask around and find out how the Oaken Leaf Guild and Emerald Vine Guild been doing lately.”

Leylin ordered Celine suddenly.

“Yes, my lord!” Celine straightened her body and walked over to a corner. The runes from the secret imprint on her body continuously brightened. Thereafter, she returned, a worried expression on her face.

“They have all received Skrill’s invitation. His influence is now similar to a spider web, extending to these two guilds…”

“Just as I thought…” Leylin sighed.

This was the final point of confirmation.

Right now, Leylin was certain that the Dense Fog Forest must have found out about the Icy Cave’s uncanniness, and decided to bribe the Eight-Clawed Spider to crowd out other guilds so that they could monopolise the entire icy cave!

“Find an opportunity to kill them!”

The flash in Leylin’s eyes caused Celine to be nervous, as if an ancient monster was seated beside her.

Currently, Leylin had impolitely claimed the entire icy world. Should the Dense Fog Forest dare tread on his property, he would not let them off easily.

“Actually, if we just want to resolve the crisis Nature’s Alliance is facing, there’s a better way, which is to reveal the secret of the Icy Cave! Even Dense Fog Forest cannot oppose the entire Twilight Zone. Under the pressure of the joint conference, the Dense Fog Forest would be akin to an ant that could easily be crushed. However, this would not be in my best interests!”

With Leylin’s strength, he could probably gain benefits merely by following the majority of the Magi, but there was just too much uncertainty.

Should those overpowered Rank 3 Magi be lured out, Leylin did not have confidence that he could snatch anything from them.

If that were the case, he would only get the leftovers, and that would truly be a pity.

Not to mention, should the Twilight Zone still have the presence of Morning Star Magi that could destroy the entire icy world, Leylin would definitely be reduced to tears.

As a result, for Leylin, it was best to let the secret of the Icy Cave Guild stay a secret until he advanced to become a Morning Star Magus. He would later then return and reap all the benefits!

“But… If that’s the case! The Dense Fog Forest would have to be eliminated, and that needs to be done fast before their leader has the time to react!”

In his heart, Leylin had already meted the death penalty to Dense Fog Forest and Eight-Clawed Spider.

With just a few thoughts, Leylin had already roughly understood the gist of the problem.

To him, since this possibility was the greatest, he would rather kill the wrong person than to not let the matter go. Dense Fog Forest and Eight-Clawed spider needed to be eradicated, and he would even be able to conveniently seize their high-grade meditation techniques and collection.

What was more wonderful was that this could be done in the name of revenge for Nature’s Alliance, which would be killing two birds with one stone.

While pondering, Leylin emanated a massive spiritual force with traces of killing intent, which caused Celine to retreat. Even Mistress Sache gave an excuse and walked away.

“What happened?” Celine worriedly asked.

Naturally, she didn’t know that with merely a word or two, Leylin had managed to deduce the truth, which had helped him make the decision to kill.

“Nothing much!” Leylin smiled, hiding the truth from her.

For interests of such a huge scale, Leylin did not feel at ease revealing his plans to others, even to Celine, whom he had gone to bed with!

“I’m thinking about what Mistress Sache said about her boy toys. What did she mean?”

Leylin cleverly changed the topic.

“Boy… toys?” Celine’s face changed, and she replied: “You- you know, some Magi may have strange interests and bizarre hobbies. Mistress Sache has sadistic tendencies and is also skilled in this area, so…”

“Oh! Sadism and masochism? I know!”

A look of understanding flashed in Leylin’s expression, but he then rolled his eyes. There really were all sorts of Magi.

“Leylin… Are you skilful in things like that?”

After some moments, Celine returned to Leylin’s side and asked shyly.

“Don’t worry!” Leylin replied matter-of-factly.

Since the culprit had been identified to be merely a medium-scaled guild, Leylin didn’t have anything to fear. What he was concerned with was how he had to proceed in order to prevent higher ranked Magi from interfering.

It was at this moment that a commotion arose among the Magi; they dispersed in two directions, revealing a line of people.

“The nine council members are here!”

Celine whispered to Leylin.

“Hm?” Leylin stared at the nine Magi walking over.

There were both male and female council members, but they were no longer young. Their hair was white, and many of them wore glasses. They held dictionary-like books and feather pens or scales, and their eyes glistened with wisdom, giving them a scholarly aura.

However, their energy fluctuations left Leylin dumbfounded.

“Peak rank one! Peak rank one! Peak rank one! They are all peak rank one! How… weak.”

Leylin rolled his eyes. “The subterranean world only possesses this much strength?”

Honestly speaking, if these nine council members only had this much strength, using Toxic Bile before he had gotten injured would have resulted in the instant death of these nine council members. He would even have killed or injured the surrounding Magi as well.

“What is going on?”

Looking at the surrounding Magi paying their respects to the nine council members, Leylin pondered.

“Looking at the situation, either the subterranean Magi have flaws that make it hard for them to advance, or the higher rank Magi have a more intimate circle, and hence do not participate in the conferences of us rank one Magi…”

Leylin stroked his chin, “Whatever it is, I have to reevaluate the strength of Magi in Twilight Zone!”

Chapter 336: Six Stars

Just when the council member was about to announce the start of the fight, Leylin suddenly interrupted him.

“What? Do you want to admit your defeat right now, Celine?”

Of course, Skrill did not dare to be brazen with Leylin. In fact, regardless of whether it was Leylin or Xerxes, he could not afford to offend either of them. Hence, he could only taunt Celine.

“Rubbish!” Celine retorted angrily, worriedly looking at Leylin at the same time.

“Leylin… He… He wouldn’t just give up because of his inability to clearly see through Xerxes’s strength, would he?”

Celine clenched her fists, and even started breaking out in cold sweat.

Honestly, with her talents and meditation skills, Celine was very confident previously that she would be able to defeat all the Magi that had competed in the previous rounds.

However, upon seeing Leylin’s strength, her confidence had dissipated into thin air.

Right now, Celine realised that she did not understand Leylin a single bit.

“Magus Leylin! Do you have any problem?”

The council member holding the books asked.

“I recall that during the evaluation, other than these battling methods, aren’t there other ways as well?”

Leylin looked around the arena and took in Skrill’s taunting, Celine’s anxiety, and Xerxes’s killing intent. He laughed abruptly and then questioned.

Once the word went out, all the Magi looked stunned.

“Yes, there is such a rule. You can even be exempted from fighting through your research contributions.” The council members quickly responded with little emotions.

“However, the results of your research have to be made public, and must be recognised by the council members. Furthermore, since Nature’s Alliance is a small-scale guild, the information you provide has to be at a rank of at least 5 stars”

Research with a rank of 5 stars was equivalent to research conducted by peak rank 1 Magi, and is obviously not easy to obtain.

Celine had the same idea previously, but unfortunately, the council members’ evaluation of research was extremely strict. Furthermore, the nine biggest large-scale guilds were already at the level where you could find the region’s finest research. Hence, very few things would interest them.

Moreover, a lot of time and effort was required to obtain research data of this level. The time invested in the research is no less than the time taken in inviting a semi converted elemental Magus. Hence, after conducting the research for a period of time, Celine gave up on that idea.

“Should you research data not be at the level of 5 stars, it would mean that you lose your independent research without garnering any gains. We hope you can think it over!”

“Please do not worry, I am very confident in my own research!” Furthermore, Magi have always been virtuous people searching for the truth, so in this path of the search for knowledge, I do not mind sharing the results of my research with my fellow man”

Leylin’s words were immediately well received by the crowd of magi.

Many high-level magi that are on friendly terms would gather to exchange their own experiences so that they could improve together.

“We can see the glory of ancient times in your being!”

The nine council members nodded their heads, “Please present your information!”

“I object!” Skrill immediately shouted. He agitatedly pointed towards Leylin, his eight-clawed spider legs seemingly trembling “We were first in issuing our challenge. Even if the information were to be presented, it can only be done so after the challenge!”

“Objection overruled! Magus Leylin’s ways are in accordance with the ancient rules!”

A few council members immediately suppressed Skrill’s objection. Magus Xerxes, on the other hand just coldly started, his thoughts unable to be determined.

Looking at the scene before him, Leylin snickered to himself.

Under the witness of so many Magi, a battle to the death would be like a monkey show set up for an audience. Was that really in his best interests?

Even though many Magi would be willing to do so under the influence of the interests involved, Leylin was not one of them!

Furthermore, in front of the nine peak rank 1 Magi, along with the Magi troops, Leylin would not be able to kill. Otherwise, as Leylin’s injuries were not yet completely healed, he would not be able to defend against the joint attack of nine peak rank 1 Magi. He also did not want to offend the nine large-scale guilds that the nine peak rank 1 Magi belonged to.

After all, the large-scale guilds must have Magi of at least rank 2. Leylin did not want to find trouble at all.

Hence since he was not able to kill, there was no point in accepting the challenge and putting on a monkey show for others.

Naturally, Leylin would choose the most effortless method.

He smiled, his every movement resembling how the ancient royalty were trained. He seemed calm, and together with the unique warlock’s charm that he had, this convinced many of the Magi.

The eyes of Mistress Sache, whom Leylin had previously met, lit up like two balls of fire.

Immediately, Leylin passed his already prepared research data to the council members.

This was, in part, the flawed articles he had seen in the Nature’s Alliance. The research had already progressed to the final stages, but unfortunately, because of the lack of crucial steps, the articles were not able to be developed into a meditation.

However, Leylin was different. He was a rank 2 Warlock, and had the support of the entire knowledge vault of the south coast. He could be said to have a bird’s eye view of the whole situation. Together with the incredible mathematical operations of the A.I. Chip, with a few tweaks here and there, Leylin would be able to produce research of a high calibre.

Leylin was able to obtain the data without much trouble, and the information did not cost very much. However, when presented externally, these data were considered to have at least a rank of 5 stars, the equivalent importance of a peak rank 1 Magus. This was sufficient to allow the Magi present to vie for the information .

Sure enough, upon receiving the crystal ball filled with research formulas and graphical information, the faces of the council members became more solemn.

Their faces were serious while they perused the crystal ball in succession, and all the while, they were animatedly engaging in discussion.

In the end, they even gathered in a circle, agitatedly discussing and letting out cries of argument from time to time.

Meanwhile, Skrill’s heart grew heavier, while Celine’s face revealed a smile. The Magi outside were anticipating the results, eager to see Leylin’s research data.

With regards to all the goings on, Leylin pretended not to notice and continued to calmly stand upright.

Just based on this cultivation of calmness during the chaos, Leylin received the admiration of the Magi here.

”Hu!”

Eventually, the council members returned to their seats. The council member sitting in the middle even removed his presbyopic glasses and rubbed the bridge of his nose.

*Bang!* He aggressively slammed his gavel downwards, which meant that the official evaluation of the research would begin.

“According to the council members’ unanimous decision, the information Magus Leylin has provided regarding the biological structure and bloodline of dark elves is to be classified as having a rank of 6 stars!”

*Hua!* The venue resonated with cries of wonder. The fact that Leylin’s provided information would be able to be pass the test was within the expectations of many of the Magi. This was because Magi were not stupid; if they were to present any information, it must be because they were confident that it would suffice.

However, little did they expect that the information Leylin provided would actually have a rank of 6 stars!

Research of this nature must be close to the standards of a rank 2 Magus.

“These data will be recorded in the collective data vault. All Magi present will be able to use these contributions…”

After the council member had made the announcement, he immediately beamed. “Magus Leylin’s aspirations and intensive studying spirit has obtained my admiration. May I know whether there will be a chance in the future to invite Magus Leylin to my institute to undergo an interview?”

“It would be my honour!” Leylin bowed slightly.

Meanwhile, on the side, Celine seemed a bit dazzled.

“Master! We have succeeded!” Only when the sound if Ilya cheering entered her ear did she return to her senses, her eyes watery with tears that were on the verge of falling.

At this moment, all the difficulties they had experienced in the past, along with the ridicule they had to suffer, appeared in her mind. “Teacher, can you see this…”

“Hmph!”

Skrill’s face was extremely dark. He glared at Celine, “Consider yourselves lucky this time around. I hope that luck will always follow you!”

After which, without turning back once, he left the venue, with Xerxes unhurriedly following behind him.

This time around, the plot of the Eight-Clawed Spider was fruitless, and with the possibility of inducing rage from the Dense Fog Forest, Skrill did not want to stay at the conference for a single minute longer.

“Leylin! Thank you!”

After Leylin returned to his seat, Celine held his hands, her face filled with a genuine smile.

“It was nothing!” Leylin smiled.

Actually, Leylin was very sure that this matter was far from over.

After their open and aboveboard plans have failed, the opponent could only utilise underhanded means now.

“Underhanded means? But those are my favourites!”

Leylin smiled coldly. Right now, during the joint conference, the only restrained party in this case wasn’t merely his opponent but himself as well. After all, he had started off as a legitimate dark Magus. Bloodshed and killing were very common to him.

When that happened, it would be too late for the other party to have regrets.

With regards to Leylin’s contributions, the Nature’s Alliance was able to be exempted from the challenge this time around, and could be considered to have survived an ordeal.

After the evaluation, there was nothing much to see at the conference.

There were only a few guilds left to compete with one another. During the majority of the time, the apprentices would compete in a friendly context. This was also one of the reasons why Celine had brought Obo and Ilya to the conference.

Leylin had completed his task at hand, and so he sat with Celine, who was beaming, as they watched other Magi compete.

”Leylin! I can’t believe that I would see you here!”

At this moment, a Magus with a gold-plated, robotic right hand walked over, his face radiating with happiness.

“I can’t believe this, you actually joined the Nature’s Alliance without telling anyone!”

“Hello, Siegfried!”

Leylin greeted him. “There was no other choice since they had something very tempting to me in their hands! Moreover, I’m only a honorary professor, which means I can also guild.”

“Oh, I know!”

Siegfried’s face revealed a smile that all men would be able to understand. It was obvious that Leylin was bewitched by Celine, was it not?

“Come! Let me bring you to meet some of the high-ranking officers in the Earth Fire Association!”

Compared to his previous interactions with Leylin, Siegfried was now more cordial.

After all, Siegfried was currently not able to discern Leylin’s true abilities. However, based on the presentation of his high-end research standards and academic attainments, it was worth it to rope Leylin in.

In addition, a few high-level guilds council members had all expressed their friendliness in succession, which made it even more plausible to try and rope Leylin in.

Chapter 340: Invasion and Siege

Continuing the trial of the joint conference, the Dense Fog Forest would most likely not be destroyed, but there would be bloodshed. In addition, a decrease in their evaluation was a possible punishment, which would be a big loss in benefits!

Needless to say, the “seriously injured” Leylin was here too!

Since there was so much hatred, the only way to end this would be through complete destruction, was something that the other party could not tolerate.

Thus, they would take advantage of Leylin being in the midst of recovery by gathering all their manpower, and destroy the Nature’s Alliance!

This was what Leylin also hoped for.

“I had specially given him a few days to rally his men. I hope he doesn’t let me down!” Leylin sneered.

Shortly after, he turned and looked towards the canyon’s exit.

“Coming!”

At this moment, Magi wearing black Chinese-styled gowns stood in a circle outside the Canyon, silently crowding around several figures in the middle.

The leader of the group, a middle-aged man with a face worthy of veneration, was the escaped guild leader of the Dense Fog Forest.

“Tsk Tsk! Gus, you really should be embarrassed, being reduced to this miserable state after getting injured from an honorary professor in a small-scaled guild!”

So ‘Gus’ was his real name, and the previously used name, ‘Xerxes,’ was fake!

Another man who stood tall beside Gus, was an elderly man in his 50s or 60s. He had wrinkles all over his face. With his slanted nose, sharp, narrow pairs of eyes, it made him look even more sinister than Gus.

Even as he mocked Gus, no anger was seen in the eyes of the surrounding Magi from the Dense Fog Forest, as if they never heard what was said.

The reason for their change in attitude was that this old man was radiating huge waves of energy.

Among the emptiness in the middle of the circle formed by the old men, radiations of spiritual force could be observed. Impressively, it was the strength of a powerful peak rank one Magus!

“If you had been me, the result would not have been any better!”

Gus sighed in the face of mockery, but deep down, was still fearful of Leylin’s strength.

Having profound knowledge of Gus’ strength, the old man turned solemn too; “If Leylin has already recovered from his injuries, then I want twice the compensation!”

“If it’s doubled, let it be doubled!” Gus promised immediately with clenched teeth.

“I have actually used an ancient ‘light protector’ rune. That’s the reason why I could recover fast in such a short period of time. The other party could not possibly have such a thing…”

This was the confidence Gus had, as he hailed from a medium-scaled guild. To him, as a small-scaled guild, it was impossible for Nature’s Alliance to have such an asset.

“Je Je! You’re right. Besides, they are at most at the same level with you, how can they stop us two on their own?”

The old man chuckled.

“My Lord guild leader! The broken signal has been repaired!” At this moment, a semi-converted elemental Magus walks over and spoke to Gus

“Great! Attack immediately! I want the Nature’s Alliance guild removed entirely from the Twilight Zone!”

A malevolent look swept across Gus’ face, and he suddenly raised his hand.

More than a dozen of different coloured bright lights fluttered out of the Canyon. Unexpectedly, each one was a rank one Magus!

As a medium-scaled guild, it was not a big problem if the Dense Fog Forest nurtured or recruited official Magi. considering the long, accumulated history of the more than 30 Magi.

This time, Gus planned to use a large number forces from his guild.

*Bang!*

More than a dozen brilliant lights rushed to the entrance of the canyon, but were immediately stopped by a membrane formed from a defensive layer of light.

“It’s just defensive formation made by an insignificant small-scaled guild! Destroy it!”

From the layer of bright light, a screeching sound was heard and black light converged, forming the shape of a large axe. The head of the axe even had strong black iron chains coiled around it which were threads of bright, cold and threatening light.

*Ka Cha!*

The giant hatchet ruthlessly struck!

In the wake of the loud strike, the entire membrane of light fell apart, disintegrating and dispersing into small specks of light that gradually darkened.

“Enemy Attacking!”

As an official Magus, Celine was the first to react. Her face turned deathly pale and a gush of cold wind sent her to the entrance of the experiment lab within the icy mountain.

*Shaaa!* The black light flashed past, a mole no smaller than the size of a young boy crawled out, his two long, grizzly beards dragging across the floor.

“This Celine! Causing trouble this time! If I am still alive later, you’ll have to send me 10 times as many berries as before!”

The mole stroked his beard, with an unwilling look on his face.

“Damn it! If it wasn’t for the deal that I made with that stupid old man at that time, I wouldn’t have to be stuck here defending his place!”

“All of the acolytes, meet me here now!”

Celine did not even have the time to force a smile, let alone talk to the mole. She just communicated directly with the rest of the acolytes in the guild.

She was extremely sure that the attack this time around was from the Dense Fog Forest’s men!

In fact, during a war between the official Magi, acolytes were just cannon fodder! By sending them out was only a disgrace, and even causing needless casualties.

Currently, they had a slim chance of survival!

Celine’s eyes flashed with a tinge of hope, and started shouting towards the laboratory, “My Lord Leylin! It is the Magi of the Dense Fog Forest! They have violated the rules of the joint conference and launched an attack on our guild!”

But what took with Celine by surprise even more than the sudden attack was the fact that there was no reply from inside.

Celine repeated the message thrice, and it was only after she could not wait any longer and broke the layer of ice, that Leylin’s voice responded. ”I’m still in the midst of recovering! If this gets interrupted, I’m afraid that there will be immediate repercussions….”

“How much longer do you need?” Celine clasped onto her handkerchief tightly.

“Ten minutes!” After some silence, Leylin’s voice was heard again.

“Alright! I will fight for you during this period of time!” Celine took a deep breath towards the acolyte that was previously there and cleared her throat.

“As the guild leader, I command you to protect this place at all costs! It might be hard to you, but with the help of spell formations, I need you to persevere just for ten minutes!

“Yes, my Lord! We will fight to the end!”

After being distracted for a moment, the acolytes below started an uproar one after another, Obo and Ilya were among those acolytes.

It was obvious and they clearly understood what the future had in store for them if their guild was defeated today.

“That’s great! Let’s activate it! Grandpa Cedric!!!”

Celine took a deep breath.

“Okay, alright! I can’t stand youngsters like you all!” the mole shook his head and suddenly plopped to the ground!

In some instant, black rays of light spread out, forming a big spell formation runes on the ground.

A barrier of light rose and combined with the original spell formation, engulfing Leylin and the experiment lab within.

*Boom! Blast!*

At this moment, a group of enemy Magi arrived at the scene, and the acolytes that were not able to get into the barrier in time were severely injured.

A small boy was cut in half by a blade of light. His upper torso was still wailing as he tried to breathe.

Another female acolyte, who was decimated into a pool of blood by a green sphere that fell from the sky, did not even had time make a sound.

More and more acolytes were instantly buried to death, by huge broken structure of the building that was shattered by magic spells, also without being able to make any sound.

As Celine looked at the devastating scene in front of her, she was unable to control herself and broke down into tears. They were the future potential Magi of Nature’s Alliance, where her sweat and blood were poured in.

“I found it! It’s here!”

This new barrier of light, which was visibly thicker and stronger than the ones before, caught the attention of the enemy Magi quickly. Very soon, more than a dozen rays of light enveloped the entire place, creating faint shadows in the middle.

*Clang!* Celine threw a communication device on the ground.

“The signal is disrupted! Hold on!”

She placed her palm on the barrier, as a huge wave of spiritual force and magical power was poured forth and injected into the barrier.

The rest of the acolytes followed suit, though their spiritual powers were very weak. With a mere touch, most of the acolytes’ faces turned pale, as though they had been beaten up by a large hammer.

*Boom!*

Both sides did not exchange many words, and more than a dozen colourful energy beams bombarded the spell formation.

*Bang!* Numerous acolytes lay paralyzed on the floor, most of them having fainted. Celine could barely even stand up straight and was on the verge of collapsing.

Upon seeing two shadows behind the numerous Magi, Celine’s expression was filled with despair.

At this time, it has not even been half the time that Leylin had requested. Fighting against the two peak rank one Magi had made Celine lose all hope and strength to fight back.

In the laboratory behind Celine, Leylin quietly waited, a cold and detached expression on his face…

“It should be roughly about now, right?” He muttered.

In fact, Leylin could have fought back, but he had waited until the Nature’s Alliance had racked up a disastrous amount of casualty…

As for the dead acolytes, they did not have much importance to Leylin, and their deaths weighed lighter than specks of dust in his heart.

As long as the opponent left irrefutable evidence of an attack, what were the deaths of a few acolytes? Also, these acolytes were under Celine’s guidance. If he really wanted to gain complete control of the Nature’s Alliance, more blood would have to be shed!

Now, however, it was time.

Gus and the rest of them had done so much damage to the Nature’s Alliance that even if Leylin were to kill them all, it could be reasoned as self-defense.

This excuse may not be very good, but it was definitely better than having none! The acolytes that have died and the data that have been perished

“Magus Gus! Why? Just why?”

Celine retracted her hands and looked at the barrier which was damaged by the combined attacks of the enemy. The guardian animal too was severely injured as it spat out blood, smiling bitterly.

“Benefits! Naturally, everything is for our own benefits!”

Gus’ voice was ice cold, as if not having any of the emotions that a normal person would have. He had also turned a blind eye to Celine’s charms.

“You hindered my path, and I just want to settle the dispute, that’s all!”

Chapter 341: Ruthless Retaliation

“What gains are you referring to? I can give them up straight away!”

There was a glint in Celine’s eyes…

“This is your final chance! If this happened before the joint conference, I might have given it a thought, but now…”

Gus shook his head and said, “There is no further need for you to stall for time! There has been no Magus who has ever been able to survive after being hit by my Fog Giant’s self-detonation. Even if Leylin manages to survive the blow, he’s probably incapacitated unable to move a single muscle.”

Celine felt complete despair as her last hope was shattered.

“Get on with it!” She closed her eyes and exposed her pale neck.

“Where is Skrill?” Gus asked at the end while he formed a ball of distortion-filled with destructive energy.

“I have no idea. Leylin personally carried out the interrogation!”

“Then you are no longer of use!”

The indifferent Gus released the ball of distortion in his hands.

*Pu!* A layer of a black scaly shield appeared out of nowhere in front of Celine, and it managed to block the explosion from the attack.

After the smoke dissipated, a black-robed Magus had already appeared in front of Celine.

“Leylin!” Gus’ eyes widened in fear as he fearfully uttered the name.

“Tell me! How do you guys want to die?” The corners of Leylin’s lips curled into a vibrant smile.

“Do it!”

Gus’ face flushed red as he shouted.

“Double the amount! Bear in mind that it is double the amount!” The old man with a hawk nose beside him released large amounts of elemental rings, forming a brass ring with mysterious runes on the surface.

While executing this attack, he did not forget to turn back and remind Gus about his remuneration.

Grey mist started to form immediately and the Fog Giant from their previous encounter appeared once again. Unlike the last time, rays of light which resembled starlight started to emerge from every Magus who was present and connected to the body of the giant, making the giant’s aura rise to a frightening level.

The brass ring was thrown around the waist of the giant and it strapped tightly around it in that instant.

“Roar!”

The giant let out a devastating roar. While its lower body was shrinking non-stop, the mist on its upper body started to aggregate once again, and formed a body of muscle with a toughness that was as strong as granite.

“A combination spell!”

Celine, who was behind Leylin, couldn’t help but to let out a sound at the sight. Even her breathing began to get rough.

“The opposing side has two peak rank 1 Magi, along with ten or so Magi elders. Meanwhile, Leylin…”

Celine had no time to process the thoughts in her head before her jaw dropped at the sight.

Silver!

A faint sliver of light started to appear on Leylin’s body.

At this moment, even the air seemed to be frozen. An oppressive pressure could be felt descending onto the battlefield.

“Materialised spiritual force! A rank 2 Magus!”

The hawk-nosed old man made a strange sound. Despite bleeding profusely from his mouth and nose, the old man started to recall his spells, risking recoil in doing so while he retreated in haste.

It was a pity that this was all too late!

A pillar of silver light streaked across the sky and arrived at the top of the old man’s head.

“No!” The old man exclaimed in anger, and an incomplete protection ruin on his neck exploded, resulting in an inferno of crimson flames.

Following that, the old man stopped in his tracks for a moment and nearly fell to the ground.

He had obviously felt the peak elemental spiritual force residing in the flames being instantly destroyed by the silver materialised spiritual force when the two forces collided.

As the spiritual force being manipulated was dispelled, the inferno of crimson flames lost sight of its target and began spreading to the surroundings.

The silver spiritual force soon descended down on its target. It formed a silver cross-shaped sword after having elongated and pierced the old man in the chest.

*Drip! Drip!*

The old man was bleeding profusely and droplets of blood could be seen dripping onto the ground. He tried humming, but no energy particles were triggered.

The solidified spiritual force of a rank 2 Magus far surpassed the spiritual force of an converted Magus in terms of quality. The spiritual force residing inside the old man’s consciousness was no match for the silver spiritual force and was completely locked down with a single hit.

This rationale was very similar to what had happened to Leylin, when he had been confined by the Gargamel on the mountain of white bones.

After Leylin had completely recovered his rank 2 Magus power, even a peak rank 1 Magus was nothing more than a slightly stronger ant in Leylin’s eyes.

“He…! He…! He…!”

The sight had the Magi from the Dense Fog Forest at a loss.

With just one single blow, the peak rank 1 Magus was on the verge of death! They had only heard of this kind of terrifying power in legends.

Gus’ face started to turn pale from despair before it finally became a grim.

“Roar!” Under his manipulation, the gigantic Fog Giant ferociously charged in Leylin’s direction.

Leylin started to slowly open an ancient scroll in his hands which was radiating with destructive energy that could be felt in the surroundings.

“Scorching Touch!” A bunch of red powder started to spill out, and two long and narrow energy beams which carried the destructive force of a rank 2 spell shot out from Leylin’s hands. The fog giant was immediately scorched and two large holes were created from the attack.

*Boom!* A large amount of the mist started to dissipate and all the Magi who were connected to the mist giant started to collapse to the ground.

In the blink of an eye, Leylin appeared in front of Gus.

*Zoom! Zoom! Zoom! Zoom!*

While he was moving, several snow-white ice arrows were abruptly shot out.

*Zoom! Zoom! Zoom! Zoom!*

Confronted with the might of the arrows, the innate defensive spell formations of rank 1 Magi were shredded easily like pieces of paper. The heads of numerous Magi exploded, similar to watermelons exploding.

“You…”

At the sight of this unbearable scenario, even Gus, who was preparing a spell, could not help but feel anger and a sense of despair.

The number of rank 1 Magi that had died constituted almost half of the Dense Fog Forest’s forces. All his efforts to accumulate this power all these years had gone down the drain as he lost 70 to 80% of his forces.

But at this moment, Gus had no time to think about this as Leylin arrived in front of him.

“Protection of Andes!” Gus shouted loudly and a colony of black ants emerged from his face, clothes, shoes and all over his body and formed a peculiar-looking black shield.

“A futile effort!” Leylin looked indifferent and raised his right hand.

A layer of black rays started to gather around his palm and formed a bunch of black scales. “Kemoyin’s Scale! Partial Snake Transformation!”

*Po!*

Leylin’s palms were filled with an enormous amount of energy which penetrated the shield. The colony of ants on the shield let out a shrill sound as they tried to gnaw at the black scales, but it was to no avail.

“Your last resort is just a scroll engraved by a rank 2 Magus? How disappointing!”

The silver ray of light in Leylin’s eyes started to shine brightly, and with his right hand, he grabbed Gus’ wrist.

*Pak!* The scroll, which was already triggered halfway, suddenly lost all its luster and revealed its true appearance of what seemed to be a broken piece of goatskin paper as it fell to the ground.

“Do you have any last words?”

Leylin asked Gus as he sealed his spiritual force.

“You will be punished by the joint conference. I swear on that!” Gus’ eyes turned red.

*Pak!* After which, his brain exploded, white brain juices, blood, and fluids spurting everywhere.

“Just this? How pointless! “

Leylin retracted his right hand.

He appeared in front of the hawk-nosed old man and placed his hands on the head of an old man who was on the verge of death.

“Do you choose death or subservience”?

The old man who was bleeding profusely and nearing death struggled to open his mouth. “I… I’m willing to be subservient to you, my lord!”

“Set a pact now and surrender a strand of your spirit source, or else you will end up like the others!”

The tone of Leylin’s voice was very indifferent, and the pile of corpses surrounding him made the old man have no thoughts of defying the order.

“I, Iren, am willing to serve under your command and become your most humble servant! Your future commands shall be my eternal mission!”

Even with his eyes blurred with tears, the old man still struggled to speak.

A fluctuating thread from the abyss was established between the two.

“Very good!” Leylin recalled the silver spiritual force that was restricting the old man.

“My lord!” Iren kneeled down to give his regards, the wounds on his body already beginning to heal on their own.

He had been restricted by Leylin and lost his ability to recover. Once he was freed from the silver spiritual force that was restricting him, there were far too many ways for Magi to heal themselves.

“Please accept your humble servant’s loyalty!” Although he had regained his freedom, the old man Iren had no desire to fight against Leylin as he had been deterred by Leylin’s actions.

With Iren’s words, a glowing spirit source floated out of his forehead and flew to Leylin’s hands.

After losing his spiritual source, Iren’s face turned pale and beads of sweat could be seen dripping down.

Leylin for his part kept the spirit source carefully.

A Magus’ spirit source was very important to them, and if Leylin were to destroy the source in his hands, the old man would suffer a severe blow and might even die straight away. The best-case scenario would be for him to have a mental breakdown.

It could be said that once Leylin had the spirit source, it was akin to him holding the old man’s fate in his hands.

“All good and done!” Leylin clapped his hands.

This kind of one-sided process and astonishing means from Leylin had made it difficult for Celine to process anything.

“My lord! You….” Celine had no idea of what to say.

“Have you … ascended to rank 2?” She said this carefully after deliberating over it for a while.

“Yes!” Leylin happily smiled “The injury I suffered has, instead, made me break through the restraints to my meditation technique and allowed me to rise to the realm of rank 2.”

Celine did not have the courage to continue probing despite knowing it was not the truth.

A rank 2 Magus! This was already a power that belonged to large-scale guilds! Facing this insurmountable gap in power, Celine could only accept whatever Leylin had to say.

“Wake those acolytes up and follow me!”

Leylin pointed to a few of the acolytes who were lying on the ground that included Obo and Ilya.

“Hm? What for?” Celine’s face was filled with doubts.

“Naturally, it will be to retaliate!”

Leylin’s face broke into a cold smile, “Since the opposing party has been so eager to find us, how can we not repay what they have done?”

“But…. The joint conference….”

Celine had only spoken a few words, but she decided to swallow the rest. At this moment, she had no other choice.

Chapter 342: Abyssal Breath

“My Lord! That’s the Dense Fog Forest’s headquarters!”

Old man Iren pointed to a fog-shrouded forest in the middle of the basin, with a look of respect on his face.

Currently, Iren was completely submissive to Leylin and existed as his servant.

Leylin walked behind him with conflicted feelings. Together with Obo, Ilya, and the other rank 3 acolytes, their faces were red with emotions.

Rank 2 Magus! Their famed professor was actually a rank 2 noble Magus who actually defeated a lot of enemies with just one blow!

They were proud of this kind of glory.

“The Dense Fog Forest is still a medium-scale guild, with an extremely strong Magi formation barrier. With several protected and contracted beings as the first line of defense, does this not mean that we are…”

Iren had revealed all of Gus’ defensive lines backhandedly.

“We do not need anything! I alone am sufficient. All of you keep in mind, without my orders, no one is allowed to step into the basin!”

Leylin’s face was stern. After which, he transformed into a gust of wind and disappeared in mid-air.

*Ssiii*

A sound could be heard as he travelled. Celine and the rest saw an illusory shadow of a snake appearing in mid-air. The huge snake forcefully appeared and seemed to transform into the face of a terrifying devil. The shape of the devil’s face seemed to resemble Leylin.

After half an hour passed they had obtained permission to enter the Dense Fog Forest, and they saw huge amounts of rotten corpses!

A few huge high-energy beings whose size resembled small mountains could also be seen dead on the floor, their corpses, not yet fully decomposed, had emitted an unpleasant small.

“Your task is to completely search this area, and take away any resources that are of value!”

Leylin slowly landed on the corpse of a huge beast. That scene had made many absolutely horrified.

“Yes! Yes, My Lord!”

Initially, Celine had doubts over why Leylin had wanted to bring a batch of acolytes over. However, now she fully understood his intentions.

……

After having searched the Dense Fog Forest, Leylin had arrived near the premises of the headquarters of the Eight-Clawed Spider guild.

This time around, Skrill appeared beside him.

If Leylin could subdue even Iren, naturally Skrill was not a big issue.

“Go! Announce that the Eight-Clawed Spider will be disbanded! And that all the Magi shall join Nature’s Alliance!” Leylin ordered Skrill.

“As you wish, my Lord!” Skrill bowed to Leylin, evidently afraid of him.

His fear was to the extent that he was willing to accept such orders.

With regards to the subsidiary guilds of the Dense Fog Forest, Leylin did not intend to exterminate all of them fully.

In any case, since they had no chance of knowing the Icy World’s secret, it would be for the best to subdue all of them to increase Nature’s Alliance’s strength.

Furthermore, all of the Dense Fog Forest Magi had been exterminated without any exceptions under Leylin’s rank 2 Magi spell that covered a vast area. There was no longer any living beings within the entire basin.

It could be said that the Dense Fog Forest guild had disappeared from the face of the earth.

Looking at the uproar from the guild headquarters, together with Iren and the people that went forth to subdue them, Leylin smiled icily.

“Next, perhaps it’s time for the rank 2 Magi?”

How long had it been since such a large-scale attack, and such a vile way of exterminating an entire guild, had happened in the entire eastern Twilight Zone?

No matter how dim-witted the large-scale guilds were, they would have to make a stand.

Moreover, according to the latest news, the dark elven empire was starting to become restless, and it was also nearing the time when the darkness creature horde beyond the Twilight Zone was approaching. It was precisely during this period of time where Magi were supposed to collaborate that Nature’s Alliance’s move could be said to be going against the tide.

“So what?”

Leylin’s face revealed a smile that seemed to suggest that he did not care, “It is precisely because of this that I am making a move now!”

“The combining of forces to deal with external forces not only restricts the Nature’s Alliance but all the other large-scale guilds as well!”

“Would they be willing to, under these conditions, lose a rank 2 Magus? How can the strength associated with a medium-scale guild measure up to a newly promoted rank 2 Magus? Furthermore, we still possess sufficient evidence to prove that the Dense Fog Forest had started the fight first, and had even encroached into our headquarters and caused a large number of casualties…”

With strength and evidence, even large-scale guilds would not act recklessly.

With regards to this, Leylin understood the logic very clearly.

After 10 minutes or so, Skrill and Iren returned.

“My Lord! The Eight-Clawed Spider guild has officially disbanded. This is our high-grade meditation technique—Abyssal Breath!”

Skrill respectfully half-knelt and passed a black crystal wand to Leylin.

“Mm. Well done!” Leylin took the wand gently, with a thread of his silver spiritual force reaching into it.

Increasing the power of Nature’s Alliance was only part of the reason why Leylin had destroyed the guilds. The main objective behind his actions was actually to collect the high-grade meditation techniques!

As time passed, Leylin frowned, which caused Skrill to start trembling.

“Only rank 3?” Leylin sighed. The Eight-Clawed Spider guild’s meditation technique had the same flaws as Celine’s Crystal Mask. Not only was it hard to develop, it was only rank 3.

This implied that the Magi from the Eight-Clawed Spider guild could at most be promoted to rank 3, and not beyond.

“I, your subordinate, am ashamed! Our high-grade meditation technique does only have 3 levels! Personally, I have been stuck at rank 1, and can only use the irrigation of the abyss’ strength…”

Skrill lowered his head and quickly explained.

“Of course, I know!” Leylin knew that this Abyssal Breath mostly used the strength of the abyss to continuously change the body to adjust to a physical state more fitting to the abyss. Skrill’s half-human half-spider appearance was the way it was due to the imitation of a special being from the abyss.

And this is merely rank 1 of the Abyssal Breath. According to the introduction of the meditation technique and the A.I. Chip’s deductions, if one were to promote the meditation technique to its highest level, one would be able to return to their original state and have the physical appearance of a normal person.

Only then would the Magus, who had been entirely transformed by the abyss, be known as the spawn of the abyss!

But of course, these were only deductions made by the A.I Chip.

According to Leylin’s estimations, to reach the state of the abyss’ spawn, one would have to develop the Abyssal Breath higher than rank 5.

Honestly, one could not be sure whether the high-grade meditation technique even had a rank 5.

“However, after all, this is a high-grade meditation technique and is a grade higher than the Crystal Mask. This can improve the A.I. Chip’s meditation techniques information database!”

Leylin kept the black crystal wand.

Because many ancient Magi were passionate about researching about all living beings in the world, they looked for patterns, obtained strength, and frequently interacted with beings of different realms. Hence, many ancient meditation techniques had a strong and strange aura.

With respect to the Abyssal Breath, Leylin estimated that it had a deep relationship with the abyssal world, and could even have been released by a strong and powerful being living within the abyss.

“Dense Fog Forest has other auxiliary guilds, namely 3 other small-scale guilds, and 15 unrated guilds. All of you shall break into 3 groups, Iren and Skrill will lead 2 groups to sweep the unrated guilds while I will be in charge of the small-scale guilds!”

Leylin immediately gave out his orders.

“As you wish, My Lord!” the surrounding Magi all bowed with respect.

Leylin nodded. Iren was a peak rank one magus, and Skrill was a semi-converted elemental Magus. To put them in charge to deal with the unrated guilds was a terrifying force to be reckoned with.

The unrated guilds did not stand a chance with the teams led by the two of them.

Furthermore, upon performing this deed, these newly subdued Magi would have no way out, and would only be able to come under Leylin’s wings.

……

Several days later, explosive news spread across the entire Eastern Twilight Zone that caused a sensation in the Magi world, and even continued to spread in the 4 other zones.

After having existed for a few hundred thousand years, large amounts of contracted guardian beasts, countless official Magi, and even a peak rank 1 Magus that oversaw a medium-scale guild, the Dense Fog Forest, were entirely destroyed!

The one responsible for it was actually Nature’s Alliance! This news had revealed that the honorary professor of Nature’s Alliance had made a breakthrough to rank 2!

A peak rank 1 Magus was considered as a large power, while a rank 2 Magus was the goal of many official Magi, which were also known as the elites of the human forces!

Typically, a rank 2 Magi would only appear in large-scale guilds. The presence of the one or two old and experienced rank 2 Magi was that of the trump card of these guilds.

Nature’s Alliance, on the other hand, was only a small-scale guild!

At this point in time, the entire eastern Twilight Zone was shocked.

Under Leylin’s control, the actions of Nature’s Alliance went extremely smoothly.

Not only did Nature’s Alliance attack all of the Dense Fog Forest’s auxiliary guilds and wiped out all traces of its history, many Magi had joined Nature’s Alliance and enhanced its strength, such that it had been promoted to a medium-scale guild! These were all within Leylin’s expectations.

Moreover, the taking over of the Dense Fog Forest’s resources was also proceeding smoothly.

This, of course, was not in accordance with the rules set by the council members and had sparked their displeasure.

However, under Leylin’s suppression, Nature’s Alliance continued doing whatever they wanted to without any hesitation. The guild sent out many troops and their strength increased day after day.

With regards to small matters like the strength of the guild, Leylin could not be bothered to oversee them and would casually instruct his acolytes to handle them.

The newly-joined Magi that were now part of Nature’s Alliance were all given roles as professors or guest professors, but in actual fact, they would only listen to Leylin’s bidding.

Celine’s powers were suppressed to the maximum, but she could only force a smile, and could not complain much.

Leylin had suddenly been promoted to a rank 2 Magi, and just his strength alone would make Celine’s previous plans prove futile. Furthermore, in terms of trickery, back in the southern coast the underhanded means that Leylin had employed did not pale in comparison to that Celine’s.

Under these conditions, Celine could only give up.

Due to her special status, other official Magi would still be slightly respectful towards her and would not reject her requests towards small matters.

Furthermore, these Magi were still under Nature’s Alliance, even if only in name, which gave Celine some comfort.

Chapter 346: A Coincidence

On a dark field, a group of cavalry chased after a lone figure.

The fleeing figure was a strange sight. He floated a few metres above the ground and had a pair of white translucent wings sprouting from his back. Each flap of these wings propelled him forward a great distance.

Behind the winged figure was a group of knights chasing after it! These knights rode on large spiders, each with eight brown, clawed legs. There were also icy blue stripes on them, and their eyes shone with bloodlust.

These were Underground Winter Spiders, the mounts of elite dark elves.

The knights riding on these spiders were not humans, but tall, slim creatures with exquisite skin; they had beautiful androgynous contours on their faces, with sharp ears and silver eyes that granted them vision in the dark.

*Bang!* The figure that was escaping in front suddenly turned his head, which revealed his handsome features and pointed ears, before he started chanting something undecipherable while swinging his arms backwards.

Five crimson red fireballs were fired out of his palm but were all dodged by the Underground Winter Spiders, exploding on the ground.

Surprisingly, the escaping figure was a dark elf as well!

“They really think highly of me huh, even sending the Underground Winter Spider knights after me!” The silhouette continued to escape but was unable to break away from the knights chasing after him.

Not only could these Underground Winter Spiders move at an incredible speed, they could crawl over any terrain, regardless of whether it was in mountains, fields or even the misty canyons. Their advance could not be stopped.

“Memphis! How dare you betray the glory of the Dark Lord? I will make you suffer, and offer your head as a sacrifice to the Sovereign Mother!”

The knight in charge wore a thin layer of leather armour. The Underground Winter Spider below him was a bit larger than the ones around it, and its upper body was covered with golden stripes.

He inhaled deeply, and the Underground Winter Spider increased its speed. Immediately after, he aimed his bow and shot an arrow that flew elegantly, the arrowhead containing a secret, constantly-glowing rune.

*Zoom!*

A black ray of light emitted out of his hand, piercing through the sky and eventually landing on Memphis’ back!

“Ahh!”

A fiery red barrier of light appeared behind Memphis’ body, but when the arrow came into contact with the shield, the barrier could not even last a second and shattered instantly.

The black arrow continued its flight, and with its unknown strength pierced Memphis from behind, protruding out of his chest.

Memphis screamed, and the glowing arrow in his back disappeared. He collapsed to the ground, his flowing blood forming a pool of red streaked with silver.

*Hiss Hiss!*

The knights in the front surrounded him.

“Cut off his head!” The knight in charge heartlessly said and motioned to his men, resulting in two of his men walking up.

At this moment, the expression on the knight’s face changed. “No! Fall back!”

But it was too late.

*Bang!*

A strong wave of energy emanated from the body of Memphis, who was suddenly holding a scroll.

Two huge balls of light were shot out, and the two approaching knights were burnt to ashes, creating a huge cloud of smoke and dust.

After waiting for the aftermath of the explosion to subside, the knight in charge stepped forward with an irritated look on his face, but by that moment Memphis had already disappeared from the ground.

“Find him for me!” His face contorted in anger. “He has been injured by my curse; he will not be able to travel far!”

……

Baelin aimed with his crossbow, and it cut through the air with a *swoosh,* hitting the wild boar in front of him.

The wild boar squealed loudly, bleeding nonstop, but all Baelin did was to pull his crossbow bolt out.

“Haha! Uncle, Baelin’s present is here!”

After a fierce battle, Baelin smiled slightly while looking at the beast lying on the floor.

At this moment, a silhouette appeared from the other side of the battle field.

“Eh? Who is this?”

Baelin walked up, and the silhouette turned around, revealing a handsome white face….

Two hours later, Jenny was on her way home when she saw the dark elf that Baelin brought back. Putting her hand on her forehead, she groaned in despair and shouted, “You idiot! We’ve already offended the higher-ups and caused enough trouble…….”

Hearing Jenny’s complaints, Baelin innocently touched his head “I had no choice, seeing how pitiful he looks…….”

“Pitiful? Do you know what that is? It’s a dark elf! He is a purebred dark elf!”

Jenny’s face was flushed.

“This may be the border, but if you bring a dark elf, it could bring so much trouble to the town!”

In these recent three years, the Dark Elven Kingdom had frequently caused much insecurity and restlessness among the people!

Just with one look at the dark elf’s luxurious clothing, Jenny only had one thought, and that was whether or not the dark elf was like her, a member of nobility on the run because of a failed power struggle.

Thinking about this connection, Jenny started to break out into a cold sweat.

Regarding the cruelness of power struggles, she finally understood and knew that regardless of where this Elf hid, in the end, it would just be extending an endless cycle of fleeing and being hunted down. On top of this, her own people would suffer the consequences!

Thinking up to here, her eyes flashed with ferocity, but could only sigh when she saw the confused and helpless Baelin. Her tone also changed to one that was milder.

“Whatever happens, we must send him away quickly. I’m sure you don’t want to cause Aunt and Uncle Veeya any more trouble, right?

Baelin scratched his head. “Oh, alright!”

……

At Baelin’s former hunting ground, a bunch of Underground Winter Spider knights surrounded a pit where Memphis the dark elf was concealed.

A small Underground Winter Spider that was no bigger than a dog placed one foot into the cave, and then clicked at the knights.

“He said that aside from Memphis’, a human’s scent was found”

“Human?” the expression on the leader’s face sank, but then he suddenly started laughing maliciously. “No wonder Memphis is well known for peace! He has already been making connections with the humans”

He gestured to his men, “Follow them. I don’t care who dares to protect him, I want to chop their heads off personally as sacrificial offerings!”

“Yes my Lord!”

The Underground Winter Spider knights responded in order. The relationship between the people of the Dark Elven Kingdom and Twilight Zone was not the best. Crossing the border by a little bit was not such a big issue, but currently, it looked as if a new war was about to break out. Even so, they could still kill a few more men, steal their food, and enslave their women!

At this point in time, the eyes of many Underground Winter Spider knights flashed red.

An hour later, a horse wagon pulled by an old, slow, horse.

Baelin was guiding the horse, while Jenny was lying on a pile of straw with the dark elf that Baelin had previously saved.

The elf’s clothes were cut open at the front, revealing a skinny body. His delicate chest was marred by an arrow wound bordered by a black aura, shaped like a spider and continually expanding.

“How is he?” Baelin turned to ask.

“The external injuries are almost healed, but a curse was cast on him, and I do not have any ideas or methods to cure it!” Jenny raised her hands.

Although this injury was shocking, what surprised Jenny even more was the Elf’s vitality, which had allowed him to persevere and survive this long while suffering from the combination of such a serious injury and curse.

“The more that I think about it, the more I feel that this is not such a good idea. Judging from the curse, it is obvious that there is an official Magus after this fellow. If we do this, we will definitely infuriate his opponents!”

Jenny’s face turned gloomy.

Upon hearing that, Baelin could not help but tremble—this was an instinct that had been cultivated over many years. “Is an official Magus something like Lord Leylin?”

“Yes! Do you now understand how much trouble you have brought us?” Jenny gave Baelin an arrogant look.

“But haven’t we already saved him?” Baelin bitterly laughed. “What else can we do now then?”

All of a sudden, a burst of flames from afar roused Baelin from his thoughts.

In the dark, vast surroundings, this blaze was getting more and more obvious, almost dyeing the colour of the entire sky a fiery red.

“That is…. Our town!!!” Baelin stopped the horse, a frightened look on his face, “What happened? Why would this big fire suddenly appear?”

Jenny had a bad premonition. At this time, Baelin turned the horse without hesitation and headed towards the direction of the fire.

“Are you crazy?” Jenny cried out loud.

“Uncle Veeya and the rest are still inside, I want to save them!”

“They can’t be saved; can you calm down a little?” Jenny said with an agitated tone.

“What? How can you be like that? Have you forgotten? Aunt Veeya has treated you so well all this time!” Baelin said as he choked on a breath of air.

“This is not…”

“Sigh….”

While the two were arguing, the dark elf in the wagon suddenly coughed and woke up.

“A human!” He blurted out in the Twilight Zone’ Language.

Jenny’s heart went cold. The dark elves spoke a different language from humans, and this elf’s proficiency in their language was jarring.

In the subterranean world, knowledge was a trademark of nobility, and mastery of foreign languages was prominent amongst them.

When she was young, Jenny had been taught the languages of dark elves, gnomes, and even grey dwarves by a private tutor. Learning them despite the physiological differences was simply a nightmare! And yet, this dark elf spoke so cleanly that it took Jenny by surprise.

“Where is this place?” the dark elf asked as he sat up and looked at the lost Baelin.

“This is the Twilight Zone. Who are you?”

“I’m Memphis, and I need to go now. I’ve given you enough trouble already; I’m really sorry!”

The dark elf named Memphis had an apologetic look on his face.

Chapter 347: Destiny

Memphis struggled and wanted to get up. But immediately, the spider made of dark aura on his chest let out a hiss. His face went pale, and he fell back down as large beads of sweat rolled down his face.

*Shuffling*

Baelin suddenly heard a mild, yet periodic rumble.

“It’s coming from the town! Did someone survive?” Baelin beamed with delight.

In contrast, Memphis’ face suddenly changed. “It’s the footsteps of the Underground Winter Spiders! They have caught up with us!”

A short while later, the silhouettes of five Underground Winter Spider Knights appeared before Baelin’s eyes.

“Memphis! You’re really here!”

“That’s great, we actually found you!”

“His head will definitely give us some merit!”

The knights started chuckling, talking in their language. Jenny only managed to understand a few terms, whereas Baelin had a blank face as he could not understand it at all.

Very quickly, the blank look on his face turned into one of horror.

This was because the knights were sharing the backs of the Underground Winter Spiders with groups of severed human heads, which were still dripping with blood!

He could even see a few familiar faces amongst them.

“Unc—UNCLE VEEYA! What did you do to them!?” Baelin’s veins popped out with anger, and he unsheathed the cross sword on his back.

“Haha…” Although the Underground Winter Spider Knights could not understand Baelin’s reproaching them, they could infer his fury from his body language. One of them used a spear to pick up a head and started taunting Baelin

At the same time, another knight held a spear and rushed forward.

“Aaaaah… I’m going to kill all of you!” Baelin’s eyes were bloodshot, and he too rushed forward.

“Secret technique! Cross Star!” Baelin’s life force abruptly exploded and formed an illusory armour around his body.

“Kill!”

Cross blade and spear collided, and Baelin and the Underground Winter Spider knight both retreated a few steps.

Underground Winter Spider knights were the pinnacle of an army whose regular soldiers each matched human Grand Knights. Combining their own ability with runes and their mounts, their strength vastly surpassed that of the average Grand Knight.

However, Baelin himself was no ordinary Grand Knight and could fight him evenly.

Unfortunately, Baelin had to fight not one opponent, but five!

After seeing the life force explode out from Baelin’s body, a few knights looked at each other, shouted a few words Baelin could not understand and rushed forward.

*Pew*

A black ray shot through the sky and landed on the shoulders of an Underground Winter Spider Knight, piercing into the knight’s shoulder with some difficulty.

Jenny stood on the carriage, bow in hand. Her face was calm whilst she shot arrows non-stop.

Naturally, she could see the situation clearly. Under present circumstances, the only way to survive was eliminating this small party.

The problem was that they were badly outnumbered, and each of their opponents was stronger than Grand Knights; exterminating them would not be easy.. Jenny smiled bitterly in her heart.

As was to be expected, Baelin was slowly surrounded by the knights and seemed unable to endure any more attacks. The illusory armor around him began to appear as if it would explode any moment.

*Creak! Creak!*

One of the Spiders, under its rider’s commands, leaped past Baelin’s resistance and arrived before the carriage

The black spear pierced forth, and the resulting winds caused Jenny’s face to change.

“Ouch!” Nearby, Baelin let out a groan. His armor had disintegrated, and blood was gushing out from all of his wounds.

*Buzz! Buzz!*

Suddenly, Jenny felt a strong energy wave explode violently next to her. She turned her head and saw Memphis struggling to open a scroll in his hands.

A grey ripple swept out, the ring of light seeming to be a spirit avoiding both Jenny and Baelin as it reached the Underground Winter Spider Knights. It was like a halo that bound the knights and their mounts.

The knights that had been bound by the halo immediately felt the enormous power they were proud of dissipating. Even their mounts began trembling as if they could not stand under their own weight.

“A Weakening Imprint! Retreat!” A knight immediately shouted.

But at this time, Baelin lost all self-restraint. “Die!”

“Cross Blade!” He violently used the last bit of his spiritual energy and executed the killing stance of the cross sword technique.

A blade of light in the shape of a cross mercilessly slashed through the four surrounding knights.

Their faces became lifeless, and in a few moments, they disintegrated along with their mounts.

*Whoosh* Jenny seized this chance and used a single arrow to pierce through the neck of the last escaping knight.

Memphis let out a smile, but abruptly spat out black blood, after which he fainted.

Half a day later, on the carriage, Jenny looked at the defeated Baelin, and Memphis beside her, and was speechless.

“Why? Why must we kill? Why must there be war?” Baelin muttered under his breath, the world having lost all colour.

“This is an answer that I’ve been looking for, but unfortunately I have not reached a conclusion!”

Currently, Memphis was using the sap from a green plant to wrap the wounds on his chest. He laughed bitterly, “The two of you have saved me. I, Memphis, swear upon the honor of the dark royalty that I will repay the two of you!”

“Let’s not talk about that for now. The conflict you mentioned previously, is that real?” Jenny was obviously more concerned about this issue than other matters.

“It’s real! I have suffered from persecution and attempted assassination from others just because I advocated for peace!”

Memphis’ eyes glowed, and his voice sank.

“What’s our plan now?”

Jenny looked at Baelin.

“I have decided! I must do my best to prevent the war this time around. I don’t want to see more people shedding blood!”

Baelin’s voice was coarse but held an unquestionable resolve.

“You’re crazy!” Jenny was trembling: “Based on your ability alone??”

“No! There’s still him!” Baelin pointed to Memphis. “I will escort him back to the Dark Elven Empire and try my best to stop the war!”

Having made that decision, Baelin suddenly felt like he was heating up.

He ripped opened his clothes, revealing a gold coin that had a peculiar exterior. On one side of the coin was a skeleton, whereas on the other side was a lucky bird; the rim of the coin gave off a dim glow. Baelin had pierced through the gold coin, run a string through it, and hung it on his neck.

Baelin caressed the gold coin, his eyes showing signs of even more determination, “Mister Leylin! Master! You support me as well, don’t you?”

……

Eastern Twilight Zone, Nature’s Alliance headquarters.

Currently, Nature’s Alliance had stabilised its strength as a medium-scale guild and had countless hundreds of acolytes, far from what it was like in the past.

Moreover, the increased presence of Magi strengthened their defenses greatly. They were now a few ranks higher than before.

In the forbidden area in the middle of Nature’s Alliance, within a huge laboratory.

Leylin blanked out and immediately looked towards the golden crystal in his hands. Currently, the crystal was emitting a faint heat, and the golden light generated from within enshrouded it.

“A portion of the spiritual force has been received?” Leylin suddenly laughed.

“It looks like Baelin has already started walking along with his destined spiritual path! The strength of fate will accumulate in his body!”

Leylin glanced at the A.I. Chip’s progress with the recovery of the meditation techniques.

Sacred Flame, the high-grade meditation technique that Leylin longed for, the same one that could predict the future, had finally been fully recovered. There were even a few areas that were being constantly improved.

On the other hand, Kemoyin’s Pupil had not advanced at all in the past three years, remaining at halfway to completion. Leylin assumed that the lack of high-grade meditation techniques meant that advancing it to the fourth grade was exceedingly difficult.

After all, the only one rank four technique in his possession could only be cultivated by Dragons, while the others had no information that could assist in the progress of Kemoyin’s Pupil.

On the other hand, Sacred Flame had been recovered much earlier, and even went through a few modifications to remove the negative repercussions.

It was a pity that the A.I. Chip only managed to simulate it to the third rank. This meant the technique only went this far, and that left Leylin feeling slightly regretful

“Since the gears of fate have started to turn, then I can only continue to scatter more of these ‘seeds’ so as to anticipate a harvest in the future!” Leylin stroked his chin and looked towards the experiment table.

The silver-white table top had a few peculiar objects on it. Among these items were a black ring, a five-coloured pendant, and a tattered notebook.

“A.I. Chip! Begin!” Leylin’s eyes shot out a blue glow, and he picked the few objects up.

[Limited AI programming has been completed, inputting data!] The A.I Chip intoned.

After a few minutes, Leylin picked up the black ring. A ray of light shot out, and out came the figure of a scholarly looking Magus.

“I am the legendary Grand Magus Merlin, you lucky fellow! You will receive my advice and become the Twilight Zone’s strongest genius!”

Leylin’s mouth quivered. The Grand Magus figure seemed to have life, as it spoke with charm.

These were the limited Artificial Intelligences that Leylin had been designing. He had the ability to control the programs remotely, which made them very useful.

Having been pleased with himself after the adjustments, Leylin placed the few items into an empty bag and walked out of the laboratory.

“My lord!”

Along the way, no matter whether they were official Magi or acolytes, all of them lowered their heads in respect. Some acolytes would even bow from a distance, and quickly walk away.

“I can’t believe that even I would receive such treatment!” Leylin abruptly laughed.

If high-level Magi had not intentionally exercised restraint, the strong radiation that emitted from their bodies would be a type of contagion that could even be lethal to low-level acolytes.

As a result, previously in the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, there were many forbidden areas, which were actually the living areas and experimentation areas of high-level Magi.

In the past, when Leylin had seen those Magi, he would also bow from a distance before quickly avoiding them.

But now, it was time for others to do so instead.

Chapter 350: Serendipity

*Snap!*

Space seemed to freeze for a moment, but then it seemed like nothing had happened.

The black spider totems began began to dissipate slowly, and Anya’s voice sounded out, “You’ve grown old already”

*Bang!* The black imprints dissolved into light. There were fewer stalks on his back now, and milky white sap flowed out of his injuries.

When the old man raised his head once again, he seemed older; patches of grey had begun to appear on his skin.

“Has this body’s vitality been taxed to its limit?” The old man looked at the spots on his body,and couldn’t help but laugh bitterly his eyes dull and lifeless.

“Time…” the old man said with a long sigh that instantly swept away the rays of light. The cave turned dark once more.

……

Aaron had returned to his room.

The last rays of twilight revealed a mix of rotting wooden boards and moldy corners. This stinky room was the ‘luxury’ he was awarded sole residence in. This dilapidated room showed how much he was valued.

Yet, at this time, he could not bring himself to care about it. His mind was occupied with his earlier encounter.

Patrol. Detection spell formation. The youth with black eyes… Memories flitted across his mind.

‘I’ve definitely seen him before! But why can’t I remember where?’ he was trying hard to recall. Suddenly, he covered his face and started screaming, veins popping out at his temples. The pain caused him to black out. His screams permeated the room until he returned to his senses a few moments later, finding himself on the ground.

Hot sweat rolled down Aaron’s face as he gasped.

“Again and again! This disease from my adventure in the wastelands is wasting away my spiritual force…”

*Bang!*

At that moment, as if unable to withstand his frustration, a piece of the floor rose up. A black gleam immediately caught Aaron’s attention.

“What… is this?” Curiosity piqued, he dug out the black object and placed it on his palm. It was a ring with ancient writings on it, one whose surface was coated in black. Aaron’s heart skipped a beat.

“A ring?” He twisted it around, “It’s still giving off faint energy waves, is it a magic artifact?”

Magical artifacts, regardless of size and grade, will save your life on the battlefield. As his thoughts turned towards that direction, Aaron couldn’t help breathing heavily.

All of a sudden, he felt a surging pain from his hand, a prick which caused him to shout and almost throw the ring to the ground.

“What’s this?” Aaron looked at his forefinger, stunned, as blood dripped onto the ring from the punctured skin. A small thorn could be seen on the edge of the black ring, which was what had hurt him just now.

*Xiu!* The blood drop was immediately absorbed like water on a sponge. The black ring flashed before turning grey. Simultaneously, the energy waves it was previously giving off vanished and the ring seemed to lose all power, now just an ordinary object.

“This… is it the ‘Binding Ceremony?’ in myths” Aaron scratched his head with uncertainty.

Although Aaron did not know much about magic artifacts, he was aware that some high-grade magic artifacts that were extremely rare required a ceremony to bind them to oneself. And the catalyst to begin these ceremonies… was blood!

“Hahaha! Kid, you’re right!” At this moment, a voice sounded in Aaron’s head.

“Who is it? Who’s there?” The sudden voice bewildered Aaron and he began to look around. He could see no one..

“I’m in the palm of your hand!” replied an aged voice.

“You are… the ring?” Aaron’s eyes suddenly widened.

“Mm! Kid, how about we make a deal?” the old man laughed heartily.

“No! I will not make any deals with you, nor will I sell my soul to you!” Aaron said firmly.

Magi were not reclusive people. Aaron had heard stories about ancient beings and exotic creatures that made deals with humans, toying with them and harvesting their spirits.

“Really? You don’t want to restore your aptitude anymore?” The old man’s laugh was sinister.

“Re… Restore my aptitude?” Aaron’s heartbeat quickened.

“I’ve grasped the mysteries of the soul. If your aptitude had been this low originally, it would have been difficult to increase it. But it’s still possible to reverse the effects of the damage to your soul…” the old man explained.

“Who are you exactly? Why would you help me?” Aaron asked, reigning his emotions in.

“I am the ancient legendary Magus, Merlin…… ‘s memory fragment!” the old man paused, causing Aaron to slip.

“Memory fragment?”

“Yes. My physical body has long since decayed, but this fragment has remained here, stuck in this ring…” The old man seemed to be reminiscing.

“As for why I’m helping you, I told you before. I want something in return!”

“What do you want?” Although Aaron was desperate for a cure to his problem, he was still alert and vigilant.

“Don’t worry, you’re someone destined for death. How much can I really ask of you? I’m not a devil that is here to collect your soul!”

Merlin chuckled, “I need you to gather my remaining fragments! And in return, not only will I cure your disease, I’ll even pass on a complete high-grade meditation technique to you and help you advance to become an official Magus…”

……

“High-grade meditation technique, an official Magus!” Aaron was delighted, but this was immediately followed by piercing agony. Originally, he had hopes of achieving all these, but now….

“Your remaining fragments? What do you mean?”

“I’d originally made many magic equipments into which I’d placed fragments of my spirit. I’d been expecting big misfortune, and prepared them to tide it over. You need to help me find the remaining fragments of my spirit…”

“Every artifact you find will be of great help to us!” Merlin reassured Aaron upon noticing his hesitation. “Besides, the current you is too weak to help me, so I’ll also help you increase your strength as much as possible!”

“What are you trying to do? Do you intend to resurrect yourself?” Aaron guessed.

“Hehe… The rules of Death aren’t something a trifling Magus like me can interfere with. I’m only a remnant filled with unfulfilled desires, and I’m unwilling to remain cooped up in a ring forever. I need your help to find my remaining fragments. Do this one thing for me, and we will be even. I swear on my own spirit!”

“You don’t need to swear, I will help you!” Aaron fiercely said.

“You’re right! What have you to gain from fooling a dead man like me? For that woman to abandon me for her own pleasure, I will not stand for it!” Aaron said with red eyes.

“Haha! Alright, even if I’m a mere fragment, I still possess a huge amount of knowledge. All you need is that to become Twilight Zone’s premier genius! Then, you can easily rise above the others once again!” Magus Merlin laughed heartily in Aaron’s head.

“Then, let’s summon the Trial’s Eye and sign a contract?” The fury on Aaron’s face disappeared, and he calmly stated this condition.

“Of course!” the old man said after a brief period of silence.

Aaron’s eyes flashed and he immediately summoned the Trial’s Eye hologram as a witness.

“Under the witness of the Trial’s Eye….”

In the room, the voices of two people swearing an oath could be heard.

……

“It’s done!”

On the other side, Leylin who was in the laboratory laughed, looked at his own body bound by Trial’s Eye and held a pitcher with the solution of a Nefarious Filthbird’s feathers.

That thing was sent on purpose by the ring.

Merlin was just a limited AI, but it could fool the inexperienced Aaron. Furthermore, at critical moments, Leylin could control him from afar.

All in all, this was just a counterfeit of a certain ring and grandfather.

“With what I’ve given you, how will you affect the wind and waves of Twilight Zone? I’m looking forward to it!” Leylin chuckled, and an intense light flashed in his eyes.

……

As a nervous atmosphere permeated Dolon City, all the commoners were evacuated. Within days, many darkness creatures surrounded it, and among them could be seen the faint silhouettes of people.

“Sir Leylin! Sir Fendix has invited you to the City Wall!” A middle aged man wearing golden armor respectfully informed Leylin.

This middle aged man was Duke Fendix, the commander of the army. The Fendix Family had consecrated numerous official Magi, many of whom were famous. Furthermore, this included two of Fendix’s own descendants.

But in front of Leylin, they were required to lower their heads like a commoner in the presence of a noble.

“Got it!” Leylin said as he slowly closed the big book in his hand and arrived at the City Wall.

Because this was the first attack, not only were there numerous soldiers and generals, but Magi were also present to watch.

“Sir Leylin!” Fendix greeted Leylin, floating in mid-air.

Leylin laughed as he flew up to join him. The two looked at a black line at the difference that was rushing at them like a tide.

“Magnificent, is it not?” The beginning stages of the war would be fought by cannon fodder. These creatures did not possess much strength, and Fendix’s expression did not even change.

“Magnificent indeed!” Leylin could not help but say lightly as he looked beyond the wall. There were hundreds of thousands of darkness creatures down below.

He had not expected so many darkness creatures to be here. And this number was only that of those in the area. The total number of darkness creatures in all the armies was definitely astronomical.

“Darkness creatures, human beings, and the other species; this land cannot support all of us. Thus, every once in a while, all these races go to war…..” a female rank 2 Magus said softly at the side.

“Among all the races, war and alliance both have occurred countless times since long ago……”

“This war will have no winners and losers. Only after all groups have used up nearly all their resources, supplies and soldiers, only then, can the war end…..”

Chapter 351: Bestowal

Upon hearing that, Leylin turned silent.

History showed that, when both sides in a war had equal military strength at all levels, this was indeed the largest possibility.

With the lifespan of the protector of Twilight Zone being at an end, they were actually at a disadvantage. Although the entire race wouldn’t be exterminated, the humans would lose large amounts of their territory.

“Our strategy this time is to rely on using the three cities to defend. Every city has three rank 2 Magi stationed there, as well as a large army. The protector of the east is on standby, ready to reinforce any of the cities as required!”

Leylin stroked his chin. “The bloodbath here will truly be terrifying….”

“Hoo.. Hoo….”

As if tired of waiting, many darkness creatures started an uproar as they charged towards the city’s walls.

Ten thousand horses charged on the field, causing the ground to tremble a little.

Fendix’s face remained unchanged and he used a secret imprint to pass a message. “Engage the first layer of defense!”

Instantly, many runes appeared on the massive city walls of Dolon, radiating light that shaped itself into a barrier.

*Boom!*

Flames! Tongues of flame shot out, swallowing the darkness creatures nearby. They gradually grew larger, slowly spreading out further.

“Isn’t it a little early to be using fire elemental formations?” Leylin cringed his brows.

“These darkness creatures may not be strong, but there are too many of them. We cannot let them exhaust our strength in numbers with just the first exchange. In addition, we need our troops to have high morale. We still have a lot of magic crystals in reserve and these outermost formations don’t consume as many. There’s no need to worry!” Fendix gazed at the battlefield and explained to Leylin casually.

Raging flames burned like a giant torch in the middle of the night, attracting innumerable Dark Moths to them.

Aaron stood at the top of the city, his face pale at the sight before him. The burning corpses had a pungent odour which sent shivers down his spine.

After waiting for the fire to burn out, the darkness creatures charged to the base of the walls and were about to enter battle with the city guard.

Out of the corner of his eye, Aaron noticed a ferocious beast with sharp claws and fierce, pearly white teeth drooling. Immediately, he looked at the grey ring on the forefinger of his right hand and shouted out within his mind: “Grandpa Merlin! If you don’t help me now, I’m definitely dead meat!”

“Fret not. With me here, nothing will happen to you!” Merlin’s voice sounded inside Aaron’s head. This was not Leylin talking to him, but the limited AI.

“Originally, you could simply have defected and run away, but it’s a pity that we are now in the middle of war! If you try to escape, all the magicians in Twilight Zone will be left with no choice but to immediately hunt you down!” Merlin seemed to sigh.

If this was during times of peace and Aaron had defected and escaped, naturally only the members of his own guild would be hunting him down. But all that changed during war,

“Of course I know this!” Aaron panicked.

“Move three steps backwards! Use the Secondary Energy Fireball Technique! Aim 50 degrees to the right!” Merlin commanded with a cold and stern tone.

Aaron’s body could not help but obey the voice, and he moved three steps backwards, avoiding the claws of a beast.

“Quack! Quack!”

A huge black crow spiraled downwards and upon seeing Aaron’s escape, an almost human glint of regret flashed in its eyes.

“Dammit! I. Want. To. Kill. You!” Aaron said quickly as he paused at each syllable and swung his right hand at the bird.

A small fireball cut through the air and struck the crow.

*Boom!* A scarlet red flame burned the crow to cinders within moments. The creature did not even get to make a sound before it was burnt to a crisp.

“Just now, that was……” Aaron’s eyes lost focus.

He was certain that his fireball had been aimed nowhere close to the crow. Still, it seemed to have foolishly flown into its path.

“Foresight! This is something you must learn quickly if you don’t wish to die on the battlefield!” Merlin said from within the ring.

And Aaron looked at the admiration in the eyes of the acolytes surrounding him, and clenched his fist tightly in the dark: “I will….”

……

A few hours later, the sound of a desolate beast’s howl travelled from afar, and like the tide, all the darkness creatures retreated. Fendix nodded his head: “It seems like today was just a probe. Let us head back!”

At this moment, several dark elf knights on their Underground Winter Spiders stood on the mud slope before the horde. Gazing at the scene, one of them nodded.

“The enemies’ three rank 2 matriarchs are gathered here; this is where the battle shall occur. Send the signal!”

One of the knights said a few words to a white carrier pigeon and released the bird immediately after.

The white carrier pigeon circled in the air and flew away into the horizon.

……

Night had fallen, and military curfew had made the entirety of Dolon quiet. Back in that small, moldy room, Merlin was talking to Aaron with assurance.

“You have already been sent here. No matter what reason you have, escaping your duties is a one-way street to death. There is only one thing you can do now, and that is serve! Accumulate a lot of contribution points, and use them to speed up your advance to a rank 1 Magus! Magi all have the power to make their own decisions, which will greatly increase your chances of survival……”

Although the entire battlefield was full of danger, there was still some hope.

At least for the magicians, the war council had set up a reward system. This allowed one to exchange contribution points for resources.

It is difficult for one to rise to power in periods of peace. War, however, produced countless heroes. It was a time when high risk met high reward.

“Of course, I know this!” Aaron thought deeply: “But my aptitude and meditation technique….” He hesitated.

“I’m working to fix your aptitude. After yesterday’s minor operation, you felt it too, didn’t you?” Merlin chuckled. The only thing manipulating him now was Leylin, who was free at the moment.

It was Leylin himself who had harmed Aaron’s aptitude in the past. Now, with the A.I. Chip and the information he had obtained from his time in Nature’s Alliance, this sort of minor injury was easy to heal.

Hearing this, Aaron’s expression relaxed. Ever since Merlin had conducted an operation on him, the pain from his injuries had alleviated, and his aptitude had been restored.

“However, just this is not enough!” Merlin continued explaining, “Your aptitude is only in the third grade, and this is your limit. Magi who can increase your aptitude have long since gone extinct. Although with your current rank you can force yourself to practice your guild’s high-grade meditation technique, it doesn’t really suit you….”

Aaron’s face sank. The high-level meditation technique passed down in this Guild was Blazing Heart, and it didn’t have many requirements. As long as one had affinity for the fire element and possessed an aptitude that was at or above the third rank, they could practice it.

But there was a problem here. His primary affinity was not fire, but water. Fire was only a secondary affinity of his. Furthermore, for a magician to practice Blazing Heart, the higher the aptitude the better. His third rank aptitude just barely met the standards.

“Basically, you have no way of getting recognition and learning the high-level meditation technique from your guild!” Merlin concluded.

“Yeah! So what now?” Aaron’s eyes were tinted by dejection.

“Hahaha…” At this time, Merlin laughed out loud and said: “Have you forgotten? I, Merlin, am a legendary Magus. How would I not have high-grade meditation techniques of my own?”

“I will bestow upon you a complete high-grade meditation technique. Furthermore, it has the frightening ability of allowing you to peer into the future! If you can predict the future, you can control everything!” Merlin’s voice was full of confidence.

“Foresee the future, control the future!” Aaron’s breathing grew heavier.

“That’s right! This meditation technique is called—Sacred Flame!”

……

In Dolon City, Leylin’s bedroom was vastly different from Aaron’s.

The gold-plated floor, the soft, silk brocade quilt, huge crystal chandeliers and gold and silver plates holding many fruits… comparing Aaron’s room to this place was like comparing a beggar’s shack to a grand palace.

“Few acolytes can resist the temptation of a high-grade meditation technique…” Leylin sighed. With his connection, he could tell that Aaron had begun using this new technique, and he let out a soft gasp.

Although the A.I. chip had repaired Sacred Flame and eliminated its side-effects, Leylin was still cautious of it. The soul was a huge mystery. While Leylin had previously assumed that his research into spirits was profound, after being at the mercy of a ghost, he had realized how ridiculous his thoughts were.

The amount of research he had done in the field of spirits was negligible. He had realized he was like a frog in a well, and completely abandoned any previous notions he had about the depth of his research.

Even more so, regarding the high-grade meditation technique Sacred Flame, he wished only to admire and respect it from afar. Although he thirsted for the power of destiny, he did not want to devolve into a schizophrenic madman.

Thus, it was necessary to collect data through live tests, which was what he had put into motion.

Leylin had a blank expression on his face, full of indifference. His gaze pierced through a veil of light and stared into the future.

……

The next day, the darkness creatures besieged the city as usual with their cannon fodder.

*Boom!* A fireball was shot and turned a huge black bear into a torch.

Aaron calmly retracted his hand. Uncaring of the increasingly reverent looks of the acolytes around him, he walked to the side and began meditating to restore his spiritual force.

“How does the new meditation technique feel?” Merlin and Aaron were conversing inside his head.

Aaron had previously only practiced in a simplified meditation technique. Even Leylin felt unfathomable that the transition was this smooth.

And after practicing the Sacred Flame, Aaron’s aura had faintly changed.

Chapter 352: Ten Years in a Flash

“I feel great! Be it restoring my spiritual force or during cultivation, high-grade meditation techniques are leagues beyond the simplified versions,” Aaron told Merlin as he stood up.

“But what about the aura that I’m giving off? If any of the guild members find me, I’ll definitely be caught and interrogated…”

“Haha… Don’t worry. This magic ring that I’ve smelted can conceal your aura and create artificial fluctuations in your spiritual force. With your current strength, even an official Magus won’t be able to discover you!” Merlin was very confident.

“Really?” Aaron’s eyes brightened.

“Of course, don’t you know who I am? Furthermore, this is a magical artifact! A magical artifact! Do you know what that means? You’re far too weak right now, or else you’d be able to display more of its power…”

“Not really, but I’ve heard about them before.”

Aaron scratched his head. “What do I do next?”

“Keep killing our enemies and accumulate merit points! I took a look at the reward list yesterday, and the potion there that can suppress your spiritual force will be of use. You absolutely must get that!”

“I understand!” Aaron clenched his fist tightly, eyes showing his resolution. “That lowly woman and the Broderick Family, I’ll be back!”

……

Two months passed by.

Outside the walls of Dolon, the war raged on. Numerous armies of dark elves had stationed themselves across from the city, their camps stretching out along tens of miles. Several golden tents stood at the center of their army camp, the aura within enough to cause even Leylin to furrow his brows.

Under organized command, the battle power of the darkness creatures and elves had risen by several levels. Dolon City was embroiled in intense battle, with the weakest rung suffering the most casualty.

However, there was a steady supply of cannon fodder from the eastern region which allowed them to hold on.

Under such high pressure, the atmosphere in Dolon City grew increasingly heavy. A sense of an impending crisis enveloped everyone’s hearts.

Aaron was now a little famous, the limelight finding him after he beat up a few acolytes who had been sent to make trouble for him.

Given that Magi valued strength more than anything else, his residence had now been shifted. This one was bright, clean, and much larger than before.

Aaron was currently sitting on a blue striped bedsheet with beads of sweat rolling down his face. Leylin, in the meantime, was monitoring his actions from within the black ring.

This was the first time he was using the unique spiritual force born from his new meditation technique, Sacred Flame, to explore the tides of destiny.

Leylin paid close attention to this and ordered the A.I. Chip to periodically collect data and accumulate information in his database.

The Sacred Flame Aaron trained in was obviously not the one which the A.I. Chip had perfected. This version had been modified by Leylin using the chip, and many manipulative portions had been added in.

“It’s here!” Leylin laughed, and black undulations filled his eyes.

Immediately after, the visions were intercepted by the ring.

Above the city, Aaron rose his arms and shot out a fireball, causing a huge wild boar to roll down, while a grin appeared on his face.

But at this moment, an anomaly occurred. A large black monkey jumped out of the retreating horde. It had three eyes, and the centre one shot out a red beam. The monkey itself exploded forth with a power that equalled an official Magus!

Without any time to dodge, Aaron was blasted into smithereens!

Such scenes flashed across Leylin’s eyes but were rather blurry and unordered.

“So that’s how it is! At this rate, Aaron will die in the siege three days later?” Leylin touched his chin.

[Information from the meditation technique has been intercepted! Allow transmission?] The A.I. Chip’s robotic voice intoned.

“Yes!” The moment Leylin spoke, Aaron’s body trembled on the bed, his two eyes losing focus and rolling back as if he had seen something terrifying.

Leylin’s had implemented backdoor changes to the Sacred Flame. By coupling these changes with the limited AI in the ring, any premonitions Aaron had would be intercepted and first seen by Leylin. Only with his approval would these scenes from the future enter Aaron’s mind.

Besides interception, Leylin could modify these bits of vision at will. In other words, Aaron only saw what Leylin had wanted him to see.

After all, it was better to be cautious towards acolytes whose training in this allowed them to see the future. If not, what was he to do if they got a hold of his plans through their prophecies?

Of course, Aaron did not have a strong cultivation in this technique yet. He was only capable of prophesying events at the ability of a level 1 acolyte, which kept him from being able to sense anything about Leylin.

Even if he advanced to become an official Magus, with Leylin intercepting first, he would not sense anything.

To become cognizant of the interception, he needed to, at the very least, equal Leylin in power. This meant he could not predict Leylin’s actions and prepare against them until he was promoted to a rank 2 Magus! Unfortunately, Leylin would not give him the opportunity to do so.

“Although the A.I. Chip could not upgrade Sacred Flame past rank 3, at least it’s no longer restricted to only females.” Leylin touched his chin.

“There aren’t enough guinea pigs yet!” He turned around and glanced at the colourful necklace and incomplete notebook on the table.

These were at most special magical objects. He only called them magic artifacts to fool acolytes like Aaron.

But it was enough.

“On the battlefield, one cannot control their own life nor death. If I put out this bait, they’ll have to bite no matter how suspicious they are.!” Leylin beamed confidently.

As for why he had not bought slaves or chosen people from Nature’s Alliance? It would be too obvious that he was the mastermind, which was not conducive to Leylin’s plans.

Meanwhile, Aaron was scared stupid by the prediction.

“Hah… I’ll die three days later, at the hands of a darkness creature with the strength of an official Magus,” he huffed roughly. He had visibly paled and was trembling in the aftermath of that premonition.

“What are you afraid of? This is just a possibility in the river of destiny. I’ve already predicted my death tens of times, but haven’t I gotten through alive and well?” Merlin appeared, looking disdainful.

“Yes, yes!” The light in Aaron’s eyes brightened. He now knew the many benefits of being able to make use of the power of destiny.

“What should we do now?” Aaron began to ponder enthusiastically.

“It’s simple! Just apply to leave this region or pretend you’re injured and hide for these few days!” Merlin seemed to be very experienced in this.

……

The dark elves’ offensive was not limited to just the eastern region of Twilight Zone.

The northern region had also suffered the charge of the dark elves. City after city fell until a few rank 2 Magi struck out, finally stabilising the situation. Still, they had been able to push the battlefront inwards by a few hundred meters. They had even dispatched elite Underground Winter Spider knights who seemed to be scouts sent for reconnaissance.

The eastern region was comparatively quiet. The tripartite defense of Dolon, Wakeshire, and Sadoor, with the continuous supply of troops, maintained an uneasy stalemate. Even so, capitalising on the endless darkness creatures as cannon fodder, the dark elves had caused many injuries to the Magi defending the posts.

It was a given that numerous acolytes would die, but even some official Magi had fallen. As for regular soldiers and knights? Too many of them were lost to even count.

In the blink of an eye, ten years passed. Leylin had been relieved a few times and periodically returned to Nature’s Alliance.

In this period of time, however, he kept a low profile and seldom did anything flashy. Hence, he did not have a large reputation.

Only he knew how much he had improved during this period of time.

“Leylin! I’ve received the heart of the Earthen Fiend. There are fifty here, and I’ve sent them to your lab!” A rune lit up and transmitted Fendix’s voice.

“Thanks a lot! I’ll get in touch with you later.” Leylin answered delightfully. “I’ve finally gotten it! Now all the requirements have been met!”

He hurried to the laboratory, where a Magus dressed in black robes was waiting for him. The man respectfully bowed his head, saying, “This is the heart of the Earthen Fiend that Lord Fendix wanted me to pass on to you. Please sign here to show that you received it.”

“En!” Leylin nodded and took the ingredients. After checking every single one, he nodded in satisfaction. He waved his arm over the piece of parchment the Magus in black robes proffered, and a black snake imprint formed immediately.

Seeing this, the Magus bowed and respectfully left.

Leylin entered his laboratory and activated spell formations for isolation and defense. A layer of various lit runes began to circulate outside.

“With all the ingredients here, I can finally attempt to brew potions!” Smiling, Leylin looked at his stats.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 2 Warlock, Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 21.1, Agility: 14.4, Vitality: 29.9, Spiritual force: 127.9, Magic power: 127 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force).]

He had spent every day of the past ten years training in his high-grade meditation technique, slowly tempering his spiritual force. Over the course of his training of Kemoyin’s Pupil, he began to feel that the issue of irritability that was caused by his premature advancement was slowly corrected.

Given the quick pace of his advancement last time, an unstable foundation was only to be expected.

However, all of that was made up for in the past ten years.

Chapter 354: Longbottom Strikes

In the many scattered images, there was also a figure that Leylin was extremely familiar with.

“Baelin?” A smile crept upon his lips.

……

“Are you sure it’s here?” Baelin asked, swallowing hard. The pitch-black hole in front of him seemed like the mouth of some weird creature. The aura on his body rose rapidly, nearly exceeding the limits of a regular human.

“We dark elves get all our Underground Winter Spiders from this hallowed place. It is where the Underground Winter Spider Emperor lives. Do you really think I’d risk my life to bring you here if I wasn’t sure?” Memphis rolled his eyes.

“As long as you can kill or dominate it, the Underground Winter Spider knights would immediately fall apart, and this war might just end,” he said with a sigh.

“How powerful is that Underground Winter Spider Emperor?” Baelin felt uncomfortable looking at the hole as if he had been laid bare before someone’s eyes.

“At least rank 2!” Memphis waved his arms, “But luckily, it’s deep in slumber right now, and won’t notice you.”

“I can’t help, though,” he added, “Any dark elves who’ve signed contracts with Underground Winter Spiders will wake it up as soon as they enter the vicinity!”

Not all ancient creatures were at the Morning Star realm. Morning Star Magi were considered formidable even in ancient times, so how could such strong creatures be common?

Baelin and Memphis had a very simple plan: they would either kill the Underground Winter Spider Emperor or force it to submit, a move so drastic which would cause enough damage to the dark elves’ military that they would be forced to withdraw,

“…Fine,” Baelin huffed.

He turned and said, “I’m ready. Come!” In front of him was a bizarre lump of meatball that looked like a huge poached egg. What was even more terrifying was the presence of dozens of eyes on the thing, all open and staring at Baelin without blinking.

“How many times must I tell you? Even if you received my owner’s inheritance and advanced to become a rank 1 Magus, the current you are far from an opponent for rank 2 Magi. Leave alone you, even with me joining the fray, we won’t survive this encounter!” The lump said, blinking. It had the delicate voice of a child.

“That was an order!” Baelin’s expression darkened.

“Alright, alright! Whatever! I finally find a new owner, and he turns out to be an idiot!” The egg-like creature shook its head.

With the order given, it shot over to Baelin’s body, extending countless meaty feelers that fused with him. Baelin grew much larger than before as the meat solidified and formed a dull red armour patterned with tens of eyes, something that made it seem very mysterious.

The moment the armour formed, Baelin’s aura broke through the limits of humans, stabilising at the strength of an official Magus.

“This map and amulet have been passed down from generation to generation. I wish you luck in this venture!” Memphis sincerely blessed him.

“Thank you!” Baelin answered, a pair of metallic large red wings spreading behind him before he charged into the hole.

The journey to escort Memphis back home had been arduous. Baelin, Jenny, and the dark elf faced danger after danger, all while being hunted down by people from both sides.

Fortunately, they had managed to survive the ordeal and infiltrate the Dark Elven Empire, getting him to a safe area. In addition, Baelin had acquired a unique inheritance which had led him along the path of a Bio Booster, a branch of ancient Magi.

After gaining this inheritance, Baelin’s progress soared, until he became an official Magus.

With the Bio Boosting armour that he had obtained and inherited as well, his strength was beyond that of a regular official Magus.

The moment he jumped into the hole, he suddenly felt as if the coin he hung around his neck heated up…

In the laboratory.

Leylin glanced at the golden crystal in his hands. Golden liquid now occupied more than half the volume within and appeared to be glittering splendidly.

“As expected of the child of destiny. This rate of improvement is something even I might not be able to match!” Leylin sighed.

Back then, he had tested Baelin for his aptitude, but it had appeared to be meagre. It was basically impossible for him to advance to be an official Magus.

In addition, Leylin was only teaching him out of curiosity and playfulness, and would naturally not impart knowledge only Magi were privy to.

Now though, destiny had played its hand. Baelin’s strength was growing boundlessly, to the point that he could now affect the results of the war.

In ancient times, the spread of ideas between different worlds, as well as the creativity and tolerance of ancient Magi, had led to the formation of many different branches. Some examples were Bloodline Warlocks, Elemental Bards, Branded Swordsmen, Steel Knights, and even the recently rediscovered Bio Boosters.

Leylin recalled the information he had recently found from an ancient volume about Bio Boosters.

These ancient Magi were extremely strange and required their inheritors to have the aptitude to become both Knights and Magi.

In addition, they had to have Bio Boosting armour!

After obtaining the armour, a Bio Booster’s strength would rise sharply, and after fusing, the armor would automatically change the body of the host; this strengthened them continuously.

In addition, this armour could be inherited. The moment a Bio Booster gained the armour left behind by a higher ranked Bio Booster, they would immediately gain more strength.

In Leylin’s eyes, Baelin was quite suited to become a Bio Booster.

“Destiny…”

Leylin sniggered and left the laboratory.

……

“Fendix, thank you for the hearts of Earthen Fiends. I’ll make it up to you for whatever I haven’t paid you!”

Holding a cup of coffee, Leylin chatted with Magus Fendix, who was in front of him.

“These are all small matters. You don’t need to be so polite!” Fendix laughed but did not reject him. Magi were quite clear about this.

“I just came out from the laboratory. How is the situation with the war?” Leylin asked after some small talk.

“It’s still the same. The tripartite defense is barely holding off the matriarchs. All our manpower is being whittled away.” Fendix’s expression showed his excitement.

“Quite a few darkness creatures have been eliminated. The regions we’ve given up already are enough for them to proliferate, so they’ve begun to show signs of retreat. All sorts of voices are already sounding among the inner circles of the dark elves. Although the matriarchs are currently suppressing them, they, too, have to worry about the repercussions of such an act…”

Leylin nodded. He knew that there were dissenting voices among the dark elves, and then there were Baelin’s actions as well.

“I reckon that if there aren’t any large changes, this war will end within five years!” Fendix seemed to heave a sigh of relief.

This conclusion was about the same as what Leylin had come up with, and he nodded as well.

*Bang!*

The door to the parlor was suddenly pushed open, and a female rank 2 Magus entered, looking grim.

“Something’s happened in the north!”

……

A while earlier…

Potti City was the center of the north’s defense. The human armies, backed by numerous Magi, confronted the coalition of darkness creatures and dark elves at that location.

A young Magus passed through a long paved pathway and arrived before a golden door.

“Magus Longbottom, is anything wrong?” the two Magi at the golden door asked.

“I have something pressing to report. Please let me see Lord Yade!” Longbottom looked to be in a hurry.

“Something pressing to report? Fine! We’ll pass on the message!” The two Magi exchanged a glance, and one of them immediately ran inside.

A moment later, the Magus returned and nodded, “Lord Yade is willing to see you!”

Longbottom immediately entered through the door.

Behind the golden door was a large room, with a milky-white radiance around it.

A Magus that looked very youthful wore a loose and comfortable robe and was sitting behind a large writing table.

“Longbottom greets the great protector of the North!” Longbottom respectfully greeted while half-kneeling.

“It’s little Longbottom! What’s wrong?” An aged voice was produced from the young man’s mouth.

“I found a small group of dark elves while on patrol. I discovered this after the fight!” Longbottom respectfully held a black scroll above his head.

A streak of blue light flashed, and it scanned the scroll up and down.

“No abnormal energy reactions! Level of danger: 0!” A gentle female voice sounded, and Longbottom trembled. He knew this was the voice of a spirit genie.

“Let me see!” With a wave of the young man’s arm, the scroll in Longbottom’s arms flew to the table and was unfurled.

Something that looked like a map appeared in front of the young man’s eyes, with all sorts of red markings appearing all over it.

“Oh? This is?”

Magus Yade began to look grim, his body automatically leaning forward.

Suddenly, the situation changed!

A translucent black seed appeared from the map and turned into a ray of light, entering Yade’s forehead.

“A parasitic seed! You-!” Yade was enraged.

Right after that, large amounts of black tendrils and vines wrapped up his body, sealing him within.

“Warning! Warning! Intruder!”

The spirit genie’s voice became frigid.

Powerful magical rays formed from a powerful spell illuminated the room.

“I’ve been waiting for this!” A fiendish smile appeared on Longbottom’s face, and he waved.

A black ray travelled by Magus Yade and destroyed the oil painting behind him, revealing a complicated spell formation.

Chapter 355: Revolution

“The core of the spirit genie!” Longbottom sighed slightly, unhesitatingly releasing a shockwave to destroy the spell formation.

*Tss tss…* Instantly, the spirit genie’s voice faded, and Potti City immediately grew chaotic.

*Rumble!*

As if long since prepared, the opposing dark elves and beast wave unleashed their most ferocious barrage of attacks.

While the Magi were engrossed in battle, the defensive spell formation that had lost its spirit genie sputtered out.

“What are you doing?” Two Magi immediately rushed out.

“Life Absorption!” Longbottom’s expression remained unchanged as he waved his hands. A few green beams flashed on the two, and they began to age visibly. Their life force was rapidly depleting.

“Begin localization!” Longbottom took a glance at Yade, who was still sealed, and produced some materials and began setting something up.

*Rumble!*

Minutes later, with the guidance of a spell formation that glowed purple, eight large spider legs pierced through, tearing the ceiling apart. On top of the giant spider that entered was a completely naked girl.

This girl had a slight smile on her face, her skin pale and ears pointy. She radiated a captivating charm.

“Greetings, matriarch!” Longbottom immediately bowed.

“Well done, Longbottom!” The young girl giggled, causing Longbottom’s heart to leap.

“Though you’ve wasted a portion of a precious Earthen Fetal Membrane, it’s still not a bad result to be able to deal with a clone of your opponent. After all, that person’s a peak rank 2 existence!”

The young girl spoke slowly. Just her voice was enough for his heart to be inflamed with desire.

Rank 2 Magi were powerhouses in their own right. If one was prepared, even the dark elves’ matriarchs would find them difficult to deal with. Additionally, there were bloodline detection spell formations scattered throughout Potti City. Any dark creature that entered would immediately be discovered.

But Longbottom was different! He was a pure human, and what more a Magus. Though he was a wandering Magus, he had some achievements and was well received.

Earthen Fetal Membrane was a top-class treasure of the Dark Elven Empire used to conceal one’s aura.

Only when all sorts of conditions were favorable to him could he make use of the parasitic seed.

This had made Longbottom very proud of himself, but her words had surprised him greatly.

“Clone?”

“Yes! Aren’t you going to come out?” The girl giggled while speaking at the air beside her.

*Xiu Xiu!* Two pure white arrows of light shattered the tendrils, revealing a hazy human figure.

This figure transformed into a long line and shot out, entering another figure that had just appeared.

“This is the real body of Protector Yade!” Longbottom stared at the figure overhead that looked exactly the same as the one before, his fists tightly clenched.

“I didn’t expect Her Majesty, the Empress to come personally !”

Yade, who was floating in mid-air, paid no attention to Longbottom who was on the ground. His eyes were riveted on the young girl before him, gaze tinged with fear.

“Hehe… With your clone heavily injured, how much of your strength can you really use? 70%? Or 80%?”

The girl could not stop laughing, while her back tore open.

……

A monster that was a cross between a human and a spider appeared in the air, and a massive darkness drowned out Protector Yade…

Not far away in the horizon, Magi were stunned to find that, besides the dark elves and the horde of darkness creatures, dwarves and gnomes had joined the battle.

Half a day later, an earth-shattering piece of news spread throughout Twilight Zone.

Potti City had fallen! The Empress of the Dark Elven Empire had personally acted and killed Protector Yade of the northern region!

The dwarven tribes and gnome kingdom had also entered the battle, and the entire northern Twilight region fell into enemy hands, entering a reign of terror.

Still in Potti City.

The master of this region had changed. Squads of elite Underground Winter Spider knights patrolled the streets, and one could occasionally see dwarven warriors and gnome puppeteers passing through.

In the great palace hall at the heart of the city.

The Empress summoned Longbottom in.

“You did very well this time, Longbottom!” The girl spoke from the bottom of her heart. If not for him plotting against their opponent’s clone, she could not have killed him as easily.

“It is my honour to be able to serve the Empress.” Longbottom gazed at the girl’s absolutely beautiful face, seeming enchanted.

“Now, I need you to travel to the central region and drum up hate against Magi.” The girl did not seem disgusted by his gaze, instead of wriggling her body to expose more of her skin to the Magus before her.

“Hate against Magi?” Longbottom could not understand the reasoning behind this.

“Yes. Magi and the nobility all hold large amounts of knowledge and power in their grasp, restricting peasants and regular humans from obtaining them. Animosity, abhorrence, and anguish have been building up through the generations. What we need now is a tipping point, an opportunity for it all to explode into a huge uproar!”

The girl continued quietly, “I need you to go to the central region and cause unrest in the name of a revolution. When the time comes, you can even spread high-grade meditation techniques.”

“…Yes…” Longbottom answered after a pause. He would cause a rebellion at his enemy’s side, and then flank the enemy from both sides.

He knew that under the governance of Magi, commoners had been living miserably. The Magi and nobles enjoyed everything, while the rest had to suffer from day to night. Even then, they might not even get a good meal out of it. Crimes could be pinned on them for offending nobility, or in the worst case scenario, they would be killed without recourse!

It was difficult for commoners to be allowed to grow even if they had the aptitude

Even if they were lucky enough to enter a guild, they would still be discriminated against and even treated as guinea pigs or cannon fodder.

Of course, if one only had resentment and no strength, they would only be mercilessly massacred by Magi. After all, power was still in the hands of Magi.

But it was different now. Magi now were confronting a great enemy, and their mental and physical efforts were mostly spent.

In addition, there were calls for a rebellion.

Sometimes, resounding catchphrase and beautiful promises for the future could attract many hot-blooded teenagers to turn their heads.

If they were given some power, it would be a disaster.

When that happened, there might be internal strife amongst Magi. How many people would die? How much blood would be spilled?

Longbottom knew this very well, but he had no thoughts of opposing this, nor any pity. All he had in him was the thrill of taking revenge.

“Leylin, I’ll make you suffer tens and hundreds of time for what you did to me. I promise!”

Longbottom howled in his heart.

If Leylin was here, he would find that this traitor called Longbottom was the little boy, Longbottom, he had played around with in Potter Town.

“En! Very good. When you’re back, I’ll carry out the bloodline changing ceremony. From then on, you’ll be part of us dark elves, even in blood.”

The girl nodded.

“Many thanks, Empress!” Longbottom touched his head to the ground.

……

“Longbottom?” Hearing the rank 2 female Magus’ words, Leylin suddenly had the urge to cry and laugh as well.

“Though the name might just be a coincidence, I have a feeling that this traitor to our race, Longbottom, is the same person as the one in Potter Town!”

Leylin sighed ruefully. When he had found out that this boy had left to seek better opportunities, he had not taken it seriously. The chances of success were much too low.

Unexpectedly, he had actually succeeded and even become a rank 1 Magus!

Without proper tools, Leylin could not tell a Magus’ aptitude. Hence, he did not know that Longbottom had the talent to become a Magus.

“But this is interesting. Looks like Potter Town is a place where Twilight Zone’s destiny converges.” Leylin touched his chin, deep in thought.

Potter Town had seemed like a regular little common town and had probably already fallen into enemy hands.

However, it was surprising that it had given birth to both Baelin and Longbottom, the two darlings of destiny.

“Baelin and Longbottom are like the two sides of a coin. One day, they will meet again, and that day will be when Twilight Zone’s power of destiny is most concentrated!”

Leylin suddenly had a strange premonition.

“It’s quite interesting being able to shape history…” Strictly speaking, he had personally created this entire situation. It was in Potter Town where everything began. It made him feel like the destiny of Twilight Zone was in his hands.

But this only left Leylin sneering.

“In that case, let me be the one to end this all!”

These thoughts merely flashed in his mind, while the other two rank 2 Magi’s expressions were filled with worry.

“Now that the entire northern region is gone, we have lost a fifth of our power.”

Fendix caressed a ring on his hand that had a ruby the size of a pebble, a dark cloud seemingly hanging over him.

“Not only that. Besides the dark elves and horde of darkness creatures, even the dwarves and gnomes have appeared!”

The female Magus smiled wryly.

Twilight Zone was a small area, and the subterranean world had all sorts of incredible races. The humans and dark elves were the two largest powers, but one could not underestimate the gnomes and dwarves either.

When they joined forces, the humans were definitely in a disadvantageous position.

“This war could result in genocide!” Fendix drew in a deep breath, “We need to get the war council and mobilise everything we have…”

“Before that, we need to first deal with the threats outside.”

A golden ring on Leylin’s finger lit up, and he immediately straightened his back, “The dark elves are on the offensive once again, and it can be confirmed that they have three regiments of elite Underground Winter Spider Knights, backed by three matriarchs.”

“Those wretched pointy-eared bastards…” Fendix got up, furious.

Chapter 356: Red Mist

Emergency sirens were blaring throughout Dolon City.

Leylin, Fendix, and the others floated across to the front of the city, watching the scene outside.

Ten years where life and resources were constantly lost had visibly reduced the numbers of the horde of darkness creatures. The newest reports suggested that the beast emperors had already made plans to withdraw their troops and end the war.

If not for the fall of the north and interference of the dwarves and gnomes, the war was on track to end in a few years. The current situation was different, however. The humans of the subterranean world were now facing the possibility of extinction.

“Underground Winter Spider knights! And they’re elites!”

Leylin looked up. Three regiments of Underground Winter Spider knights

Huge spider legs trod the ground silently, their dark elf riders wreathed in exquisite thin armor that looked ornamental. The surface of the armors was composed of intricate patterns. Matched with the handsome faces and lances, they seemed like a royal parade to Leylin.

Although these knights seemed extravagant and pretentious, the searing bloodlust they emanated was tangible. This was something only battle-hardened elites with fearless hearts could have.

“These are the dark elven royal family’s knights. I didn’t expect them to be sent out!” Fendix looked grim.

“Elite Underground Winter Spider knights are slightly more powerful than our Grand Knights. Those at the level of vice-captain and above are even as powerful as official Magi. Three formations of a thousand each, there are three thousand here!” The female Magus inhaled sharply.

“They’re planning to conquer Dolon City in one go!!”

Leylin sighed lightly, “Do we need to act?”

“There’s no other way!” Fendix smiled wryly, “But their matriarchs are sure to obstruct as well, and we have no guarantee that we can win against them. I can already feel the power of the abyss emanating from their bodies…”

Cities were usually watched over by rank 2 Magi. The opposing camp had three matriarchs whose mission was to tie down the rank 2 Magi of the defending city. If they could not, the three rank 2 Magi would cooperate to cast a few large-scaled magic spells which would decimate these troops.

“There’s no choice. Let’s use ‘it’.” Leylin suddenly exclaimed.

“Hm?” Fendix chanced a glance at Leylin. “That’s our trump card that we’re planning to use in the final battle…”

“This is already the final battle!” the female rank 2 Magus interrupted before Leylin could answer, “I agree!”

“Alright, I’ll agree too!” Fendix glanced at the large dark elven army and laughed wryly, “This truly might be the final battle.”

With the three Magi cooperating, a unique order was sent down using secret imprints, and under the lead of the Magi, the troops on the ground shifted some special items onto the city walls.

They were numerous giant casks. They were like the wooden barrels found in bars to store beer, with firm iron hoops on either side keeping them steady. There were also letters of the Twilight Zone written on them in blood red, indicating danger.

“Now, let us wait and see!”

The three Magi exchanged glances, and then fixed their attention on the fighting.

“Attack!” With the signal from the dark elves at the other side, a large wave of darkness creatures charged towards them.

“Engage the third layer of defense!”

Fluorescent light exploded at the walls, revealing unending defensive runes. Large amounts of energy particles brought with them a terrifying destructive power, launching outwards.

The darkness creatures charging over were injured by energy particles of multiple elements, covering their bodies with wounds. It resulted in a rain of flesh and blood.

A few of the more powerful ones dodged the attack. They climbed up on the carcasses of their comrades and clashed with the soldiers and Magi on the walls.

In a moment, blood and fire exploded!

The Magi and knights on the walls bellowed, and all sorts of spells and energy fluctuations were released. Numerous darkness creatures fell from the walls.

This scene had repeated often in the past, and each time the dark elves would end up retreating, which ended the fight. Now, however, things seemed to have changed. The horde continued to charge with reddened eyes, unfearing of death.

*Tak tak tak!* Regular explosions sounded. The elite Underground Winter Spider knights seemed to have received an order, as they began to advance..

Although they were merely 3000 strong, they were like a surge of steel flooding over when they acted together.

“Go!” Underground Winter Spiders with barbs on their legs easily climbed up the city wall like monkeys.

For darkness creatures, the city wall was lofty and difficult to reach, but for these Underground Winter Spider Knights, they were like a level road.

“Attack!” One of them rushed towards the wall, brandishing the black lance in his hand.

Multiple snowy-white pointed javelins were sent thrusting like blooming flowers, and a few soldiers in leather armour collapsed, blood splattering everywhere. Amongst them, there was even a knight in heavy armour!

In front of the elite Underground Winter Spider Knights, regular soldiers and knights could not take on even a single blow, and only Grand Knights had a chance to win.

“Secondary Energy Fireball!”

“Vine Winding!”

“Icy Pearl!” The magicians waiting on top of the city walls immediately acted,and the knights who had just rushed up the walls were drowned in the colourful rays of magic spells.

Their powerful bodies and mounts that they had always been proud of were torn into pieces by various spells.

However, the surviving Underground Winter Spider Knights still charged on fearlessly, and many captains and vice-captains launched forth with spells of their own, clashing with the Magi on the walls.

“Hands of Corrosion!” A knight in gleaming armour, riding a larger spider than its peers, called out loudly. Numerous black palms extended from the air and advanced towards the opposing Magi.

“Ah!” A level 3 acolyte’s face was caught by one of the black hands and immediately wasted away, blood and flesh wearing away.

“Be careful! He’s a vice-captain and has the strength of an official Magus!”

A middle-aged Magus with white air spoke in a low voice, his innate defensive spell formation flickering.

“The situation doesn’t look good,” Leylin commented, watching the scene below.

At this moment, the three Magi felt a few bursts of spiritual force aimed at them that equalled their own strengths being released from the enemy camp. If they dared intervene, they would be faced with a terrifying attack by the matriarchs.

In a situation where the higher-ranked forces were level, whoever first made the first move would be at a disadvantage.

Thankfully, Leylin and the others were not planning on doing so.

From the looks of it, though, only rank 2 Magi could change the outcome.

“Let’s begin!” Leylin spoke lightly, the apathy in his eyes becoming more evident.

“The command has been sent down. I only hope the matriarchs won’t go crazy and fight with us!” The ring on Fendix’s finger flashed red as he smiled wryly.

At this moment, it looked like the official Magi on the city walls had received the command.

“Begin! Activate!” They shouted, and all sorts of spells were aimed at the casks, causing them to explode into fragments.

*Rumble!*

The wooden boards exploded open, and the red liquid within spilled to the ground.

This red liquid was very muddy and looked to be some red wine that had yet to settle. After reaching the ground, it became volatile and created a red mist.

In that moment, the top of the city wall was wrapped in red mist.

“Be careful of the toxic attack! Activate your defensive runes!”

A dark elf in golden armour ordered.

*Weng Weng!* In the twinkling of an eye, multi-coloured rays rose from the dark elven knights’ armours.

After being wrapped within this layer of light, the knights charged towards their enemies once again, undaunted.

They were very confident in the durability of their bodies, since they were members of a high-energy race. Dark elves might have lower reproductive abilities, but the durability of their bodies far surpassed that of humans. This racial ability extended to the immunity to many toxins.

It wasn’t as if the humans hadn’t considered using poison, but most poisons that were deadly to humans only left dark elves feeling slightly giddy, or gave them a nosebleed.

Using poison would only hurt them more, and lead to more city guards dying. Thus, after a few attempts, the humans had given up on this method.

Now, however, the situation was slightly different.

“Hm?”

An Underground Winter Spider knight rushed up the city wall and sent a Grand Knight flying. Just as he was about to stab his lance into his opponent’s heart, he suddenly lost his grip, and the lance fell to the ground.

Recalling the short burst of weakness, the knight wondered, ‘What’s going on? How did these toxins paralyse me? Didn’t I already activate the runes that defend against this?’

The sudden realisation that the red mist had passed through the defensive layer without obstruction alarmed him. It was as if these runes were fake.

Large numbers of yellow pustules and blisters erupted all over his skin, bursting as quickly as they had formed. The knight screamed out, miserably.

“Attack!” A ray of light flashed, and the Grand Knight that had been sent flying grasped this opportunity and brandished the giant steel sword in his hands, slashing it at this dark elf’s neck.

A line appeared, which soon turned into a fountain of blood.

This dark elf’s delicate, pale neck was severed, its skull rolling on the ground.

Chapter 357: Alicia

Similar events occurred all along the city walls. Even the Underground Winter Spiders weren’t spared. Their eight legs crumbled down and their eyes dimmed, following which they were overrun by stampeding troops…

This frightening effectiveness in battle managed to surprise even Fendix who was hovering in the air. “This toxin is truly very strong! If we manage to produce it in large quantities…”

His eyes beamed with excitement.

“It isn’t as simple as you’d think!” Leylin smiled bitterly, “I specifically concocted this using plant concentrate based on the anatomy of dark elves. On its own, it isn’t a toxin, which is why it can pass through their defensive runes. Once it enters their bodies and begins circulation, it begins to react with their endocrine system. In a matter of moments, the benign gas transforms into neural poison.

“This is just a petty trick that makes use of a gap in their defenses. Once this battle ends, the dark elves will change their runes to protect against this method of attack, which will render it useless in the end!”

In fact, Leylin based this poison off his own rank 2 spell—Toxic Bile. With the help of Nature’s Alliance’s research, he managed to get the approval of the joint conference, which only helped him improve upon it.

“Even so, Sir Leylin’s research on dark elves has far surpassed ours.” The female Magus showed admiration at Leylin’s accomplishment despite him downplaying it. That alone showed the level of Leylin’s ability in alchemy and the depth of his research on dark elves.

“After this, I’m afraid that even I will have to pay a visit to the joint conference to learn from Sir Leylin’s works,” she said as she broke into a smile.

“I would gladly welcome any discussion with you, what’s more, any fresh thoughts you may have on the subject,” Leylin said humbly.

“This isn’t the right time to speak about this, the matriarchs are about to act!” She pointed at the dark elves’ camp across them where the spiritual force was climbing to its peak.

“They seem to have become anxious now, and might leap into action at any moment. We should prepare.” Fendix took out a short black gentleman’s cane. A sparkling diamond, as large as an egg, was embedded into the top.

Leylin smiled without saying a word.

Nearly three thousand of their elite Underground Winter Spider knights were fighting in this battle, half of their entire force. It was only to be expected that the turn of the situation had made them anxious.

At this moment, darkness energy particles gathered together, and a strong wave from a spell arose from the opposite side.

“Black Torrential Rain!!”

A sweet female voice was accompanied by a large amount of water vapour condensing above Dolon city. This was followed by a storm of endless black raindrops descending upon the city.

When the black raindrops and red mist came into contact, an explosion sounded out. They fused into a charred-black liquid that dropped to the floor, revealing the Underground Winter Spider knights who were lying on the ground, on the verge of death.

Leylin’s poison was only powerful against the elite Underground Winter Spider Knights. A rank 1 Magus could use the energy in their body to resist it. As for matriarchs who were rank 2 existences? It could not affect them in the slightest.

”Peng! Peng! Peng! Peng!”

The ground cracked apart, and numerous strands of black hair emerged from the depths. These snake-like hairs wound around those knights who were still alive and pulled them back.

In just a moment, the hairs had managed to pull back a dozen miles, bringing the knights to safety.

Still, half of the Underground Winter Spider knights had already perished.

“You…!!!” A few rage-filled voices emerged from the sky above the enemy camp. The black vapors dissipated, revealing the appearances of the three dark elf matriarchs.

Leylin examined them.

These matriarchs all possessed the ravishing beauty intrinsic to dark elves. The revealing clothing made of a leather-like material displayed their voluptuous bodies and their hands were adorned with thorn whips.

‘Yup! They definitely resemble the dominatrixes from my previous world!’ Leylin thought as he rolled his eyes.

At this moment, the opposing three matriarchs were already on the verge of exploding into anger, powerful spells taking form in their hands.

“You guys dared to go against the agreement and take action!” Fendix touched the short cane which he was holding and remained stoic.

“Humans! How dare you use such despicable means to bring harm upon my brave soldiers, I will behead the lot of you and gift them to Her Majesty!” The matriarch at the center lashed out in the dark elven language, paying no heed to Fendix’s accusation. She wore the most revealing outfit of the three, and the two golden rings at her bosom gave off a sensual vibe.

“Hehe! Since when did the dark elves that are renowned for being sinister and cunning start accusing others of using despicable means?” The female Magus said with a sneer before Leylin had a chance to speak.

”Speaking anymore is useless! Take action!!” Leylin exclaimed.

Large amounts of black mist appeared, forming a gigantic black snake whose back was filled with patterns. It sucked one of the matriarchs into it.

Leylin had grown bored of remaining in this place in spite of the minimal danger and occasional respites. He wanted to end this once and for all so he could head back and further his plans.

“Begin the counterattack!” Fendix sent out via secret imprint as he sneered.

“Retaliate! Retaliate! Retaliate!”

A sea of voices flooded out from within the city walls. The door which had been closed for a long time started to creak open. Numerous knights and magicians rushed out, heading for the dark elves’ camp.

After the previous battle and Leylin’s poison, the dark elves had suffered a devastating blow that had forced a retreat. It looked like the humans had taken hold of the advantage now.

Leylin did not pay much attention to the situation below. After some probing attacks, he had begun to lure one of the matriarchs to a suitable battlefield.

A dark elf matriarch had strength comparable to a rank 2 Magus, and Leylin could not afford to let his guard down against such a strong opponent. In addition, both the extent and range of destruction brought down by a rank 2 spell far surpassed that of one at rank 1. Thus, his opponent willingly followed him so that they could avoid unnecessary casualties.

After all, the two armies were in a melee, and any attack would definitely harm both parties. Considering their already low population, the loss would hurt the dark elves more than it hurt the humans.

In actual fact, looking at the two sides engaged in battle, the matriarch was pain-stricken by the loss.

Dark elves took 300 years just to reach adulthood. This made it much more difficult to recoup the loss of their soldiers, and every single member of their army was irreplaceable. On the other hand, humans with their high fertility and short life cycles had no such problems.

One-third of the elves on this battlefield belonged to this matriarch’s army, and among them were her own descendants.

“Here should be fine!”

Leylin brought the matriarch to a plain which was not far from Dolon City

There were a few cities near this plane, but they had all been evacuated long ago. The roads leading to the plain were already covered with weeds, and unnecessary casualties were unlikely to occur here.

“I am known as Alicia, you are worthy of knowing my name!”

This matriarch had completely calmed down, as she had to face an existence whose power rivaled her own.

Looking at this elf who was dressed in revealing leather, Leyin flashed a smile. ”I am Leylin!“

*Kacha!*

As he said that, he suddenly shot backwards, dodging a shadow spider.

This floating shadow spider had ominous green eyes, and the mouth which had just tried to bite Leylin was now producing a crunching noise.

“Do all you matriarchs act this shamelessly?” Leylin had been stumped by her actions.

“There is no use for face when up against someone of a different race! Surrender and defect to our side; I’ll gift you with my family’s bloodline and bestow unimaginable rewards upon you!”

The matriarch licked her sexy lips and flaunted her voluptuous body, hinting at him subtly.

”Hehe… this kind of seductive energy once again!” Leylin shook his head.

A large amount of spiritual force chased the energy out.

“Scorching Touch!” He scattered a red powder just as he was chanting the spell, and red rays started ripping across the sky and immediately appeared in front of Alicia. The might of the two forces from the ray made her pale.

”Aldershkry!” Alicia started to chant and a white shield started to hover in front of her. On the surface of the shield was the image of a spider web and flowers.

*Peng! Peng!*

The scorching rays attacked the shield one by one, and screeching sounded out.

Cracks started to emerge on the surface of the shield

*Kacha!* Under Alicia’s stunned gaze, the white shield shattered to pieces and fragments flew in all directions.

“This shield was smelted from the ore of the mine guarded by the Underground Winter Spider Emperor! You shattered it!” Alicia’s gaze at Leylin was now filled with dread.

“Could you consider my proposal? You can have all the females in my clan, including me…”

“Sorry! I can’t see any sincerity in your words!” Silver spiritual force continuously shot out with Leylin’s detached reply.

He was not a lecher, and the price of betrayal was far too steep when compared to the profits he would obtain.

Chapter 358: Defeat and Assistance

Anyone who betrayed their community for profit would immediately be labelled as unreliable. How, then, would they do well in the opposing camp?

Furthermore, Leylin was confident in the humans’ ability to defend. Even if the protector of the eastern Twilight Zone were to perish, and the entirety of it fell into enemy hands, he still believed the humans in the subterranean world were not weak enough to go extinct.

As a result, matriarch Alicia’s temptations did not affect Leylin in the slightest.

On the contrary, Leylin was eager to fight this rank 2 matriarch.

“Perfect. The template of a rank 2 Magus, as well as the rank 2 spell models the A.I. Chip deduced, can now be tested.”

Leylin’s eyes flashed, which caused Alicia who was opposite him to feel cold within her heart. She had a bad premonition.

But Leylin would not give the other party a chance, and he swiftly made the first move. ”Shadow Flames!” Dark red flames poured into the sky, forming a pillar of raging fire.

[Shadow Flames: rank 2 spell. Elements: darkness, fire. Might: 120 degrees (Elemental essence conversion added)]

These were the A.I. Chip’s stats on the spell which had been evolved from the Latent Fireball that he had previously made.

Over the last ten years, Leylin had obtained the spell model of a powerful rank 2 spell from Nature’s Alliance. The guilds that they had consumed had also net him quite a few such models as well. Of course the Alliance, as a medium-scale guild, had possessed the most outstanding model.

Thereafter, during his stay in Dolon, he had exchanged for many more rank 2 models. By luck, he had even managed to collect two damaged rank 3 models, which he had treated like gems and diligently copied down. The A.I. Chip had been tasked with restoring these two models.

The power of these dark red flames had clearly surpassed that of Scorching Touch from before.

Matriarch Alicia had a solemn face. Suddenly, she took out her whip and cracked it in the air.

*Pa!* The cracking of the whip had compressed the air, producing a sonic boom.

“Come out!” Complex black patterns emerged on Alicia’s face, covering the right side of it like a mask.

“As you wish, My Lady!” Space seemingly split apart, and a cute spider as white as jade materialised out of thin air. The blood red lines across its carapace only served to make it look cuter.

*Hiss* The matriarch let out a hiss, similar to the sound of a spider stridulating.

That white jade spider immediately targeted Leylin, its back shooting out large amounts of thread that emitted cold air.

The densely packed threads tangled together, forming a white cocoon that surrounded the elf and beast.

The A.I chip made his vision flash blue, and the details of the white jade spider surfaced immediately.

[Underground Frost Spider, a mutation of the Underground Winter Spider. Has an extremely strong ability to mutate!

Strength: 35; Agility: 16; Vitality: 46.9; Spiritual force : 27; Special abilities: 1; Thread defense: the Underground Frost Spider’s threads have the ability of ice, and is the bane of many rank 2 fire-type magi; Stealth: the Underground Frost Spider’s shell has abilities to reflect light, allowing it to be concealed with the surroundings.]

Leylin had never slacked off on feeding the A.I. Chip’s database with information after entering Twilight Zone. By now, a large portion of Twilight Zone’s special items were already recorded within it.

“A matriarch with an Underground Frost Spider as a familiar? One that can suppress fire elemental Magi?”

Leylin’s smiled lightly. “What a pity, my Shadow Flames are mainly composed not of fire, but of darkness!”

Along with the change in Leylin’s intent, the dark red pillar of fire immediately transformed. The red glow at its center quickly faded, being replaced instead by a dark black which took over most of the space. In a moment, the shadow forces occupied most of the pillar.

”Ingest!” Leylin grabbed at the air with both hands, and the large pillar swept Alicia’s giant white cocoon into itself.

*Sssii!* Large amounts of white gases appeared on the surface of the white cocoon, moving about in the air.

*Hiss* Leylin even heard the bloodcurdling sounds of the giant spider.

*Boom!* The large white cocoon suddenly exploded, smashing into the reddish-black flames.

From within the white fog, a silhouette surfaced.

The matriarch had connected her body directly on top of the Underground Frost Spider, forming a monster that was half-human and half spider. It reminded him of his subordinate, Skrill.

‘This look is very compatible with Skrill!’

Leylin laughed mockingly, but he knew that these two parties were vastly different. Skrill had used his meditation technique to alter his physical appearance, but this matriarch had fused her body with that of her pet, maybe even her soul!

Based on strength alone, Skrill could not compare to this elf who was already rank 2 and possessed many techniques that he did not.

”Disgusting, disgusting humans!” the elf that formed the upper half of this abomination hooted on the spider’s back.

*Ding! Ding!*

The elf held a spider leg that looked like white jade. The long spider leg instantly transformed into a white scimitar. Along the elegant curve of this scimitar were pretty patterns that glowed repeatedly. The blade emitted some white fog, which emanated cold rays.

”Kill!” The voice of the elf transformed into a wave of bright rays that enveloped her, which gradually disappeared into the air.

“Is she concealing herself now?” Leylin stroked his chin and smiled wryly.

Although dark elves were quite capable in open combat, they preferred more underhanded tactics. They would make use of their own bodies and beauty to tempt their opponents, or hide away in corners, to launch sneak attacks.

However, as a dark Magus, Leylin had come across many of these tactics, and employed them himself. He tilted his head and smiled, rooting himself to the spot and narrowing his eyes.

A few minutes later, a ray of cold white air quickly slashed across Leylin’s body, but was met with the exterior of his body rippling. The body had been a mere phantom.

“You’ve fallen into my trap!” Leylin materialised in a corner, his body ringed by defensive darkness elemental particles.

“You are the one who fell into a trap!” Alicia laughed softly, as another body shot out explosively from the side, targeting him with his own tactic.

*Boom!* A large white web filled with mucus flew out and trapped Leylin. White sap fell onto him, and the sounds of corrosion rang out as it continuously seeped into his body.

“So that previous attack was fake!”

Leylin smiled gently, but his expression did not show any dejection, as if the person trapped was not him.

With a flash of white light, Alicia appeared in front of Leylin. Currently, she looked apathetic. She held a white scimitar and was about to directly chop off Leylin’s head.

However, Leylin’s demeanor made her feel uneasy.

*Boom!* As Leylin’s head flew upwards, a strange transformation occurred in mid-air.

The head dissipated into a large number of black shadows, condensing many darkness elemental particles to form a cage that bound the matriarch.

“Rank 2 spell, Illusory Body: Second Stage!”

The surrounding space flashed as Leylin removed the darkness elemental waves concealing his body, appearing in front of Alicia.

Closer inspection revealed the sensuality of this matriarch’s body; the temptation it induced was shocking.

However, Leylin’s expression was as cold as ice. A black spear ringed with red flames instantly appeared in his hand.

“Rank 2 spell: Lance of corrosion!”

“Go die!” Leylin said beneath his breath, the black spear in his hand being launched forward.

The space warped where the spear passed, and a strong corrosive force continuously condensed onto its tip.

“Explode!!!” Upon seeing the terrible force the spear contained, as if able to destroy the very earth, Alicia’s face changed instantly. She resolutely chanted a few spells under her breath.

Suddenly, the Underground Frost Spider screeched irritably, the blood lines on its body enlarging and dying almost its entire body red. Moreover, weirdly, its body swelled up.

A ray of white light swiftly separated Alicia and the white spider.

*Boom!*

The spear exploded intensely at Alicia’s original location.

The black chains instantly exploded, which caused the exploded flesh and blood to strike the black spear.

Two large energy forces melded and grew denser, causing large distortions to the void.

*Bam! Bam! Bam!*

When the distortions had condensed to a point, it ended off with a violent explosion.

Even though the forces collided in mid-air, the remains of the energy waves they generated headed towards the ground, blasting off layers of stone and soil. The waves swept the area, causing large-scale destruction.

Alicia’s silhouette flew out of the explosion. However, things did not seem to look good for her, her lower body dripping with fresh blood. Being caught right in the middle of the explosion, she’d naturally received the brunt of the force it generated.

However, she currently did not have time to care about her injuries. Looking over herself restrainedly, she turned into a ray of blood that disappeared into the horizon.

Leylin stood where he was silently, and did not give chase.

To him, helping the humans retain their lands was just a passing favour. He did not want to kill a rank 2 existence of the opposing party, as he did not desire an animosity that could not be resolved.

Of course, some preparations had to be made to expedite the end of the war.

Leylin smiled wryly. Having roughly figured out his next course of action, he rushed towards the other two groups.

Fendix’s opponent was the matriarch who wore the two rings on her bosom. This opponent’s strength was tyrannical, and she had suppressed Fendix and limited his movements. Fendix ended up constantly on the defensive, which embittered him.

Chapter 359: Death and Insanity

“Hm?” At this moment, Fendix and the dark elven matriarch looked toward the side.

“Fendix, I’m here to help!” Leylin closed in rapidly, his clothes rustling in the strong wind.

“Umbra’s Hand!”

Large numbers of shadows emerged from behind him, and transformed into what looked like a giant hand which obstructed the matriarch.

“What’s your situation? How much magic power do you have left?” Leylin glanced at Fendix, who was already slightly pale.

“Half, and I can release one more formidable spell. How about you?” Upon seeing Leylin’s arrival, Fendix heaved a huge sigh of relief.

“I’ve already sent that matriarch away. All that’s left is her,” Leylin pointed at the matriarch across them, “I remember you still have a powerful offensive spell—Violent Thunder Chains, right? I’ll keep her occupied. Quick, go and prepare it!”

“Alright!” Fendix gritted his teeth.

Though he had seen through Leylin’s intentions, this matriarch was his arch-enemy! In the past, Duke Fendix, the army’s commander and a member of his family, had been killed by this person’s army. He could not wait to end her!

Besides, they were at war. Killing a matriarch would reward him with an enormous number of merit points!

Leylin watched the matriarch, a slight smile creeping onto his face…

Minutes later, Fendix roared. A dazzling blue light filled the region, and snakes of electricity began dancing in the air, trapping the opponent within.

Innumerable streaks of lightning fell, and a few minutes later all that was left of the matriarch was ash and charcoal falling from the air.

“The dark elves are withdrawing!” Just as Leylin and Fendix had taken care of the situation here, the other rank 2 Magus hurried to them, “The matriarch who was fighting me seemed to have received some news, and suddenly escaped. I couldn’t catch up to her at all… Ah! You! You killed her…”

The female Magus clapped her hand on her mouth, unable to express her astonishment with words.

……

The dark elves that surrounded Dolon City retreated quickly. The three thousand Underground Winter Spider knights that had attacked were a very large power in the eastern region. Many of them had temporarily been transferred over from the other two armies.

Now, with Leylin’s poison facilitating a counterattack, a good number of them had been lost. The siege of Dolon had ended, and their victory even led to a chain effect.

What’s more, the death of a rank 2 matriarch had caused Dolon City to become the heart of the battle.

However, Fendix and Leylin did not choose to rest. Instead, riding on this momentum, they led troops in to save the other two large cities.

After their formidable forces had been weakened considerably, the dark elves were pushed back step by step, and were finally chased out of the east. This gave the human race a ray of hope.

As for the merit points from killing the matriarch? Since Leylin was intentionally keeping a low-profile, all of them ended up in Fendix’s hands.

He cared little for reputation, and this seemed to be very important to Fendix, as if there was a grudge involved. Hence, he was happy to do him a favour. After all, Fendix had helped him quite a bit previously, and had also promised to make it up to him in the future.

……

“We won in the east? That’s great!” Aaron, who was currently in another city, heard the news.

Shockingly, he was dressed in a gray, tattered cloak, and soot covered his entire face. The ring in his hand concealed his energy fluctuations.

The whole city was now caught up in a wave of joy.

Whether it was nobles, commoners or knights, they darted to the streets the moment they received the news, exhibiting their ecstasy with no inhibitions.

The threat of the dark elves had loomed over this area for far too long. Hopes had plummeted further when the north was broken through, and the news of whole cities being slaughtered had terrified everyone. The people needed some good news to raise their spirits.

The city master’s residence had been opened to the public, and he’d even ordered chefs to serve great amounts of oatmeal bread and fruit juice to the public.

“This may be good news, but it’s much too distant from you right now.” A white ray of light shot out from the black ring, projecting the image of a wise old man in Aaron’s mind. “Leave the moment you get it! The Mambo Family that governs this city is not something you can take on easily!”

“I know!” Aaron nodded seriously, and disappeared into the crowd.

*Gu!* Minutes after he left, a small squadron surrounded the area, red flames burning. Among them was the figure of a woman in a pink gown.

“He was here not long ago. Seal the city! We can’t let him escape!” the woman exclaimed grimly, and the soldiers immediately dispersed. Soon, the shrill sound of bugles resounded throughout the city.

“You actually dared to steal my family’s most valuable treasure! You will pay for this in flesh and blood!!” The woman glanced at the area once again, and issued this frightful vow before travelling through the flames.

*Rumble!* A tongue of flame swept up to a height of five to six metres, and the figure of the woman completely vanished.

*Hah…*

After a few close shaves, Aaron stealthily left the city and reached a hideout he had previously prepared.

This was an underground karst cave. After doing away with all traces of the entrance and activating a defensive spell formation, Aaron finally heaved a sigh of relief and sat on the ground.

“That was too dangerous! It was only one item, did they have to chase after me so fervently?” Aaron complained, and then glared at Merlin in his mind. “Let me make this clear. If it will still be this dangerous to gather materials for the Meteor Sword in the future, I might have to give up on it. The sword may be a precious high-grade artifact, but it isn’t as precious as my life.”

“Hehe, don’t worry. This Teardrop Gemstone was the most difficult material to obtain. As long as you have your predictions, the rest are relatively easier to get our hands on.”

Immediately after, the old geezer looked stern. “The Teardrop Gemstone is a precious treasure of the Mambo Family, and it’s only natural that it was guarded so tightly. The weakening curses cast on your body are a pain, and I’ll need to spend some time analysing them. For these next two months, your strength will be restricted to that of an acolyte.”

“Sigh… But it can’t be helped!” Aaron sighed, and then thought back to the female Magus in the pink gown, his facial muscles twitching.

“I’m still far too weak. Grandpa Merlin, is there any method to advance in Sacred Flame quickly?”

“Of course!” Merlin stroked his white beard.

“Although most high-grade meditation techniques become harder to train in the further you train in them, and require many otherworldly materials to allow one to advance, my Sacred Flame is different!”

Merlin’s voice carried a hint of pride as he delved into his memories.

“Not only does my Sacred Flame give you the power to see the future, it can also allow you to advance quickly through the convergence of destiny’s powers. In theory, as long as you interfere with destiny as much as possible, you can advance at a terrifying rate!”

“Hss…” Aaron breathed in sharply, “So if I cause havoc in Twilight Zone, doesn’t that mean I can rush to becoming a Morning Star Magus?”

“Dream on!” Merlin was ruthless as he glanced at Aaron disdainfully. “How strong is the power of destiny? Just prodding the river of destiny could cause you to be ground into powder by the inertia of fate. I trained in Sacred Flame for hundreds of years and still only dared follow in Destiny’s footsteps, merely speeding up the process.”

“No matter what it is, this can help me increase my strength! I’ll do it!” Aaron suddenly clenched his fist.

He had returned to his guild an official Magus. He had also made them pay, to a certain extent, but the result was far from what he had imagined.

That young noble who had stolen his fiancee still had a Magus family backing him, with an official Magus in charge. Aaron could do little more than accept his apology for stealing his bride.

After this experience, his thirst for power had become more intense. This was why he was in a hurry to wander around, as well as gather materials to forge the Meteor Sword.

“So where is the area where destiny converges?” Aaron looked at Grandpa Merlin, eyes full of hope.

“You’ll need to find out yourself!” Merlin seemed to be implying something.

“En! I have to use Sacred Flame!” Aaron’s eyes brightened.

“That’s right! You’ve been promoted to an official Magus, and can therefore take a peek at the real long river of destiny!” Merlin gave an amiable smile.

“I’ll take a look now!”

Aaron impatiently sat down and entered a meditative state.

A unique spiritual force emanated from his body, linking with passage of time in the underworld and the rivers of history.

“Hm?” Aaron suddenly moved, holding onto his head and crying out miserably.

Scattered images, containing the bloodlust and vengeance of spirits flooded his mind.

—In the central region of Twilight Zone, a young Magus in black robes was currently speaking in a basement to an audience of malnourished and sickly teenagers. These teenagers, however, had extremely bright eyes that were almost blazing. Behind the Magus, the twisted image of a spider seemed to appear—

—The Dark Elven Empire! A teenager riding on a large Underground Winter Spider cheered excitedly, with a dark elf smiling wryly beside him—

These and a few other sporadic fragments appeared in Aaron’s mind, making him feel like a brick had been stuffed into it.

About half an hour later, Aaron reawakened, but he was breathing roughly.

“Those two people must be the ones around which the powers of destiny converge!” He sounded resolute.

“As long as I’m by their side and gain their trust, I can affect the children of destiny and accelerate the progress of Sacred Flame!

“When the time comes, you will all die! Haha…”

Aaron began to laugh madly, a faint trace of insanity in his expression.

Chapter 360: Invitation from the Central Region

The war had ended.

Leylin, who had returned from the battlefield, was now leisurely drinking some coffee.

With a thought, he accepted the scenes that the A.I. Chip transmitted to him.

“Baelin truly is Twilight Zone’s child of destiny, but Longbottom is really surprising me…” Leylin stroked his chin, watching Longbottom who was currently spouting resentment.

“Using a revolution to cobble together an army, gathering wandering Magi who are unsatisfied with the rule of the guilds, and passing high-grade meditation techniques to common acolytes? Ingenious!” Even he had to appreciate Longbottom’s methods.

The Magus World had never been a fair place, but the immense strength of Magi had meant that nobody could overthrow them.

To cause trouble in the Magus World, it was necessary to incite disharmony within their ranks. It looked like Longbottom was doing well. He was even bringing about a revolution!

“Perhaps this happened in the south coast’s past as well, causing the power of guilds to wane and letting academies take their place…” Leylin made a sudden association.

However, the first of the revolutionaries would not be able to find peace, as the conservative factions would attack them, giving them a horrible death.

This was why Leylin had no intention of introducing the system of academies to Twilight Zone and had instead kept a low profile and assimilated into their culture.

“It looks like Baelin and Longbottom are like two sides of a coin. Both are the children of destiny for this era! However, one is a hero, while the other is a rebel.” Leylin picked up the cup of coffee on the table and took a sip.

Sometimes, rebels were merely heroes who failed in their conquests! If Longbottom’s revolutionary efforts succeeded, then he would be immortalised as a model in the Magus World, extensively praised and recorded down in Magus history.

If, instead, Longbottom was bested by Baelin, he would go down in the books as a rebel; a traitor who had betrayed mankind, forever shamed by history.

“The final decisive battle will definitely be between these two! Before that, the force of destiny will quickly increase their power, even if it might not be beneficial to them in the long run.”

Leylin was very clear about the path a child of destiny could take.

While they were making their mark on the world, they could obtain an inheritance just by wandering around. By going into a random danger zone, there could be a grandpa giving out techniques, allowing them to advance quickly, and thereby causing many geniuses to be so ashamed of themselves that they committed suicide!

“Longbottom seems to have gained a bloodline, and Baelin is even better off. Not only has he even found the path to becoming a Bio Booster, which suits him best, he has even subdued the Underground Winter Spider Emperor, which is a creature with a might similar to a rank 2 Magus!”

Leylin, who had seen much in the world, could naturally judge their general strength through these scenes. The unexpected luck they had caused even Leylin to envy them.

At the same time, he had been frightened slightly. “If I had continued with him, wouldn’t I have been played by destiny and become the grandpa handing out techniques?”

Leylin looked grim. Baelin had actually gotten some benefits from him. Although he had been affected by his emotional instability as a warlock, one could not deny the hand of destiny in this matter.

After all, destiny was not created out of anywhere. It needed a form of catalyst, which would infinitely increase the probability of it appearing.

For instance, Leylin could have chosen to craft potions instead of taking in a disciple to while time away, but he had instead chosen to teach Baelin the ways of knights.

Out of everyone in Potter Town, he had settled on Baelin. How much probability and luck was involved?

“Since you want to play, let’s have a good time!” Leylin raised his cup and sent a challenge out to the skies.

[Beep! Based on scans by the limited AI, slight instability has been detected in target Aaron. The target seems to be in the early stages of mental breakdown. Immediate adoption of countermeasures suggested.]

At this moment, the A.I. Chip prompted, and an image of Aaron going crazy was projected in front of Leylin’s eyes.

“Looks like things are getting quite troublesome! Although the effects when training as an acolyte were removed in this new version of Scarlet Flame, the effects don’t seem sustainable for those who advance to become Magi.”

Leylin’s expression darkened. This was why he had not trained in Sacred Flame. Not only did he already have Kemoyin’s Pupil, he feared the side-effects brought about by training in the technique.

The spirit had far too many secrets. Even with the unworldly calculative ability of the A.I. Chip, it was still not able to analyse the mysteries of the spirit.

“A.I. Chip! Gather stats from Aaron’s current condition, and modify Sacred Flame again. Also, check on the other guinea pigs!” Leylin commanded.

Immediately after, the images of two other people were projected before Leylin.

He had not limited himself to forging the ring. His counterfeit grandpas had been passed on in secret during these past ten years, disguised by various methods as a ‘coincidence’ each time.

The A.I. Chip’s scenes showed him a young female acolyte and a strong man who also trained in Sacred Flame, cold sweat rolling down their faces.

“The power of destiny!”

All of a sudden, the two of them opened their eyes and looked at the central region.

“Everything starts and end at the same place! There’s them as well…”

The two of them made the same prediction, fear flashing on their faces.

Through the interception of this information, Leylin naturally knew what they were afraid of.

“Hehe… have they sensed the others training in the technique? It seems Sacred Flame still can’t be practiced by more than one person.”

The high-grade meditation technique, Sacred Flame, had come from the Botelli Family. Traditionally, only one person in a generation could successfully train in this meditation technique, while the rest would suffer a mental breakdown and die.

However, with modifications from the A.I. Chip, as well as Leylin’s lack of concern, this meditation technique had been passed down to many acolytes, and they had all risen to become official Magi through Sacred Flame!

[Due to the unusual nature of this meditation technique, they will need to kill each other to determine a victor. Only then will Sacred Flame be complete.]

Leylin smirked at the A.I. Chip’s newest conclusion.

“This Sacred Flame really is a fraud!”

His thoughts were now very clear. He would definitely not train in such a bizarre meditation technique.

How to take advantage of their prophetic powers and set up the situation was worth looking into, as well as the question of who would win the fight.

Leylin touched his chin, deep in thought.

……

Five days later, an unexpected guest paid a visit to Leylin’s villa.

*Clang!* Four giant metallic legs charged straight through and finally stopped by Leylin’s garden, setting off a cloud of dust and creating a ruckus behind them.

“My apologies, Magus Leylin! This large guy hasn’t been easy to control. It might be because it’s in its mating season…” Logan jumped off the back of his metallic lifeform, looking apologetic.

“No worries Magus Logan,” Leylin smiled. Shaking his head to show he did not mind, he gestured to invite the Magus in, continuing, “Please come in. I’ve collected some items which may interest you.”

A bit later, Celine who’d rushed over for some business saw the protector of the east, Logan, sitting on a chair and singing praises of the giant grilled fish on the long table.

“What type of fish is this? I’ve never seen it before.”

“It’s a hybrid of the Mamhar Fish and the Barracuda. I bred it myself!” Leylin laughed.

This creature was an accidental product of a bloodline experiment. Unexpectedly, it had ended up tasting quite good, which prompted Leylin to serve it to guests.

As the flesh of this fish was extremely delicious, and also had the function of strengthening the body of a rank 2 Magus, it was very popular.

After finding this out, Leylin immediately ordered Celine to open up a massive aquafarm, preparing to breed this type of fish at a large scale. It would be another addition to his profits.

While learning under the light Magi of the south coast, Leylin had taken care of numerous secret planes and had learned that something like that had a lot of significance and value.

As a bonus. Celine had been extremely agreeable to him recently at night, her eyes so bright it seemed like she could blink out liquid.

Leylin’s conjecture was that she had thought he had been diligently managing the guild, which touched her.

Leylin had merely laughed off her misunderstanding, not bothering to explain and instead enjoying his luck with her.

After enjoying the fine liquor and good food together, Leylin finally cut to the chase. “I wonder what I can do for Protector Logan, that you’ve come all the way here?”

“I came here today because I have a presumptuous request of you.” Logan looked serious, and slightly embarrassed.

“What is it?” Leylin seemed calm, while Celine who was beside him grasped his fingers.

“On behalf of the central region’s guilds’ alliance, I invite Nature’s Alliance to move to the central region! We have prepared the resources afforded to a large-scale guild for you, and there is a seat for Nature’s Alliance waiting amongst our ranks. In other words, once you go there, Nature’s Alliance will become a large-scale guild!”

Logan went straight to the point, saying everything in one breath.

The moment the words left his mouth, Leylin could feel Celine’s breath becoming more hurried.

Large-scale guild! That was the ultimate dream of all guilds in Twilight Zone! As the heart of Twilight Zone, the central region was also where the population was the densest, and represented the essence of the subterranean humans.

Most guilds could only wish to expand there.

Celine had always been striving for Nature’s Alliance to rise through the ranks, and she did not seem to find this situation to be strange as all. Meanwhile, Leylin was thinking of something else.

“Has the situation in the central region become that bad?” He suddenly asked.

“Hm?” Logan’s expression froze.

Moments later, he laughed wryly.

Chapter 361: Movement

“I really can’t hide anything from you!” Logan laughed bitterly. “As you know, the situation in the central region is not favourable. The dark elves are a part of it, but the Protector of Twilight Zone is the more pressing issue…”

Leylin roughly understood the situation. Powerful rank 2 Magi normally overtook the duties of protecting the north, south, east, and west of the Twilight Zone, but central Twilight Zone was different.

That area housed the elite forces of Twilight zone, so the overseeing Magus was titled the “Guardian of the Realm”. The current generation’s Guardian possessed the strength of a rank 3 Magus.

But intelligence reports said that the lifespan of the Guardian was nearing its end; he hadn’t even appeared in public in the last few decades. His seclusion was so foreboding that it was probably the main reason for the dark elves, dwarfs and gnomes to gang up on them.

“You…” Celine clenched her fists tightly, her face turning red from anger, she had finally realized the meaning of the invitation. If it was during peacetime, and one was allowed to enter the central region and become a large-scale guild, that was a truly fortunate event. But now?

The dark elven army had just been routed in the east, giving them some room to breathe. On the other hand, with the fall of Potti City, the center was facing a surge of dark elves and other enemies from the north. This meant the situation in the center was currently much worse than in the east.

At such a time, what sort of invitation was this? Wasn’t this just a request for troops and cannon fodder?

Celine almost cursed before she realised that the person sitting across her was the rank 2 Protector of the East. She suppressed her rage by force of will, leading to nothing but a smudge in her expression.

Leylin remained silent for a while. He finally let out a bitter smile. “The central region was originally protected on all four sides. It was extremely stable and peaceful, and was the best choice for accommodation. But currently, it’s being eyed by our enemies. Logan, do you really want me to suffer?”

“I understand your problem! But…“ Logan said hesitantly, “Firstly, I can tell you, this is an order of the Guardian of the Realm. We are to summon forth assistance from all four regions. Additionally, regardless of the other large-scale guilds’ intentions, I can guarantee that my own guild will step forward and enter the central region!”

Logan stood up and vowed solemnly to Leylin, even bending his head all the way to his knees.

“Sir Leylin! For Twilight Zone, and for the entire human race, I hope you can help us!”

In that moment, Leylin felt like Logan’s body was glowing. That expression greatly moved Celine who was at his side.

“Hu…” Leylin locked his brows, and seemed to be deep in thought. Logan and Celine, on the other hand, were afraid to even breathe too loudly for fear of interrupting Leylin’s ruminations.

“I’ll help you…”

After a few moments, Leylin produced an answer, bringing a sudden streak of joy across Logan’s face and causing Celine to worry. She wanted to speak out, but was abruptly thwarted by Leylin continuing, “but I have a few conditions!”

“Speak!” Logan’s voice could not conceal his excitement.

Leylin raised his index finger. “Firstly, The resources and seat you promised previously must be handed over to us unconditionally!”

“Of course; you’re entitled to the resources and treatment given to a large-scale guild. If that bunch of brats dare to embezzle anything, I will kill them immediately!” Logan’s tone was merciless, but during war the protector did indeed have the authority to do such a thing.

“Great!” he raised another finger, “In addition, I need to keep my land and position in the east!”

“Want to leave an escape route? Sure! I can promise you that! Anything for mankind!” Logan considered the condition for only a few moments before he agreed in delight.

“Anything for mankind!” Leylin chuckled to himself. He had always known that the central region would be where everything would come to a head, and his plans also required that he go there. Hence, he had already considered going to the central region.

Keeping a hold of their land here was obviously for him to retain the icy cave. There would have been no further negotiations if this point had been rejected. Leylin would rather secede from Twilight Zone than share the icy cave with anyone.

Now, he didn’t mind putting on a little show.

Logan was truly touched. Many large guilds that he had visited previously had refused to help. After all, Magi were all rational beings, and they too had to think of their subordinates. The central region was now full of danger; how then was it more alluring than the east?

“Ley… … Sir Leylin, Twilight Zone will forever remember your contribution!”

Logan appeared very reassured, as he entered his metallic lifeform and hurriedly left. It seemed like he still had many guilds to visit.

“Sir! Why did you…” Immediately after Logan left, Celine asked with urgency.

“I have already decided. You can stay behind and guard this place if you wish. In any case, we will retain our land in the east. Going to the center is merely a gamble. It doesn’t matter if we fail, and if we do manage to succeed, Nature’s Alliance will become one of the central region’s large-scale guilds! Isn’t that what you’ve always been dreaming of?” Leylin smiled at Celine, placid.

“But… what about your safety?” Celine knew that the rise of Nature’s Alliance was founded completely on the formidable strength of the man before her. Were they to lose him, the consequences would be unimaginable.

“You do not need to worry about my safety, for I will not put myself in a deadly situation. Furthermore, do you not trust my abilities?” Leylin persuaded her calmly.

Celine nodded and her heart calmed. As the person who came into contact with Leylin the most and the one closest to him, she deeply believed in the man’s unfathomable abilities.

Sometimes, the display of just a fraction of his power could scare her breathless.

“Okay! Pass the orders. A new batch of Magi and acolytes are to be chosen, we set off in ten days!” Leylin commanded.

“Yes!” Celine saluted withdrew herself with a bow. Nature’s Alliance was currently under Leylin’s sole command, and nobody in the guild could disobey him. Although there were some small troubles initially, Leylin’s absolute authority ensured the orders for the mobilization of their forces were sent out methodically.

Although many acolytes feared the disorder in the central region, they also craved adventure. Despite the danger, there were also many magicians there who had gained rewards aplenty.

As for the higher ups? Their fates were in Leylin’s hand, so what choice would they have?

After ten days, an enormous squadron had been formed, and began advancing towards the central region

Meanwhile, at the entrance of the canyon of Nature’s Alliance, Celine was clad in a purple gown. She observed the squadron proceed slowly until they disappeared along the horizon.

Due to some considerations Leylin had, he wanted Celine to remain here.

“You must definitely return alive!” She prayed as she returned to Nature’s Alliance.

“Guild master!” Several official Magi and acolytes hastily greeted her. They knew of Leylin’s and Celine’s relationship, and the fact that both of them were the nominal masters of the guild, so they did not dare to be negligent

Upon witnessing this scene, Celine felt some emptiness in her heart, but shortly after, another unfamiliar feeling arose.

“You may rise! The dark elves in the eastern region have already retreated, leaving behind many resources for us to conquer. This is our chance!” Celine’s voice was cold yet noble, and no one dared to look straight at her.

“Things will only be interesting when some leeway is given to these sorts of women”

Meanwhile, on a luxurious vehicle pulled by a giant salamander, Leylin stroked his chin and he broke into a demonic chuckle.

A woman like Celine could only bloom completely if authority was given to her. Hence, Leylin had intentionally given her position and power in the guild. He was sure that, in their next meeting, she would definitely not disappoint him.

Furthermore, his goals during this journey to the center were too large for Celine’s strength to be of assistance to him. He was also not in the mood to get intimate with her, so he had left her behind.

“The central region!” Leylin quietly went over the intelligence he had gathered regarding the central region.

It was the core of the entire Twilight Zone with a very high population density. The strength of its large-scale guilds largely surpassed that of guilds in the other regions. Yet, this was not the most horrifying fact…

“The Guardian of the Realm… …” Leylin let out a sigh.

The position of the Guardian was normally given to the most powerful Magus in the entirety of Twilight Zone.

But the Protector of the East, Logan, had met him several times and their abilities should be on par. Hence, the Guardian of the Realm should be a powerhouse even amongst rank 3 Magi. If not for his lifespan that was almost depleted, Leylin would not dare to play such tricks.

The squadron proceeded gradually, and the roaming darkness creatures and bandits on their path fled in all directions the moment they spotted them. They did not dare to obstruct Leylin’s party and offend them

The bandits were observant and naturally realised that this squadron was composed of Magi. As for the darkness creatures, they could sense the strong aura travelling towards them and escaped for fear of death.

Thus, the journey was rather a peaceful one.

Along the way, Nature’s Alliance had amassed a following of several other medium-scale guilds as well as a few small-scale guilds. They, too, had heeded the call and wanted to go to the central region to keep watch.

Upon witnessing Nature Alliance’s standard, the guild masters of different guilds immediately came forth to visit him, and even let go of their pride to discuss the possibility of joining forces to advance.

After all, the fact that Leylin was a member of Nature’s Alliance was made known to many. That was a rank 2 Magus! With him there, the procession would definitely make it to the central region without any hiccups.

“Although there are a few idealists in there, most of them are those with great ambitions who are willing to take a gamble!”

After a look, Leylin evaluated these people indifferently.

However, he still agreed to their requests. The horse carriages, which formed a large procession resembling a river, began to travel towards the central region.

As Magi could illuminate the path ahead with spells, there was no need for the carriages to carry torches.

The giant sunstone was placed on the top of a carriage, illuminating the surroundings and their path brightly.

Chapter 362: A Fair Trial

*Rumble!*

Faint fluctuations travelled over, and for there to be so many undulations despite the long distance allowed the people in the carriage to ascertain their identities.

“They’re Magi, official Magi! It looks like they’re battling. Do we still proceed?” A peak rank 1 Magus guild master approached Leylin’s carriage and bowed, asking for further instructions.

“Of course!” Leylin spoke indifferently. With the power, they held when they banded together, they could easily go on a rampage in the eastern region. Thus, they were fearless.

The guild leader seemed to have the same thoughts and, after a moment of pause, they continued to advance.

The rest of the party noticed the energy fluctuations as they closed in. One of the two seemed to have reservations with approaching them, while the other hesitated for a moment before heading in their directions.

“Trying to use us to block the enemy?” The Magi in the group of carriages silently waited while smirking.

*Xiu!*

Seconds later, a red streak shot over from afar, and a young Magus appeared.

This Magus looked quite ordinary but for the black ring on his right index finger and his resolute eyes. After seeing so many official Magi, his eyes widened and he tried to take a long way around them.

“You can’t escape! How dare you steal our family’s treasure!” a woman’s voice sounded out. The young man quivered, bit his lips, ground his teeth, and then dashed towards the group of carriages.

“Save me! I’m a wandering Magus, and for some reason, this mad woman is chasing me. She keeps slandering me and saying that I stole her treasure!”

This young Magus was naturally Aaron. After recuperating from his injuries, he had been unlucky enough to meet with the Magus from the Mambo Family, and had been chased all the way here.

As for blocking this group’s path, that was naturally Merlin’s idea.

“Will they save me? After all…” Aaron worriedly communicated with Merlin in his mind.

“Don’t worry! I’ve already completely concealed the aura of the Teardrop Gemstone. That crazy woman behind us won’t find anything!” Merlin promised confidently.

As for that confidence, it was definitely due to a certain someone within the carriages.

“Hehe… Young man, you’re pretty good to have actually helped me gather the Teardrop Gemstone. I didn’t even know the Mambo Family had this in their collection!” Leylin smiled lightly, a cold glint in his eyes.

*Xiu!* At this moment, a pink ray shot into this area, and the female Magus who had been chasing after Aaron appeared in their midst.

After seeing the group of carriages with so many Magi, she felt her chest tighten perceptibly.

“I am Ophelia of the Mambo Family! My apologies if I am offending you, but please do not stop me from pursuing this vile thief!”

The group was arranged haphazardly, with a few small scale guilds in front. Ophelia’s tone was therefore not that polite.

After all, the Mambo Family was quite famous in this region.

“How dare you! Who do you think you are?”

“The Mambo Family? Never heard of it before.”

Although those in front were a just few small scale guilds, their higher-ups were watching on from the back, and even the legendary rank 2 Magus in charge of Nature’s Alliance was present. They were naturally unrestrained in their answers.

“You…” Ophelia’s voice lowered, and a faint aura of danger emanated from her body.

How many people in her family dared to speak to her like this?

At this point, however, more carriages had arrived, and the markings caused Ophelia to swallow the words she was planning to say, making her dumbstruck.

“The Lost Clock, Twisted Black Clouds, Infernal Blood, and… Nature’s Alliance!”

Ophelia’s eyes widened. These were all medium scale guilds, and each one of them was powerful enough to pressure the Mambo Family—especially Nature’s Alliance, which had a powerful rank 2 Magus in charge.

The moment they were provoked, they would squash her like one would an ant.

On the other end, Aaron gaped, stunned. “So many! So many Magi and acolytes! Are they migrating?”

“Ophelia had no intentions of offending anyone; please forgive me!” Cold sweat rushed down Ophelia’s spine, and she immediately dropped to the ground and bowed.

“Haven’t you dealt with this yet?” At this moment, Leylin opened the door and descended from the largest and most luxurious carriage in Nature’s Alliance’s group.

“Lord Leylin!” All the Magi there immediately bowed.

“Ley-Leylin! The legendary rank 2 Magus said to have heavily injured a dark elven Sovereign Mother! Why is my luck so bad?” Ophelia was snarling on the inside, but she wouldn’t dare to even break into a cold sweat in this man’s presence.

“What’s going on?” Leylin furrowed his eyebrows, asking even though he knew the situation.

“My- My apologies, my lord!” A Magus from the Alliance was frightened so badly he couldn’t even speak clearly.

“What’s going on?” Leylin repeated once again, but the atmosphere had frozen. The entire group was quiet, and even some guild leaders of medium-scaled guilds, who were peak rank 1 Magi themselves, did not dare to make a sound.

“My lord, it’s like this….” Ophelia tried her best to make herself sound calm, narrating the whole story.

“Oh! Is that so?”

Leylin turned, and Aaron was pressed to the ground by an invisible force.

“I’ll give you one chance. You said you used your family’s secret method and found him. Do it again in front of us! If the Teardrop Gemstone is on him, then he shall be judged by us all. If not…” Leylin’s dangerous gaze landed on Ophelia, causing her head to tingle.

“If it isn’t, then Ophelia is willing to accept punishment!” Ophelia grit her teeth and forced out an answer.

“Not only that, those of us here are responding to summons from the central region to engage in battle. If you are proven to be wrong, you shall be prosecuted by the war council for obstructing military affairs.”

Leylin smiled to make up for his harsh words. “Well then, begin!”

“What do I do? What do I do?” Aaron watched Ophelia who had already begun to use her family’s secret method and the official Magi who were preparing to watch a good show. He repeatedly asked Merlin in his mind, while not even daring to look at the legendary rank 2 Magus at all.

“Don’t worry. I’m the legendary great Magus Merlin. What is a little rank 2 Magus to me?” Merlin boasted shamelessly, “With my spirit force concealing it, this girl definitely won’t find anything!”

“Then why didn’t you use it previously?” Aaron felt like he had been conned.

“A lot of my spirit force has been used, and it hasn’t been replenished,” Merlin explained vaguely, causing Aaron to immediately begin reproaching himself. How could he not trust Grandpa Merlin, whom he had grown up with?

“You’re dead meat!” Ophelia snickered while lowering her head, pointing at Aaron with the ring.

“There is a tracking spell formation on the Teardrop Gemstone passed down by my ancestors. As long he has it on him, my ring will emit red rays of light. Look, my lords!”

Ophelia pointed the ring at Aaron, and shouted a word, “Mambo!”

Aaron’s heart was at his throat, and he almost closed his eyes to wait for the judgment of destiny.

“Eh?” “Oh!” “Ah?”

All sorts of sounds resounded by Aaron’s ears, but none of them were the accusations he had expected.

He secretly chanced a glance at Ophelia, who was now looking lost and dejected.

“How is this possible? How is this possible? It wasn’t like this the last few times!” She lifted the ring and scanned him a few more times.

The ring had no response, as if it were just an ordinary ring.

“Haha! How is it? Aren’t my concealing methods powerful?” Merlin chuckled heartily in Aaron’s mind.

In reality, all of this was Leylin’s work. If not for him being there, Aaron would definitely have been seen through.

“How?” Ophelia shrieked, unwilling to give up as she took off the ring and inspected the formations within.

Moments later, she yelled out, “It must be you! You must have hidden the Teardrop Gemstone somewhere along the way!

“No! It must definitely be on your person. Hand it over!” Blazing pink flames appeared on her body.

“Enough! What a farce!” Leylin was still playing the role of a fair, altruistic judge.

“No! My lord, you need to believe me!” Ophelia’s voice cracked, sounding a little hoarse.

*Bang!*

A resplendent, silver light flashed, and the flames on her body were extinguished. She retreated a few steps and fell to the ground, her expression still full of stubbornness.

“Haha, that girl actually dares to resist. She’s in trouble!” Merlin rejoiced in Aaron’s mind.

“What’s happening?” Aaron immediately asked.

“That Lord Leylin is a rank 2 Magus! His solidified spiritual force is not something a little girl like her can withstand, but she actually dared do so. What should have been a light injury will now become more serious, and might even affect her sea of consciousness…”

“Ah? Then what’s going to happen to her?” Aaron began to blame himself.

“What else can happen to her? If a rank 2 Magus wants to discipline her, she’ll still need to endure it even if she’s not in the wrong. She can’t complain either,” Merlin continued taking joy in her pain, and took the opportunity to educate Aaron, “This is the law of the Magus World!”

“Leave this place and never appear in front of me again! It seems like you just made a mistake this time. I won’t report it to the war council!”

Leylin hummed lightly and returned to the carriage.

“Thank you for your mercy, my lord!” His actions elicited words of gratitude from the female Magus.

Ophelia left the area in a daze. Although she was in despair, were she to continue staying here, a few peak rank 1 Magi would make short work of her without Leylin even lifting a finger.

“What are you looking at? We’re leaving!”

Soon enough, the carriages continued their journey.

Chapter 363: Infiltration into the Central Region

Aaron stood in a spot alone, and no Magi bothered him.

This was his second time experiencing a feeling of loss. The first time? Naturally, it was when his spiritual aptitude had deteriorated, and his engagement was broken off.

Aaron held onto the black ring in his hands tightly. That was the gloomiest moment of his life, but thankfully he found this!

“Grandpa Merlin? When do you reckon I will reach the level of Master Leylin?” Aaron silently asked in his heart.

It had never occurred to him to use his connections. In Dolon City, he was but a small acolyte, whereas Leylin was a powerful rank 2 Magus. The latter would surely not remember him!

“Relax, isn’t it just rank 2?” Merlin had inherited Leylin’s twisted sense of humour. It whispered into Aaron’s mind: “As long as you can find the two children of destiny, and trigger the river of destiny, your cultivation in Sacred Flame will increase exponentially. Advancing to rank 2 or 3 will be a simple task!”

“In that case, I have to increase my speed!” Aaron clenched his fist and looked into the far distance; for an instant he was filled with hope.

To Leylin, what happened to Aaron was but a hiccup in his journey.

Even though Aaron was a chess piece of his, he never requested Aaron to join him. After all, keeping Merlin at his side was enough.

Moreover, he did not want to give Aaron or the others any clues, lest they discover his intentions.

Leylin lowered his head, concealing the bottomless glow in his eyes.

……

After advancing for half a month, the squadron had entered the central region.

Their journey there had been very peaceful, with nothing happening.

Their squadron was one that was composed of magicians. They had no lack of even peak rank 1 Magi, and Leylin, a rank 2 Magus was leading them. It was already considered pretty good that they had not looked for trouble with others, forget anyone daring to offend them.

With the aid of spells, they travelled rapidly, not being impeded even by rough terrain. Commoners would face difficulties when trying to trek through narrow valleys and scale steep cliffs. Magi just settled any problems with a few spells.

“Is this central Twilight Zone? The quality of life here far surpasses that of the east!”

Leylin had lowered his hood and looked around at the neatly built houses by the roadside. He nodded at the occasional farmer he saw.

The center was the essence of Twilight Zone. Darkness creatures were a rare sight here, and the population density was very high.

However, currently, Leylin could see squires dressed in leather armour running across the region. The farmers mostly looked worried; with north Twilight Zone having fallen, the big war was at their doorstep! The dark elven soldiers and dwarves, gnomes and even darkness creatures from outside the region could all directly arrive at the central region after bypassing the north, which could create a lot of trouble for them.

The central region lacked the strength to repel such raids, especially in terms of magicians. They had no choice but to send out orders to all 4 zones and recruit more acolytes.

At this point in time, a Nature’s Alliance Magus came forth and reported to Leylin: “My lord! The leaders of a few medium-scale guilds have come forth to say their goodbyes; they are going to return to the zones they came from!”

“Let them go! They don’t have to specially report to me!” Leylin coldly ordered.

A large number of orders sounded in the distance. Some of the smaller troops, like the distributaries of a river, left Nature’s Alliance’s side.

“What a pity!” Leylin glanced at the small and medium-scale guilds that were leaving, and let out a sigh.

Even though the resources in the central region were good, they had to be exchanged for with one’s life!

If these guilds could survive the big war, they would naturally get land as their reward. However, if they risk suffering heavy losses, or even being completely wiped out, then leaving would be the best choice.

Though the central region was rich in resources, even it could not support all the guilds that came.

The war would choose the real winners who would end up with the last laugh! Still, many guilds swarmed to the central region. Even though they knew it was all a gamble, they did not hesitate for a moment to stake everything on this wager. They hoped to gain a lot from it.

“After the war, how many guilds would there be left?” Leylin sighed lightly and closed the windows.

“Send the orders down, we are to advance at full speed and rush to our territory as soon as we can!” On the surface, Leylin was still representing Nature’s Alliance’s interests, and hence he had ordered so casually.

“As you wish, my lord!”

The orders were quickly passed down through magic spells , and the sounds of the Earth Salamanders and Wildebeest came repeatedly as the entire squadron’s speed increased a level.

……

In yet another region, a few haggard travellers entered the boundaries of the central region.

“Is this the central region?” Baelin swept off the dust on his body and looked at the big city ahead.

He was dressed in oversized grey gunny robes, and a spider streaked in gold would pop out onto his shoulders from time to time.

“Yes! Advancing after Tran City should lead us to central Twilight Zone!” Memphis was next to Baelin. However, he had currently lost all resemblance to a dark elf, and only looked like a pale-skinned royal.

“Could you get your Underground Winter Spider Emperor to hide? It’s very easy to attract attention here!” He once again looked at the mischievous spider that climbed onto Baelin’s shoulder, and smiled wryly.

*Hiss* This golden spider seemed to be able to understand human languages, and upon hearing what Memphis said, it let out a threatening screech.

“Aru says that he has restrained his aura, and only rank 2 Magi can see through his transformation; so even if formal Magi were to see the Underground Winter Spider Emperor, they would only treat it as a mutated ordinary spider!” Baelin translated for Memphis, “Also, if you dare to suggest this ever again, he’ll eat you!”

“Alright!” Memphis was rendered speechless.

This Underground Winter Spider Emperor was Baelin’s reward from their excursion into the Dark Elven Empire! Originally, they had planned to attack or subdue the Underground Winter Spider Emperor to halt the war.

However, the Underground Winter Spider Emperor had confoundingly decided to follow Baelin, becoming the Magus’ contracted familiar.

Memphis had not expected that, and after he found out that it could have been the workings of his ancestral amulet, he felt so cheated that he almost went and banged his head against a wall.

Although he knew that his ancestors were royals of a strong clan, he had not expected them to have left such a strong agreement that the owner of the amulet could actually control the Underground Winter Spider Emperor!

That was a being with the strength of a rank 2 Magus! Were he to have gained control of it, the Underground Winter Spider knights would have defected to his side, but now?

Memphis smiled wryly as he looked at Baelin who was standing at the side.

Even though they had the Underground Winter Spider knights, the proud dark elves simply would not admit that a member of another species could exercise control over their sacred objects. On the contrary, they had viewed this as a great humiliation, and had even launched into a relentless killing spree!

Memphis had seen the Dark Elven Empire’s plans fail. He learned through his connections that the dark elves were plotting yet another scheme in the central region, one that could potentially destroy the foundations of the human race!

Upon receiving the news, Baelin had become restless and filled with a strong sense of duty. After ensuring that Jenny settled down, he secretly entered the central region with Memphis.

“What happens to us after this? Do we tell the Magi what we found out?” Baelin suddenly realised that he had no idea about his next course of action.

“Just based on our own merits?” Memphis pointed to himself and smiled bitterly, then pointed to the Underground Winter Spider Emperor on Baelin’s shoulders, “A dark elf and a suspicious man with an Underground Winter Spider Emperor?”

“I’m afraid that, before we even utter a single word, the other side will have started flinging spells at us. Needless to say, this information would only be heeded if a rank 2 Magus passed it on, and Aru’s stealth would not hold up against such an existence!

““Furthermore, upon seeing an Underground Winter Spider Emperor, a rank 2 Magus would even kill us immediately! After all, their bloodlines ensure that dark elves would instantly weaken the moment an Underground Winter Spider Emperor dies. They would even lose their endless supply of mounts! This would definitely be a huge blow to the Dark Elven Empire! What do you think they would choose to do?”

“Essentially, there’s still no way!” Baelin squatted down and felt dejected.

“However, it is not entirely hopeless!” Memphis’ tone changed.

“There’s hope?” Baelin’s eyes lit up.

“Do you remember that I mentioned Magus Leylin earlier?”

“Master Leylin?” Baelin’s voice held a tinge of respect within it. He saw Leylin as a teacher and was grateful and respectful to him.

“Yes! That Leylin! Did you know that he is actually the most recent Magus to reach rank 2?” Memphis lowered his voice. Even though Leylin was a member of another species, he still held a respect for the strong.

“According to the news I received, not only did he help Fendix attack and kill a rank 2 matriarch at Dolon, he had defeated another matriarch before it! My clan’s intelligence has already marked him as a threat with a danger level of 8!”

“Master! He is actually so… strong?” Baelin’s eyes widened. He had personally witnessed the strength of a rank 2 matriarch.

In the Dark Elven Empire, he and Memphis had been hunted down by a matriarch. If not for the protection of the Underground Winter Spider Emperor, they would definitely not have been able to escape.

The matriarch’s unyielding strength had left a deep impression on the minds of the two.

And now, he was being told that the Master Leylin who had taught him before was even stronger than a rank 2 matriarch?

Baelin’s feelings at that moment were very complicated. There was pride, but there was also regret.

“Yes!” Memphis nodded his head: “Though we’re not of the same kind, I admire him greatly as well!

“This Master Leylin is definitely a heavy presence in the Magi world, and even has ties with you. You need only pass the intelligence to him…”

Chapter 366: Backlash

The field had been partitioned, with a large mill occupying the center.

Not far away, there was a small farm and a stone castle. However, it was very small and lacked a moat.

At a glance, it looked to be the territory of a small aristocratic family.

In a shadow, Ernis had respectfully lowered his head and was reporting to Longbottom. “My lord, I can confirm that this is a secret stronghold of the Green Water Gardens guild. The Great Magus Rosby who is in his down period is hiding here.”

“En! This is their nest, and there should be many defensive spell formations. Since they’re a rank 2 Magus, even if they were weakened temporarily, they cannot be compared to an ordinary peak rank 1 Magus!” Longbottom muttered to himself, and then glanced at his subordinates.

Those following him were all official Magi, but few were even semi-converted. He could unearth their potentials, but what he needed was time.

He had brought them along now as a declaration of allegiance, to form an impassable divide between them and the ruling class.

Longbottom glanced at the few figures dressed in black robes. These people had slim bodies and had concealed their features with large cloaks. The cloaks were so large, in fact, that one could not even tell the men from the women.

These were the backup he had been given by the dark elves. All of them were at the peak of rank 1.

As for the rank 2 matriarchs? Every single action of theirs was being monitored; it was impossible for one to sneak across the border to conduct an assassination.

In addition, even if they somehow got in, they would be surrounded and attacked by the Magi of Twilight Zone.

Dark elves could bear the deaths of rank 1 Magi, but rank 2 matriarchs were the backbones of their clans; their presence was a spiritual support to the clan members, boosting their morale. The death of a matriarch was a heavy loss for any clan.

It was for this reason that Fendix, who had killed a matriarch, had gained large rewards from Twilight Zone as well as a huge bounty from the Dark Elven Empire. Honestly speaking, the rewards that the crazed dark elves promised had even tempted Leylin.

Fendix himself was so frightened that he spent all his time at the headquarters of his guild, and had naturally not come to the aid of the central region.

“Go!” With Longbottom’s order, flames of death descended on this peaceful field.

*Rumble!* Fireballs rained down like meteors, sending sparks flying everywhere.

“What’s going on?” A knight dressed in the garb of nobility rushed out, shocked.

“A- An attack from Magi? Why? Are they dark elves?”

*Xiu!* After seeing the situation, he retreated without the slightest hesitation, leaving his territory, subjects and even family behind.

As a knight who had entered the battlefield before, he knew the terror that Magi brought with them. He knew that once they attacked, this place was doomed.

“Don’t let any of them go!”

Longbottom watched the knight who was darting away and pointed at him like one would at an ant.

A deathly light streaked across the sky and reached his back. Like cutting through cotton, it easily penetrated the knight’s defence and exploded on his back.

*Bang!* A hole that could fit a basketball was opened up, revealing white bones and black blood. The knight’s eyes were filled with fear, as well as shock. The powerful inertia allowed him to run a few more steps before he fell with a thud.

Under the constant onslaught of spells, the village turned into a sea of fire. None of the peasants lived, and it soon turned into a white land.

However, Longbottom was still not satisfied and ordered the Magi to quicken their actions.

Layers of soil were lifted, revealing a glossy rock wall, with runes on it concealing any energy fluctuations.

“Hehe, he’s actually like a groundhog hiding under the feet of regular humans, and has even carved energy runes to conceal his aura. This Magus Rosby really is rather timid…” Longbottom sneered, and pointed at the magic wall.

“Destroy it!”

*Rumble!* Numerous spells were interrupted by several rays of light before they could reach the rock wall.

*Rumble!* The rock separated, revealing a large door.

*Thud! Thud!* Accompanied by heavy footsteps, four large silver guards walked out.

These silver guards were all adorned in heavy armour, and their expressions were moulded to be blank. There was even some light flashing out of their eyes like a searchlight.

Ernis immediately stepped forward and spoke “Rosby is very careful and cautious. He hasn’t revealed this location to any other Magus, and even the guard has been set up by him alone, consisting only of Secret Silver Puppets. Hence, he’s the only one in here. We need to prevent him from fleeing.” As for how he had found this out, it would stay a secret.

“When working together, these four Secret Silver Puppets are equivalent to two peak rank 1 Magi. The two of you, go up there and stop them. The revolutionary army will be around to keep them from fleeing.” Longbottom quickly sent down the command.

The two black-robed people charged up without a word.

*Roar!* The Secret Silver Puppets yelled and brandished their large silver swords, battling the black-robed elves.

Immense energy fluctuations gave rise to a storm, sweeping through the region.

The revolutionary army Longbottom had brought with him dared only to watch on from a distance, occasionally supporting the two and pinning the guards down.

“Ernis and the rest, follow me.” Longbottom shook his robes, and the rest of the dark elves and Ernis followed him.

Only after they were far from everyone’s eyes did Longbottom speak to Ernis, “Quick! Find the escape routes Rosby could be using!”

“Come with me!” Moments later, Ernis led the way.

“Go!” Longbottom watched Ernis who was leading the way, eyes darting everywhere. Nobody could guess his thoughts.

In a little farm about five kilometers away…

*Pala!* The soil flipped over, revealing a dark pathway.

A grim middle-aged man in dark red Magus robes walked out. After glancing at his surroundings, he immediately unfurled a scroll. Green hurricanes blew forth, and a large pair of wings formed on his back.

“I can’t stay here any longer. How did this get out?”

This Magus was obviously Green Water Gardens’ rank 2 Magus, Rosby.

He was obviously in a stale mood. The location that only he knew of had been leaked, and someone had even found him while he was weak. The whole situation reeked of a conspiracy.

However, he had another question. “I didn’t tell anyone about this place. How did they find out?”

However, he did not dare dwell on this for long, “This place is dangerous. I’ll think about it after I leave.”

Just as Rosby was about to spread his wings, an extreme sense of danger came upon him.

He immediately retreated, his figure turning into an afterimage.

*Rumble!* A large explosion occurred right where he had been standing, and the energy particles that were dispelled caused massive damage to the ground.

*Xiu! Xiu!* Two black streaks of light flew across the sky, forming a cross in mid-air. These arches accurately homed in on Rosby’s wings.

“This trajectory? It’s the dark elves’ curved archery! You are dark elves!” The wings fell apart, and Rosby paled before crying out in alarm.

*Shua!* Black light flashed, and a distortion appeared in the air, revealing a few figures.

Longbottom took the lead, and the two robed people behind him also took off their clothes, revealing pale, handsome features and pointed ears.

The twisted runes on their fantastic black bows were now flickering.

“Humans and dark elves! Looks like you are the revolutionary army that has been causing such a ruckus. You are the leader, right? Longbottom?” Rosby calmed down.

“Yes!” Longbottom bowed, “As a rank 2 Magus, you are my senior, but for our hopes and future, please die.”

*Rumble!* Just as his words sounded, the dark elves suddenly attacked.

Black streams of air formed what looked like a spider web and fell from the skies. On Longbottom’s body, the phantom image of a large giant spider appeared and jumped onto the web, hissing loudly.

“Combination magic? Its power is almost as much as that of a rank 2 spell!” A strange smile appeared on his face, “But just that isn’t enough.”

*Rumble!* A torrential power exploded forth from Rosby’s body, as if a landslide or tsunami had come upon the area. Silver spiritual force slashed at the skies like a sharp sword, and quickly severed the web into two. The phantom image was also bisected, causing both Longbottom and the dark elves to pale.

“Rank 2 strength! You’re not weak anymore!” Longbottom had become deathly pale, his voice quivering.

“Impossible! Impossible!” Ernis could not believe it either.

“Recognise the reality of it! Your opponent is a rank 2 Magus. How could he not have a few trump cards? Even if his strength might have been lowered because he was in his down period, he can still suppress that for a while and reveal true rank 2 strength!” Merlin’s voice sounded in Ernis’ mind.

“How is this possible? I didn’t predict…” Ernis was flushing red, but suddenly became silent, like a duck that had been grasped at the neck.

“Do you understand now? You’re only a rank 1 Magus, and in ancient times you’d be considered as just having crossed the gates of becoming a Magus. With just this bit of strength, it’s impossible for you to completely predict the trump cards of a rank 2 Magus using Sacred Flame, even if he were weakened or heavily injured. The fog of destiny may shroud him, or even counterattack!”

Merlin’s voice was as cold as ice. “Now, do you know why I fell?”

Chapter 367: Clone Seed

Ernis looked defeated. “So I’m definitely going to die?”

Merlin sneered in his mind. “Not necessarily! Longbottom is a child of destiny, and is not one to fall so easily. Besides, do you think the matriarch backing him doesn’t have any contingency plans?”

“You dare offend me, a respected rank 2 Magus? You will pay for this humiliation in blood!”Rosby declared grimly, and a line of spiritual force converged that was tinged silver.

The rank 2 Magus had even been slightly frightened. If he hadn’t possessed a technique that could temporarily suppress his weakness, he could have died just then.

A rank 2 Magus dying at the hands of a group of rank 1 Magi would be the biggest joke in Twilight Zone’s history!

Rosby felt like a robust adult who had been bitten by an ant. The humiliation irked him to his soul.

This secret technique was not without cost. His period of vulnerability would be extended, and in the times of war, this could have had deadly consequences. Hence, he was now truly enraged.

“I shall turn you into maggots, making you rot and suffer underground for ten thousand years. I swear it!” Rosby’s eyes were completely red, and great amounts of solidified silver spiritual force swept through the area.

“Damn it. Use that!” Longbottom yelled.

The two dark elves behind him exchanged a glance and nodded, silver rays shooting out of their eyes. In that moment, their expressions were that of those preparing for death.

They then produced jewelled daggers with a strange curve, aimed them at their own hearts and jabbed in.

*Puk! Puk!* Two peak rank 1 elves collapsed, a bloody mist spreading from their chests.

The phantom image of the spider behind Longbottom had been seriously injured by spiritual force and was on the verge of disappearing. However, it suddenly twitched and absorbed the red blood-mist, quickly restoring itself. Its aura continually strengthened, until it was almost strong enough to rival the rank 2 Magus ahead of it.

“What- What’s going on?” Ernis was astonished.

“Hehe, nothing much. It’s just a sacrifice! The same old thing that the dark elves always use.” Merlin laughed sarcastically.

“Dark elven society is made up of clans. Every clan has its matriarch, and they all have immense control over their descendants. This control runs deep in the blood, and is very difficult to free oneself from. Even if it’s a peak rank 1 Magus, a mere spiritual suggestion would convince them to kill themselves without hesitation.”

“The meditation technique Longbottom is training in is one that absorbs life energy. After absorbing that of two peak rank 1 Magi, although he can’t defeat his opponent, he will most likely escape…”

“Hm? What about me?” Ernis was suddenly put in a difficult spot. Longbottom could leave, but he was just a semi-converted Magus. How was he to escape?

“This is the retaliation of destiny! Longbottom, being a child of destiny, can escape successfully. You’ll be left behind as an outlet for the rank 2 Magus to vent his anger upon!” Merlin’s voice was frigid, rendering Ernis silent.

His eyes turned white again as he tried to think up some countermeasures. He was trying to make a prediction, but he did not get anything.

“What should I do next?” Ernis’ voice was hoarse.

“Pray! At this point, you can do nothing but pray!” Merlin’s voice displayed his helplessness, “If I still had my body, killing him would be as easy as crushing an ant. But now? You can only hope he doesn’t prolong your life to torture you.”

“No! No! I still have hope!” Ernis stared hard at Longbottom, “As long as my lord is willing to save me, I can…”

Ernis’ words stuck in his throat. He watched as Longbottom, who was manipulating the phantom spider and battling with Rosby, quickly withdrew.

Black gas flew everywhere and increased his speed. In a moment, he disappeared into the horizon.

“I… I…” Ernis’ eyes were filled with despair.

On the other end, Rosby who had lost Longbottom turned his attention to the semi-converted Magus.

A giant silver claw flew forth, its strength not something that Ernis could resist, and grabbed him!

“Am I going to die? I can’t accept this!” Ernis closed his eyes. Powerful solidified spiritual force causing the magical power in his body to become sluggish in its movements. He could do nothing in the face of a rank 2 Magus’ wrath.

“Rosby!”

At this moment, a low voice sounded from the horizon a long distance away, carrying with it a berserk energy.

“Hm? An opportunity! A person seeking revenge against Rosby seems to have appeared. I’ll use my power to cover your presence. Quick, run!”

Merlin’s voice was hurried, and with a sudden feeling of coldness infiltrating his senses, Ernis found himself able to move once again. He quickly escaped, dodging the attack of the giant claw. Without looking behind him, he quickly left.

Rosby did not pursue him, because a rank 2 spiritual force was now focused on him. He raised his head and saw a black figure rushing over from the horizon.

This figure’s face was shrouded by black mist, causing him to be unable to tell the real appearance of this person.

“Who are you? I don’t think we’ve met.” Rosby sounded out.

He was currently in a very dangerous situation, and his secret technique could lose its effect at any time, causing him to fall down to rank 1. That would be very dangerous.

“It doesn’t matter who I am, but this is a seed I planted. How could I let you harvest it?” The figure’s voice was robotic, obviously having been altered.

“Seed? Harvest? Are you…” Rosby’s stunned expression immediately warped into an immense fear.

Mist! Large amounts of black mist brought with it a silver luster, forming a large maze that trapped him within.

“He plans to limit my strength, and after my secret technique stops working, he’ll deal with me.” Rosby could tell his opponent’s intentions with a glance. He waved his arm, and numerous silver arrows flew into the mist.

*Pu pu! Pu pu! Pu pu!*

The arrows of light flew into the wall of mist and instantly disappeared, causing Rosby to pale.

“You don’t need to consider calling a friend or anything of the sort. This place has already been sealed by me, and no information can be transmitted out.”

The voice from before sounded in the black maze, but it did come from a single location.

His opponent was very cautious in dealing with a rank 2 Magus that had used a secret technique to somehow return to his regular strength. He had not appeared, preventing him from using some powerful force that could destroy everything.

A look of hopelessness appeared on Rosby’s face.

Ten or so minutes passed, and Rosby bellowed, unresigned. The aura on his body quickly weakened, and lines of wrinkles appeared on his face. His appearance changed from that of a middle-aged man to that of an old man.

This meant the secret technique was no longer in effect. He was once again weak, vulnerable.

Seeing this, large amounts of mist pounced on him…

*Pak!* The black maze dispersed, and a single black flame fell, burning Rosby’s corpse to ashes.

Leylin weighed the green ring in his hand, a smile blossoming on his face.

“As expected of the guild leader of a large-scaled guild. He’s accumulated plenty of things, and there’s even a spacial magic artifact!”

He stared closely at the ring in his hand. It was extremely slender and looked like it was for a female to use. Its surface was decorated with flowers and vines, forming an exotic image.

“There are many good items in this spatial ring, but the defensive layer on the surface is slightly troublesome. I’ll need to use the A.I. Chip and slowly analyse it.”

Leylin scratched his chin and kept the green ring away.

Rosby was a rank 2 Magus and had a spatial item. He would definitely have a lot of resources on his body, the total value of which could even exceed that of those stored in Green Water Gardens’ headquarters.

Gaining this was akin to robbing a large-scaled guild, as well as all the property belonging to a rank 2 Magus.

“The gains aren’t too bad this time. Also, hehe…” Leylin laughed coldly.

On the surface of the ring, he felt a tiny connection to a being a distance away. This meant that Rosby had yet to truly die.

The connection was minute, and if not for Leylin already being a rank 2 Magus, as well as the A.I. Chip’s help in carefully scanning the ring a few times, he might not even have noticed this.

If his opponent were to escape this time and find the ring on Leylin’s person, things would be bad.

But now? Leylin glanced in the direction that Ernis had fled, a slight smile on his face.

“It’s great that you could come back!” Longbottom glanced at Ernis, revealing a bright smile.

“I was just lucky!” Ernis laughed wryly, though the seed of distrust had been planted within him.

The two of them had already returned to the little manor.

The four Secret Silver Puppets had been reduced to dust after being attacked by the two dark elves and many Magi.

“Do you know who that Magus is?” Longbottom asked Ernis.

“No, but he should be an enemy of Rosby’s. The strength of a rank 2 Magus is too far off, so I couldn’t gather any useful information.” Ernis seemed a little regretful.

All of a sudden, he felt a prophecy entering his mind, and his eyes turned white.

“Rosby is dead, but the seed of a clone is still within the headquarters of Green Water Gardens!”

Ernis quickly passed on this information to Longbottom and asked, “What should we do?”

“Is there a need to ask?” A sinister smile appeared on Longbottom’s face.

“Summon our people. We shall go to their headquarters!”

Chapter 369: A Competition for Geniuses

Leylin deliberated over his phrasing. “But to do that, you’ll have to deploy the higher-ups!”

If the guilds joined forces, they could naturally extinguish the scattered rebels, but part of their forces would be tied down. With the north down, and casualties stacking up at the center, the cost outweighed the benefits involved.

“Then what do you suggest?” Logan seemed to be able to tell the hidden meaning in Leylin’s words.

“The rebels led by Longbottom definitely need to be suppressed and exterminated, but I believe we can try to pacify the wandering Magi.”

Leylin stroked his chin.

“How? Twilight Zone has a limited amount of resources. Are you, Nature’s Alliance, going to pay out of your pocket?” Logan was slightly annoyed.

“No, of course not!” Leylin smiled while he shook his head, “What do you say we hold a competition for young Magi?”

“Competition?” Logan was baffled.

“Yes, a competition between geniuses! It will be targeted at young Magi, with generous rewards and the opportunity to join some guilds. If they obtain a certain ranking, they can even enter a guild of their choice!” Leylin declared his scheme.

“With this, not only can we unite more wandering Magi and express our goodwill to the organisations behind them, we can also shift their focus from the unfairness of guilds to the vying for a position, causing internal friction!”

“This… Let me think…” Logan scratched his beard.

Leylin paid no attention to him and smiled, because he knew Logan was considering his suggestion.

As expected, minutes later, Logan roughly slapped the table, “It’s a good idea! Of course! Why didn’t I think of it?”

He stood up and quickly paced around the room. “No matter how much we try to tempt those old Magi, it’s all going to be in vain. They’ve already lost all chances of improving anyway, and won’t be able to cause many problems!

“On the other hand, the competition offers young Magi more than just glory. The generous rewards and the opportunity to join a guild will surely tempt them! We just need to hand some things out, and it will definitely change the dynamics of their army. We might even be able to pick up some good seedlings! Not bad… not bad at all!”

Logan kept nodding. He, too, knew that pressuring the lower strata was not a good idea, especially in times of war. Prying them apart would lead to a much better ending.

“I’ll go and report your suggestion to the council, they’ll definitely agree!” he did not even bother to hide his excitement, yelling out his agreement.

Meanwhile, Leylin revealed a profound smile. There was something else he had yet to say, but he was sure Logan understood it as well.

Setting up a competition to select Magi and taking them into guilds was also a type of revolution. This was a step in the direction of the setup of the academies on the south coast.

This way, Longbottom’s righteous cause would be wounded in multiple ways. When that happened, it would be the best time to capture and kill him!

At the same time, the various Magi training in Sacred Flame all fell into a stupor. They were all receiving a prophecy.

“Countless stars are congregating there. It is the location of both the beginning and the end of everything!”

Aaron’s eyes recovered from having been all-white, the fear still lingering in him as he patted his chest.

“I actually automatically made a prophecy! Looks like the force of destiny is unprecedentedly powerful.”

“Of course! A competition between genius Magi! Not only wandering Magi, but also geniuses of guilds can also enter. The judges will be the protectors of the four regions who are at least rank 2, and the legendary protector of all regions might even appear!”

In front of him, Vinas rolled her eyes and said sarcastically.

“You-” Aaron was so furious that he turned red, almost getting up.

“Alright, alright. Can you not quarrel!”

Baelin was now wearing his Bio Boosting Armour, his aura more vast and profound as a result of the power of destiny converging on his body. Though he couldn’t feel anything himself, for Aaron and Vinas who trained in Sacred Flame, the change was as obvious as the lighting of a torch in the darkness.

“What did you see?” Baelin asked curiously.

Under his supervision, these two prophetic Magi were currently at peace, having decided to first crush the dark elves’ conspiracy before battling it out among themselves. Sometimes, however, the two would be at odds, which would end up giving him a headache.

“Not too long later, central Twilight Zone will hold a competition for young genius Magi! The only restriction is that one must be younger than 50 to attend.”

“In addition, the champion of the competition will even be able to meet the great protector of all regions and be given access to profound Magi academic knowledge, as well as assistance to advance forcefully.”

Aaron couldn’t help but gulp. Even he was enticed by such temptations.

The young female Magus called Vinas continued, “Most of Twilight Zone’s geniuses will attend, including Longbottom who’s sided with the dark elves. He’ll be waiting to cause trouble!

“And because there’s another Magus like us helping him and covering him with a fog of destiny, I can’t tell for sure what their exact plan is and whether they’ll succeed.”

“Longbottom…” Baelin muttered, his eyes dim.

He knew that this kid that he had thought highly of had quickly become an official Magus and even sided with the dark elves. He’d probably played a big role in the fall of the north.

“I remembered him being a very polite and enthusiastic boy… and his sister…” Baelin’s expression looked complicated. If Leylin had chosen to impart his knowledge to Longbottom, everything would have been different.

Aaron noticed Baelin’s indecision. “Lord Baelin, Longbottom is now a traitor to humanity, a destructive person who is masterminding a rebellion. You need to draw the line, and capture him yourself!” he advised.

“That’s right! I can tell that the large conspiracy in the central region involves many rank 2 Magi, and they will show their strength during the competition. You need to defeat Longbottom there and thwart their plans to save humanity!”

Vinas sounded incomparably resolute. She believed she was now walking the path of ancient heroes and was working hard to protect the harmony and stability of the human race. There was an aura of piety about her.

“I understand…” Baelin smiled wryly.

Somewhere else, Longbottom had also obtained this information from Ernis.

“A competition for young geniuses? A pageant for the Magus world? Many rank 2 Magi and protectors will even appear there as judges?”

Upon hearing this, green light shone out of Longbottom’s eyes, “This truly is a great opportunity to finish everything in one fell swoop!”

Ernis was silent as he felt two powers other than his own in the river of destiny. They would surely meet at the competition.

“Is it finally here? The final victor shall be me! Only I will be able to train in Sacred Flame till the peak and become the ruler of Twilight Zone!”

Ernis roared in his heart, though he looked calm on the outside.

“Send down the orders. All sections are to halt all activities and enter stealth mode, preparing for the upcoming competition. Also, inform the matriarch that I need support. Powerful support!”

Ernis respectfully bowed his way out upon hearing Longbottom’s orders.

Longbottom’s aura had become an enigma. After absorbing the essence of a rank 2 Magus, his strength had soared so high that Ernis could not tell the limits of his strength.

“Leylin, Baelin! Everything shall be settled there!” Longbottom mumbled, and the large phantom spider figure became more solid, as if becoming real.

……

Time passed, and news of the central region holding a competition for young geniuses spread like a hurricane to all four corners.

There was only one requirement for entry; all participants needed to be below 50 years of age. The rewards were very generous; not only were there great amounts of precious resources and research to be won, the top thirty could freely enter a guild of their choice. The large-scaled guilds in the central region all provided a few places, and there was even a small rumour going on that the Guardian of the Realm would meet the champion and take them on as their disciple!

All of Twilight Zone was elated. Many young wandering Magi, and even guild geniuses, all left their stations and headquarters to head to the central region.

Many of them cared little for both the resources and the opportunity to join a guild, but apprenticeship to a rank 3 Magus was a temptation they could not resist.

Leylin expected this.

The plan was accepted as soon as Logan reported it. The Magi of the council were definitely smart enough to see the benefits of such an event. They even decided to make it a recurring thing, to ward off such troubles permanently.

However, even Leylin was initially surprised that the Guardian of the Realm would announce such a thing. It led him to make a few guesses.

“Looks like the Guardian of the Realm doesn’t have much time left. I just don’t know if the inheritance is meant to draw out the malefactors, or is sincere.” Leylin touched his chin.

However, he was very optimistic towards all this. With it, the competition would be even more popular, and work even better for his plans.

Those so-called ‘genius Magi’ probably brought with them forces of destiny. Though they could not be compared with Baelin and Longbottom, when they were all added together, the sum was not something that could be ignored.

Chapter 370: Response and Countermeasure

The dark elves were rather quiet in this period of time.

Although they had managed to take over the north, navigating through territorial disputes with the dwarves and gnomes consumed most of their energy.

Hence, although central Twilight Zone was under immense pressure, the situation seeming dire, all they had to deal with till now were a few scouts and wandering riders.

Balanced on this razor’s edge, the central region had still remained peaceful. The preparations for the competition even made it seem like it was flourishing. As more and more Magi rushed over, it had gained fresh blood and increased strength.

After seeing this, Leylin suspected this was another intention of the war council. They wanted to attract more Magi over to increase their fighting strength

……

In a shady swamp.

A toxic purple fog permeated the place, the rotten sludge concealing the bones of various darkness beasts. Occasionally, a few three-eyed crows would caw as they flew past, which was jarring to the ears.

In a dimly lit cave.

The walls were lined with spells that made them impermeable to the sludge and fog.

A black-haired old man was running his hands through the hair of a young Magus, his touch containing affection. “My child! In the ten years you’ve been here, you’ve learned everything I have to offer. Now, you are free to explore…”

“Gom has brought back some information. The holy land for us Magi, the central region, is holding a competition for young geniuses. Not only can the champion obtain great rewards, they can even meet with the Guardian of the Realm, a rank 3 existence. What’s more, they could even get the opportunity to become his inheritor…”

“A rank 3 Magus?” The youth, who had until then not looked in the least bit serious, suddenly turned solemn.

“Yes. You are the most formidable genius I’ve ever seen, and I believe there are few who can match you in the entirety of Twilight Zone. I believe the victor shall be you, though I’m afraid I won’t get the chance to see it…”

The old man sounded slightly regretful, and his hands halted in mid-air.

His originally smooth and tight skin began to age rapidly, layers of wrinkles forming as if an old branch that had lost all its moisture. His black hair gradually greyed out.

His body withered at a rate that could be seen by the naked eye, ending up a dried corpse.

“Master? MASTER!” The young Magus was dubious as he looked at the master who had always accompanied him.

*Thud!* The old Magus turned into a withered, dried black corpse.

*Poof!* The youth bumped into the Magus’ arm, and the corpse turned to dust in front of his eyes. Ashes spread out, leaving a complete set of Magus robes on the bed.

The young Magus was dazed, and only recovered after a long while.

Even if Magi could manipulate the radiation of energy particles to obtain a longer lifespan than regular humans, there was still a limit.

Even with dangerous modifications to the body, Morning Star Magi could only extend their lifespans by a few decades. It was difficult to succeed, and could cause Magi to end up with a strange, terrifying appearance.

This old Magus’ life energy had been exhausted, and he had reached the end of his life.

Regular rank 1 Magi, those that were not of ancient branches like Warlocks, had 200-year lifespans. This old Magus had lived for a very long time, and had not advanced in his meditation technique. His time was now up.

“Master!” The youth stood there silently, images of the times he spent with his master flashing across his mind. A long while later, he turned and left.

*Rumble!* After he left, the earth caved in, forming a void that allowed the surrounding sludge to enter.

“Master, don’t worry! I will definitely be the glorious victor!” The youth swore to the heavens, and left without hesitation.

As he left, a tear fell from the corner of his eye.

……

“The family’s honour is in your hands.”

In the southern region, in an ancient Magus’ castle.

Dim rays of light fell on a long, rotten table. This black wooden table was about ten metres long, and extended from the head of the hall to the door.

On the tablecloth, there was a silver lampstand and all sorts of fruits and delicacies. A few figures were seated sparsely around it.

The old woman at the master’s seat, who wore a black high-hat and multiple red gems and emerald rings, was giving a young girl a reminder.

She was silent for a while, and then spoke resolutely, “I understand, grandmother.”

Only she knew that, under the cover of luxury, this family was already waning.

The wooden table was already rotten, and the castle had not been repaired for decades. Even their defensive spell formations were deactivated due to a lack of magic crystals. Among the aristocratic Magi, they were basically a joke.

The silver lampstand and delicacies at this table, too, had been gathered with some difficulty. The ornaments on her grandmother’s fingers? Fake trinkets! The originals had long been pawned off.

The girl was silent, knowing that in order to raise a Magus like her, they had paid a large price.

“I’ll definitely become the victor of the young Magus competition and revive the family!” She vowed.

“Good! Let us drink to Lilina’s promise!” The old woman laughed and raised her cup.

“Cheers!” The rest of the relatives all cheered and finished all the alcoholic drinks in their hands. After, they pounced on the delicacies on the table.

Even though they were the descendants of a Magus family, fruits were not things they could have often!

Upon seeing this, the old lady had a bitter expression. This caused Lilina to be even more resolute in her convictions.

……

In the faraway northern region of Twilight Zone.

Groups of human slaves were tied up with thick ropes, and herded towards a city.

There were countless humans, and the one similarity between all of them was the shared expression of despair and numbness.

All of them were originally people of the northern region, but after it was attacked, they lacked the time and strength to move and all turned into slaves.

They would be lucky to be enslaved. Most captives only had one choice, which was to become offerings to the various matriarchs!

At the highest point of a city built in corundum, an absolutely beautiful dark elf maiden was staring on coldly.

“Human’s reproductive ability is too powerful. Their population is tens or even a hundred times ours! How should we rule them? The only way is to kill them until they are fewer than us or to the brink of extinction. Then we wouldn’t have to worry about any instability.”

A command that was cold, detached and inhuman was produced from her lips.

Behind her, elite dark elven secret guards drew back respectfully and passed down the order, resulting in the formation of a red sea.

What was more terrifying was that the corpses of these humans would be recycled to be used as army provisions for the gnomes, dwarves and even dark elves!

“How is it going with the Underground Winter Spider Emperor?” She asked indifferently.

“Through investigations, we can confirm that the mother body is not dead, and we’ve also appeased our elite knights. However, in the holy land, the disappearance of the mother body’s aura is still causing a disturbance amongst the Underground Winter Spiders.”

Another matriarch with a gold crown on her head in black leather revealed a great amount of skin as she bowed and reported.

“Trash!” A cold glint flashed in the maiden’s eyes, “Sacrifice the original head guard of the holy land!”

“Yes!” The icy intent behind those words caused the matriarch behind her to quiver.

“That mere human dares profane the holy land of us dark elves? We need to use his flesh and soul to scrub off this humiliation!” The maiden vowed.

“My lord, here is the newest intelligence from Longbottom!”

At this moment, the door opened. A dark elf shrouded in translucent black muslin held a brass circular cylinder and knelt, offering it to the maiden with both hands.

The girl laughed slightly, and a slight wind blew the cylinder over to her hands.

After seeing the letter, she bit her lips, her reddened lip providing a stark contrast to her pale skin, causing the guards around her to gulp.

“A genius competition in the central region?” She muttered to herself again and then ordered, “Gather the matriarchs. I to convene a meeting of Dark Nobility!”

She felt that this was a turning point that could give her the chance to take care of the Magi in the central region in one go.

However, she had a sense of extreme danger from the will of the darkness.

After pondering over this for a long while, the maiden sighed and decided to put this question up for discussion.

……

After news of the genius competition spread, the entirety of Twilight Zone and even the surrounding dark elven, gnome and dwarven empires all responded to the news.

All sorts of Magi, regardless of race, hurried towards the central region.

In that moment, there really seemed to be a sense of instability.

Leylin, who was meanwhile waiting for the fish to bite, patiently waited for the competition to begin. As he had been the person to suggest this and was plenty strong himself, he was able to get a position as a judge.

As for the people in Nature’s Alliance? All of them had been sent off on miscellaneous missions.

As Leylin’s number one subordinate, Iren was nowhere to be found every day, and nobody knew what Leylin had ordered him to do.

Chapter 372: Fire Scorpion

Luckily for Leylin and the other judges, they were rank 2 Magi and had a very high status. Even if they were discontent, the audience did not dare show this on their faces, and instead placed their attention on the competition going on.

Leylin’s eyes brightened at this moment.

Following his gaze, there appeared a person he was interested in on an elevated stage at the southeast corner.

“Arena 34, the fifth round of the selection! Here are participant numbers 273 and 35!” The announcer was a peak rank 1 Magus dressed in formal Magus attire, his hair perfectly combed.

Almost at the very moment his words ended, a line of fire flashed, and a beautiful woman with a great body arrived at the centre of the stage.

This female Magus had voluptuous, sexy curves and had intentionally worn tight clothing, her chest bursting out of the seams of her clothes. However, she looked a little young, as if she had yet to be of age.

This angelic appearance and devilish, arousing body immediately garnered the interest of the audience.

“Oh, I remember now! She’s Fire Scorpion of the western region. She actually came here!” A Magus blurted out, and through many layers, the voice entered Leylin’s ears.

“Fire Scorpion?” Leylin was slightly flabbergasted at this nickname.

“Haha, has Magus Leylin gone to the western region before?” Also on the platform, a rank 2 Magus laughed after hearing Leylin’s voice.

He had a white cloth wrapped around his head and his pupils were blue. This was the typical style of the western region in Twilight Zone.

This Magus was the leader of a large-scale guild in the western region.

Though the central region was the main essence of Twilight Zone with many highly-ranked Magi, they could not take up all the spots for judging. It was necessary to hand out a part of the seats to Magi of the four other regions.

“Fire Scorpion is rather famous at our side, and it’s said she’s rather ruthless. She even killed a few of her husbands, which earned her nickname as the Fire Scorpion!”

Without waiting for Leylin’s answer, the rank 2 Magus continued, “Actually, if not for her specializing in fire magic, we would definitely call her the black widow!”

“No, I just hear about her occasionally.” Leylin shook his head.

What he was focusing on was not Fire Scorpion, but her opponent.

With the impatient looks of the judges on the platform, the opponent who was late had opened up a route for himself and entered the arena.

This was a youth in green Magus robes, a sinister look in his eyes.

“Hmm, this youth?”

Before Leylin could speak, the rank 2 Magus was already surprised.

“What is it? Do you know him?” Leylin asked with a smile.

“Yes! The Magus in green robes is another formidable character known in the western region— Green-robed Carl. How unexpected that they’re matched together in the first round!”

The rank 2 Magus also from the western region sighed lightly, as if finding it a pity that these two geniuses were matched so early.

”Green-robed Carl?” Leylin was laughing inside.

Rank 2 Magi were very sensitive to auras. Whoever they met with, if left with a deep impression or memorable aura, the next time they met, it would be difficult for the other parties to conceal themselves.

For this reason, the Magus was confident in his judgment.

However, through his mole, Ernis, Leylin spied on his opponent.

Yes. This Green-robed Carl was, in reality, Longbottom in disguise.

Through the lingering spirit in the notebook in Ernis’ hands, Leylin had watched in high definition the real Green-robed Carl being killed by them. He watched as they then skinned the man and, using special musical means, used it to transform Longbottom’s appearance.

What was even more wonderful was that Ernis had no idea that he was unwittingly leaking information while he was hell-bent on working for the dark elves. Hence, for any spells that could sense and test one’s thoughts, there was no reaction at all, which allowed him to survive.

At this moment, the A.I. Chip sounded.

[Skin Covering spell model has been completely analysed. Inputting into rank 1 spell model database!]

This Skin Covering spell was what Longbottom used to deceive everyone. Though it was only at rank 1, mysteriously it was able to trick even rank 2 Magi.

In addition, this spell did not originate from Twilight Zone, but rather, from a hidden inheritance of the dark elves. No Magi would expect this.

It was a pity that Leylin knew this beforehand, which caused their hard work to be in vain.

Even this spell model had been intercepted and taken by Leylin in secret and, with the A.I. Chip, completed.

If Longbottom knew this, he might really spew out blood.

Leylin had a sick interest in this but held it in.

Sometimes, the fruits of victory would taste better when waited for.

“Who do you think has the larger possibility of winning?” All these thoughts passed through Leylin’s mind, but he still continued the conversation with the rank 2 Magus.

“Hm…” The rank 2 Magus muttered to himself and decided, “Though Carl’s corrosive spells are renowned, and he possesses a middle-grade magic artifact, Fire Scorpion is a decade older and thus, has accumulated a decade more of experience. In addition, fire energy particles are capable of restraining corrosive-type energy particles, which is very remarkable.”

“I think differently. Perhaps that kid called Carl can really create miracles!” Leylin laughed lightly.

“Oh? Can you tell me the reason?” The old Magus looked interested.

“About that, please let me keep it a secret.” Leylin rejected with a slight smile.

“You…” The old Magus laughed as well, but gave more attention to arena 34.

Meanwhile, Longbottom who had transformed into Green-robed Carl, was feeling terrified. “Damn it, a rank 2 Magus’ gaze swept this location quite a few times. What is it that piqued their interest?”

He quickly considered, “I previously gained much information regarding Carl’s habits, and I’ve even secretly grasped his signature spells. The Skin Covering spell shouldn’t have an issue, so what went wrong?”

“No, it’s possible that there’s nothing wrong. It’s just that my battle with Fire Scorpion has attracted their attention! After all, this is still the start. It’s very rare that two official Magi get matched together at the start.”

Longbottom racked his brains, considering it from all angles. If Longbottom knew everything had happened only because of Leylin’s sick sense of humour, he might really get so mad that he would collapse.

This careless attitude of his had obviously enraged the opposing Fire Scorpion.

“Carl, you dare underestimate me! I’ll make you pay the price!”

Fire Scorpion was so furious that her face was flushed red, her chest quivering and shaking her breasts, which caused the surrounding Magi to hiss in excitement.

“Fire Scorpion!” Fire Scorpion shouted under her breath, and quickly began to chant in broken sentences and syllables.

Traces of bright red energy particles converged, forming large numbers of little scorpions crawling out from the ground and surrounding Longbottom.

“Rain of Corrosion!” Longbottom chanted in a low voice.

Droplets of green rain fell from mid-air, and every time the droplets made contact with the ground, a faint sizzling sound of corrosion could be heard even as white gases were being formed.

After the white gas disappeared, a deep hole was seen on the ground.

Those fire scorpions were even more pitiful. Clustered raindrops were inclined towards them, and in no time, they had all turned into a pool of pus-like liquid.

“It’s appeared! Green-robed Carl’s Rain of Corrosion! It’s an omnidirectional attack with no dead angles, with an offensive power of up to 40 degrees!” A Magus of the western region who had his head wrapped shouted excitedly.

Whether it was the corrosive raindrops or the fire red scorpions, the moment they reached the boundaries of the elevated stage, they would immediately fall apart due to the layer with translucent defensive ripples, turning into pure energy particles and being absorbed into the spell formation.

This was a defensive and absorption spell formation that was set up under every stage to limit the damage range to within the stage.

“Flames of Rebirth!” At this moment, Fire Scorpion’s expression showed her confidence in prevailing.

With her chants, a blue fireball suddenly appeared and exploded in front of her. The small blue flames dispersed like starlight and fell into the liquid on the ground.

*Rumble! Rumble! Rumble!* Like flower petals, blue flames blossomed on the ground, and fire scorpions crawled out once more, spitting threads of fire.

“Rain of corrosion!” Longbottom yelled once again, corrosive raindrops falling.

“It’s useless!” Fire Scorpion shot out a spark and revived the red scorpions that had fallen.

“I have more spiritual force than you, and the spell ‘Flames of Rebirth’ absorb 50% of the energy I’ve expended from using spells. With such a fierce consumption in our competition, you’re definitely not a match for me!”

Fire Scorpion attacked and did not forget to hurt her opponent’s morale with her words.

“Damn it!” With the increase in red scorpions, Longbottom’s activity scope had been reduced to a corner of the stage, and he looked about to fall off.

“If I didn’t have to worry about those rank 2 Magi, I would use my true strength! With just one hand, I can drain you till you become a dried-up corpse!”

Longbottom thought mercilessly. “I can only use that.”

He punched his hand deep into the ground, and traces of black liquid appeared from within his arm and entered the surface of the ground.

“Gushing Dark Springs!” A black corrosive fluid first appeared under Longbottom’s fist, spreading in all directions like a ripple.

The red scorpions were drowned by the black fluid.

Though Fire Scorpion was expending all her effort on employing ‘rebirth of the flames’, the fire scorpions that were resurrected were still swallowed up by the black spring.

After seeing this, Fire Scorpion turned deathly pale.

Finally, the moment the black fluid was about to cover her body, she raised her right arm, “I admit defeat!”

“Hmph!” Seeing this, Longbottom had to give up all thoughts of pursuing the matter despite his unwillingness to do so.

Chapter 373: Finals in the Secret Plane

“He actually used up all his spiritual force and formed a corrosive attack able to cover the entire area of the stage!”

The old Magus beside Leylin was astonished as he touched his beard, “Looks like Carl has improved quite a bit! It’s a pity that with this method, too much spiritual force is consumed. He’s destined not to succeed in the next selection battle!”

“That might not be so,” Leylin laughed and pointed in a direction, “Look!”

“Oh?” This rank 2 Magus looked in that direction and laughed, “He actually used a precious spiritual force restoring potion? Such a thing could save his life at a crucial moment!”

In a corner, Longbottom’s hands trembled and he almost flung out his potion bottles.

“Again! Again!” His expression darkened.

Leylin snickered in his heart. His own gaze was now at a stage where Longbottom could not discover it, so he constantly directed the attention of the rank 2 Magi beside him to the fellow, causing him a lot of stress.

Having teased him enough, Leylin did not want to shoot himself in the foot and directed the attention of the rank 2 Magi away. “By the way, are you interested in visiting my laboratory after the competition ends? Nature’s Alliance’s special fish is somewhat effective for rank 2 Magi…”

At another end, Longbottom sighed, “Then again, Green-robed Carl’s original strength loses out to that of Fire Scorpion. Though I tried to conceal it, I still attracted attention. I’ll need to be more careful in the future…”

“My apologies, please let me pass!” At this moment, a Magus squeezed in, looking hurried.

“What are you doing?” Longbottom pushed the other person away.

The two were suddenly caught in a daze.

Though they had disguised themselves, Longbottom was still able to recognise Baelin at first glance, while Baelin had also recognised his former buddy.

The two of them stared at each other, but because of some unspeakable reasons on both ends, they silently swallowed their words. They did not attempt to expose each other’s identities.

“Number 188! Number 188!” At another end of the stage, the judge was starting to get impatient.

Baelin’s body trembled and he hurried on. “I will stop you!” he said softly when passing Longbottom.

“I’ll wait and see!” was the immediate reply.

As match after match went on, a few geniuses made a name for themselves, resulting in the adulation of the audience.

Leylin had also picked out a few people. “Lilina from the western region, Haylon of the voodoo marshes, and then Baelin as well as Longbottom and their friends and subordinates will take up the top few spots in this genius Magi competition.”

With his knowledge as a rank 2 Warlock, he easily found those so-called ‘geniuses’.

Usually, these geniuses would be considered the ‘main characters’ of the era and were important figures in history. However, such influence was nothing compared to Leylin!

“The champion should be either Baelin or Longbottom.” Leylin concluded.

“They really are the converging point of Twilight Zone’s forces of destiny. Their strength has risen by so much, and I believe these two have even touched the boundary of the rank 2 realm.”

Leylin sighed in awe. With this rate of improvement, even Aaron and the other ‘fake’ geniuses he had made with his grandpas, leave alone Lilina and Haylon, were left in the dust.

The preliminaries were very quick.

By nightfall, about half out of the numerous contestants who had signed up had been eliminated. Numerous Magi became familiar with some of the great battles here, and some were even turned into videos and supplied to large-scale guilds to pick from.

Baelin and Longbottom, as well as the other contestants that Leylin had thought highly of, had not failed their missions. They passed through the preliminaries, and even earned themselves a reputation.

Amongst the Magi at the competition area, they had become somewhat famous.

“Haylon!” “Lilina!” Carl!” and the like finally reached the ears of rank 2 Magi.

……

“The forces of destiny have converged further!”

While resting that day, Leylin proceeded to a luxurious room that was especially prepared for him and looked out the window at the sky.

In this short period of rest, many events were unfolding.

In a contestant’s room, a few black-robed Magi were threatening Haylon from the voodoo marshes, “If you see our young master tomorrow, you must forfeit! If not…”

“Scram!” Haylon raised his eyebrows.

“What did you say?” The few Magi were instantly enraged.

“I told you to scram! Didn’t you hear clearly?” Haylon stood up, his eyes now completely red.

Black and red rays of magic exploded from his body.

“There are Magi from large-scaled guilds monitoring this area. You dare-”

These Magi evidently did not expect him to be so stubborn and irritable. The moment there was a difference in opinion, he attacked without hesitation.

*Rumble!*

Several rays of magic burst in the rooms, the stray ripples surging and shaking the surrounding walls till they turned to powder.

“What’s going on?” A group of Magi wearing the patrolling uniform rushed over. They represented the dignity of the organisers and were backed by many rank 2 Magi. Since they had such powerful backers, they naturally confident.

The few black-robed Magi exchanged glances and everyone saw the helplessness in their eyes, “Please!”

Meanwhile, they had a deep hatred for this person who was ruining their plans and could not understand the situation.

The youth seemed to sense something and gazed into the distance, revealing for the first time a hint of grief within.

“Seizing the championship is Master’s dying wish. Anyone hindering me from achieving it will die!”

……

Under the dim yellow light, Lilina looked at a blue pearl in her hands, seeming undecided.

The light blue pearl was smooth, round and beautiful, with little flecks of gold that formed the image of a palm at the heart of the pearl.

This was the last treasure of her family. However, it also held within it horrific side effects, which was why Lilina was feeling hesitant.

She then thought about the sacrifice of her family, and their current condition.

Though their family was a Magus family, resources were not so easily obtained in the Magus World. With all hopes of revival left to her, her shoulders were weighed down by far too much pressure.

“I must become the champion and lead my family on the road to revival!” Her expression turning resolute under the lights, she pressed the blue pearl to her forehead.

*Sssii!* The pearl merged into her forehead.

A smear of deep blue began to flicker on Lilina’s body.

……

“My lady!” Longbottom removed his disguise and gazed at the human figure within the black mist, kneeling deferentially.

“En! Little Longbottom, though you are beginning to carve your own route and have almost reached rank 2, the accumulation that happens with time cannot be overcome so easily.” A charming female voice sounded from within the black mist.

“I will now condense all the life force essence of my race onto you in order to help your Life Absorption meditation technique truly break through to the second level.”

“Many thanks, my lady!” Longbottom looked ecstatic.

In his mind, he instantly recalled the figure sitting on the platform. “I’ve finally, finally caught up to you! I really want to see the expression you’ll have on your face… Leylin!”

……

“What are you thinking about?”

Aaron watched Baelin, who was standing aside.

“No… It’s nothing. I saw Longbottom, and he’s changed so much…” Baelin sighed, looking worried.

“Listen to me, Baelin! Longbottom has now completely sided with the dark elves and will cause bring chaos to the human race. Your mission is to stop him. You cannot forget this!” The expression on Aaron’s face became serious.

“Yes, I will stop him!” Baelin repeated, strengthening his tone of voice.

Days later.

With the Eternal Light spell as well as strength of the Sun Stones, the area was illuminated.

A Magus wearing the attire of a host first bowed towards the platform, and then announced the schedule for the competition.

“All of you are the best who have gone through round after round of selection! A victor will appear amongst you today, and the top thirty will have the opportunity to choose a guild to enter! This includes any large-scaled guilds…”

The moment these words left the host’s mouth, the area was filled with an uproar.

The hundred or so remaining contestants’ eyes revealed different emotions. There was passion, contemplation and excitement.

*Cough!* The host coughed lightly, and the area fell silent.

“The competition shall be held here!” He pointed at the stage right in the centre.

A giant spell formation had been set up atop the stage, while crimson runes were spread around. They emanated a strange light that caused one to shudder in fear.

“The finals of the competition will be held in a secret plane. You will be sent to a random location in the secret plane, and there is only one way to win. Defeat your opponents and obtain the points on their amulet!”

The host raised a milky-white amulet that was only the size of a finger with a simple number written on it.

“In the secret plane, there are no rules. Besieges and usage of external items is allowed.”

“I would like to remind all of you that even though we will install a spell pattern that will teleport you out the moment you are at the brink of death, there are always accidents. Hence, there is the real possibility of death in the secret plane, and I want you to consider this carefully.”

The host spoke indifferently, and a bloody smell assaulted the nostrils. Baelin was surprised. With this lack of rules, it was easy to slip up. Even with the aid, it would be difficult to keep one’s life.

After all, the mysteriousness of magic could not be surmised by the regular person. Perhaps there were methods that could forcefully break the life-saving methods the organisers had set up and cause a large number of deaths.

Chapter 375: Teaming Up

Leylin turned his attention to another screen.

In the sky above a verdant forest, Longbottom, disguised as Green-robed Carl, had run into Haylon.

These were two favoured dark horses had a large possibility of gaining victory. This immediately attracted attention.

Many contestants had already been eliminated in a short period of time. With fewer participants remaining, the remaining screens had increased in size.

……

Within the secret plane.

“Green-robed Carl?” Haylon glanced at the strange youngster in front of him.

“I’d originally wanted to skip the trouble of defeating you guys one by one, and had decided to wait to make a move and harvest a large number of points at once, but forget it. I’ll make an exception for you and take your point right away.”

Longbottom looked at Haylon in front of him, a sinister smile on his face. Now that he was getting closer to the goal, he did not have to disguise himself so carefully. His opponent’s identity as a genius made Longbottom, who had been born a commoner, feel a sense of disgust.

“You seem to hate me?” Haylon’s brows furrowed, “It’s alright, anyone who obstructs my path shall die anyway!”

“Jeje, who do you think you are!” Longbottom laughed weirdly, and released part of the bindings on him.

Cold! Powerful!

A berserk wave of spiritual force swept across like a hurricane.

“Peak rank 1?” Haylon’s expression that had always been as cold as ice was immediately smashed through.

Longbottom’s ‘burst’ had also caused a frenzy outside the plane.

“Peak rank 1? I remember Green-robed Carl is only forty-five years old, right?” A judge wearing reading glasses asked a Magus behind him, “Fano, when did you reach the level you’re at?”

The Magus by the name of Fano was an old geezer with a white beard. He looked ashamed as he spoke, “Your subordinate is ashamed. After training hard on the Icy Throne for 70 years, I reached this realm at 115 years old.”

“If he studied on his own, this Carl really is a genius!” This judge raised his spectacles, “Run checks on him. If there’s nothing wrong, we can consider enticing him into entering our guild.”

Leylin, who was also on the judge panel, saw that many of the other judges had sent down the same order and couldn’t help but laugh inside.

If this was a few days ago, they might be able to find out about Longbottom, but now? By the time they had run their checks, Longbottom might already have achieved his goal. What use was it then if they found out?

”You’re already at the peak of rank 1!” Haylon blurted out, unable to maintain his indifference any longer.

“This is the expression! This is the expression!” Longbottom chuckled aloud, “I want those people who look down on me to realise how wrong they are!”

He laughed crazily, flushing red as if he were sick.

“You’re crazy!” Haylon’s voice became cold, and large numbers of silver-white light blades appeared from his robes, swirling in formation.

“Go!” Haylon pointed at Longbottom, and the many light blades formed a dense mesh and tried to pull Longbottom in. Meanwhile, he turned into a black shadow and disappeared into the sky.

“You overestimate yourself!” Longbottom snorted coldly, a layer of green mist surging forth.

*Tss tss!* Great numbers of silver-white light blades entered the mist and immediately produced sounds of corrosion, dissipating one by one.

“Come here!” Longbottom’s right hand became a phantom image and reached deep into the air.

Next, a black shadow was pulled out from the surrounding space.

Haylon’s expression was that of disbelief. “That’s impossible. This concealing technique is my master’s special technique! How could it…”

“That strong aura of life on you betrayed you!” Longbottom explained, his expression showing his disdain.

Meanwhile, Haylon went limp, as if this was a huge blow to him.

“Kid, you’re very luckily. If we’d met earlier, you’d long since have turned into a corpse, but now?” Longbottom halted his intentions of using Life Absorption and turning him into a dried-up corpse.

This was still within the secret plane, and he was being monitored by the Magi outside.

If he hid his true strength, he could pass it off as being exceptionally talented or having gained some inheritance. Whatever it was, Twilight Zone was huge and it was no surprise to have some fortuitous encounters.

However, Life absorption was a dark-elven meditation technique. If it was exposed, the competition would be halted, and he would be faced with several rank 2 Magi who would combine their efforts to kill him.

“But I really don’t want to just let you off!” While lifting Haylon, a smile appeared about Longbottom’s lips.

This smile was enough for Haylon’s hair to be raised, and he immediately thought of using the spell pattern for escape. However, it was too late!

A green light sword ripped through Haylon’s forehead, and with the corrosive force invading, he could only cry out miserably.

“Ah…” Amidst the painful screams, Haylon’s body was bound in light pillars and transported out.

Longbottom took out his own amulet and saw the number rapidly rise to thirty, and revealed a satisfied expression. After closing his eyes for a short while, he began to hurry towards another location.

*Thud!* Outside the secret plane, Haylon’s body fell to the ground, large amounts of black blood flowing out of his orifices.

“His mind has been damaged! Quick, get Master Dojek here!” The healing Magus who came over took a look and quickly shook his head.

A moment later, Dojek narrated something to Leylin and the other committee members at the judging area.

“His sea of consciousness has been destroyed? There’s no cure?”

“Yes, Haylon’s sea of consciousness has completely been destroyed by a corrosive spiritual force. There is no way to restore it. At most, I can only save his life. From hereon, he can only live on as a commoner…”

Dojek’s expression was dim. Haylon truly was a genius, but he had not realised that no matter how amazing the genius, they could fall before they truly matured.

However, his long life had allowed him to experience much, and with a sigh, he left.

Leylin and the committee members had a brief exchange regarding the issue, before they promptly tossed this matter to the back of their minds.

The final competition carried the risk of death! Just crippling a Magus wasn’t much.

What they were more interested in were the methods Longbottom had used to heavily injure Haylon before he had been transported out.

“It seems to be a combination spell. By instantly transmitting large amounts of energy particles to destroy the composition of the sea of consciousness…”

There was a flash in Leylin’s eyes.

He felt that after large numbers of geniuses had fallen in this competition, the force of destiny shrouding the area had become richer till the extreme.

The surging river of destiny was like a giant gunpowder warehouse. With just a little spark, it would explode violently.

“I didn’t expect the three of them to meet. Time for a good show!”

Right after, Leylin realised something else and changed his focus to a screen at a corner.

“Based on the guide of destiny!”

Three voices sounded in unison, with both male and female voices.

Aaron, Vinas, and Ernis who were all training in Sacred Flame, the geniuses Leylin had created himself, finally came together.

If anyone had been focusing on these three Magi, they would realise that after entering the secret plane, they had not fought with any Magi and instead, had been hurrying forward.

Just as they were about to encounter enemies, they could predict and evade them.

Hence, the three somehow passed through half of the secret plane and met at a corner on the plains.

“It’s the first time we’re meeting in real life! I’ll introduce myself. My name is Ernis!” There was a smile on Ernis’ face. His gaze swept past Vinas and Aaron, and stayed on Aaron’s ring and Vinas’ multi-coloured necklace for a long while.

“Aaron!” “Vinas!”

“Are you going to repent for all you have done?” Aaron asked, standing with Vinas.

Though they were competing against each other, he and Vinas were on the humans’ side, and had no good feelings towards Ernis of the dark elven camp.

“I’m just used to looking at issues from a different point of view!” Ernis laughed, obviously not wanting to say more.

After all, there was a large group of Magi watching. How could he expose himself?

“Then die!”

Just a moment before, they had speaking nicely, and in the next, Aaron immediately became hostile and attacked.

A silver cross blade hilt appeared in his hands, and was only a third as long as a regular cross blade. It had lost its sword blade and point, but a sharp energy fluctuation burst out from it.

A ray of light streaked through the air, bringing about with it numerous ripples and aimed at Ernis.

Ernis seemed to have predicted it and dodged, looking delighted at the sword hilt in Aaron’s hands.

“So you’ve forged it too! I won’t have to conceal anything anymore.”

A silver-white slender long sword tip appeared in front of Ernis. The sharpness it emanated was even above that of Aaron’s attack.

“Go!” Ernis pointed at Aaron, and great amounts of silver light shot out from the tip of the blade.

Formless ripples collided with the silver light and quickly dispersed, as if nothing had happened.

However, the surrounding grass had become much shorter, cut through smoothly as if it had been sliced through in that instance by some light.

“This is it. All devious plots are useless to us. All we can depend on is solely strength to fight it out!”

Ernis yelled, his sword tip flying into his hands and shooting out great amounts of light.

Seeing this, Vinas sighed and retrieved a silver-white sword blade from behind her back and besieged Ernis with Aaron.

“Hmm?”

The Magi outside suddenly made sounds of astonishment.

“These three middle-grade magic artifacts have reached the peak. Also, why does it feel like the sword hilt, sword blade and sword tip can be combined to create a magic artifact with more power?”

Chapter 377: The Conspiracy Unravelling

”Ripple of corrosion!”

A green circular ripple immediately appeared before Longbottom, and shook continuously, as if it was trying to push Baelin out.

However, Baelin’s face remained composed, and from his blade large amounts of vertical eye phantoms appeared.

”Bio Boosting armour and sword!”

The sword with the vertical eye phantom gave off rays of flames, and evaporated all the green ripples. With indomitable strength, it directly targeted Longbottom’s right chest.

Blood flowed through the corner of Longbottom’s mouth, and a long wound opened up on his chest. He flew through the air, and landed on the ground, giving rise to a long trail of blood.

*Boom!* The many soil layers behind him had piled up into a small mountain, and had finally offset the inertia in Longbottom’s body, which had caused him to be unable to stop.

”You lost!” Baelin landed calmly in front of Longbottom, his emotions complex. There was no visible hint of joy or victory in his expression.

”I lost!” Immediately, Longbottom’s face registered his defeat.

*Cough!* He violently coughed out a mouthful of fresh blood: “Bro… Brother Baelin, I have some things regarding my sister that I wish to talk to you about!”

”What about your sister?” Having heard Longbottom’s familiar address, Baelin’s heart softened. Moreover, Longbottom’s sister was his first love!

Baelin could not help but lower his body.

”My sister, she… she…” Longbottom’s voice gradually became softer, which caused Baelin to get closer to him.

”She wants you to die!” After seeing that situation, a hint of a maniacal smile flashed across Longbottom’s face, and a crystal in his hands was launched like a lightning bolt.

”Not good!”

Baelin’s eyes widened, and he unceasingly flew backwards, his Bio Boosting armour continuously adding layers of defense.

But it was too late. A grey ray of lightning detonated in front of Baelin’s chest, and smashed the milk-white talisman.

*Boom!* A pillar of light enveloped Baelin, and caused him to disappear from the secret plane in an instant.

*Crash! Bang!*

Baelin’s figure appeared at the site of the competition, his face still registering shock and grief. He looked at the charred area above his chest and remained silent.

”Haha! Even though the tactics weren’t entirely legitimate, at least I won!” The Magus from the west, who had bet against Leylin, immediately laughed loudly.

”That’s right! You won!” Magi were not knights, and did not have to conform to a code of honour. Even though Longbottom’s tactics were overboard, and he used whatever he could to obtain success, he was undoubtedly the champion! Leylin naturally had to recognise this point.

What was more important was that there was nothing wagered on this. To concede defeat was nothing much.

Leylin’s attitude actually caused these Magi to feel embarrassed.

”Actually, the Magus that you thought highly of was strong too. Not only has he reached the level of a peak rank 1 Magus, he is walking the ancient path of the Bio Booster. If I am right, his armour was inherited from at least an ancient rank 2 Bio Booster. If we were to compare their true strengths, he would still surpass Carl”

”En!” Leylin nodded outwardly, but he did not agree with the claim.

Even though Baelin was strong, Longbottom was not a person to be provoked. A son of destiny just like Baelin, his most terrifying dark elven meditation technique and other secret cards had not been revealed.

Of course, both of them had suppressed themselves for the sake of the Magi who were watching, and Baelin himself had concealed his trump card, the Underground Winter Spider Emperor. Were the two to have battled without considering the consequences, both parties would have equal chances of winning.

By now, Longbottom had finished off the remaining few Magi in the secret plane, dominating his opponents, and the host announced loudly, ”The champion has already emerged. He is Green-robed Carl from the west! Let us cheer for him!”

”Carl!” “Carl!” “Carl!””

The Magi present instantly let out cheers of happiness, and welcomed Longbottom.

”What are we to do? Should we openly reveal his identity in public?” Aaron secretly communicated with Baelin.

”No! Not at all! He threatened me earlier on. Should we do so, he will immediately initiate his plot and bring huge amounts of casualties to the Magi present. Before we clearly understand what he’s planning, it would be best not to do so!”

Baelin hesitated, and was seemingly indecisive.

Regardless of how they were communicating secretly, the process of the competition had been advancing bit by bit.

”Now, may we invite our champion and the other 30 Magi on stage, for our 9 most distinguished and high-ranked judges to give out the prizes…”

Along with the host’s voice and cheers, a stage decorated with gold and silver, bedazzled with numerous rays started rising slowly from the middle of the site.

Other than Baelin, Longbottom, and a few other Magi who held other intentions, the 30 Magi who had obtained a high enough score walked up to the stage emotionally.

To them, this was the pathway to fame, the glorious road to success.

”Let’s go. They are actually having us present prizes to them! What a bother, couldn’t they just have passed down the prizes?” A rank 2 Magus from the west complained to Leylin.

”This is actually the important stage where budding Magi obtain credit due to their ambitions. Even though it’s only a ceremony, it still has to be done!”

Leylin smiled and got up, and went to the golden stage together with the other rank 2 Magi.

”I, Victory, rank 2 Magus and guild leader of Glorious Sword, solemnly announce that this Magus from the west is the champion of this season’s young genius talent competition!”

The rank 2 Magus standing in the middle announced, at the same time placing on Longbottom a golden crown encrusted with gems.

”Carl!” “Carl!” “Carl!”

Many Magi were cheering, and bouts of cheers got overpowered by other bouts of cheers.

”Other than obtaining the reward previously, Carl, you have the opportunity to choose a guild to enter! What is your choice?”

Victory had high hopes for Carl, and hence in his voice held a tinge of excitement and pressure, as well as feelings of enticement.

”My choice is obviously…”

Longbottom deliberately hesitated a while and then said, “It’s obviously the Dark Elves, you idiots!”

”What?” The jaws of numerous Magi dropped open. They all thought they’d heard wrong.

”Not good, we have been cheated by him!” On the other side, Baelin’s face immediately changed, the armour on his body once again surfaced. He had wanted to rush over, but unfortunately, it was already too late.

”Mud membrane!”

A layer of clay-coloured invisible film surfaced from Longbottom’s body, with 9 rays of lights shooting out of his body, directly shooting at the 9 rank 2 Magi judges on the stage who had no time to dodge the attack.

*Kacha! Kacha!*

A deep blue ice layer immediately spread out on their body, and caused all 9 Magi to freeze into ice sculptures.

In the ice sculptures, the numerous rank 2 Magi had life-like expressions of anger or fear.

This sudden change had shocked all the Magi present at the site.

”Longbottom! What are you doing! Release Master Leylin now!”

Baelin suppressed the rage within, having seen the ice sculpture of the already frozen Leylin. He had originally wanted to undo his pretense here and give Master Leylin a big surprise!

Furthermore, from the bottom of Baelin’s heart, he respected Leylin and had treated him like a teacher. Having seen Longbottom’s actions, he instantly felt anger.

”Carl! What are you doing!” The face of the host on the stage instantly became more solemn, a ray of a peak rank 1 energy wave imploded from his body.

*Boom! Boom!*

2 rays of spells attacked the surface of an ice sculpture, yet it was entirely useless, and could not leave any traces on the crystal clear surface of the ice sculpture.

”There’s no use, the matriarchs of the dark elves used one thousand years to extract this essence of the cold abyss. Even rank 2 Magi cannot be able to overcome it…” Longbottom’s voice was unhurried.

”As for Leylin? I’ve wanted to kill him for so long! And now, he is finally in my hands. Do you reckon I would easily let this opportunity go by? Haha…”

Presently, Longbottom had removed all restrictions, and laughed hysterically.

*Boom!* A light ray flashed across, Longbottom removed the skin alteration spell on his body, and recovered his original appearance. At the same time, a strong and enormous energy was released from his body like the surging waves of the ocean.

”And this noisy crow, I’ve borne with you long enough!”

Longbottom lifted his hands and a dark silver spiritual strength exploded. The body of the host, not having time to react, exploded into a rain of flesh.

The Magi standing on the stage immediately retreated, with one of them shouting out, ”Solidified spiritual force! Rank 2 Magus!”

”This is the leader of the revolutionary army, Longbottom! I saw his face in a picture once!”

”It’s already too late. Attack!” Longbottom shouted.

*Swish! Swish!* Numerous shadows appeared all around the competition site, all tearing apart magic scrolls.

Dark clouds instantly enshrouded the area, and large numbers of tiny spiders were shot out of the dark clouds. The spiders spat out threads continuously, binding up the entire area in a short duration.

From a distance, the competition site that was enshrouded by a white silk wall looked like a giant cocoon.

Baelin’s face dimmed, and the aura on his body exploded forth. He treated Longbottom as a rival. “So your target was not only the 9 judges but also all the Magi in this competition site!”

He was secretly shocked. Around 20% of the elite Magi of Twilight Zone were present at the scene, and if they were to all die here, it would be a terrifying blow to the humans.

”Kill!” At this point in time, the black-clothed men hiding amongst the crowd immediately took action, and many more spiders drilled their way through the cocoons, surrounding and attacking the human magicians.

Large amounts of silk wove together into a formation, weakening the human Magi while channeling the strength to their opponents. Immediately, lights flashed and explosions occurred everywhere.

The obstruction made it impossible for the human Magi to escape. Some Magi, eyes turned red, fired off spells in all directions, adding further to the chaos.

Chapter 378: Channelling of Lifeforce

“These aren’t just the people of the revolutionary army!” Baelin stared at the many black-robed Magi and his expression darkened.

“Haha… Of course!” At this moment, Longbottom had no more qualms. “The matriarchs of the dark elves have already infiltrated this area. Not long after, blood will flow, and the dark elves will rule the subterranean world!”

Longbottom’s face was slightly flushed.

“You lunatic!” Baelin roared, and charged at Longbottom.

“Life Absorption!”

Longbottom shouted, and a large phantom image of a spider appeared behind him.

Compared to the last few times, the image had become even larger and even held a terrifying aura. From the eyes of the spider, a very human light could be seen, as if it now held an intelligence of its own and had now become alive.

“Aru!” Baelin whistled for a while, and a gold phantom darted out from within a small crack amongst the spectators and dropped to the ground. Its figure suddenly increased in size, and in the blink of an eye, it was two stories tall.

This was a giant, golden Underground Winter Spider. The stripes on its body gave it a very elegant feeling, and the phantom image on Longbottom’s back kept snarling, as if its honour was being challenged.

“Underground Winter Spider Emperor! So you are really the sinner responsible for the theft of the sacred creature!”

The cold glint in Longbottom’s eyes expanded, and several greyish-green streams of air rose from his body.

“Ah!” “Ah!”

Two short yelps were heard.

These belonged to the two official Magi who were unfortunately struck by the stray streams of air. The moment they had contact with the greyish-green air, their bodies wilted and they turned into dried corpses that had died in an incomparably pitiful manner.

“You dare rob life force that does not belong to you. You’ll be devoured by it sooner or later!”

Baelin’s expression was dark as he rode the Underground Winter Spider Emperor, looking like a gallant knight.

“How would you understand how brilliant Life Absorption is?” Longbottom merely gave a cold answer to Baelin. Meanwhile, the giant spider phantom image pounced forward, the strange streams of air like black holes that greedily sucked in the life force within Baelin.

Baelin’s expression became grim as he patted the Underground Winter Spider Emperor he was on and collided with Longbottom.

The energy particles formed from the clash between two rank 2 Magi created havoc as they sent a few people unlucky enough to be hit by stray particles flying. They were seriously injured.

Within the greyish-green vortex, a knight on a giant golden spider was emanating red light. He looked like an ancient dragon-slaying prince as he charged towards the heart of the vortex.

The battle kept changing location and caused a few stages to be completely destroyed.

At this moment, the nine judges were trapped. The rank 2 Magi were already the most powerful in this entire competition area.

The result of Baelin and Longbottom’s match could even decide the life or death of all the Magi here!

Hence, even while battling with the revolution army and dark elves, many Magi tried to spare some energy and watch the battle.

What attracted their interest the most were the nine ice sculptures on the platform!

These Magi knew very well that a small part of their chances of survival depended on Baelin, while most of it depended on whether these rank 2 Magi could break out of their restrictions.

Even Longbottom would be reduced to dust under the combined attacks of nine rank 2 Magi.

“Cough! Wake up, my lords!”

At this moment, light flashed in a corner and a grey-haired Magus appeared.

He mumbled spell incantations, a huge blazing fireball striking the nine sculptures and turning the podium made of gold and silver into a sea of fire.

This Magus despaired as he saw the flames soon dying out under a layer of white frost. Dense icy mist lingered and froze the whole podium into ice and snow.

Meanwhile, not even a corner of the nine ice sculptures had melted.

“What a waste of energy. This is the icy air from the abyss and is a rank 2 spell which can be sustained for a long time.” Longbottom watched on and began to laugh coldly.

Without waiting for his orders, a few dark elf special guards in black-robes charged forward and began to battle with the Magus in grey robes. Not long after, a sharp dagger pierced into his chest.

After seeing this, the many Magi who had plans to rescue him all fell silent, putting away all thoughts of rescuing the judges.

Most of them wanted to break away from their opponents and successfully leave this place.

At this moment, the battles in the area became more brutal and intense.

Outside the competition area, everything had yet to die down.

*Teng! Teng! Teng! Teng!*

At the horizon far away, a black line suddenly appeared. It gradually closed in and the two ends began to shrink, and it felt like the line would surround the whole competition area.

When the black shadows came closer, it could be seen that they were actually the elite Underground Winter Spider knights. There were a great number of dark elven Magi, which included multiple matriarchs and even Anya.

“Seal off that area and don’t let any human get away” Anya commanded, and then pointed at the cocoon in the middle, a gentle voice transmitted to every knight’s ears.

“Fight for Her Majesty!” “Fight for Her Majesty!”

The many dark elven Underground Winter Spider knights cheered and then began their attacks.

“Prepare for Joint Earth Pitfalls Spell! Begin!”

At this moment, brownish-yellow lights flashed and countless depressions appeared in front of the Underground Winter Spider knights. They were like long trenches, with earthen spikes piercing upwards and stopping the knights in their tracks.

There were a few knights who had moved too quickly and fallen into the trench, their chests, arms, thighs, and even faces pierced through like skewered meat. Those who had yet to die kept howling in pain.

Three figures appeared in mid-air, causing Anya to furrow her brow slightly.

“The protectors of the east, west, and south have all arrived. What about that old Guardian of the Realm?”

“I’m right here. I wouldn’t need you to worry about me!”

Green light flashed, and the the old protector appeared before Anya. Though he seemed weak and did not have much of an aura, Anya looked as if a great enemy had appeared in front of her.

“I didn’t expect you, Anya, to use the dark elves’ crown as a means to enter Twilight Zone without letting even the dark elven knights know about it…” He smiled slightly while greeting her.

The crown of the dark elves was a sign of the authority of the Dark Elven Empire. It was also a very powerful magic artifact.

It had a very simple function, which was to conceal the energy aura of a large group of people and their mounts. The key point was that it could turn around the battle. However, every time it’s used, it can only be used again after a fifty-year wait, which is why this inherited magic artifact of the magic elves could not be used flippantly.

Now, the dark elven crown could finally exhibit all its strength and shield numerous dark elven armies into the central region, almost wiping out all the Magi at the competition area.

“Except for the protector of the northern region who has died, all of the lord protectors are here. What’s this? Do you want to stop me?” A little green vortex appeared above Anya’s hands, glimmering with a mysterious light. It attracted the attention of everyone to look at the vortex, which had the intention of sucking human spirits in.

“Protecting Twilight Zone and the human race was our vow when we took on the role as protectors. This is an honour worthy of exchanging our lives for!”

The Guardian’s face was filled with layers of wrinkles and he looked about to die of old age. However, his eyes still shone with light.

Anya sensed that, although the life force of the Guardian was like a flame that was sputtering out, it still emanated light and warmth that even caused her to be worried.

The allied Magus army appeared behind these few protectors confronted the dark elves.

“The plan was actually leaked out. Who was it?”

Anya’s brows furrowed and then straightened out, “Whatever it is, we’ve finally restrained your nine rank 2 Magi. There are still many elite Magi and acolytes within the competition area. In other words, we have a sure victory in this war!”

“Attack!” Without waiting for the opposing Magi to finish their preparations, Anya immediately ordered for the dark elven matriarchs to attack.

With a flash of her body, she somehow disappeared from the air and, when she reappeared, she was in front of the Guardian of the Realm.

A fair palm brought with it a terrifying devouring strength and was pressed towards the old man’s chest.

“Floating Light!” The light in the old protector’s eyes became brighter and he exclaimed.

Numerous tiny rays of light surged out continuously and formed a protective shield in front of him.

The moment Anya’s hand made contact with the shield, a low sound was produced, and the ground suddenly trembled, the space even beginning to quiver.

“Old geezer, how much longer can your life force sustain you?”

Anya’s expression remained unchanging as she continued her attacks.

A tremendous vortex formed behind her, and any Magus that was sucked into it, turned into a dried corpse in an instant.

“Activating combination spell pattern!”

The expressions of the protectors of the other three regions changed greatly, and as if they had made up their minds. They headed into the skies, shooting out great amounts of green threads that connected with the Guardian of the Realm.

Tremendous rays from light force wrapped around him, and the next time he reemerged, he had already become a handsome and sunny middle-aged man.

If not for the familiar spiritual aura about him, nobody would recognise him.

As for the three other protectors, they began to age visibly.

“Good! Good! Good!”

Anya bit her lips. She could naturally see that the three rank 2 Magi were entrusting their life force to the Guardian. However, this meant that, after today, the four of them would have all their life force consumed and lose their lives.

Chapter 380: Baloney

“Don’t be silly!” Vinas laughed weakly as she reached out and caressed Aaron’s face.

“Sacrificing me, a single person, will allow you to save the entirety of Twilight Zone, what’s there to hesitate?”

At the present moment, although her lips have gone pale and chapped from the loss of blood, her face remains full of radiance and it hurt Aaron to see her like this.

“No! You’re doing this for me! You’re doing this for me!”

Advancing to the second rank did not ensure that he could match up to Longbottom, but it would at least greatly increase his chances of escape.

Aaron wept, tears flowing down his face uncontrollably.

Vinas laughed, her tone full of gratification “This impermanent fate! We were destined to be enemies, yet we fell in love… with each… other”

*Bang!* Vinas’ palm fell listlessly.

Shortly after, a strong current of concentration, along with a warm and gentle scent, was injected into Aaron’s consciousness.

Sacred Flame started to revolve quickly, causing Aaron’s aura to rise sharply, and he broke through the bottleneck of a rank 2 Magus.

*Snap! Snap! Snap!*

The three parts of Meteor Sword assembled together, emitting bright silver rays, and from the light, a tall and thin sword shaped like a cross slowly appeared. The aura of a high-level magic artifact, also much closer to the level of becoming a magic weapon, spread out in a powerful manner.

“AAAAAAAAHHH!!!!”

Aaron roared as he lifted the Meteor Sword and he transformed into a long arc as he charged into the midst of the battlefield.

Any magi who obstructed the path, be they from the Twilight zone or from the Dark Elven Empire, all faded into the air under the power of the Meteor Sword.

“What’s the matter?”

In the middle of the battlefield, Longbottom stared at the huge incoming arc. With fierce eyes, he stopped toying with Baelin. A fireball aimed right at his head hit him.

*Pew!* The Meteor Sword released a ray of light, accurately targeted at the attack launched by Longbottom.

A great and powerful wave of energy surged forth like raging waves.

Although at this moment Longbottom could still kill Baelin, he would definitely suffer huge amounts of damage.

“Rank 2?” Longbottom’s pupils froze. Energy at this level, in addition to a high-level magic artifact designed for offence, was a great threat to him.

As such, Longbottom made a choice. Without moving his body, his quickly moved backwards, layers of grey-green protective shields formed in front of his vision.

“Kill!” In the middle was Aaron’s silhouette. At this moment, as he charged forward with the mighty sword, silver threads of spiritual force continued to condense onto the arc, causing the sharpness of this high-level magic artifact to increase exponentially.

*Bang! Bang!* The protective shield set up by Longbottom was torn apart like crisp paper, and the blade of the sword even touched Longbottom’s eyes.

“Are you trying to kill me? With just you alone?” Longbottom had a sinister expression on his face, and the shadow of a spider appeared on his body, with its mouth wide open, clasping directly on the long sword.

Snap!

The sound of a slight explosion rang in the air, following which, the silhouette of two people flew away, retreating.

Longbottom stroked his face, as below his left eye, a stream of blood flowed.

Whereas on the other end, Aaron’s arm produced a bone crunching noise as he quickly retreated to where Baelin was.

“You… are you alright?” Baelin finally expelled the Corrosive spell’s energy left by Longbottom within himself and he stood up.

Although he did not witness the previous scene, he felt that the expression on his friend’s face was not right.

“Your strong armor has been damaged! Use this!” Aaron glanced at Baelin. He then passed the cross-shaped sword in his hand to Baelin. “The energy it can display in your hands will be much much greater than what it displayed in mine”

Now was not the time for idle talk, Baelin immediately took over the Meteor Sword, but the deathly stillness in Aaron’s eyes still frightened him.

“This again! This again! Why is it that everytime I am about to succeed, there will always be more obstructions sprouting up?” On the other side, Longbottom observed this scene with a grim complexion.

”So what? Having one more rank 2 Magus does not change anything! You will all die here today!”

Longbottom roared. The phantom spider on his back suddenly did something unpredictable.

It ruthlessly widened its mouth and plunged its sharp incisors into Longbottom’s shoulders.

Strings of red which were visible to the naked eye was extracted from Longbottom’s body. And the spider image on his back grew redder and started to expand.

Although Longbottom’s body continued to become thin and weak, leaving only skin and bones, which looked terrifying, the energy in his body was increasing exponentially, as though there was no limit.

“Dark Elven Ritual of Life! We cannot let him complete it or he will advance into the peak of rank 2, even though he will have to pay for it with his life…”

Aaron’s voice grew hoarse, but he immediately transformed into a silvery arc as he rushed at him.

”Old friend Aru! This time I will not hesitate and be benevolent. Just you wait, I will save you!”

Baelin gripped the Meteor Sword tightly. This melee weapon, when in the hands of a powerful warrior, also let out a deafening screech.

“Kill!” Baelin had a face of determination. The eye on his armor opened once again, and a huge restrictive aura suddenly arrived at the site, aimed at Longbottom who was in the center.

“Haha… Come! Come!”

Longbottom who had a stick-thin figure laughed wildly, and engaged Aaron and Baelin.

*Bang!* After the ritual of life, not only did his aura increase, it seemed to have experienced a transformation, allowing him to gain a huge boost.

He raised his bony right arm against the Meteor Sword in Baelin’s hands.

*Bang bang!* The two came into contact, letting out a horrifying sound of metal brushing against metal. The Meteor Sword in Baelin’s hand could only cut the skin on Longbottom’s hand, following which it was blocked by Longbottom’s arm which was stronger than steel.

“Huh!” Baelin face was full of shock, he chopped another time, but the long sword that pierced Longbottom’s face was stopped by his teeth clenching hard.

“Sacred Flame!”

Aaron pointed at Longbottom, a wave of pure white blaze laced with threads of silver fell, causing the area around Longbottom’s body to burn.

Longbottom’s Magus robe, rings and accessories were all melted in the blazing fire but his body remained intact, just like sturdy metal.

“What is happening?” Jumping on this chance, Baelin finally drew out the long sword, standing up with Aaron who had retreated to a corner.

“The Ritual of Life has begun, and at this point his life does not belong to him, it belongs to the noble Mother of the Abyss. Simply put, the source of his life has been transferred and his body is only a puppet now. Whatever harm we inflict upon his body won’t have any effect.”

Aaron’s face turned serious, with a hint of frantic “But his ritual of life has not been completed, so the core should still be in the process of transferring, later I will control and mark him, take care of the rest!”

“Got it!” Baelin nodded “How are you going to…” he could not finish talking before Aaron madly dashed in.

“Die!” Longbottom watched Aaron charge towards him, his eyes full of vengeance and violence.

He abruptly sent out a fist. The black fist collided with Aaron’s chest, letting out a crisp sound.

Snap! Longbottom’s face suddenly changed and he retracted his fist. On his knuckles, a bone had already been pierced through and strands of black solidified blood could be seen.

“Wh…What’s happening? How can an ordinary Bone Piercing Spell take down my defenses!” There was a huge change in Longbottom’s expression, and he seemed to have thoughts of retreating.

*Bang! Bang! Bang!*

But it was too late, Many silver bone piercings started to come out from Aaron’s body, and his eyes turned white. Surprisingly, he was able to predict Longbottom’s retreat route. After dodging his long range attack, he clung onto Longbottom.

“Ah! Ah! Ah!”

Several bone piercings acted like a trap and pierced Longbottom all over, but Aaron grew even worse, blood spurting out of his body.

“Heh heh… This is my upgraded version of the Bone Piercing Spell, enjoy!”

Aaron’s face was a mixture of madness and relief as he yelled, “Vinas, I am coming!”

“You lunatic!” Longbottom roared. He pounded on Aaron’s back with his fists, and the great tremors even caused the ground to vibrate.

“Quick! Over there!” Aaron was bleeding from his nose and mouth, he used a sliver of spiritual force to mark out a position.

That was on the flowery pattern on the abdomen area of the spider tattoo on Longbottom’s back. It was now shining with a silver light.

“Kill!”

Baelin’s expression was calm as a great silver aura was released, forming silver white flames.

Large amounts of flame gathered on the Meteor Sword, a terrifying energy wave spreading throughout the entire competition venue, causing the surrounding Magi to involuntarily stop what they were doing.

The huge wings behind Baelin rose, carrying him into the skies, causing him to look like a red meteor streaking through the skies.

“Die!” At this moment, Baelin no longer showed signs of hesitation and unwillingness. The long sword ruthlessly pierced through the defense of the spider image, the blade directly cutting through the marked position.

The illusory spider screeched, and its eight legs started to tremble irregularly. Suddenly, it was sent tumbling down. It then turned into black smog and dispersed.

“Ugh …glug…..” Longbottom’s expression was very weird; he looked as though he wanted to say something but could not, all that could be heard was a constant gurgling noise made within his throat.

The light in his eyes dimmed until they were a dead black.

*Bang!* Longbottom’s corpse fell to the ground and sent a huge patch of dust flying.

“We… succeeded!”

Baelin mumbled to himself, feeling as though he lost a part of himself. He felt empty, as though he had lost something very important to him.

“Be careful, the darkness has not ended!” Both of Aaron’s eyes turned white and he fell to the ground, a pool of blood forming beneath his body.

Chapter 381: Coin of Destiny

“Darkness? What darkness? Hasn’t Longbottom’s scheme been thwarted?” Baelin was doubtful, but he no longer had the time to think. He scooped Aaron up in a hurry, preparing to treat him.

Strands of green rays emerged from Baelin’s fingers, and merged with the horrifying wound on Aaron’s body, helping him stop the bleeding and mending his tissues.

“Aaron, Aaron! Are you alright? Hang in there!” Baelin constantly cried out, large amounts of tears spilling from his eyes.

“Longbottom! Lord Longbottom is dead!” At this time, in the middle of the competition venue, the revolutionary army and dark elves who had just lost their leader all fell into a state of chaos.

*Cough Cough!* Aaron coughed violently and opened his eyes. “I… I’m still alive?”

“Of course, you’re my prophet. How can you die without my permission?” Baelin covertly brushed away his tears and laughed.

”Oh no!” Aaron suddenly started to struggle.

”What’s happening?” Baelin hurriedly helped him stand up.

“Danger is still near! In fact, it’s in our immediate vicinity!” Aaron’s face showed increasing terror, “He… He is…”

*Bang! Bang! Bang!*

A person wearing an exquisite black robe emerged amidst sudden applause. Every move of his held an inexplicable aura of authority and grace, and he slowly entered their field of vision.

“As expected of a Magus practicing Sacred Flame. Once you reach rank 2, even I cannot escape your prophecies!”

“Master Leylin! Weren’t you…” Baelin looked at Leylin. At first, he felt joy, but then he noticed the nine statues erected in the center.

“A mere Ice Seal of Eternity, what can it do to me?” Leylin laughed casually, not revealing that he had known about Longbottom’s plan from Ernis. Even if he hadn’t known, though, his frightening power and affinity with frost would have let him escape quite easily.

*Bang!* As though to verify Leylin’s words, one of the nine ice sculptures suddenly exploded, revealing the silhouette of a puppet which quickly dissipated.

“What… What’s happening? Ah! Haha… Haha… I get it! Master Leylin, this is just a prank, isn’t it?” Baelin laughed forcefully, but the unease in his heart had reached its peak.

“Prank? Oh! Yes, I love cracking jokes with you, just not today. I was just excited by your performance and wanted to excuse myself!” Leylin snapped his finger.

*Swish! Swish! Swish! Swish!* Light flashed everywhere, and a large number of Nature’s Alliance Magi appeared. Some came out from beneath the stages, some from behind the seats, and some just materialised from the shadows.

These Magi all had their concentration and powers intact, and embarked on a ruthless massacre the moment they entered. The dark elves and Twilight Zone Magi all fell at their hands, and were swept in a matter of seconds.

“Second level seal enhancement begin!” The leader, Iren, immediately tossed out a scroll.

*Bzzzt Bzzzt!* A frightful wave of energy dispersed, and an even larger fleet of Magi appeared at the center of the competition venue, reinforcing the gigantic spider cocoon.

“Lord Leylin? Why?” Baelin kept retreating, looking as though he was on the verge of breaking down.

“You are one of the higher-ups in Twilight Zone, and also someone I look up to. Why…”

“No particular reason, after directing a play for so long, it’s time I came to wrap things up!” The corners of Leylin’s mouth turned into a sinister smirk.

“Play? What kind of play?” Baelin did not dare to think further.

“A comedy about a silly hero, and a group of foolish Magi!” Leylin smiled subtly, and pointed at Baelin’s neck.

Boiling hot! Scalding hot! Baelin felt an unnerving heat exuding from his neck, penetrating through his armor, roasting his skin and muscles.

*Boom!* A streak of gold light emitted from his neck and returned to Leylin’s palms.

It was a peculiar gold coin, one face of which had a lucky bird and the other a skull. The sides of the coin also had elaborate patterns and prints on them.

“This was the gold coin you gave me, was it all planned from the very beginning?” Baelin laughed pathetically.

“No! I did not have such plans back in Potter Town, but on the way to the Eastern Capital, I found out that you were the Child of Destiny, so I decided to do this!” Leylin looked at the gold coin in his hand, excitement written on his face.

“Hehe….. You are all liars! Liars!” Baelin laughed hysterically. Rays of silver light burst forth from his body, and he charged forth, Meteor Sword in hand.

*Pow!* A fist of immense strength landed firmly on his cheek, causing the Meteor Sword to be swung out of his grasp even as he was sent flying.

Alas, the Bio Boosting armour on his body failed to hold any longer and disintegrated midair.

“Your destiny was to become the victor of this revolution in your battle with Longbottom! And after Longbottom was taken care of, how do I put it… You are no longer of use to destiny. And without destiny on your side, you are but a dead dog to me…” Leylin ruthlessly attacked Baelin.

It was the truth. Before Baelin completed his mission, were Leylin to have made a move, he had a premonition that something would inexplicably block his path. But now? There was nothing that could stop him.

This was the very reason why many accomplished heroes never got another chance to take risks and could only choose to live in seclusion among the commoners..

“Coin of Destiny, step one accomplished!” Leylin turned around and looked over at where Aaron was.

*Pew!* At this moment, a stream of light also emitted from Aaron’s ring, and in front of him appeared the Great Magus Merlin.

“Little Aaron, what did you promise me then?”

“I promised that other than collecting your shards, I’ll have to help you complete another task!” Aaron’s expression was a mix of terror, alarm, and agony.

“Now, I request of you, to return to me the Sacred Flame!” Merlin’s voice was extremely calm, but Aaron couldn’t help but turn pale at his voice. “Grandpa Merlin, I’ve always been respectful to you as though you were my own grandfather…”

“But, the moment you advanced to the second rank, you realised it, no?” Merlin’s illusion transformed continuously before settling on the image of Leylin.

“So all of this; me gaining the inheritance, practicing Sacred Flame, meeting with Vinas; it was all your doing?”

Aaron turned around and looked at Leylin, his pupils pitch black.

“At first it was, but the melodrama at the end was something I couldn’t predict either. It looks like the stability issues with Sacred Flame still have to be solved!” Leylin’s voice was extremely cold, “Now, hand it over!”

“AH!” As soon as Leylin voice sounded, Aaron felt as though his consciousness was split open by someone who wanted to extract something.

The extreme horrifying pain caused him to roll around, and his face contorted into demon-like expressions.

Shortly after, Aaron felt the spiritual force he had so painstakingly cultivated with the Sacred Flame was drawn out from him entirely.

Strands of silver spiritual force formed a vortex in midair, and Aaron who lost his meditation technique had his powers depleted progressively, from rank 2 to rank 1 before hitting rock bottom—an acolyte.

“The spiritual force of Sacred Flame!” Leylin’s smile broadened. He sang with excitement, “Along with the sacrifice of a Child of Destiny!”

With his deep voice sounding, the surface of the Coin of Destiny shone with a thin layer of light and was lifted into the air.

“With the magnanimous power of destiny, along with the foundation and spiritual force of the Sacred Flame that split apart and then merged together!”

Leylin pulled out a crystal already full of golden liquid, and threw it into the spiritual force vortex.

All of a sudden, a surge of silver white flames emerged from within.

“There are still three broken and unwilling souls!” Leylin’s smile became even wider, and two items flew out from Aaron’s body.

They were a worn-out notebook and a five-colored necklace. At this moment, an illusion flickered on each of the two items.

“Vinas! Vinas!” Aaron struggled as he saw the face of his lover on the five-colored necklace, however, Vinas’ expression was ever-changing, from tenderness, to detachment, to distraught…

“You can join too!” Leylin pointed at Aaron’s forehead and it exploded like a watermelon. The black ring in his hand also flew into the air, joining into a triangular formation with the other two items.

“With great power from the fragmented souls as the main body, the Sacred Flame meditation technique as the core, and finally injecting a large amount of the power of destiny…”

Leylin’s voice grew in fervency.

Following the chanting, the triangular formation and meditative vortex grew closer, giving off small explosions.

“AHHHHHHH……” Baelin hissed violently and charged forth once again, but before he got close, he was already thrown out by the airwaves.

“Seal!” A complex and awkward-sounding ancient incantation finally fused into two short seals.

*Boom Boom!* A gigantic vortex formed, compressing the vortex and triangular formation into the Coin of Destiny like a funnel.

When everything ended, flashes of light appeared on the Coin of Destiny, yet it seemed as though nothing had changed.

“Beautiful, isn’t it?”

Leylin let the gold coin float in midair and with a wave of his arm, the Meteor Sword voluntarily flew into his hands.

“You did all this, just for those two items?”

Baelin was beyond miserable, his eyes with a tint alike to flames.

Chapter 383: A Fallen Empress

The human camp was more complicated.

Many Magi, acolytes and even common soldiers had been gathered together like a mixed flock of birds.

It had turned out this way due to the lack of core leadership. The deaths of the Guardian of the Realm and the Protectors had left them without a stable chain of command. Hence, many problems arose, not the least of which was disputes in command. Many ambitious parties were working from the shadows, plotting their own schemes.

“Oh? People are gossiping about me?” Back at his own camp, Leylin was updated with the latest report, and his face revealed a mysterious sinister smile.

“Don’t bother with them. These rumours will be deemed baseless soon enough!” Leylin waved his hand and flashed a faint smile.

Suddenly his face changed as he looked towards the northern skies, “She’s here!”

A tiny black speck suddenly rose from the northern skies, bringing a huge and irresistible power to bear upon the two armies.

“Your Majesty.” Numerous elite Underground Winter Spider knights knelt down to salute with zeal in their eyes.

Anya looked up to face the human army, her beautiful face and body exuding a mysterious charm.

“Where is your commander? I want to see him!” she spoke with a sweet yet icy tone to her voice, as alluring as a rose in a bloody scene. It was tender and beautiful, yet dangerous and deadly.

And so that voice with the strength of a Magus was heard even on the side of the humans.

Numerous ordinary troops started fainting and dying, many of them shedding patches of hair and bleeding furiously.

This was the result of radiations emitted recklessly from a high ranking Magus’s spell, causing the destruction of the normal human’s body.

The acolytes too started to faint one after the other, until only official Magi could remain clear-headed, although even their fighting strength was heavily reduced.

Streams of green air could be seen, being drawn out from the human camp and transferred to Anya who was hovering in mid-air.

“A false domain! There were rumours that the dark elven empress had attained such a high level— the ability to suck life and power out of them is a formidable gift!”

Leylin’s expression showed signs of interest and he turned to look at the other high ranking Magi.

In the human camp, the rest of the high-ranking Magi were waiting in their tents in silence. Waves of spatial magic power permeated the air.

“The battle has yet to begun, and you’re already about to run away?” Leylin laughed uncontrollably, but then felt that it was only right. After all, these Magi had thought that the empress of the dark elves had been severely injured. If not, the Guardian of the Realm would have survived as well.

What now?

“At this moment, the Magi outside would mostly likely be vehemently cursing me, huh?” Leylin shook his head, as his body floated to mid-air.

*Roar!* A massive, ferocious aura that seemed to emanate from a predator of ancient times burst forth.

A wave of violent air rolled and surged through, causing huge chaos to the opposite camp. The other Magi noticed that this wave of energy was not inferior to that of the dark elven empress!

“Bloodline Skill—Intimidating Gaze!”

*Snap!* Leylin’s life force rose ferociously, as if a chain or seal had been broken, and at that moment, he had crossed the category of a rank 2 Magus and entered a deep and unmeasurable realm.

This kind of change upset Anya, “Rank 3! You have already advanced to rank 3! “

Yes! Before the murder of the Guardian of the Realm, Leylin had secretly arranged for his advancement to a rank 3 Magus.

With the Giant Serpent’s Breath potion and the usage of a large amount of top-notch resources, Leylin’s spiritual force had turned bright silver long ago, and his power had been enhanced greatly.

As for the next level in Kemoyin’s Pupil, Leylin already had it! In fact, with the A.I. chip’s enhancement, it had become even more all-encompassing.

That in addition to the enlightenment from the Tree of Wisdom formed the perfect conditions to ensure success.

Leylin’s intention was to elevate his power to be on the same level as the best of Twilight Zone, so that he would have the confidence to carry out his plans.

The breakthrough had surprised Leylin. His materialised spiritual force had been refined continuously and, at the same time, the foundations of the spiritual force crystal had been constructed. The swiftness and ease of it had left Leylin with an unfathomable feeling.

It could be the result from the use of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s blood or from the accumulated knowledge from the A.I. Chip. It might be the great essence of wisdom found in the ancient tree that no one knew about. Or it could be the different factors all coming together that assisted Leylin in acquiring his current position. It had surely surpassed his own expectations.

The enhanced A.I.Chip thus refreshed Leylin’s status.

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 3 Warlock

Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent

Power: 23.6

Agility: 20.1

Physique: 35.7

Vitality: 203.4

Magic Power: 203 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force)]

[Host has obtained an innate spell upon advancement— Intimidating Gaze!]

[Intimidating Gaze: After numerous blood purification, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, as an elite ancient predator, has its might absorbed and assimilated into the bloodline Warlock. They who held the dignity of creatures from ancient times has a force field with an intimidating effect!

Effect: any living being that is within the perimeter will have their powers suppressed. Those with weak willpower will enter a state of confusion. Rank 1 Magus will have their abilities weakened by 50%, rank 2 Magus weakened by 30% and Magi of the same rank will have their stats reduced by 10%!]

With such an ability to suppress the power of his enemies, Leylin seemed genuinely ready to dominate the field. In fact, he could be considered an ideal Magus to dominate everything!

Unlike the domain of a Morning Star Magus, which gave them complete control, Intimidating Gaze only applied certain effects to those caught within its area of effect.

With Leylin now using Intimidating Gaze, the Underground Winter Spider knights felt as if an eye from the depths of hell was gazing upon them, which caused them to collapse to the ground. As for the matriarchs, their faces turned ashen, warping with terror.

Leylin took a calculative look at the empress in front of him. Strictly speaking, this could be considered their first meeting.

His relentless gaze transcended the opposing party’s demonic charm, instead, he paid more attention to the decorative design on her body.

A moment late, Leylin sighed and responded faintly: “So… You were already seriously injured!”

The suppression of injuries by the branding of runes on the body, as well as the familiar scent, reminded Leylin of the Guardian of the Realm who had perished. The vicious fight with him and the Protectors had obviously caused Anya to suffer serious injuries, leaving her with no choice but to retreat.

Anya looked at the youthful Leylin, showing a bitter smile.

“Do you know? Dark elves’ lives are filled with hardships. When I was young, every winter I would witness many dark elves firmly geared up with weaponry. My mother told me they were gearing up for war, and after the war, we would have enough food and provisions to survive…” Anya’s face was filled with loss, her voice angelic. The corners of her eyes sparkled.

“My mother told me that, far away on the southern side, there was a huge empire of the human race. It was continuously fighting with us for survival. Hence, every year we suffer huge losses and death. I’d decided then that I would lead an army of dark elves and break this cruel cycle…

“But now, unfortunately, I am unable to do so…”

Anya turned to look at the dark elven camp one more time, and at this moment, an enormous uproar occurred. Several rank 2 matriarchs disregarded the frightening energy wave and stormed straight forward.

“Can you promise me, that you will preserve the dark elven race?” Anya lowered her once arrogant head, pleading.

Looking at the intelligent and well-respected empress of the dark elves in front of him, Leylin nodded his head lightly, “I promise you that I will preserve the dark elves and see that they remain in Twilight Zone….”

“However, what the other Magi do afterwards will be out of my hands. Moreover, whether the dark elves are able to survive within the ecology laboratory is also another unpredictable matter…’ These words were left unsaid.

“Thank you so much!” Anya smiled, the crown on her head giving off a glaring ray of light.

The moment Leylin swung his hand, a huge golden Spider appeared and landed in the center of the field. It sat facing the Underground Winter Spiders across it and started hissing loudly.

The Underground Winter Spiders then became increasingly restless, and many of them started to show signs of instability. Some even turned against the dark elven knights riding them and started biting at them.

Aru, the Underground Winter Spider Emperor, had originally been sealed by Longbottom. Leylin had unsealed it after the events at the arena and subdued it for his own use.

To a certain extent, Aru might be the common ancestor of all Underground Winter Spiders, hence to have such unbelievable power for use by him, he was thrilled to possess this killer weapon.

“Here we go!”

Leylin exclaimed lightly, fine black scales appearing on his body and striking Anya’s at the same time…

Along with the loud hissing of both opposing spiders and the clash of the two Magi, the two opposing troops on the ground also started to assemble and started the attack in full force, the roar of their voices shaking the earth….

Twilight Zone, year 5782. Magus Leylin Farlier led the human army to crush the army of the dark elves along with their empress. Magus Anya, along with rank 1 and rank 2 matriarchs, were not spared. Together with the rest of the army, they collapsed at the scene and countless lives were lost.

Chapter 384: Guardian of the Realm

After Leylin’s progression to rank 3 and the defeat of the dark elves, all the dissent and secret plots in the central region quieted down as if they had never existed.

As a newly promoted rank 3 Magus full of vitality, one who wasn’t struggling to even protect the realm, Leylin could easily find the time to destroy those guilds that did not subject themselves to his rule. He was poised to control Twilight Zone for centuries to come.

Faced with the pressure from such great power, no matter how unwilling the Magi in the central region were, they dared not offend him.

At this moment, the few survivors from other guilds appeared, diminishing all talk against Leylin.

They were all elite Magi from different guilds, and a few rank 2 judges were also among them. They joined together to testify that what Leylin had said before was the truth, which waived all doubts immediately.

They were all Leylin’s captives at that time. Those rank 2 Magi had long since submitted to Leylin. They were not fools. Knowing Leylin’s power and their own waning influence, most of them recognised the truth.

Of course, there were some stubborn ones that all perished gloriously in the “war.”

Twilight Zone year 5783. Aided by his rank 3 power and the glory of defeating the dark elves, Leylin was pronounced the Guardian of the Realm under the witness of many Magi in the central region.

From then, Leylin became the sole power controlling Twilight Zone’s Magi, and the sacrifices and darkness behind his radiant glory were often ignored by the masses.

People would only end up remembering Leylin’s glorious achievement of defeating the dark elves. They composed folk songs and legends in his praise, leaving out the hard work of Baelin, Aaron, Vinas, and even the previous Guardian. Those names were buried beneath the documents and historical records concerning Leylin’s eternal brilliance, and his legend continued.

After succeeding the title of the Guardian of the Realm, the first order Leylin passed was aimed at making Nature’s Alliance the core strength of Twilight Zone. He gathered large masses of Magi to construct the Nature’s Alliance Academy at the heart of the central region.

Although Leylin had not planned to do so originally, the present him did have the strength to implement the academy system, reaping great rewards in the process.

After establishing the Nature’s Alliance Academy, a few large-scale guilds who had good relationships with the Alliance made a high-profile announcement. They would merge with Nature’s Alliance Academy to form a formidable guild. Of course, this was all due to Leylin’s control in the background.

Following that, Leylin no longer had to worry. The rapidly rising academy naturally edged out other nearby guilds, continually expanding its capability and area of influence.

It was clear to Leylin that the south coast’s model was more just and fair than the guild system followed by Twilight Zone. They had also relinquished the tradition of inheritance from master to disciple. Although there were still many mentors, very few of them continued treating their acolytes like slaves.

Furthermore, how many acolytes could a mentor take on? How could they compare to the large-scale classrooms of an academy?

Many large guilds started to relinquish their narrow-minded restriction of meditation techniques to combine forces, as it would definitely be much stronger than the strength of individual guilds.

This was the success of the system! It was also the improvement of an era, once it became a trend, it could not be stopped!

The guilds that were left behind, in order to not be overshadowed by the academies, also had to establish institutes and enroll many acolytes to survive.

This allowed talented commoners to have a very good chance.

Academies that were more free and open could also accept roaming Magi. Without the meditation technique restriction, it became much simpler for roaming Magi who wanted to join academies.

Leylin had noticed this long ago. Although guilds that practised the same kind of meditation technique were very united, they also became highly xenophobic. After joining a guild, if a Magi did not practice that guild’s meditation technique, they became targets for ostracization.

But academies did not face this problem. The flames of the revolution started by Longbottom were also snuffed out gradually by the institution of academies.

Leylin did not actually mind this. What he prioritised was still the meditation techniques of the guilds and their valued research.

Indeed! Under the advocation of fair, just, transparent and free communication by the academy’s rules, guilds that joined the academy had to contribute their unique meditation techniques and some precious research.

Under Leylin’s leadership, this large amount of precious information was stored in the academy’s library for all Magi to peruse, and this trend developed ardently.

It must be said that after relinquishing the narrow-minded notion of a guild, such open communication and probing indeed benefitted the Magi a lot, causing the Magi of Twilight Zone to improve their abilities.

As for these meditation techniques and research, all of it was naturally kindly accepted by Leylin, greatly increasing the A.I chip’s database.

It can be said that at this point in time, a large portion of Twilight Zone’s meditation techniques and high-level research was pocketed by Leylin, including all precious resources.

Nature’s Alliance was now the most influential in the central region. No matter what Leylin desired, as long as it was within Twilight Zone, he needed but to ask. A large number of commoners, acolytes, rank 1 and even rank 2 Magi would unhesitatingly go get it for him no matter the cost.

This was the benefit of authority.

Time passed.

Twilight Zone, year 5785.

Sensing that every party had completed their preparations, Leylin, with his title of Guardian of the Realm, sent out an appeal ordering alliance forces from all regions to recapture the north!

Indeed! After murdering Anya, Leylin chose to retreat and did not directly attack the North region, but that place was now easily obtainable.

It was very clear to him that though he had exceptional abilities, he first had to sort out his own skills. Although impulsively sending troops to defeat the dark elves, recover their lost lands and gain reputation could work out, the real gains would definitely be reaped by others harbouring ambitious schemes.

In addition, at that point in time, he did not have the title of Guardian of the Realm! Leylin was not foolish enough to fight on the front lines and let the Magi at the back reap the fruit of his efforts.

Hence, he would rather watch on as the north’s remaining dark elves waged war against the dwarves, gnomes, and even themselves, letting them wear themselves out before he would act.

But now, the time was ripe.

Compared to the previous appeal, Leylin was now the Guardian of the Realm, the ruler of Twilight Zone. The orders of the greatest leader of the Magus world naturally carried more weight.

Once the order was passed down, not only did all the guilds in the central region send out Magi and soldiers to form an alliance, even the east, south and west regions sent out large masses to help.

Something worth mentioning was that Leylin only had true control over two regions— the center and the east.

As for the west and south, their attitudes toward Leylin as the Guardian of the Realm were rather ambiguous.

But Leylin did not care, after organising the center and east, relying on the strength of the academies in these two regions was enough to crush the other party.

He had abstained from doing so earlier because his time was occupied by internal restructuring.

But now? The other regions had also sensed that conditions were not favourable for them, and they started to yield.

After all, sending out armies in accordance to the appeal was an act of allegiance.

Leylin stroked his chin, the corners of his mouth curled up in amusement.

North Twilight Zone.

Throngs of troops lined up neatly and advanced forward constantly.

Meanwhile at the back were large numbers of Magi riding peculiar transports.

The troops were neat and orderly, and unified by the same order, compared to the previous army organised by Leylin, this one seemed much more powerful.

Due to the passing of the dark elven empress three years ago, most of the dark elves had already withdrawn from north Twilight Zone. Only some of the more stubborn members of their race were left struggling along with the dwarves and gnomes.

And such strength, to a congregation of many Magi, especially the human troops led by Leylin, was as insignificant as dust.

The troops had an irresistible force. They conquered expansive plots of land by barely expending any energy and even pushed through to Potti city.

At the entrance of the city, the flag of the dark eves could be seen flying high, amidst thick smog, giving off an ominous feel.

“Potti City! The original line of defence of the north, and also the place where Protector Yade died!” Leylin looked at the few dark elves and sneered, “This is a strategic border town, could it be the dark elves are still dreaming of dividing the land with us?”

“Pass down the order, all troops are to pitch camp here, we will attack tomorrow!”

Leylin casually passed the order to his left and right-hand men, and they passed down the message layer by layer. The entire troop stopped and found themselves suitable spaces to pitch camps. At the moment, the Magi and normal soldiers were busy, but they were not in disorder, displaying the good control Leylin had over his army.

In the center of the closely packed camps was a big gold tent, decorated with exquisite gemstones and incense. There were even teams of Magi patrolling outside of it.

Although the Guardian of the Realm did not fancy all this, it was necessary etiquette.

“Hm?” Leylin who was meditating in the middle of the gold tent suddenly opened his eyes and his mouth turned into a smile.

After a few minutes, a congratulatory voice could be heard “Master!”

“Enter!”

The front curtain was unveiled and a middle-aged man with white hair entered, his being radiated with the scary energy of a rank 2 Magi, but at this moment, he kneeled down on one knee as a form of respect to Leylin.

“Reporting to master! There is a rank 2 matriarch of the dark elves who claims to be an old friend and wants to see you!”

“An old friend?” Leylin smiled, “Let her in.”

Chapter 387: Discovery of a Warlock

Celine watched Leylin who was bathing in the light from the sun stones, seemingly intoxicated by the sight.

Leylin still retained his handsome young appearance, as if the passing of time did not leave any traces on him. He, who was glimmering with golden rays, seemed to be a war god wrapped in golden robes.

It was this young man who had already reached the apex in Twilight Zone, having seized immense authority that nobody could even imagine of possessing!

“How are the results of the experiment?” Celine asked.

“Quite alright!” Though there was a smile on his face, it seemed slightly dark, and Celine tactfully did not ask further.

Leylin’s hand groped around her body, but his thoughts were someplace else.

Through supplements from numerous high-grade meditation technique, the A.I. Chip’s meditation technique databank was becoming even more complete, and it had even simulated the fourth level of Kemoyin’s Pupil!

However, Leylin was still slightly worried. He planned on searching for the original Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique to compare as well as improve his own. It was always better to be more careful when it came to anything that had to do with the spirit.

If the situation with the meditation technique was a good thing, there was something else that made Leylin’s mood the worst it could be. He looked at his stats.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 3 Warlock

Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent

Strength: 23.6

Agility: 20.1

Vitality: 35.7

Spiritual force: 206.5

Magic power: 206 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force).]

“Fifteen years! It’s been fifteen whole years, and the improvement in my meditation technique has been slight. If not for the numbers given by the A.I. Chip, I would have suspected I had completely stopped improving.”

Leylin’s expression was dark. In these fifteen years, he had hovered around the level of a rank 3 Warlock that had just advanced. He had not even reached the Vapour Phase of his spiritual force. This speed was making him go crazy.

Though Leylin liked to enjoy himself, those were things he did while he was not increasing his strength. At his level, he might not have a rival in Twilight Zone and be the tyrant he was. However, how was this the life that he wanted?

Before obtaining the greatest strength at the apex, Leylin did not plan to slow his footsteps.

“The resources of Twilight Zone are plentiful for rank 1 and 2 Magi, but for rank 3, they’re insufficient. In addition, based on calculations by the A.I. Chip, to become a rank 3 Magus with gaseous spiritual force, I need to have a Vapour Phase spell formation, but it doesn’t exist in Twilight Zone!”

Leylin pondered, “In addition, there’s still the Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique. Though the A.I. Chip has simulated a portion of it, it’s better to get the original and refer to it.”

“All these can’t be obtained in Twilight Zone!”

Leylin made his mind, while the beautiful woman beside him let out a frail gasp.

Leylin, who had come back to himself, realised that his hand seemed to have reached a very deep place that was causing Celine to let out pants.

Without telling Celine his plans, Leylin embraced and ferociously rolled her onto the bed…

……

Even though he enjoyed this pleasure, Leylin did not lose himself to it. He rejected Celine’s suggestion of gathering the Magi of Nature’s Alliance Academy and instead left, keeping a low profile and travelling around Twilight Zone.

On one hand, Leylin was filled with curiosity about Twilight Zone. After all, he had never truly toured the area, and only gathered information through maps and the information in the A.I. Chip, which was only one aspect of it.

More importantly, Leylin wanted to try his luck. He might even be fortunate enough to discover the legacy of some ancient Magus!

Leylin rejected Celine’s requests to accompany him and went on the road since he was used to travelling alone.

He weaved through Twilight Zone. He went deep into the nests of darkness creatures, but also headed to the edge of the world, to see the Magma Sea that stretched as far as the eye could see.

While journeying, Leylin disguised himself as a common wandering Magus. With the A.I. Chip and directions from the coin of destiny, he found quite a few inheritances and the like.

It was a pity that these were all small harvests, and were dispensable to Leylin.

The more dangerous areas, such as Icy World and the Weeping Ghost Grounds that were extremely terrifying, would cause damage to the coin of destiny and were not places Leylin could go to as of yet.

Even so, with his own instincts and the slight directions of the coin, Leylin continued to wander.

A thick darkness constantly shrouded around the earth, and only the light on the carriage persisted, illuminating the surrounding area.

“Is that Grand Ivy Canyon is a ruin left behind by Morning Star Magi?”

On the carriage, Leylin was conversing with another wandering Magus.

Leylin was now concealing his frightening rank 3 aura, and also made adjustments to his outer appearance. Nobody would be able to recognise him as the legendary Glorious Guardian.

After all, he did not want to be surrounded and watched everywhere he went.

He was now having a delightful conversation with a wandering Magus he had just met.

“Yes! I once excavated the outer portions of a ruin and found part of a sculpture there… The surrounding aboriginal culture has also recorded this matter.” The slender blue-haired Magus with a goatee was speaking excitedly.

His name was Pharen. Though he was merely a rank 1 official Magus, he was unusually interested in travelling and adventures. He had once explored many famous ruins and had a great reputation amongst wandering Magi.

Leylin listened quietly while sitting beside him, occasionally asking a few questions and providing opinions, which caused Pharen’s eyes to sparkle.

With his current knowledge, there were few in Twilight Zone who could be compared with him. With just a few words, Pharen was full of praise for him.

Leylin chatted with him once in a while, forcing down the anxiety in his heart.

“I forcefully made a prophecy while disregarding the damage done to the Coin of Destiny. I finally found out that the way to improve further is in the west, but now that I’m here and almost at the Magma Sea, why haven’t I discovered anything yet?”

Leylin dug his hands into his bosom and caressed the surface of the coin of destiny.

On the simple gold coin, there were already two fine cracks, causing Leylin to feel pain in his heart.

“Oh! By the way, may I know what Sir Reynold’s intentions are in accompanying me deep inside here?” Pharen asked.

This was a question that had been in his heart for a long time.

“This is the common territory of the dark elves and dwarves. Though us humans have now seized control, if they see us in the outskirts, we could easily be surrounded and attacked.”

“There are a few things I have to take care of. Besides, I want to see that magnificent scene you mentioned about the lava tides.” Leylin laughed slightly in answer.

Pharen’s eyes brightened, feeling like he had found someone who could understand himself.

“Not bad. Based on my guesses, the lava tides that are going to burst out will be the largest in a whole century! They might even surge to the surface!” Pharen’s face was flushed.

“That’s impossible. There are several hundred kilometres of earth crust until we reach the surface!” While Leylin said this, his heart suddenly lurched.

The surface? This was something worth considering. Perhaps the directions from the coin of destiny had to do with this.

Of course, Leylin was not going to start fantasising and think that he could use the magma and break through the crust. That was something even Morning Star Magi might not be able to do.

“But this is still possible in theory. As long as I find a suitable place and channel, such as a volcano…”

Leylin touched his chin, thinking that he would need to inspect a few lava lakes that could link him to the surface.

While Leylin was deep in thought, a strange undulation caused him to awaken in surprise.

“This is…” Red rays flashed in his eyes, “A resonance with my bloodline… Who is it?”

He abruptly looked in a direction, stirred up and grim.

“What’s going on?” Pharen waved his hand curiously, and the carriage stopped.

Immediately after, he felt Magi’s energy fluctuations travelling from the direction Leylin was looking at.

“So it’s a battle between Magi! Sir Reynold’s acuity is truly admirable!” Pharen sighed in heartfelt awe.

Just this extraordinary sensory ability made it clear that this Magus called Reynold was ranked far above him.

An energy aura far away sensed something and began to head in this direction at a mad dash.

“Sir Reynold, it looks like they are going to use us as a shield!” Pharen sneered.

Such a scheme was as crude and laughable as a little tease in the eyes of Magi. However, seeing someone dared provoke himself, Pharen’s eyes flashed with an icy glint.

*Shoo!* A brownish-yellow ray launched over.

The response from his bloodline became more intense.

The yellow light stopped in front of the carriage, revealing a middle-aged Magus. His skin let off a bronze light, and there were numerous traces of burning on his skin. The lines on his face were resolute, and even while heavily injured, he still emanated the charm of a mature man. What was even more eye-catching were his eyes, which was a pair of amber pupils!

“A Warlock! He’s definitely a Warlock, and he has a deep relationship with my bloodline!”

Leylin’s eyes met with the other’s, and they immediately understood each other’s identities.

After seeing Leylin, the middle-aged Magus’ expression slackened and he produced something like an emblem to Leylin, “My lord, please save me!”

He used the Byron Language, which was a mandatory subject for all Magi. Leylin naturally understood.

*Thud!* As if he had relaxed too much, the middle-aged man could not hold on any longer and collapsed, fainting on the ground.

*Pak!* The emblem accurately fell in the palm of Leylin’s hand.

Chapter 388: Mankestre Bloodline Warlock

The emblem was rather small, the back being a bronze base.

After seeing the symbol on the front, Leylin’s pupils suddenly shrunk.

It was a giant black serpent formed from numerous runes, holding its tail in its mouth and forming a strange circular imprint.

“That symbol! I’ve seen it before in the Dylan Gardens!” Leylin obviously would not have forgotten this. The memory was still fresh in his mind.

When he was in the Dylan Gardens, there was a large oil painting of this black snake holding its tail in its mouth in Great Magus Serholm’s inheritance. Behind that oil painting had been where Leylin had obtained Kemoyin’s Pupil.

This symbol could be said to mark the beginning of Leylin’s path as a Warlock!

“Him being a Warlock, the resonance of our bloodlines, and the symbol!” Leylin weighed the emblem in his palm, “Looks like he was what the Coin of Destiny was leading me towards.”

“What? Reynold, you know him?” Old Pharen asked.

“No, but I need to rescue him.” Leylin’s tone was light but held within an unquestionable resolve.

“My apologies, but if you insist, we can only part ways here. I don’t want to meet with any trouble.”

As a Magus, Pharen instinctively declined.

A rank 1 Magus like that usually represented some form of trouble, and Pharen had no wish to provoke it.

Besides, he and Leylin had merely met en route and just got along well. He wasn’t close enough to Leylin that he’d take risks for him.

“Of course. You can leave first.” Leylin answered, not finding Pharen’s choice strange.

If Pharen was the type to ardently insist on staying with him, he wouldn’t have been able to live to this age.

“I’m sorry!” With an apologetic look on his face, he made to get on the carriage and leave.

“Stop right there!” At this moment, a sudden sound was heard, bringing with it a loud boom.

Five or six streaks of glaring lights shone over from the skies, and by the time the shine dissipated, the figures of six different Magi had appeared.

They were evidently a mix of races, and the presence of dark elves and dwarves surprised Leylin,

*Rumble!* Amidst the flying dust, a group of elite Underground Winter Spider knights and dwarven soldiers hurried over.

“Human Magus?”

The dwarf and dark elf in charge furrowed their brows after seeing Leylin and Pharen.

Twilight Zone was now a place where the human race had the highest status. Even in the outer regions, human Magi would be respected. Of course, if they were in the desolate outskirts, there would be situations where these races murdered humans and robbed them of their treasures.

Although such acts occurred, there would be no traces left behind, lest the humans use it as a cause to invade.

It was difficult to eliminate two Magi and prevent news from spreading.

“This is a despicable thief that stole the sacred item that our two races are jointly protecting. Magi, please don’t misunderstand!” The dark elven and dwarven Magi warned them.

“Protecting a sacred item? What is it?” Leylin curiously scanned the unconscious middle-aged Warlock with his spiritual force and then found a green bundle of vines in his arms.

A concentrated life force extended from within the vine ball.

“So it’s this!” A look of understanding flashed in Leylin’s eyes.

This bundle of vines was actually called the Vitality Fruitvine, and it held within a large amount of life force essence. To those races that trained in meditation techniques like the dark elves’ Life Absorption, it was truly invaluable.

It could replenish much life force and treat injuries or even save lives and was naturally thought of highly by soldiers and the artisan dwarves. That was why these two races were looking after it together.

The reason why Leylin was so knowledgeable on this was because this fruit had always been a major product in the dark elves’ and dwarves’ yearly offerings, and Leylin enjoyed a whole portion of them alone.

Because of him, there was a shortage of these Vitality Fruitvines. Even the theft of one fruit would result in one getting in much trouble and being hunted down.

“Though you are human Magi, these sacred items have to be offered up to the Guardian of the Realm, Lord Leylin!”

Seeing Leylin still unmoved, a dark elf threatened.

“Magus Reynold, you’ve brought me trouble!” Pharen laughed bitterly.

Pharen naturally knew of the famous Guardian of the Realm. Se was the ruler of the entirety of Twilight Zone!

Even he, a wandering Magus, had many mentors and acolytes to take care of. He could not truly break away from them.

At the mention of the legendary rank 3 Magus, Pharen seemed to have plans of casting away this troublesome matter. “Reynold, we…”

“Pfft-!” Leylin could not hold it in and began to laugh.

The smile on his face became so big that he even bent down, holding his belly with both hands, unable to rein in his laughter.

“Human Magus, why are you laughing?” Their leaders exchanged a glance, having a bad feeling.

At this time, they took note of the handsome young man in front of them, his face seeming to be exceptionally familiar with them.

“It’s the first time someone’s used my own name to threaten me!” After laughing, Leylin’s expression darkened.

At the same time, there was a strange change to his face, as if there was a spontaneous removal of some concealing method.

An aura similar to the awakening of an ancient wild beast began to emanate from his body.

*Thud! Thud! Thud! Thud!* The eight legs of the Underground Winter Spiders began to tremble and they weakly fell to the ground. The Underground Winter Spider knights and Dwarven soldiers all fell.

Leylin took a step forward, and space seemed to freeze.

The six Magi in mid-air were forced to the ground, expressions full of terror.

“You- You- You’re Leylin Farlier, the Guardian of Twilight Zone, the Great Emperor of the Night!”

Pharen’s mouth widened, his goatee sticking up. His fingers were trembling and he was so scared he was almost unable to speak.

Goodness! So the one who had been journeying with him was the lord Guardian whose name had spread far and wide? The one who was almost deified?

Pharen immediately searched through his memories until he found he had not said anything unpleasant about Nature’s Alliance or Leylin himself, and then heaved a sigh of relief.

After that, however, his heart got stuck in his throat once more.

Previously, he had been planning on leaving Leylin and that Magus to flee for his life. Would this behaviour gain the displeasure of the Radiant Guardian?

Compared to the inner conflicts Pharen had, the blow Leylin’s appearance had towards these other races was completely different.

“Greetings to lord Guardian of the Realm!” The dark elven and dwarven Magi immediately bowed.

Even if he were a fake, the unique energy undulations from a rank 3 Magus could not be mistaken.

The Magi of both races had a very deep impression of Leylin’s expression, and even if they were turned to dust, they would not get it wrong.

After all, Leylin had destroyed the splendour their two races had possessed, and even killed their rulers brazenly!

Leylin was now like a devil king or monster to them.

“En! Tell the people behind you that I’m going to take this man. This Vitality Fruitvine will also be considered part of this year’s portion.” Leylin indifferently ordered.

He was not planning to use raw force because that would just be bullying them.

“Understood, my lord.” The dark elven and dwarven Magi heaved a long sigh, bowed, and then withdrew quickly as if there was a great monster chasing them.

The news of Leylin’s appearance here was much too mind-blowing, and they had to bring this news to their higher-ups immediately to be able to respond.

……

“Are you awake? If you are, come here!” The middle-aged Magus opened his eyes, Leylin’s voice sounding by his ear.

He immediately got up and saw Leylin standing aside, playing with a test tube full of blood. Within that test tube were strands of earthen-yellow that had congealed, unable to scatter.

“Kubler greets my lord!” he immediately knelt respectfully, looking deferential and awed, as if a wolf that had seen its king.

Leylin had sensed this. He had the feeling that through his bloodline, he could influence this Magus.

This was a terrifying thing.

“The Huge Mankestre Snake! Your bloodline comes from the Wilted Huge Mankestre Snake.” Leylin concluded.

“Yes. Warlock of the Mankestre Bloodline, Kubler, greets my lord!” he bowed once more.

“No wonder…” Leylin shook his head.

He finally understood the strange feeling he got from this man.

The Wilted Huge Snake Mankestre was said to have a trace of the bloodline of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Though it was thinned out, it was still a descendant of the Kemoyin Serpent.

In the face of a true Warlock of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, it was natural to be affected and suppressed by him.

When Leylin was still an acolyte, he had once seen a Huge Mankestre Snake. Though it was still young, it was enough to cause him a headache.

The matured body of this Huge Mankestre Snake was comparable to that of an official Magus. Though it was nothing in Leylin’s eyes now, that was a terrifying strength for acolytes.

“Well then, tell me your history and your reason in coming here.”

Leylin spoke expressionlessly, though his eyes were enough for Kubler’s heart to turn cold.

Though he could not use spirit-searching spells on official Magi, it was very easy for Leylin, a Warlock who had already advanced to rank 3, to completely smash the spirit and extract spirit fragments from him.

Though he would not get a complete set of information if he did that, and this Warlock would definitely die, it was very possible.

Fortunately, Kubler was evidently a sharp-witted man and deathly afraid of Leylin. Soon enough, he systematically narrated his origins.

After hearing a few words, Leylin’s expression became grim.

Chapter 389: Central Continent

Kubler claimed to be a Magus from the central continent.

The hometown of the great Magus Serholm, the core of the entire Magus world, The sacred land of Magi—the central continent!

As for why Kubler was at this place, Leylin could not care less. On the contrary, he was very interested in the route Kubler had taken to get here.

If they were to walk this path in the opposite direction, would they be able to successfully reach the central continent? Leylin spoke the question in his mind,

Kubler’s face showed a moment of hesitation before he respectfully divulged the truth, ”In actual fact, the surface right above this subterranean world is the central continent! I learnt of the exact spot where the lava erupts from a research manual passed down through my family. After calculating the weaker points in the lava, I followed the pathway to arrive at this place.

Having heard Kubler’s account, Leylin more or less understood the procedure of his entrance.

On the whole, this was like what he had previously envisaged, and would also explain why the other party’s body had horrifying burn wounds—no matter how precise his calculations of the lava’s weak points were, the flames and the high temperature were not something a rank 1 Magus could bear.

If he had not by chanced upon the Life Vined Fruit, he might have already become a charred corpse!

“Mmm! I already settled the inconvenience with the dark elves and dwarves. You can have this as a reward for being open with your information!” Leylin waved his hands and threw the Life Vined Fruit into Kubler’s hands.

“Thank you, my Lord!” A tinge of gratitude appeared on Kubler’s face.

To him, managing to keep his life had already been a huge reward. As for the fruit that was full of vitality, it was a welcome surprise.

*Sizzle!* A few fine red blood vessels sprouted forth from his fingers, drilled into the insides of the fruit, and started to draw large amounts of life essence.

With a lively green radiance appearing on his body, his burn wounds recovered quickly. The scars gradually faded, eventually disappearing without a trace.

The scene reminded Leylin of the parasitic body of the Huge Mankestre Snake he had seen as an acolyte. The two seemed to have a certain level of similarity in their abilities.

Moreover, the method of directly drawing in vitality seemed to be inspired by the meditation techniques that could absorb others’ spiritual force.

Of course, those were all small matters.

Having seen Kubler’s state improving, Leylin then asked him about the Black Serpent emblem “Also, this symbol. What meaning does it actually have?”

“What? My lord actually doesn’t know?” His response further surprised Leylin, but Kubler calmed down a moment after his reaction. “It doesn’t matter, the bloodline cannot be faked.”

After seeing Leylin’s look of puzzlement, Kubler immediately explained to Leylin: “This is a symbol of our organisation—the Ouroboros Clan!”

“The Ouroboros Clan?” Leylin nodded, that name was indeed very vivid: “Is that an organisation of Bloodline Warlocks?”

“Yes! Furthermore, within the Ouroboros Clan, we only accept Warlocks who hold the bloodline of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent or its descendants!” Kubler answered very certainly.

“Additionally, a Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock with great power, simply by joining the Ouroboros Clan, could instantly obtain a relatively high rank…” he added after shooting Leylin a glance.

“Since this is the case, then I have nothing much to hide!” Leylin laughed. “In actual fact, I too am a wandering Magus. I came to Twilight Zone by accident and chanced upon the inheritance of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent among historical remains! It was there that I first saw the symbol of the Ouroboros Clan!”

Leylin spoke honestly. Even though he spoke vaguely, and did not reveal any real details, Kubler was smart enough to not ask further.

On the contrary, he fed large amounts of information regarding the central continent to Leylin.

From this information, and records that he had obtained from ancient books, Leylin finally pieced together an image of the Sacred land of the Magi.

The central continent was the core of the Magus World. It spanned across a huge area, and had an abundance of precious resources!

There, official Magi were as common as the clouds, and rank 2 Magi were the elites! Rank 3 Magi were respected, although there were different ranks to them. Only Morning Star Magi truly held clout.

Organisations in the central continent needed a Morning Star Magus to oversee their development if they hoped to grow in power. Some small organisations were occasionally built by rank 2 or rank 3 Magi, but they were short-lived, typically being destroyed after a short period of time.

“You say we have Warlocks at the Morning Star realm overseeing the Ouroboros Clan?” Leylin was most interested in this.

After all, they were rank 4 Warlocks with the bloodline of Giant Kemoyin Serpents! This was clearly his path ahead!

“Yes!” Kubler was clearly very pleased with Leylin’s usage of “we,” with his tone and expressions being much intimate.

“Among the ranks of our Ouroboros Clan, the Grand Elder, Second Elder, and Third Elder have all reached rank 4. If they joined forces, they could even contend with a rank 5 Radiant Moon Magus! As a result, our Ouroboros Clan could be said to have some fame in the central continent!” Having said this, Kubler clearly felt proud.

“Rank 5! Radiant Moon Magus?” A doubtful expression crossed Leylin’s face, and he asked Kubler to clarify the rankings of Magi after the Morning Star realm.

Official Magi had a total of 9 ranks, and they were respectively termed Magi from rank 1 to 9.

And for every 3 ranks, there would be an extremely large bottleneck.

From rank 1 Magi to rank 3 Magi, and from the rank 4 Magi to rank 6 Magi, and eventually rank 7 and above, the differences between them was extremely terrifying.

The central continent was slowly regaining the splendor of ancient times.

Not only were rank 4 Morning Star Magi becoming common, even rank 5 Radiant Moon Magi and rank 6 Breaking Dawn Magi would appear periodically.

Morning Star, Radiant Moon, and Breaking Dawn were the honorific titles of rank 4, 5 and 6 Magi respectively.

“Am I akin to a moon or sun?” Leylin laughed in his heart, “However, just a Morning Star Magus has a lifespan of more than a thousand years and possesses tremendous strength. The even greater glory and radiance rank 5 and 6 Grand Magi possess can be understood from just that…”

Kubler had not discovered Leylin’s thoughts and continued to narrate, “I don’t qualify to know about what comes after the Breaking Dawn realm. Moreover, the few Magi who are at rank 6 are all the most influential leaders of the central continent, and are titled our ‘Kings!’”

“King of Magi? This term has a lot of meaning to it!” Leylin nodded.

“There are three main powers in the central continent. The Warlocks tied together by bloodlines, the Magus organisations that hold a lot of high-grade meditation techniques, and the Academies where various powers mingle with each other! Together, these three sets control over 70 percent of the resources and land of the entire continent. The rest is occupied by an assortment of human Magi and other species…”

With Kubler’s description, a blueprint of the central continent gradually appeared in Leylin’s mind.

Strange species! Large amounts of resources! High-ranked Magi! And a larger stage and space for improvement!

A flame ignited within Leylin’s eyes, as well as an even stronger urge to immediately rush towards the central continent.

Immediately, he suppressed the desire and impulse.

“Alright! Now can you explain to me why you would risk your life to escape from the central continent?”

Leylin’s eyes that radiated coldness glanced into Kubler’s, which immediately made the latter feel a chill in his heart.

“Ac… Actually…” Kubler’s did not look good. After which he knelt down before Leylin, and placed his forehead tightly on the ground.

“Lord Leylin! Please accept me as one of your henchmen!”

“What do you mean? Please explain yourself clearly!” Leylin’s face remained unchanged. After which, he heard some untasteful stories from Kubler.

To put things simply, Kubler had offended someone in the Ouroboros Clan, which had left him with no choice but to leave. Now, he wished to obtain Leylin’s protection so as to once again return.

Honestly speaking, from the looks of the central continent Magi, the subterranean world and other areas were all desolate. If not for the fact that he was forced into such circumstances, why would he willingly leave his hometown?

“Why do you think I can protect you?” Leylin desired to know. Before asking clearly, he would not easily promise anything.

“Of course! My lord has already achieved rank 3, and is a Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock, with a bright future. How can people like us rival that?” Kubler said matter-of-factly, and had a faint tone of admiration and inferiority.

“This subordinate has offended a Black Horrall Snake Warlock, who has the potential to at most grow to rank 3. The high-ranked officers of the Ouroboros Clan would definitely not side with him…”

“Growth potential?” Leylin was alarmed and understood that he heard something extremely important.

“Does My lord not know yet?” Kubler, on the other hand, had already in favour of himself, changed his address of Leylin.

“The inheritance I obtained did not contain any object in this area, please detailedly explain!” Leylin’s face looked upset. His heart had a bad omen.

“Yes! Subordinate will not hide anything!” Kubler’s attitude was extremely upright, and he had started to follow the standards of vassals; Leylin could not be bothered to correct him.

As Kubler narrated, Leylin’s face got gloomier, and eventually was like that of the sky before an imminent storm.

Chapter 391: Planning for the Afterlife

“No, don’t worry! I have better plans!”

Leylin smiled faintly: “Furthermore, I still have some things to settle here….”

Kubler’s heart was too full of worry. He wondered whether his Lord was going to wait a hundred years for the next cycle.

Mankestre Bloodline Warlocks like him did not have a long lifespan. He could, at most, last two or three hundred years. A hundred years was, to him, a significant portion of his lifespan!

But… Kubler looked at the man whom he now served. As a vassal, the Lord has the last say, so what more could he do than laugh bitterly?

“I’ll be heading out for a while. Stay here and monitor the lava flow data, and contact me periodically using our secret imprints. In the meanwhile, use the special rocks here to make one of these. All you have to do is follow this blueprint!”

A fluorescent blue light flashed in Leylin’s eyes. It took him but a moment to form a design and imprint it into a crystal ball.

Kubler’s face changed slightly as he received it, and he respectfully lowered his head. “Yes, my Lord!”

“Alright!” Moments after the order was given, Leylin transformed into a dark silhouette and disappeared.

A black streak pierced through the sky, creating friction with the air and leaving behind an ear-piercing screech.

Even if he had time to prepare, it was running out, so it was important to make the most of it!

Nature’s Alliance, North Twilight Zone.

Celine sat behind the huge and luxurious office table and stretched lazily, revealing her perfect curves.

Although doing irksome corrections and office affairs every day was very troublesome, she found the tiring job enjoyable.

It made every cell in her body shiver with excitement — and even made her slightly moist down below — every time she thought about how every word she put to paper, even every sentence she uttered, would make a big difference to the fates of numerous acolytes and even Magi.

“But it is a pity that my position here is not fully secured….” Celine glanced at her flat and smooth abdomen, a rather reluctant expression on her face.

“What’s wrong? Are you still grumbling that you’re not with child?”

The voice of a young man suddenly sounded from inside the office.

“Ra… Radiant Guardian!”

When the other female Magi and office administrators saw Leylin, they could not contain the excitement in their eyes. Files were overturned and cups of tea spilled as they rushed to bow.

“Mmm!” Leylin said as he nodded and waved.

All the Magi except Celine left the office quickly, completely silent.

“Yes!” Celine looked into Leylin’s eyes without fear.

Although the mental state of this impeccably handsome man was rather decent, his attire was somewhat dusty and messy.

‘Could this be the aftermath of rushing and being nervous?’ As a keen and observant woman, Celine immediately realized this…

“Leylin, you’re currently standing at the peak of Twilight Zone. One step and you can turn the entirety of it into a Magus kingdom, and pass it on through the generations!” Celine’s voice held a mixture of excitement and confusion, “A child! All you need is a child! An inheritor to your power!”

Her eyes clouded up as she hugged Leylin.

If it was the past, Leylin definitely would not hesitate to argue with her over it. But now, Celine noticed the calm in Leylin’s eyes; calm like the still waters of an old well.

A realization hit Celine, making her immediately sink into immense fear. The day she loses Leylin’s affection would be the day she loses everything. This was also the reason why she strongly wished to bear Leylin’s child.

Even as she struggled to think of a method to show her affection, Leylin’s next words beat her down into the abyss.

“I have to go!”

“You’re going?” Celine was feeling slightly giddy, “Where to?”

“I’m leaving this place! Leaving Twilight Zone!” Leylin paused at every word, making sure Celine heard everything clearly.

“Are you mad? Why do you want to leave this place? You’re the king here! You’re my sun and my star. You are my everything….”

What would happen once Leylin leaves? The mere thought of scenarios that might happen if he followed through with his words made Celine sink into extreme fear. She hugged Leylin tightly, tears flashing at the corners of her eyes.

And yet, Leylin cruelly pushed her away, his hand cold as steel.

Celine calmed down and gazed at the emotionless Leylin.

“As you know, I’m actually not even a Magus of Twilight Zone, it was all an accident!” Leylin slowly said.

Regarding his history, after going through so many interactions and investigations, this woman had probably speculated a lot already.

Sure enough, Celine’s face remained unchanged and she evidently did not feel surprised.

“I seek the pinnacle of the Magus world. The scene of different worlds from the top will be the most beautiful view one could ever hope for… So I cannot stop advancing. I must continue forward until I achieve my goal! I believe you too can understand this!”

Leylin looked into the depths of Celine’s eyes.

At this moment, Celine had already completely calmed down. ‘Or rather, was it all just an act before?’ Leylin’s thoughts stopped here as he couldn’t help but secretly feel a little annoyed.

“I do! I’ve always known that when this place is can no longer fulfill your requirements any further, you would leave. I fully understand that, but I never thought that our separation would be this quick, or in this manner!”

Celine chuckled bitterly as she combed through her messy hair.

“Fate is unpredictable!” Leylin tried to hide the news about the central continent. “Plus, I’ve also made appropriate arrangements!”

“What arrangements? I can’t keep the other races and rank 2 Magi in check. Even I rose the ranks to the peak with your help, I’m only a rank 1 Magus, not someone they’ll listen to!” Celine was indeed very realistic and had already accepted the reality of Leylin leaving and was already planning her own future.

*Swish!* Leylin flicked his finger and a black ray of light penetrated the window, landing on the huge black stone sculpture in the plaza in front of the teaching block.

*Buzz!* The sculpture started trembling and a thin barrier of light flickered at the top.

“I left some of my aura on this sculpture. As long as my main body doesn’t die, this barrier of light will never dissipate… Believe in the deterrence of this rank 3 Magus and you’ll still be able to continue for a very long time!”

Other than being a clear indicator of whether he was dead or alive, there was absolutely nothing else that was useful about this aura.

But as long as the Magi of Twilight Zone knew that Leylin was still alive somewhere, he would be a terrifying deterrence to them. And this was a way of assuring that the relations and power he left behind still existed!

“Good! What else?” Celine’s voice finally contained some hope.

“These!” Leylin handed her a few fine, white crystal chips.

“These are some spirit sources that I control: Iren, Gogoer and a few Rank 2 Magi! As long as they’re in your hands, there will never come a day where they betray you!”

These Magi were the core strength of Nature’s Alliance. In fact, as long as Celine had them under her control, the entirety of Nature’s Alliance would be subject to her manipulation.

As long as there was no internal conflict, Nature’s Alliance was the most powerful in the entire Twilight Zone. Even if Leylin suddenly went missing and caused a stir, it would not affect Nature’s Alliance too much.

After all, this was still Leylin’s backup plan. He still had the treasures of the Icy World waiting to be excavated and he would not give up on them so easily. This was also the reason why Leylin specially rushed back to prepare. Celine herself wasn’t an important enough reason for him to return.

“Besides, when I disappear, you can simply claim that I’ve gone to a secret facility for research. Anyway, it’s common for high-rank Magi to spend a decade on research, no?”

“Alright, good bye!” Leylin finally said and left.

This was similar to how a person working at an office would act before leaving every morning. Leylin simply left after a few words, not at all like someone who was going to leave for someplace far away.

In any case, Leylin had already seen Celine for who she was: a woman whose heart will never truly be moved. She was just calculative and thirsty for power. Looking at her suppressed excitement as she held the spirit sources, she must have already been rejoicing on the inside.

“Hold on! This will not be the last time right? What I said before was true, I will take care of your bloodlines, and turn them into the Guardian of the next generation…” Celine bit her lower lip.

“I’m sorry. I don’t have much time!” Leylin’s figure transformed into a black ray of light and he shot into mid-air, disappearing into the horizon in a flash.

Leylin understood Celine’s plans very well.

Bloodlines of high-leveled Magi were hard to come by. Furthermore, he progressed incredibly fast. Celine thought that his bloodline was from an ancient, fearful creature. Hence, she wanted him to leave some of his seeds behind.

In actual fact, Leylin was now a first generation Bloodline Warlock. The blood descendants he left behind would also have the Kemoyin’s Bloodline and would naturally be Warlocks! With a bit of nurturing, they would be unbelievably strong!

But why would Leylin do that? Even when he fooled around with numerous girls before, he had secretly controlled his secretion and made sure not to leave any descendants behind.

A clink sounded in Celine’s hands as Leylin walked away, leaving behind remnants of a delicate gold cup.

She always had great confidence in her charm and knowledge, but looking at the situation now, it seemed like Leylin did not have the slightest bit of concern towards her. This hurt her pride badly.

But a smile crept onto her face once again as she stared at the huge number of spirit sources in her palms.

Now that Leylin had left, the power of Nature’s Alliance truly lied in her hands! A wave of happiness drowned her heart as her face flushed.

Everything had happened just as how Leylin had predicted. Under Celine’s leadership, Nature’s Alliance naturally became stronger.

Though there was unrest in the Twilight Zone for the 10 years after Leylin’s absence, it would still be contained.

This, too, was related to Leylin’s prior subjugation of the power-hungry Twilight Zone Magi and the major powers of other races.

Gradually, the tales of Radiant Guardian Leylin turned into a legend. As for Leylin, a new journey was just beginning for him…

Chapter 392: The Central Continent

Magma roiled around like water in a rough sea, emitting heat waves that swept across, a hint of the incredible power beneath.

A sheet of golden liquid lay at its center, as if a lake within the lake. However, this magnificent sheet could stop Magi in their steps.

Above the lava lay a giant passage, tiny voices sounding from it now and then. The rock around this passage was very hard, and no one knew where it led.

*Swish!* A silhouette appeared on the shores of the lake. The light dispersed to show a very young Magus, his long black hair tied up casually and his skin fine and smooth. His handsome face was filled with the dignity of a ruler.

This was naturally Leylin, but his robe was currently a little dusty. The hurried round trip had drained him.

“My Lord!” a middle-aged Magus with bronze skin saluted.

“Are you finished?” Leylin asked casually.

“Yes! Please follow me!” Kubler led Leylin to a hole he’d dug near the lake.

A giant ball lay at the center. The dark ball seemed to made of stone, its surface was a glossy black. On a side of the ball was a door which revealed that it was hollow.

“According to your blueprint and orders, all parts were made from the hardest layer of this metamorphic rock to bear the high temperature of the central magma. The joints were even reinforced by runes…” He reported at Leylin’s side like a loyal servant.

He didn’t even mention the difficulty in collecting the rock and casting it into shape.

“Good job!” Leylin nodded, looking at the runes inside the ball with surprise.

This Mankestre bloodline Warlock was much better than he’d expected at alchemy.

“No, it’s my pleasure to serve my lord, there is no trouble at all!” Kubler saluted humbly with his hands crossed before his chest.

This sort of respect was expected in front of Magi with higher bloodlines. Kubler had grown used to it during his time in the Ouroboros Clan.

“The lava lake is becoming more active recently. I’m afraid this means that it’s about to erupt!”

At that time, the place would be flooded with lava, blocking the entirety of the passage.

Kubler had come down here when the volcano was dormant, and had still suffered horrific burns. This had left him in fear of the lava. Although he went with his lord’s plan, he was still worried. However, the servant had no right to make the final decision. He could only make suggestions and had to follow his master’s orders.

“I understand. The eruption will occur in an hour and 23 minutes. Prepare yourself!” With the A.I. Chip’s ability to observe and forecast the eruption, Leylin knew the timing much better than Kubler did.

He had run this plan by his A.I. Chip’s calculations, and the success rate was over 90%. Why would he risk his life if not?

More than an hour later…

A black ball was floating on the red lava as if it was in the water.

Kubler sat inside with Leylin, face pale. Watching the lava outside through a magic screen, he stammered out, “My… my Lord, this plan is too dangerous!”

Once the ball was crushed, they would be devoured by endless lava! Even if he was a Magus, this kind of horrifying death made him shiver.

“Calm down!” Leylin stared at lava outside calmly.

*Blub! Blub!* The lava had reached its boiling point, and the whole cave began to tremble, dust falling off the walls.

[Beep! Eruption will occur in 10, 9, 8…]

The A.I. Chip had begun the final countdown.

“Now!” Leylin’s eyes flashed, and the terrifying strength of a rank 3 Magus burst forth.

“Freeze!” With his hands as the centre, a layer of deep blue ice spread out along the walls. Cracking sounds rang out as this phenomenon soon extended to the outside, enveloping the ball in ice.

This ice was so cold even the boiling lava could not melt it. White vapours arose as the two surfaces came into contact.

“This can earn us some time!” Leylin said with a smile, and then looked at the screen of the A.I. Chip.

[3! 2! 1! Critical limit reached!]

*Boom!* With the prompt of the A.I. Chip, Leylin and Kubler felt tremors envelop the ball. It was like they had entered the body of a terrifying ancient monster, and that monster had woken up with a thundering roar!

“AAAAAAH!” Kubler screamed with fear, his hands waving around as he struggled to find something to hold on to.

Then, he felt a force that could be from the explosion of the universe as a huge impulse hit the bottom of the rock ball. The lava rose into the sky like a dragon taking flight, except this dragon had a small rock ball on the front.

Lava surrounded them and rushed into the passage. The ball shook continuously as it hit wall after wall, but what frightened Kubler to death was instead the high gravity!

As the ball had rushed up like a rocket, the two inside dealt with an equally large gravitational force.

The intense force pulled at Kubler’s skin, making him feel like he was being bitten all over by ants. The pain made him lie on the ground like a frog, and he felt like if he wasn’t a Warlock with a strengthened body, he would have died long ago.

Booms sounded out and the trembling continued. The terrifying power of nature made Kubler feel like a tiny ant. All he could do now was pray; pray for an early release from this torment, pray that this rock ball would hold out

Thumps and explosive noises continued to sound out. This was a giant volcanic range, and today its central volcano had accumulated enough pressure to erupt.

Masses of black smog were ejected into the sky, forming a sea of gray clouds that shrouded the nearby lands in darkness.

Rivulets of lava flowed down the mountain slopes, looking like arteries on flesh.

*BOOM!* Finally, with a huge explosion that caused an earthquake, the volcano erupted.

It was as if heaven and earth were torn asunder, and the world was ruined. Red lava, dotted with gold, burst into the sky transforming into countless fire dragons that flew in every direction.

Fire raged, and explosions rang forth even as the earth quaked. It was like armageddon.

Amidst this terrifying lava were multiple rocks. Boulders that were as large as hills hit the ground with great force, cracking the earth underneath and ruining everything around them.

*Bang!* Among the countless boulders in the sky was one rock with a particularly regular shape.

This rock ball streaked across the ground, leaving behind it a long track of burnt black. The surface of the ball was still a dull red, as if it was ready to melt any moment.

The ball soon began to crack apart, and a portion was thrown off with a bang, revealing a hollow interior.

“So this is the central continent ?” Leylin came out of the ball, exhaling a breath that was as hot as fire itself.

The hellish scene nearby did not affect him. Instead, he was filled with delightful anticipation. “The central continent, here I come.” he murmured in his mind.

It took a while for Kubler to slowly crawl out of the ball, coughing. His body was in a mess, with some burn marks on it.

The layer of ice Leylin had made had been thawed within a few dozen seconds of the eruption. Afterwards, the rock ball had heated up to extremely high temperatures. They would have been roasted had they not been Magi.

“Exciting! This is so exciting!” After retching for a while, Kubler wiped his sweat off, fear in his eyes.

“Relax! We got out safely, didn’t we?” Leylin turned back and smiled. “It’s quite fair for us to pay a small price for concentrating a day’s journey into a few minutes!”

“Yes, my Lord!” Kubler could do nothing but smile.

“So is this the central continent?” Seeing Kubler collect himself, Leylin wanted to confirm it with him.

“Yes!” Kubler said even as his expression turned complicated, “This is the Mt. Asura of the central continent. The land that we are standing on now is undoubtedly of the central continent.”

……

Three days later, in a small town.

A giant gleaming revolving gate swung around as carriages and people wearing strange clothes passed by, some of them official Magi.

Leylin was sitting in a hotel room, the pudding and juice in front of him all but untouched. He was staring outside with a dreamy gaze.

At that time, the door was opened with a thump and Kubler stepped in.

“My Lord! I’ve bought tickets for an airship heading to the Black River Domain that leaves tomorrow morning! In at most four days, we will arrive at the headquarters of the Ouroboros Clan!” His voice was tinted with excitement.

Chapter 395: A Scene

“I would like to walk around for a while, you may leave here!”

Leylin saw a hint of disappointment in Jessia’s eyes after he told her that, and Nolan heaved a sigh of relief.

He chuckled as he turned around and raised his hand and disappeared among the stream of people, with Kubler immediately following.

With his astonishing senses, Leylin faintly heard two people behind him arguing in constrained voices.

“This is really….” Leylin shook his head, “Instead of focusing your limited energy on pursuing the truth, you focus on such things…”

“But I suppose this is probably a commoner’s pleasure right!”

He nodded his head after shaking it, called out to Kubler and continued his journey.

“After entering the Black River Domain, the Ouroboros Clan Headquarters—Phosphorescence Swamp will be very near…” Kubler was naturally very familiar with this place and had a tinge of both fear and longing.

After hiring a horse chariot, both he and Leylin enjoyed the scenery along the way.

If they had hastened on with their journey, they would not have been so slow in progress. However, Leylin was not in a hurry and had wanted to enjoy the sights and sounds of the central continent, hence he chose to travel by chariot.

As night fell, the two arrived at a small town.

Accommodations at the inn were cramped, and the air was filled with the odour of alcohol, sweat, and manure.

Leylin furrowed his brows at such conditions. Since this was the only inn in town, he still reluctantly accepted it as it was still better than spending the night in the open.

After putting down their luggage, Leylin and Kubler headed to the main hall intending to have a meal.

The menu for dinner was beef and potato stew with some fresh vegetables. That was all the town had to offer. Surprisingly it was deliciously prepared with an enticing scent to boost one’s appetite.

“Huh?” At this moment, Kubler’s expression changed.

A gush of profound ash-colored dust started stirring from the main door of the inn, spreading continuously and extending to the other parts of the inn enveloping other travellers and the owners themselves.

*Crackle! Crackle!*

The commoners, whose bodies were covered with the ash-colored dust all stood frozen, their bodies as stiff as a candle.

“It’s a freezing spell! There is a Magus around and we are the target!”

A shocked Kubler stood up and exclaimed with anger. Yellow energy emerged from his body and spread all around.

A circular radiance surrounded their round table, protecting them against the fate of the other travellers.

Leylin was totally unfazed by what was happening and was still enjoying the town-brewed wheat wine.

*Bang!*

The wooden main door burst open and 2 Magi wearing black robes entered the room. In front of their chest, Leylin saw the familiar red ruby emblem.

“Nolan! We meet again!” Leylin raised his glass and greeted casually.

Indeed, Nolan was among the two entrants. He had a vexed expression and stood, glaring at Leylin. “Where is Jessia? Where? Hand her over!”

“Jessia? Isn’t she with you?”

Leylin chuckled.

“She left! I thought she was abducted. Based on the location markings marked on her body, I am sure she is here!” Nolan’s eyes turned red.

“Location markings?” Leylin laughed in amusement, “How insecure are you? To put such a spell on your lover?”

“I do not care. Uncle! It is him! I am sure this is the Magus who took Jessia!” Nolan tugged at the sleeve of the Magus standing beside him and pointed at Leylin.

The accompanying Magus shifted his eyes and abruptly took a step up.

A ray of silver flashed by and the light barrier on Kubler’s body collapsed immediately.

“A rank 2 Magus!” Kubler mumbled under his breath.

Nolan looked on proudly upon hearing it while the other Magus had no expression on his face.

In his eyes, he did not regard Kubler who was a semi-converted Magus. However, he was distracted by the silent Leylin who sat quietly by the side.

“Sir, we the Rolithe Family have no intentions to use force. The fiancée of our successor has gone missing and it is a big matter. We need to inspect this place and we seek your cooperation…”

Power was exhibited first, followed by etiquette. It was a remarkable way of handling the situation, much better than what Nolan did.

“Absolutely!” Kubler was surprised that Leylin agreed instantly.

“Many thanks!” Seeing how cooperative Leylin is, the two Magi eased the tension on their faces and Nolan fell silent.

“Over here!”

Nolan looked into an odd mirror he was holding in his hand and rushed forward.

“Let’s take a look!” After his satisfying meal, Leylin got up and together with Kubler, stepped forward as well. The two Magi followed closely as if they were afraid of Leylin’s escape.

“Ah…. Jessia…… My Jessia……”

Upon reaching the room where Leylin and Kubler’s luggage was, they heard Nolan’s cries.

“Bad news!” Kubler rushed in and saw a white coloured woman’s dress on the bed, there was a big patch of blood stain on the stomach area and some portion had dried to a dark colour.

“What happened?”

“Jessia! Jessia! How dare you….” Nolan’s face flushed a fiery red as he yelled and stormed forward.

“This is trouble!” Kubler frowned, a layer of yellow scales appearing on him and his huge hand and suppressed Nolan who had lost his self-control onto the ground.

“Warlock from the Ouroboros Clan?”

The Rank 2 Magus expression immediately changed to become a vicious one as well.

“Even if you belong to the Ouroboros Clan, abducting the fiancée of our Rolithe Family’s successor and treating him with such disrespect, you have to give me an explanation!”

The rays of silver in his eyes amplified and streaks of silver whips appeared in his palm.

“Wait!” Leylin smiled subtly, his hand on the shoulder of the Rank 2 Magus.

“Huh? What is happening?” Although it is just a hand, but it felt like a mountain. In fact, the Rank 2 Magus felt his body stiffen and couldn’t even lift a finger.

“Innate spell—Ring of fire resistance!” the Rank 2 Magus emitted a layer of flame from his body, forming rings of fire with it, with streaks of silver on the edges, blazing the surrounding atmosphere ferociously.

“Annihilation!” Soon after, he heard Leylin mouthing the word.

*Hiss Hiss!* The blazing flames were put out immediately, leaving no room for the smoke to reignite the fire.

An enormous and horrifying spiritual force assaulted the Rank 2 Magus, destroying his defences, took over his consciousness and confined his magic power.

“Ra… rank 3 Magus?” The Rank 2 Magus turned his head with difficulty, his throat dry and rough.

Leylin had been using his skills to suppress his spiritual force and energy undulations all this time. Now, he undid the suppression bit by bit, and a huge tide of energy was released causing the atmosphere to become heavy.

“So tell me, if I want Jessia, do I need to be sneaky about it?”

Leylin shot them a look and asked sarcastically.

“Of… of course not! It is our mistake! We’re sorry!” the rank 2 Magus shook his head promptly. In the central continent, the sighting of Magi might not be uncommon, but it was not easy to witness the presence of a rank 3 Magus. And among the large-scale powers, rank 3 Magi were high-ranked with stable power and authority. They did not need to resort to any unscrupulous methods when dealing with rank 2 Magi.

At this time, Nolan was speechless. Although Kubler had lifted the spell on him, he lay helplessly on the floor with cold sweat trickling endlessly.

The Magus with the highest power in the whole of the Rolithe Family was only at Rank 3. If Leylin was displeased and had them killed, the other Magi might not even have the ability to seek revenge.

Thoughts of killing them crossed Leylin’s mind, but he eventually let it slide.

To him, there were no benefits in killing either these 2 Magi or even Jessia. Additionally, he might provoke an enemy with rank 3 strength.

Even though he was not afraid of the opposite party, he did not want any trouble.

“Follow me!” As such, he looked nonchalantly at the rank 2 Magus and Nolan, who was still lying on the floor before heading out.

Kubler followed Leylin closely, with the rank 2 Magus and Nolan close behind. In the face of a Rank 3 Magus, they had no chance of trying any tricks, hence they could only follow Leylin’s orders.

Leylin walked on with a destination in mind and soon they left the town and reached a paulownia tree forest.

Nolan didn’t quite understand anything, he merely followed suit.

Leylin came upon what seemed like the biggest paulownia tree, and knocked gently on the trunk as if he were knocking on a door. “Anyone there?”

*Dong Dong!* The tree trunk produced a dull sound, but there was no response and all was quiet.

“You are very clever! And attentive to your set-up. However, you are still not wise. After completing your work, you can’t help yourself but return to find out the reactions of others!”

“I have already noticed you, you should show yourself! Otherwise.….” Leylin’s voice turned chilly.

“Humph! Alright, alright, here I am, what are you going to do about it?”

*Shhrrk*, the surface of the tree trunk split open to reveal a round door. Jessia, whom they had first met on the airship, jumped out and grabbed Leylin by the arm.

“Brother Leylin! You are so awesome! How did you discover me?”

On the other side, both the rank 2 Magi and Nolan were speechless, anger filling them to the brim.

Chapter 396: Phosphorescence Swamp

“Jessia, What are you doing? Get back here now!”

Flames blazed in Nolan‘s eyes when he saw Jessia holding on to Leylin’s arms shamelessly with her breast almost pushed towards him.

The rank 2 Magus on the other side immediately stepped up and delivered a hard slap to the back of Nolan’s head, causing him to bend forward.

Droplets of cold sweat were trickling down his forehead.

It was obvious that what had happened today was all a misunderstanding. The crucial point was, they were lacking in ability when compared to the opposing side

Moreover, any slight mishandling of the situation would enrage a rank 3 Magus, and on top of that worsen their relationship with the Ouroboros Clan. At this point, thoughts of death crossed his mind.

“Anyway, it is just a small misunderstanding! Forget it!“ Leylin replied indifferently.

Before the rank 2 Magus could reply, Leylin’s ice cold voice was transmitted to him, “This is the price for offending me!”

*Bang! Bang! Bang!*

The rank 2 Magus, Nolan and Jessia collapsed and were flung out, blood trickling down the sides of their mouths.

“Leave, all of you! I do not want to see you all ever again!”

“Thank you for sparing our lives, my Lord!” the Rank 2 Magus gave a respectful bow, and quickly pulled Nolan and an unwilling Jessia away from the scene.

“I believe such troubles will continue to occur in the future….” The look in Nolan’s and Jessia’s eyes when they were leaving left Leylin with the feeling that this matter was not over yet.

The common hatred might have spurred them into an alliance in the future.

“What nonsense is this?” Leylin felt rather gloomy and thought he should not have gotten involved with matters between husband and wife.

“My Lord, should I…” Kubler spoke up with an ominous glint in his eyes

“No!” Leylin shook his head.

He fiddled with a dark and shiny gold coin in his hand, silent and in deep thought.

……

Phosphorescence Swamp.

This was the general headquarters of the Ouroboros Clan. Very few other Magi ventured out to this place.

The swamp was a sea of thick black wetlands and the air was a continuous mix of cold and chilly yet hot and blazing. Occasionally, flashes of green phosphorescence could be seen on it.

“The concentration of energy particles in the air is very high here! This location is a good find indeed!”

Leylin looked at the graphic data collected by his A.I. Chip, nodded his head and told Kubler who was standing behind him.

Although the average energy concentration in the central continent had far exceeded that of the south coast and twilight zone, the energy here was even more prominent.

Within Phosphorescence Swamp, the concentration of darkness elemental particles was the highest followed by that of fire. The concentration of these two elements was ten times higher than the average of Twilight Zone.

“This is merely on the outside, if an element pool or secret plane was built, I believe the disparity would be more terrifying….” Leylin thought to himself.

“Yes, such a location with a combination of darkness and fire particles is rare. Historically, when we first occupied this place, there were 5 Morning Star Magi who combined their forces to destroy a few powerful enemies, and brought along a country of commoners….” Kubler was brimming with pride as he explained to Leylin.

“My Lord, due to my current identity, there might be some trouble here!” he added.

He had been framed by others and was wanted by the Ouroboros Clan, hence before the accusations were lifted, he was afraid of being treated like a criminal.

“Not might, it’s already here!” Leylin pointed out. Soon a few profound dark shadows suddenly emerged from the nearby swamp.

*ROOAAAR!* Two high-energy serpent-shaped living creatures suddenly emerged, making a big splash. The silhouettes of two Magi could be seen on their heads.

“This is not even the headquarters of the Ouroboros Clan, yet patrolling the perimeter are rank 2 high-energy living creatures and rank 2 Magi! Looks like they have a very strong base!” Leylin felt a resonance of bloodline from the serpent-shaped living creatures ridden by the Magi. In fact, they seemed to be blood descendants of the Kemoyin Serpent!

“Kubler! How dare you step foot in this place? Didn’t you leave?” From where the 2 Warlocks were standing, a surprised voice was transmitted out and it didn’t sound flustered.

Under these circumstances, Leylin discreetly nodded his head. It would seem like Kubler was indeed innocent. The grassroots troops understood perfectly and even started to attack before they laid eyes on him.

“This is not my fault, I was framed by Johnny!” Kubler raised his voice, his face flushing red.

“We do not care about the details, just for the fact that you dare to step foot in Phosphorescence Swamp and brought an outsider!” Another Warlock immediately continued.

“I apologise! But I am not just any outsider!” Leylin smiled faintly, took a step forward and garnered the Kemoyin’s bloodline and the rank 3 spiritual force in his body, letting off a ferocious explosion.

Just like a hurricane, the energy willfully and violently started to sweep everything away. The awe-inspiring kind of familiarity in power left the two lower rank living creatures cowering and bowing with respect.

“A noble rank 3 Bloodline Warlock? Who are you? It is an honour to meet you!” The other 2 bloodline warlocks who possessed lineage of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline immediately felt the suppression from Leylin. They knelt down to show their utmost respect.

“I am a wanderer from afar and unintentionally accepted a Warlock inheritance. I met Kubler along the way and wanted to take a look at the Ouroboros Clan. Why? Am I not welcome?” Leylin asked indifferently.

“Sure! Sure! It is an honour for us to receive you!” The bloodline resonance between two Warlocks could not be faked. Hence the two Warlocks were very sure Leylin was a warlock of a pure Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline! And this level was the highest in the entire Ouroboros Clan! Who would dare offend him?

“Very well! Show us the way!” Leylin nodded his head and gave the order.

“Yes! Yes! This way, please!“ The two Warlocks made eye contact and immediately offered Leylin a position on the back of a huge snake. Kubler was offered one next, and he was secretly touched.

One of the Warlocks could be seen secretly sending a message, probably with the intention of informing others, but Leylin did not bother to pay attention to it.

The Rank 2 serpent moved with great speed along the swamp, emitting an aura of terror that made all other animals stay clear of their path.

“What species of snake is this?” Leylin stroked the dark green scales beneath his feet.

“This creature is an improved version we created using a specialized combination of bloodlines. Their abilities are very suitable for those of the Ouroboros Clan…” A rank 2 Warlock immediately explained to a curious Leylin, hoping to pleased him.

“That explains why I have not seen such information before!” Leylin nodded his head, “What is your name?”

“Maron! My name is Maron, my Lord! “ The Warlock named Maron immediately replied with a look of glee in his eyes.

“Alright Maron!” Leylin nodded his head, knowing what to do to garner reverence.

The two giant serpents glided along with great speed. In about 10 minutes or so, Leylin reached the depth of the Ouroboros Clan.

Here, a row of massive structures was combined together, forming a small scale Magus city, and at the front of the gate sat two enormous stone sculptures of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent.

With the delicate black scales coupled with the ferocious pupils, they looked like they could very well be alive.

At this moment, a small group of Warlocks was already waiting near the gate.

“Haha… Welcome home, my bloodline brothers!”

A young Warlock that looked like a goblin stood in front of the small group, his eyes that glowed with a purple radiance lighting up upon seeing Leylin. He stepped forward, stretched out his arms and hugged him.

“Thank you!” Leylin returned the hug unnaturally and asked, ” May I know….”

“Oh ! Haha! Look at me! I am so excited by your arrival that I have forgotten to introduce myself!” The fellow had very fair and exquisite skin that seemed to be emitting some kind of peculiar charm, a common trait among Warlocks.

“My name is Robin, you might not know this, but as long as a Warlock has the Kemoyin’s bloodline in him, he shall be considered to be a part of our family! My brother!”

Leylin could sense the aura from the opposite party and it was similar to his own Kemoyin’s bloodline. In fact, based on his spiritual force, Leylin was sure the young Warlock had not only long attained the status of a rank 3 Warlock, but also ascended further, with his strength and spiritual force at a high level.

“Oh, I see! My name is Leylin!”

“Yeah! Leylin right? Follow me! A Lord wants to meet you!” Robin held onto the arm of Leylin with an expression of excitement, totally ignoring Kubler who was behind him.

“Lord? Might it be…” Leylin’s pupils dilated.

“Haha! That’s right! My teacher, A Rank 4 Warlock! Morning Star Magus! Duke Gilbert has been waiting eagerly to meet our new blood!” Robin replied cheerfully.

Upon hearing the name, all the Warlocks bowed their heads in unison in a show of respect.

Rank 4 Warlock! Theoretically, this was the highest level for a Warlock of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline! In fact, it was also a truly high level for the whole of the central continent. Even within the Ouroboros Clan, there were no more than three Warlocks at such a level!

Leylin took a deep breath: “It is truly an honour!”

“Come! Follow me!”

Robin quickly led the way, with the rest of the Warlocks following respectfully behind.

Leylin noticed how the Warlocks all showed their respect to Robin along the way. It seemed like Robin held not only a high rank in the clan, but also a great deal of authority…

Chapter 397: Rank 4 Warlock

Following Robin, he passed by various bizarre buildings with strange styles. There were all types out there, and before Leylin had the time to identify them, he was led by Robin into another building.

After passing around a corner, there came across another Warlock in black gilded clothing.

There were also rings of mysterious black patterns on his face.

“Johnny!” Kubler, who had been following behind Leylin immediately clenched his fists, seemingly terrified as he hid in Leylin’s shadow.

“Greetings to Marquis Robin!” Johnny came before Robin, and then greeted him using the etiquette of nobility.

“It’s Count Johnny! Here, let me introduce to you Leylin here! He’s a rank 3 Warlock about to join our clan!” Robin smiled slightly.

“So it’s Lord Leylin!” Johnny bowed, “Though it’s the first time we’re meeting, I have a request. I wonder if you could agree to it.”

“If it’s about Kubler, I’m afraid I can’t agree.” Leylin immediately answered.

“That’s a real shame,” Johnny answered indifferently, not looking the least bit exasperated, causing Leylin to shiver inwardly.

“What if I say I’m the one asking?” At this moment, another voice interrupted.

“Marquis Wood!” Besides Leylin and Robin, the other Warlocks immediately bowed.

Leylin glanced at him. It was a blonde middle-aged man, brightness and resolution in his expression that also held an imposing aura. There was also the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline on his body, and it even overshadowed Robin.

“Kubler is a criminal who stole a precious treasure from me. I hope you can hand him over to me.” Wood’s eyes were fixed on Leylin, a pressure being emanated from him.

Kubler was ashen, and after seeing Johnny’s look of satisfaction, he immediately understood that after seeing he had a new master, Johnny immediately asked someone else for help.

“So are you handing him over?” In that moment, numerous thoughts flitted through Leylin’s mind.

On the surface, Wood was truly a Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock, as compared to Johnny with Black Horall Snake bloodline, his bloodline was more noble. In addition, he had entered the rank 3, and from the perspective of one looking at merely profits, it was better to give Kubler up.

Exchanging a rank 1 Mankestre Warlock who had no hopes of advancing for a favourable impression from a rank 3 Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock, there was little to consider in this trade.

Johnny, who understood this, immediately looked smug, while Kubler looked defeated.

“My apologies, but no.”Leylin’s voice sounded, allowing Kubler to recover from his despair.

“Master!” Kubler let out a long breath, looking touched.

“Hm?” Wood’s gaze that was sharp like a sword pierced towards Leylin, “Have you thought this through clearly?”

“Of course! Very clearly!” Leylin did not hesitate and met his gaze.

There was the talk of three ways of thought in his previous world, but Leylin’s principles had long since taken shape, and they were to prioritise benefits! The moment he had to make a choice, he would consider his own benefits and choose the best course of action.

Such a line of thought was not purely about tangible benefits; it also took into consideration reputation, familial and romantic love, and other such things. Of course, all this varied from person to person.

Some felt that love was priceless and decided to be biased towards it, while others believed it was worth 50,000 or 100,000 units. They would then make the corresponding choice.

For instance, if time was spent on working or going out with family, Leylin believed that working for one day amounted to 100 units, but with the family, he would lose 300 yet gain 600 from the happiness in his heart. The total profit would be 200. When comparing things, it was indeed better to go out with the family.

Using this logic, if his work earned him 1000 and the value of going out with his family were 300, it was an obvious decision to continue working.

Now, handing Kubler over might give Wood a good impression of him and provide a good foundation for this period of time. However, in the long run, the gains do not compensate for the losses.

‘Kubler followed me and brought me to the Ouroboros Clan. In exchange, I will ensure his safety. All this complies with the principle of an equal exchange. If I abandon him now, not only will my reputation be damaged, I will also have abandoned my own values.

“In addition, I’m definitely being watched over by many lords. If I appear to be too cold-blooded, they will definitely be disappointed. This will cause an eventual loss in the future, which is even worse than offending Wood.’

Though Magi were generally cold and rational, the leaders always had to advocate for hope, hot-bloodedness and sacrifice. If the lower ranks of the organisation did not strive to better themselves, and they weren’t hot-blooded enough to sacrifice themselves, what benefits would they gain in the end?

The essence of any group was the unequal responsibilities of the higher and lower levels.

Honestly speaking, Wood was merely a rank 3 Warlock. The moment Leylin entered, he would have a similar status. At most, there would be a slight difference in their strength. Would Wood actually dare do anything?

If he withdrew right now, the onlookers would immediately be disappointed, and nobody would then rely on him.

After comparing these, Leylin finally made the choice that would benefit him the most.

“Good, very good! I hope you won’t regret this in the future!”

Two streams of white air were expunged from Wood’s nostrils as he glared at Leylin. With a fling of his robes, he exited from the side, with Johnny following closely behind.

“Don’t worry! The moment you enter our Ouroboros Clan, you’ll be given the position of a Marquis. Wood wouldn’t dare do anything to you out in the open.” Robin believed Leylin was worried about Wood taking revenge and immediately consoled him.

“So if I don’t join, does that mean he’ll take revenge very quickly?” Leylin rolled his eyes, but he could tell that he was being invited to their organisation. He immediately answered, “Of course! Where else can I go to if not to the Ouroboros Clan?”

“Haha…” Robin burst out in laughter and patted Leylin on the shoulder, “Exactly! In the entire central continent, the Ouroboros Clan is the best place for Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks to join. You made the right choice!”

“Alright, let’s not let the lord wait too long.” Leylin reminded him. If not for the fact that there were rank 4 Warlocks in Robin’s organisation, he would not have agreed so readily.

“Oh, right! Yes, come with me!” Remembering there was work at hand, Robin immediately led the way.

The two chatted as they walked, and after passing through a few obstructions, they finally arrived in front of a small villa.

“My mentor, Gilbert, is a very amiable person. There isn’t any etiquette required, so just relax.”

Robin smiled towards Leylin and then opened the door to the villa, bringing Leylin inside.

The furniture on this level was all ordinary but placed very cleverly, giving a very warm atmosphere. Robin left the rest of the people outside and brought Leylin straight to a study room on the second level.

“Mentor, I’ve brought Leylin here!”

Robin spoke lightly to the wooden door, which then automatically opened with a creak.

“Greetings to Duke Gilbert!” The moment Leylin went in, he did not first take in the surroundings or the appearance of Duke Gilbert. Instead, he saluted him.

“Good child! Raise your head and let me look at you properly.” Upon hearing this, Leylin looked up, his eyes flitting across.

This place was filled with bookshelves. The smell of black truffles emanated, and behind the red desk was a bald old man wearing a nightgown. He was clean-shaven, with layers of fine wrinkles on his body.

“Is this the realm of a rank 4 Warlock, a Morning Star Magus?” Though Leylin’s senses were more powerful than the average rank 3 Warlock, he had not sensed this person in front of him. In his spiritual senses, there was nobody behind the desk, but what was in front of his eyes proved that he was truly there. The disparity of this left Leylin feeling giddy.

A glint of wisdom flashed in Gilbert’s eyes. He scanned Leylin for an instant and then concluded, “You’re very young! You’re not even a hundred and have even advanced to be a rank 3 Warlock. Though there was support from the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline, your talent and efforts are commendable.”

“Hm… Are you willing to be my student?” Gilbert asked after staying silent for a moment.

“Of course. Greetings to Mentor!” Leylin immediately bowed.

Since he had already agreed to join their organisation, there was no disadvantage to having another person to rely on. In addition, this rank 4 Warlock was more than capable of guiding him.

“Haha… good! Very good! I was already planning to give up on disciples, but I’ve been sent a genius…” Gilbert chuckled, the wrinkles on his face unfolding.

“Congratulations Leylin! From hereon, you’re my junior!” Robin congratulated him.

“En! This is your senior, Robin. There are a few others who aren’t here. I’ll introduce you to them in the future.” Gilbert was evidently elated.

“Also, your title and territory will be given to you soon. Robin will bring you to take care of all these matters. You’re from another continent, yes? Robin! Bring him to my storeroom and show him Crystal 1 and let him have a better understanding of our Magi in the central continent.

Gilbert saw through a great many things with a single glance, not allowing Leylin to refute anything.

“Understood, mentor!” Robin and Leylin could only bow before leaving the room.

“That’s… it?” Leylin was still in disbelief. Wasn’t this too simple?

“To officially join us, there’s obviously more to do. However, since you’re mentor’s student, things will be different!” Robin said all this matter-of-factly.

“In addition, you still have to take care of a few miscellaneous issues. Mentor means for you to take care of everything before you see him again. He will then consider what knowledge to pass on to you.”

Chapter 398: A Morning Star’s Final Technique

“By the way, what’s all that about title and territory?” Leylin asked hurriedly.

“Oh, that? All official Warlocks who join our Ouroboros Clan will obtain a title and a set territory.” Robin began to go into the details and explain it to Leylin, since they were now on the same side.

Through Robin, Leylin then found out that the hierarchy within the Ouroboros Clan was implemented similarly to that of the feudal nobility.

There were five rankings, from the highest to lowest, as a Duke, then a Marquis, Count, Viscount, and then Baron. Rank 1 Warlocks were Barons, rank 2 were Viscounts, rank 3 were Earls. Then came the surprise- if Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks reached rank 3, they would immediately gain the title of Marquis! This made Leylin aware that discrimination came everywhere. It was lucky he was in the privileged class, rather than the one discriminated against. Rank 4 Warlocks would then be Dukes.

The position and treatment he would get were correlated to the title.

There a total of three Dukes in the Ouroboros Clan. They had formed an Elders Association, and were called the great elder, second and third elder, and they held the most authority in the Ouroboros Clan.

There were, even more, differences as well. If Warlocks who had Giant Kemoyin Serpent or Black Horrall Snake bloodlines would have their title evaluation and territory given very quickly. However, if it was a bloodline like Mankestre, things would be slightly more difficult. Take Krubler, for instance. Though he could be given the title of a baron, but until now, all the processes had not gone through. Territories and the like? There was no word about it.

But Leylin was different, for he was a pure Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline Warlock, as well as the student of the third elder, Duke Gilbert. He had a great background, and he was prioritised. Titles and territories would be presented to him quickly, and also be given the best treatment.

Robin did not bring Leylin out right away, but instead went towards the basement. This was as per Duke Gilbert’s instructions, where Robin brought Leylin to see something.

“Leylin, have you seen the spells of Morning Star Magi?”

While walking, Robin would occasionally speak to Leylin.

“The spells of Morning Star Magi? Of course not!” Leylin’s emotions skyrocketed, “You mean we’re going to see that?”

There were rumours that Morning Star Magi could shift mountains and fill seas with just a wave of their arms, displaying terrifying power able to destroy the heavens and wreck the earth. At this thought, Leylin’s heart began to burn.

“I thought so. Mentor Gilbert believed that only after seeing Morning Star Magi attack would you be able to understand your path better.” There was a hint of a smile on Robin’s face.

“I just hope it won’t scare you!”

“How’s that possible?” Leylin laughed involuntarily. If this was in the past, that might have happened, but he had gained part of the bloodline memories from the Morning Star Scorpion Man. He had even witnessed an ancient legendary war, so there was nothing that could scare him.

“Hopefully!” There was a slight smile on Robin’s lips. Like Leylin, he did not leave the villa and entered the underground area.

*Clang!* After opening a metal door, a large complicated maze appeared before Leylin’s eyes.

“This is the Disorientating Maze, a spell pattern that us central continent Magi prefer to use. It is primarily used as sentry and defensive force.”

Robin explained to Leylin, “As a student of our mentor, we have the power to enter the first and second level. As for the deeper levels, our mentor has yet to open it up to us.”

Immediately after, he stood in front of Leylin and smiled at the entrance to the maze, “Open!”

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* A layer of rock fell, and a single giant pupil appeared on the wall of the maze.

“Remember, this is another student of my mentor’s — Leylin. He will have the same authority as I do.”

“Master has already told me.”

A spiritual force imprint extended from the giant eye. Leylin could tell that it was the core of the maze, similar to the spirit genie.

The giant eye stared straight at Leylin. In that moment, a slight force field covered Leylin, and he tensed.

Fortunately, this force field was not on the offensive and merely surrounded Leylin. After extracting part of his aura, he left.

*Crash!* The maze dissipated, revealing a pathway. There were different small doors at two sides, with markings on them.

“This is Mentor’s laboratory and storeroom. Everything in the villa is a guise. Follow me.” Robin headed into the path, while Leylin followed closely behind.

“Here!”

Robin guided Leylin for about five minutes, and then opened a door before entering.

The moment he entered, he saw an engraving on a door that said ‘Image Resource Room’.

In this storeroom, it was exceptionally dim. Crystals flickering with different colours were giving out magnificent rays of their own.

“Crystal Number 1! It’s this one!” Robin picked up a red crystal on a wooden shelf the size of a fist, and placed it on a pedestal with a depression on it, at the centre of the room.

“This is a projection crystal. We use it to store important footage, such as some important experiments, or battles between high ranking power.”

*Buzz Buzz!* After the spell formation was activated, the light in the room dimmed, almost becoming pitch-black.

The red crystal on the pedestal suddenly brightened.

A dazzling light shone down!

Leylin found himself standing atop a little hill. Green plains extended as far as the eye could see.

He grabbed at a black beetle that was flying past him, and it went through his palm, appearing on the other side.

“3D holograms? It’s very similar to the simulations of the A.I. Chip!” Leylin sighed in awe. At the peak of science and magic, there were definitely similarities between them after all.

“This is a classic battle that happened in the central continent’s history. This is the attacker.” Robin appeared beside Leylin, pointing to the east.

The scene was pulled closer, and a human city appeared. At the side, many corps were lined up, creating an imposing aura.

What shocked Leylin the most were the members. All of them were official Magi! There was not one regular human or knight.

“This is an imitation of the ancient Magus corps, ‘Thorned Hammer’. The members were all official Magi, and the team leaders were rank 2 Magi. The captain and vice-captain were rank 3 Crystal Phase Magi, and the corps could even cooperate to display a large-scale fire elemental spell! The range was vast, and on average, its strength was above 470 degrees!”

Robin explained to Leylin.

Now, two Magi flew out from the Thorned Hammer corps. The auras on their bodies far exceeded those on Leylin and Robin. They were emanating the tremendous bloodthirst of veterans of war. This aura could even be seen on regular members of the corps.

Lelin knew that this valour and confidence in victory was built upon multiple conquests. Every time this corps levelled an enemy nest, stepping on the bones of their enemies, they would gain more confidence, even taking in the resentment of the defeated and increasing the strength of their spells.

This was the way of war of ancient corps.

The two Magi of the Thorned Hammer corps flew out and roared at the city, obviously to urge the city to surrender.

Above the city wall, it was empty but for one lonely figure.

“This is the other party in this battle—Morning Star Magus, Flame Manipulator, Lord Kason!” There was a trace of reverence in Robin’s voice.

Leylin looked this Morning Star Magus over. The Magus called Kason looked like a middle-aged man, wearing luxurious gold robes with embedded with them metal at the sides. There was a fiery-red jade band on his forehead.

Facing this entire corps of ancient Magi, there was no sign of fear in Kason’s expression. Instead, he began to berate his opponent, probably telling them to withdraw lest they suffer the consequences.

After the negotiations fell through, the entire Thorned Hammer corps roared, powerful and complicated spell undulations connecting all of them and converging on the two rank 3 Crystal Phase Magi in mid-air. Even through the video, the frightening waves were enough for Leylin’s expression to change.

In the face of this ancient corps, all he could do was flee, and he might not even be able to escape successfully.

At this moment, Flame Manipulator Kason finally moved. Rings of spell rays brightened on his body.

……

First was a red spell, the energy undulations indicating rank 1. Following it was a rank 2 spell…

A total of four rings of light brightened on his body, and at the last spell, it emanated tremendous waves that even surpassed a rank 3 spell.

“A rank 4 spell?” Leylin glanced towards Robin, who was beside him.

“Wait a while more. The show’s about to start!” Robin gazed steadily at Kason, envy and anticipation evident on his expression.

“Foolish Magi, today, you shall know how the dignity of ancient Morning Star Magi was established!”

Kason warned with righteous words.

Immediately after, the small energy undulations amplified on his body and seemed to change, to the point that even the rank 3 Crystal Phase Magi grew extremely fearful.

“Rank 1 innate spell—Burning Zone!” As soon as this spell was launched from Kason’s body, it covered the entire region.

“Rank 2 innate spell—Blazing Attachment!” Little sparks were created in the skies.

“Rank 3 innate spell—Lava Region!” Great amounts of flames scorched the surface of the ground, forming a lava-infused land.

“Rank 4 innate spell—Meteor Descent!” With Kason’s yell, meteors appeared in the sky, one after the other.

“Complement: Ancient Morning Star Magus Final Technique—Fire Rain Annihilation”

After the four innate spells were combined, the fusion generated a change that made Leylin’s blood run cold.

Chapter 400: Female Warlocks

“Don’t worry, I won’t spread this!” Leylin promised immediately, knowing what Robin meant.

“Good! Come, then. I’ll show you your manor and some important places like the trading hall! Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks are our most valuable members. You will enjoy the best we have to offer…”

The Ouroboros Clan held quite a bit of fame in the central continent. There was no doubt that they controlled a huge region teeming with mortals and acolytes. Parts of this land would often be granted to the higher-ups within the clan.

Some of the Warlocks in the clan built giant castles in their territory. They preferred to stay there, and seldom visited the headquarters. Slowly, they would expand their families.

On the other hand, most Warlocks who held a high hope for further advancement were the exact opposite, choosing to stay behind at the headquarters, leaving the territory to someone else to manage.

Given that Leylin was a Marquis, his territory would undoubtedly be quite large. The production of magic crystals as well as other resources from it would far exceed the poor south coast and Twilight Zone.

Additionally, he would be given an isolated manor in the headquarters as his personal residence.

The trading hall was like a stock exchange. A screen hung in the air, displaying various fields of information as numbers blinked with different colours. Under the big screen were Warlocks of different ranks looking hurried as they whispered to the staff behind the counters.

Every organisation had a place like this. It was similar to a hall where missions were issued, and handled part of the exchange of goods. Leylin was very familiar with such places, but never before had he seen one this large. One message on the screen left Leylin embarrassed, “Rank 1 Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock with a decent bloodline. Selling the opportunity for a night’s irrigation of seeds. Price: 1000 contribution points. Additional requirement: The female’s appearance must be approved by me.”

“This…” Leylin didn’t know what to say.

“Haha!” Robin was not surprised at all.

“After the passing of generation after generation, most Warlock families will have their bloodlines thin out. Exceptions to this rule do exist, but are very rare. Even among Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks, there are those whose bloodlines are weak enough to match Black Horrall Snake or even Huge Mankestre Snake Warlocks. Therefore, Warlock families generally search for those with pure bloodlines to improve their own fading ones. There are some weaker Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks who live on this income. Although it’s difficult for a Warlock to sire a child, it’ll happen eventually if they try often enough.”

“That I know!” Leylin said contemptuously. He was quite unhappy about this kind of work, where they were basically pimping themselves out.

“By the way, you do have a very pure bloodline, Leylin. You’re also quite strong yourself, so be careful. The female Warlocks will go crazy over you!” Robin said with a teasing smile.

“It doesn’t matter. I won’t do this no matter what!” Leylin said assuredly. This kind of act violated his bottom line, and he would not do something that went against his basic principles.

“Your wants have nothing to do with it. Some female Warlocks with high bloodline purity will capture ones like you and not let you go until they become pregnant. Given that the male suffers no substantial losses and revealing this would generally hurt their reputations, they choose to silently endure, thus making it hard for us to interfere…” Robin’s following words dumbfounded Leylin.

Robin looked Leylin up and down, and nodded to him. “Don’t worry. Based on your current strength, there are few female Warlocks in the clan that can actually capture you.”

“Robin! What a coincidence!” Suddenly, a woman’s voice rose up behind them. Robin turned back and saw a female Warlock with long black hair creating a divide in the crowd as she approached them. While occasionally eyeing Leylin, there was an undisguised hint of excitement on her face which sent shivers down his spine.

“Who is this handsome fellow? We haven’t met before, have we?” The aura of this female Warlock was the same as Robin’s, their spiritual force have both reached the Hydro Phase. She was also a well-built beauty, with a charming appearance and fair skin.

“This is Marquis Leylin, a new member of the clan who is under Mentor Gilbert’s tutelage!” Robin said with a smile on his face but he felt uneasy.

He transmitted to Leylin, “Be careful! This is one of the female Warlocks I just told you about—Blood Serpent Miranda!”

“Hello, Marquis Miranda!” Leylin knew her status and gave her a salute.

“Marquis Leylin! So is this the first time you’ve come here? Why don’t you follow me? I can show you around, and we can even go to my manor later where I show you the enthusiasm of our female Warlocks!”

Miranda’s eyes shone with excitement as she surveyed Leylin and ran her tongue along her lips. This further increased her charm to the point that few males could resist her.

“My apologies! I’d prefer to be lead by Robin!” Leylin denied. He liked beautiful girls, but it was only if he was the dominant one. It would feel too humiliating to be used like a tool for mating.

“Don’t refuse me so fast! Five thousand contribution points! Five thousand contribution points for one night! Deal?”

Miranda offered a price without any hesitation, and the Warlocks around inhaled a deep breath. It seemed like five thousand contribution points was quite the number.

“That’s enough!” Leylin’s face turned solemn, his hand reaching for the hilt of his sword.

“So that’s how you want it. Then let me tame you in my own way!” Miranda felt no fear for Leylin, and instead a foxy expression appeared on her face.

She’d seen through Leylin at first glance, and knew that he was a newly advanced rank 3 whose spiritual force had not reached the Vapour Phase. Meanwhile, hers was already in the Hydro Phase.

Rank 3 Warlocks were divided into those with Vapour Phase, Hydro Phase, and Crystal Phase spiritual force. There was a huge gap in strength between each phase. With Leylin being two phases below her, she was not worried even if he had some secret weapons.

“Right here?” Miranda’s eyes narrowed into slits, a dangerous aura bursting forth. Dense scales appeared on her body in the shape of flowers which made her even more alluring.

“Miranda! Stop!” Another clear female voice arose, and a red snake flew over.

“You!” Miranda waved her hands. Countless black wisps appeared around her, bumping into the red snake. Robin ended up having to repress the following explosion, but even so many Warlocks were pushed down by the aftermath of the clash.

“Another one! Leylin, your luck today is just too poor!”

“Another one?” Leylin looked at the source of the sound.

The one who attacked with the red snake just now was also a female Warlock, her long black hair cascading to her waist like a waterfall. She possessed a voluptuous body that was in stark contrast to her saintly face.

“This is Marquis Freya! I’ve never heard about rumors of her capturing male warlocks, but her family’s bloodline has been declining in recent years. They are looking for a suitable male to marry into their family, be careful!” Robin transmitted to Leylin who currently could only keep silent.

“Freya! If you want a man, there are plenty in my castle that I can gift you. This one is mine!” Apparently, Miranda had already considered Leylin her own prey.

“Miranda, you slut! I’m not here for romance. I’m here to ask him to join my family!” Freya retorted sharply.

“No way! I saw him first!”

“So what?” With the argument escalating, the danger around these two women grew and everyone around backed away.

Leylin stood between them, feeling amused and annoyed. Rather than asking for his own opinion, these two were fighting over him like he was a victory item. “Listen here! Are you even going to bother about my opinion?”

“You?” Miranda smiled faintly, “Weaklings have no right to an opinion. Even your Mentor wouldn’t say anything about this. I have an elder backing me as well.”

On the other side, Freya expressed her silent agreement.

“Fine! I will let you know who is the weakling!” Leylin drew his sword from its sheath. The Meteor Sword was a high grade magic artifact; it began emitting a scary aura.

Streams of black light shot at the two women, containing within them the horrifying toxins of a Kemoyin Serpent. Meanwhile, Intimidating Gaze, his rank 3 bloodline spell, shot forth.

Although similar waves shot forth from the two women, they retreated the moment they came in contact with Leylin’s domain.

“An Intimidating Gaze this powerful?” Robin looked at the weaker Warlocks who had fallen to the ground. “It seems like Leylin’s blood purity is much higher than I expected.”

With a flash of black light, two distinct sounds rung out. A red whip in Miranda’s hands cracked into two, and Freya retreated a few steps as a red ring in her hands was crushed into a powder.

Chapter 403: The Astral Gate

“Morning Star Magus?” Leylin looked doubtful as he glanced at his Mentor.

“Yes. Only the massive spiritual force of Morning Star Magi can withstand the consumption as you step over. In addition, many dangers in various worlds are unable to be dealt with by regular Magi. At the very least, you need to be at the Morning Star realm.” Gilbert looked stern.

“With your current spiritual force, with the help of the spell formations and the astral gate, you’ll at most be able to approach a few Magus Worlds and receive a few sections of incomplete information even if you drain all your spiritual force. You may not even be able to obtain all of the information.”

Gilbert shook his head.

“If you really must do this, you could aid me in my experiment regarding projection of coordinates.”

After that, through Gilbert’s explanations, Leylin found out some fundamental information on how to use the astral gate.

This experiment of crossing over to different worlds consumed a lot of energy, and there were rules when it came to transporting objects. In general, receiving information through spiritual force consumed the least energy, but the moment any substance was to be transported, the consumption would increase several times. If a Magus were to go over, the energy required was tremendous, to the point that it might even cause Morning Star Magi to exhaust themselves!

In reality, in both ancient and recent times, there were so many Morning Star Magi who had consumed large amounts of resources and energy only to find a desolate world, ending up with nothing despite their efforts.

The astral gate had always been a place where fortune and danger coexisted.

The Magi in the central continent seldom travelled over. They preferred to send out a few spiritual force coordinates, as well as use things like teleportation spell formations.

This was similar to setting down fish bait, and then waiting for the other side to accept it.

Though the chances were so small that they were below one in ten thousand, there was a real possibility of intelligent beings receiving the spiritual force tokens that were floating in spatial cracks.

Next was to bewitch these beings and then gather information regarding these other planes and determine their coordinates. If this information was determined valuable enough, Morning Star Magi would then open the true astral gate and then travel there in great numbers, seizing control of the plane!

“Why does it sound like we’re doing the same thing as a cult, as if some satanic summoning ritual?” Leylin was bewildered.

“It is something like that! Those devils or whatever they are come from a different plane near us. They like to gather spirits through this method. If not for them concealing themselves so well, we would have long since used the coordinates and tried to kill them!”

A killing intent rose in Gilbert’s eyes.

“Well then, Mentor. I would like to enter your experiment with the astral gate!” Leylin immediately requested.

“Alright. While I am experimenting, you can be my assistant, observing and studying by my side.” Gilbert watched Leylin’s resolute gaze and nodded.

……

After leaving Gilbert’s villa, Leylin was in a very good mood. Not only had he gathered many ancient secrets, he was now qualified to participate in the space experiments.

“In the future, I want to make my own astral gate!” Leylin decided.

At the very least, he would need to go to that Purgatory World at least once. He would gain a solution for the shackles of his Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline there.

Of course, this was the hope of the entire Ouroboros Clan. Leylin’s mentor, Gilbert, and the two other Morning Star Warlocks were crazily searching for the coordinates of the Purgatory World.

It was a pity that the multiple worlds and coordinates were like the numerous stars in the sky. With their method of trial and error, it was impossible to know how long it would take from them to find Purgatory World.

However, Leylin had plans of his own. He would not mention them yet.

“Leylin!”

Around a corner, Leylin heard a voice and halted his footsteps, seeing a blonde middle-aged Magus walking over. However, there was no longer the calm and dignified look he had had. Instead, he was flustered, and even the energy fluctuations around him were unstable, as if he had gained injuries.

“What is it?” Leylin was in no mood for this sheltered Warlock who had once threatened him before, Woody.

“Don’t think you can do whatever you want just because you have someone backing you, you gigolo!” Woody’s expression was terrible, looking as if he wanted to gobble Leylin up.

“Gigolo?” Leylin’s heart jumped, and he had a bad feeling about this.

“Woody! Aren’t you starting yet?”

A female voice that made Leylin’s hair stand. He then saw that Warlock Freya from before, pulling at a pet that seemed to be a black sheepdog.

Upon closer inspection, Leylin realised there were complicated black patterns on its face, its eyes flashing with intelligence. However, all that was inside them was now despair, frenzy and an unspeakable dread.

“Morphing technique! This is—Johnny!” Magi naturally did not recognise people by their appearances. The familiar spiritual waves immediately allowed Leylin to tell the true identity of this sheepdog.

“This is—Crazy!” Seeing the dog leash around the sheepdog’s neck, Leylin could confirm Johnny even had thoughts of suicide.

“Wooo!” After seeing Woody, the sheepdog began to whimper even more, as if hoping its original owner would save it.

Woody paled in anger, but did not do much.

He then gritted his teeth, bowing slightly to Leylin, “Marquis Leylin, please forgive me for my previous offences. Please do whatever you please with Johnny.”

Having said this, Woody immediately turned to leave, disappearing after turning a corner.

“How is it? Do you like my gift? To change him into this form, it used up a precious morphing scroll I got from my Mentor!” Freya pulled the black sheepdog till it reached his side, anticipating his reaction.

“I…” Leylin could only force a smile.

He had heard from Robin that compared to the wanton Miranda, Freya kept her chastity and did not do anything to charm male Warlocks into becoming their toys. However, in order to improve the bloodline in her family, she would go around looking for suitable candidates.

At this moment, she seemed to have chosen him! The earnest look on her face seemed to be giving Leylin a headache.

Though she was a student of the Second Elder and was thus doted on, for her to become hostile to another Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock and even punish members in the same circle as she was in, she would definitely be under immense pressure.

Of course, as a Warlock, she had inherited emotional instability and perhaps would not think too much of her actions.

Through the A.I. Chip, Leylin noticed the unstable aura on Freya’s body. It was apparent that pressuring Woody was not such a simple task, and both sides would suffer losses. The reason Woody had automatically conceded was because his bloodline instability was not flaring up. He knew how to weigh his benefits.

“I- Whatever! Do whatever you want with Johnny!”

Looking at the whimpering sheepdog on the ground, Leylin really sympathized with it.

“Also, here are two things for you!”

Leylin passed her a high-grade healing potion, as well as a high-grade potion of tranquility.

He was not one to accept favours from others. A healing potion was a small matter, but what was more important was the high-grade potion of tranquility. This was the strengthened version of the potion of tranquility, and Leylin had even added parts of the Icy Jade Scorpion’s bloodline. Though the effects were reduced, it was still very effective for Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks.

He really hoped this potion could slightly inhibit her crazy tendencies and stop her from bothering him.

Watching Leylin seemingly fleeing and disappearing along the road, Freya caressed the two potions in her hands and smiled, “It’s great as long as you have a good impression of me! You’ll be mine.”

……

If Leylin knew what Freya was thinking, he would probably regret his actions. Now, however, he had found Robin.

“Hm? You want to take a look at your territory?” Robin looked at Leylin in front of him.

“Yes! Mentor Gilbert has finished his teachings, and all that’s left are preparations for the astral gate. There’s nothing left for me to do, so I want look at the territory.”

Leylin spoke. After his current trip, Gilbert was done with teaching him. He was a rank 4 Warlock and had numerous tasks to carry out. On top of that, he had to focus on his research and could not continue coaching Leylin.

Before conducting the astral gate experiments, a lot of time was needed to prepare the materials, adjust the frequencies and the like.

Leylin wanted to make use of this time and first leave the headquarters. A part of it was because he wanted to see his territory, but another reason was because he was really a little scared and wanted to hide outside.

“Oh, it was Freya!”

Robin thought for a moment and suddenly began to laugh. He seemed to have some knowledge regarding what had just transpired.

“She’s actually not half bad! She hasn’t had a partner in the past, and her mentor is also a Morning Star Warlock. You should just marry her!” Robin even teased as he suggested.

“If I really want to marry someone, I can take her into consideration, but you know…”

Leylin’s lips quirked in a wry smile. Though Freya was doing all she could to get into his good books, her final goal was to make him a breeding machine. Even if they did become companions, she would want him to marry into her family. How could he stand this?

In the deepest part of his heart, Leylin believed himself to be a male chauvinist, and he could not stand for this.

“That’s true. Besides, you’re still young!” Robin thought for a moment and then nodded, as if having expected this.

“Young? I’m almost a hundred!” Leylin was speechless.

“Haha, I’m almost five hundred, and I’ve had 24 wives! I’ve married into several families.” Robin’s expression showed his experience in this area.

“When you’re at my age, you’ll think little of this sort of thing.”

Chapter 408: Precipitating 3 Years

Potions Grandmasters were rare in the south coast, and at that time, Leylin was only a rank 1 Magus. Thus, he needed to avoid doing things that would leak his secret and lead to trouble.

But the central continent posed no such problems. Even the Ouroboros Clan alone housed a few reputable Grandmasters, not to mention the entire continent.

Furthermore, Leylin had already become a rank 3 Warlock, and his strength now was leagues ahead of what it was before. With Gilbert as his back-up, he had no cause for fear. Thus, it wasn’t much of a problem to reveal a bit of his prowess in the field.

It was still important to keep it a secret on the whole. Leylin’s Potioneering ability was honed over many years by personal tests and A.I. Chip simulations. In addition to the Chip’s assistance during the act itself, he’d reached a level of skill that bordered that of the most respected Potions Grandmasters, a mysterious and unfathomable realm.

But it was unnecessary to show his complete prowess. On top of that, through Potioneering, he could get hold of a majority of the recipes from the central continent for free. Moreover, most were exclusive, and would contribute greatly to Leylin’s database.

Leylin hoped from the bottom of his heart that, after acquiring all the information the central continent had with regards to Potioneering, he would have a breakthrough in his skill!

……

3 years later.

Leylin was in his manor in the Ouroboros Clan headquarters. Because of the many people and slaves in the region, the manor was not as empty as it once was. Once it had started functioning properly, clean-cut slaves and coquettish maids were walking about everywhere.

There were even some acolytes mixed into this sea of people.

Leylin had gathered all the gifted people in his territory and brought them here. He normally left his Warlock vassals to guide them, and only came out to teach himself when he was in a good mood.

This arrangement of Leylin wasn’t well received by the acolytes but they stayed on for the opportunity to work under him. Some of the acolytes and Magi even specially moved to his territory.

Inside the specialized living area, Leylin was conversing with Robin.

“Honestly speaking, Leylin, your Potioneering ability has greatly surprised me!” Robin was playing with the test tube in his hand. The purple liquid inside rippled and reflected a myriad of colours.

Leylin had granted himself both wealth and fame through the selling of potions and Potioneering for his clan members over the last three years.

The number of high-ranking Magi and Magi of affiliated clans seeking for Leylin’s Potioneering had been on a steady increase.

And Leylin wouldn’t reject their offers most of the time, though his success rate was a little lower than the Potion Grandmasters of the Ouroboros Clan, Leylin’s fee was much lower when compared to theirs. Besides, many Potions Grandmasters had already filled their schedules with requests and were unable to take on any more requests.

Precisely because of this, Leylin was able to come across the recipes for a large number of rare potions, which added to his Chip’s database as well as his own skill.

“I just have a slight interest in Potioneering. After all, I started my time as a Magus by becoming a Potions Master’s acolyte!” Leylin laughed weakly, his eyes and expression tinged with nostalgia.

“That itself is extraordinary! And I have to mention that it’s more than impressive for you to keep up with your meditation technique while making vast improvements in your Potioneering skills!” Robin looked closely at Leylin, “Your spiritual force is almost ready to move on to the Vapour Phase, isn’t it?”

“Indeed! I’m about to buy a Vapour Phase spell formation and plan to try and break through soon!” Leylin nodded with confidence. He had nothing to hide.

He’d earned a lot of contribution points through Potioneering. With that and his own resources, Leylin had indiscriminately bought spiritual force potions for his own use from the Ouroboros Clan. With the fourth layer of Kemoyin’s pupil as a guide, Leylin’s path had been clear of any obstacles. With a distinct aim, his spiritual force had improved significantly in this period.

The resources of the central continent could not be compared to those of Twilight Zone and the south coast. In addition to the energy-rich environment, it was much easier for Magi to break through and better themselves here than elsewhere.

“Mm! A Vapour Phase spell formation costs roughly 100,000 contribution points. With the addition of the necessary materials for it, the total will come up to about 150,000! Do you have enough? If not, I can lend you some for now!” Robin said in goodwill.

“Thank you so much!” Leylin laughed.

Although Potioneering was a very profitable business, Leylin had only been in it for a very short time. He’d even spent a huge number of contribution points to purchase spiritual force potions. Thus, he was not so well-off.

The Ouroboros Clan allowed one to exchange magic crystals for contribution points, but there were some considerations that led to Leylin not considering that path. One of them was a fixed limit on the number of crystals a Magus could trade for.

“Oh and here is the information I plan to handover to the clan! Help me do an appraisal!” Leylin chuckled as he handed a folder to Robin.

After skimming through, Robin lifted his brows and looked back at Leylin, straightening his back in astonishment. “You… You actually want to bestow your high-grade potion of tranquility to the clan?”

The high-grade potion of tranquility was an improved version of the one Leylin acquired from the great Magus Serholm, which helped to suppress the emotional instability of Warlocks. Of course, what he offered the guild was the rudimentary version that was not based primarily on the Icy Scorpion’s Breath. But it still proved relatively impressive in repressing the emotions of high-rank Warlocks

The emotional instability of high-rank Warlocks was quite obvious. Although there were some methods and potions to control them circulated inside the Ouroboros Clan, the Magi could never have enough.

As long as the root of this problem was not dealt with, such medicine would always be in high demand. In the past three years, Leylin had refined and manufactured vast quantities of high-grade potions of tranquility, turning them into one of his biggest sources of income. That he was willing to sell the formula left Robin extremely surprised.

“Of course!” Leylin laughed as he shook his head. He did not have the time to concoct and sell potions of tranquility for money. Furthermore, this was an advanced potion! Normal Potions Masters would not be able to achieve a high success rate at concocting it. It would still be easy for him to return to the business to earn contribution points if he wished.

“Just this alone is worth around 25,000 contribution points. Looking at you now, it doesn’t seem like you lack points!” Robin laughed bitterly.

“I wish! Honestly, I was thinking of borrowing some from you, senior! I still have a shortage of them!” Even as he said this, Leylin slyly lifted the corners of his mouth, making Robin feel a little closer to him.

At times, the bond between two people can be improved through the act of mutual support.

“Oh! You won’t be able to support your Magus Tower’s construction much longer, will you?” Robin’s expression changed into one of understanding, and Leylin just chuckled bitterly.

The construction of Leylin’s tower was more or less done over the part three years and now it was mostly down to the detailing and decoration of each floor.

And Leylin’s expectations were exceptionally high. The materials selected were practically the most premium ones and the resources exhausted were comparable to a chain of mountains.

To be honest, Leylin’s wealth was enough to sustain the following add-ons to his tower but he didn’t want to be completely transparent. So the facade of a poverty-stricken individual was absolutely necessary.

“Ah… Leylin, I told you so! Why did you not set your standards lower back then during the planning process, or build it here at the headquarters directly? It wouldn’t have resulted in this situation then!” Robin consoled.

“No!” Leylin shook his head with a resolute tone.

“The Magus Tower is a reflection of the rank of its Magus. When I build one, it must be the best of the best! Moreover, I have to think about the future. The Tower being in my territory will act as a deterrent to the surrounding forces.”

“Makes sense. But it is still unwise to use up all your resources for it! I almost prostituted myself when I was building mine, even with my family and the clan’s resource….” Robin pummeled his chest, fear lingering in his voice.

Leylin could only roll his eyes at the near-promiscuous flashback as Robin moved on to the main concern, “Anyway, how much were you thinking of borrowing?”

“I’d like to ask, how much are you able to lend, senior?” Leylin asked as a smile tugged at the corners of his mouth…

In a short while, Leylin arrived at the trading hall of the Ouroboros Clan with a large number of contribution points in hand.

After spending the past 3 years here, Leylin was already familiar with the place and headed straight to his destination upon arrival.

‘A.I Chip, Report my current status!’ Leylin silently said in his head.

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 3 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent Strength: 23.6, Agility: 20.1, Vitality: 39.1, Spiritual Force: 240.5, Magic Power: 240 (Magic Power synchronized with spiritual force)]

The A.I Chip faithfully processed and sent the information.

As a Magus, spiritual force and magic power were the most important numbers. Vitality was the foundation upon which spiritual force was built and sustained, and had to be strong enough; otherwise, the Magus’ body would collapse.

When his strength and agility reached their maximum, Leylin temporarily took his focus away from them and raided for potions and alchemist spell formation in the clan that can boost his Vitality resulting in his terrifying increase to nearly 40.

Looking at these numbers, Leylin felt that his own body terribly surpassed many high-energy beings. Not only was his rate of recovery alarmingly fast, he was able to take on any Magi below rank 2 unarmed!

His bulky physique made cultivating his spiritual force a piece of cake, and he was already prepared to break through the bottleneck that was the Vapour Phase.

“A.I Chip! Simulate my current shape and compute the conditions needed for me to move on to the Vapour Phase!”

Chapter 412: Lamia Hair

Much to his chagrin, Leylin had discovered that even though the Ouroboros Clan had a long heritage and was a large, powerful organisation, there were many traditions and complex regulations that were very tedious.

Especially in terms of hierarchy; nobody knew whether it was inherited from the Giant Kemoyin Serpents, but their hierarchy was very rigid.

Previously, even if they were all Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks, Kesha who had reached the Vapour Phase would pay no attention to someone like Leylin. Yet, the moment he made the breakthrough himself, here she was, her attitude having flipped completely. This had dumbfounded Leylin.

Lucian was the same. He who was at the Crystal Phase was the strongest here, and sat quietly in a corner, drinking smugly. Unfortunately, everyone had already accepted such behaviour as a norm.

Even if he rolled his eyes internally, Leylin understood that he could only do things according to the rules.

”Senior Lucian has always been like this. He has suffered a lot previously, and just can’t bring himself out of it!” Robin transmitted after noticing Leylin’s gaze.

”Actually, he’s extremely delighted at your breakthrough. Normally, he wouldn’t even deign to take a glance at a banquet invitation!”

Perhaps because he was Gilbert’s butler, Robin’s communication and observation skills were outstanding. Just a glimpse at Leylin in his peripheral vision and he’d realised things, explaining Lucian’s attitude.

“Don’t worry, I understand!” Leylin smiled wryly. Even if Lucian decided not to show him respect, he could do nothing about it.

Even with all his trump cards, Leylin could at most deal with a Hydro Phase rank 3 Magus. With that kind of difference in strength, it was useless to talk about it. Had Lucian not considered his Mentor Gilbert and the fact that it was Leylin’s first invitation, he might not even have come.

”Oh, right! Let me introduce you to my apprentice, Snoopy!” A reserved youth walked up at Leylin’s introduction, a dimpled smile on his pockmarked face.

”He… Hello distinguished masters!” Snoopy greeted all the Magi, stumbling on his words.

A few rank 3 Warlocks merely nodded aloofly and did not pay much attention, and even Kesha’s 2 younger generations looked down on him.

They could see Snoopy’s Black Horrall Snake bloodline at one glance. Even though a rank 3 Warlock bloodline was considered a big deal even in the central continent, those with higher bloodlines thought nothing of it.

Immediately, they linked this sight to Leylin’s top subordinate, Parker and guessed the motives behind Leylin’s acceptance of this apprentice. They would naturally not pay any more attention, but on account of Leylin, they had nodded their heads in recognition.

Fortunately, Leylin had only brought Snoopy out for exposure, and quickly dismissed him after he had bowed to everyone.

Snoopy’s response was quick, and his withdrawal was even faster. With a tinge of embarrassment on his face, it appeared to Leylin as if he was fleeing.

”This is the hierarchy of Warlocks!”

Leylin sighed internally. In comparison, though Kesha’s 2 younger generations were slightly lower in strength, because their bloodline was distinguished and there was the possibility of making a breakthrough to rank 4, they would immediately receive more attention. Even the rank 3 Elders would consider this normal.

For Warlocks, even though bloodline could not determine your lowest achievements, it could dictate your greatest.

Take for example the two Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks Kesha had brought along. They needed only to put a bit more effort and spend more time, and it would be child’s play to reach the Vapour and even Hydro Phase. However, the advancement to the Crystal Phase depended on one’s innate talent. As for the breakthrough to the Morning Star realm, innate talent alone was not enough. There was a huge amount of luck to be factored into it!

After all, they were not first generation Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks. Their bloodline was not as pure, and could not allow for the adults to easily advance to rank 4.

In actual fact, in the entire Ouroboros Clan, there were already no more absolutely pureblood Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks. Their bloodlines had faded with the passage of time. For the three elders to break through to the Morning Star realm required not only a large amount of resources and effort, but also a stroke of luck.

Leylin did not know how pure his bloodline was, but the A.I Chip and the recognition by the few seniors and Mentors seemed to suggest that it was not too bad.

In fact, he had immense confidence in the bloodline purification skills of the A.I Chip.

During the period of time he was in the Ouroboros Clan, he had discovered that even in the central continent, there were no microscopes here that could form images at the genetic and atomic levels.

Their research at most halted at the cells. Their best microscopes could at most see the structure of a cell.

Previously, the A.I Chip had directly extracted the part of the genes that belonged to the Giant Kemoyin Serpent from the bloodline essence of the Black Horrall Snake, and reconstructed them.

Leylin even suspected that the bloodline within his body could compare to that of a first generation Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock!

Mind you, that was a bloodline that allowed a Warlock to progress to the Morning Star realm automatically as he aged.

Leylin’s own improvement had been too rapid. He was only a hundred years old, an infant among Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks. Thus, he did not have a deep enough understanding of the frightening potential of his bloodline.

Still, it took way too long for Giant Kemoyin Serpents to mature. If he was to advance at the same rate as his bloodline would let him, he would only be a rank 1 Warlock as of now. With the passing of time, he would feel his spiritual force growing slightly even if he did nothing but sleep all day. After finishing semi-conversion and complete conversion, his strength would soar. At about 500 years of age, he would become a rank 3 Warlock. As for a Morning Star Warlock? That would take him until he was 900 if he only depended on his bloodline.

In other words, Leylin’s current improvement was rapid to the point that his bloodline could not keep up with him.

‘Even if I have almost 900 years of life according to the A.I. Chip, the risks with waiting that long are way too high!’ he thought as he stroked his chin. On top of that, Leylin can’t be sure that the purity of his bloodline was enough for a breakthrough to the Morning Star stage by the time he reaches 900.

As such, he would continue to work hard!

At the very least, his bloodline shackle would not retard his progress before he hit rank 4, and he would be able to advance to that realm without any obstacles.

“Penny for your thoughts?” His introspection had obviously drawn Robin’s attention.

”Oh… It’s…” Leylin summarised his ruminations on his bloodline growth, obviously concealing his conjecture on its purity and instead diverting the conversation to how he could develop his bloodline.

”…So, you wish to find out whether there are any medicines or materials the Ouroboros Clan uses to speed up bloodline growth?” Robin looked at Leylin, and did not know whether to laugh or cry.

”Many Warlocks depend on the strength of their bloodlines when using their meditation techniques to slowly improve in ranks. A case like yours, where the host’s strength surpasses that of the bloodline’s growth is extremely unlikely…”

”Unlikely, but not impossible!” Leylin was determined. The central continent had many groundbreaking talents, and the Ouroboros Clan was where Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks congregated. There must be a way!

Still, any solutions that existed were sure to be extremely precious and hidden. Leylin had never seen such a thing in the trading hall.

“Indeed. Like you, Leylin, our organisation has had a few Warlocks in the past whose strengths far surpassed their age!”

Kesha interrupted, “And they used a top-notch precious material to increase the growth of their bloodline to remarkable results!”

”What material?” Leylin’s eyes glowed.

”Lamia Hair!” Kesha did not intend to leave Leylin in suspense, and gave him a specific term.

”A.I Chip!” Leylin recited internally: “Query the database for Lamia Hair!”

Collecting data and books was habitual for him. Naturally, he hadn’t slacked off on it in his time in the Ouroboros Clan.

The Ouroboros Clan was a major power of the central continent. Its library had a rich collection of data, and since Leylin was a Marquis, he had little restriction on what he could read, and had thus expanded his database significantly. What was remaining was naturally not too big a problem.

Although he could not claim that he knew everything about the central continent, the knowledge he had accumulated in this period would not lose out to that of a scholar who was a few hundred years old.

[Lamia Hair: It is an ancient precious material. Legend has it that a strand of hair from the ancient Lamia has a extremely horrifying ability. Rank: 3, Rarity: 4, Description: The Lamia was an extremely tyrannical being in ancient times. Other than strange spells, they were experts at controlling lower serpents to attack, and normally lorded over snakes! Legend has it that they were direct descendants of the Snake Dowager, and were comparable to Radiant Moon Magi in adulthood!]

Leylin saw the description given by the A.I Chip and could not help but smile wryly.

A description in terms of rank and rarity was standard on the central continent. Rank 3 indicated that the material was only effective for rank 3 Magi, while the rank 4 rarity meant only Morning Star Magi could get their hands on one.

Needless to say, the assessment on how it could compare to a Radiant Moon Magus in adulthood shocked Leylin completely.

A Radiant Moon Magus was at rank 5! They exceeded Morning Star Magi by one full rank, and there were few Magi on the central continent who possessed such strength.

How would Leylin, who could not afford to offend even a single Morning Star Magus, dare to think of a plan involving Radiant Moon Magi?

Of course, the strength of the beings themselves was one matter, the resources were yet another.

”For senior Kesha to mention it, could it be that Mentor has strands of Lamia Hair?” Leylin’s eyes lit up. The ancient Lamia had been extinct for a long period of time. But some remains could have been discovered by Magi, and it would be extremely normal to obtain these resources as a result.

Chapter 414: Noah

“Perhaps the Lamia Hair within the pocket dimension was not obtained by capturing an ancient Lamia. There might have been someone who advanced their own Lamia bloodline to the extreme and has even gone through atavism, thus leaving this item behind.”

When a Warlock’s bloodline was concentrated to its limit, it would transform into its original form. Once this process was over, a Warlock would discard their original appearance as a human, and completely turn into a creature alike to his bloodline origin.

By that time, the Warlock would no longer be human. Even those with the same bloodlines would not be able to tell that it was a Warlock who had gone through such a process.

In other words, if Leylin did so, he would truly turn into a Giant Kemoyin Serpent.

“Hm… Forget it.”

Leylin imagined himself as a giant serpent, only able to swallow raw food everyday and looking for female serpents whenever he had to sate his desires, and it made his whole body shiver.

‘The Morning Star morphing technique is enough. I have no desire to really become a giant serpent,’ he decided.

He pursued strength and dominance, as well as his own freedom. If the option was that he obtained unequalled strength and yet suffered for eternity, it was fine if he was not unrivalled.

In addition, the closer he was to the source of his bloodline, the greater the suppression of his mind by higher members of his race.

In the ancient war of the Icy World, the Snake Dowager was the only thought in mind. Many Giant Kemoyin Serpents who risked their lives and battled with beings from other worlds were more than aware of this. Leylin did not want to be controlled by someone after all his efforts and become cannon fodder.

Of course, all this was far into the future. Right now, all he was focused on was using the Lamia Hair to nourish his bloodline, allowing it to mature faster and bring him to the Morning Star realm.

In the central continent, rank 3 Warlocks were respected, but only Morning Star Magi held any actual clout.

Only after reaching the Morning Star realm could he perform experiments on astral gates alone, attempting to travelling between various places and worlds. This was the only method for Leylin to solve the issue of his bloodline and could not be substituted.

After thinking about it for a while, a silver light flashed in his hands, and a dull gold coin appeared.

‘If I go to the pocket dimension, will I be able to get all that I want and leave safe and sound?’ With this thought in mind, Leylin tossed the Coin of Destiny in his hand.

*Pak!*

The coin landed steadily on the back of his hand, revealing the image of a luckbird. At the same time, slight cracks appeared on it.

Noticing this situation, Leylin kept the coin away, and a flash of excitement could be seen on his face before he turned serious.

‘It’ll work out, but the power of a Morning Star will hinder me?’ The Coin of Destiny was a unique magic item that Leylin had sacrificed blood and tears to make. It had the terrifying ability to predict the future, but could not be used when powers at the Morning Star realm and above.

Every time a prediction involved a being with Morning Star strength, the coin would crack further and further until it would eventually be destroyed.

Leylin had a feeling that after losing this Coin of Destiny, he would not be able to create another for a long time.

‘What does this prophecy mean? Is there a Morning Star creature slumbering in the pocket dimension, or will there be Morning Star Magus outside who’ll interfere’ Leylin rubbed his eyebrows, the many possibilities flying through his mind and giving him a headache.

The Coin of Destiny was a non-living thing and its prophecies were vague enough to baffle him on occasion.

In addition, destiny could not be grasped so easily. Even the coin could make some wrong predictions, especially in a place like the central continent where almost every area was overseen by Morning Star Magi. They would affect destiny even more.

Morning Star strength was already able to slightly affect the force of the river of destiny.

The strong grasped their destiny. This was an eternal truth.

Hence, the prediction of this coin could only act as a reference and might not be accurate. Blue light flashed in Leylin’s eyes, and all sorts of possibilities streaked through his mind…

About two months had passed in the blink of an eye.

Leylin was now in front of the black Magus Tower, with various runes and strange metal plates on the ground.

“Enchant!” Foggy spiritual force congealed to form a solid rune pen that carved out refined, complicated patterns on the metal plates. All the patterns combined to form a dazzling spell rune and imprint.

After the last stroke was completed, the many metal plates were shrouded with dim light.

“Your enchantment techniques have probably reached the level of a master and are not far from those of a grandmaster, my Lord. My respects towards you!” Parker glanced at the enchanted metal plates, of which almost all had been done successfully, his expression revealing his admiration.

The young man in front of him had reached the Vapour Phase before he turned a hundred, leaving him biting the dust. His knowledge in potioneering had even reached the level of a grandmaster. It seemed like his enchantment knowledge was also not to be underestimated, at the level of a master!

‘Looks like my master’s future will be hard to predict!’ Parker suddenly had this thought. ‘This is good too. I’ve made the right choice!’

Leylin cared little for Parker’s thoughts. He glanced at the enchanted metal plates that he had worked on, looking satisfied.

In actuality, with the support from the A.I. Chip, what he was least afraid of was complicated things like this. His skills in enchantment and alchemy had long since reached the level of a grandmaster.

He had even intentionally failed a few so that he would not be seen as terrifying.

He would be considered a genius if he could be one or two steps ahead of everyone. However, being ten or more steps ahead would cause panic, and he would be seen as a freak. Leylin obviously did not want that to happen.

“Parker, spread these isolation plates within the positive and negative energy elemental pools based on the blueprint from before. Is that understood?”

Leylin took a white towel from a deferential Snoopy and wiped his hands as he spoke to Parker.

The Magus Tower was now completed with the efforts of the Stone Tribe men. The next order of business was to carve defensive runes and activate spell formations.

The Warlocks that sided with Leylin were like him, spending all their time adding these runes on all sorts of materials. After inspection, they were stored until the building’s construction was completed.

“Understood, master.” Parker respectfully bowed 90 degrees, leaving Leylin flabbergasted. This new vassal of his seemed to be even more respectful than before.

However, this was to be expected. The might of a leader was built from strength and obedience.

“Also, I’m planning to leave. When I’m not around, you’re in charge of everything regarding the construction of the Magus Tower. A few supportive facilities have been built. However, the activation of the spell formations will wait until I’m back, I’ll do that myself,” Leylin commanded.

These miscellaneous matters could be passed on. As long as he was the one checking everything and activating the spell formations, there was no problem.

The last step, which was to give life to the structure, was enough for Leylin to make the whole Magus Tower perfect and even have a spirit of its own. If there were any issues, all would be known to him.

“Understood. Master, are you going on a long journey?”

The Magus Tower was only half-done, and it was the lifeblood of a Magus. Usually, nothing could move them from the tower, which was why Leylin’s actions were very strange.

“Yes! I’m going to the headquarters, but it is not certain how long it will take.” Leylin glanced up the sky, into the distance.

He had a reason why he had to go there. The temptation of the Lamia Hair was too much for him. In addition, besides the last few steps, the construction of the Magus Tower now was all about the details. There was no need to stay here and supervise.

……

A few days later, outside Phosphorescence Swamp.

“Haha, Leylin, you’re finally here. We’ve been waiting for you!” Upon seeing Leylin’s figure, Robin immediately moved over and gave him an enthusiastic hug.

“My apologies. I had some work to do so I’m a little late.” Leylin had an apologetic look on his face as he greeted Kesha.

Besides Robin and Kesha, there were nine other Warlocks whose auras made it evident that they had reached rank 3. Leylin couldn’t help but sigh in admiration at these Warlock families who had accumulated their bloodline and strength for a long time. Just a casual request would call forth many powerful Warlocks.

“This is Noah. You’ve seen him at the banquet before.” Robin laughed as he pulled Leylin aside.

“Uncle Leylin!” This young man named Noah had wine-red eyes that were very memorable.

This young man was Robin’s nephew, and he had a very concentrated bloodline. He had already reached rank 3 and Robin thought highly of him. Leylin had also seen him once before at the banquet.

As for the rest of the rank 3 Warlocks, Robin merely skimmed over them.

Headed by Leylin and the other three Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks, the eight other Black Horrall Snake Warlocks were also at rank 3 but had a lower status.

Out of these eight rank 3 Warlocks, Robin had brought over five, and with his nephew added in he held the most authority in this small group. Kesha had brought three Black Horrall Snake Warlocks from her own family over. Those rank 1 descendants from before had not appeared at all, and it was probably because she knew this expedition would be dangerous, and it was pointless to bring them along.

Leylin was alone and looked quite pitiful.

Out of all his subordinates, only Parker was somewhat acceptable. However, he was useless in this expedition, and might even have hindered them. Leylin though it’d be better if he just stayed and looked after domestic affairs.

“Alright. Since everyone is here, let’s go! The Forgotten Zine is very far from here, and it will take a month by airship.” Robin waved his arm in high spirits.

Chapter 415: The Descendants’ Issue

Leylin and company’s departure did not rouse much commotion in the Ouroboros Clan.

Warlocks did not spend all their time on research. Adventuring and the exploration of pocket dimensions were also deemed normal for them. Due to their longevity, even were they to disappear for a few years, their absence would be inconspicuous.

The twelve rank 3 Warlocks moderated the horrifying radiation and energy undulations on their bodies and went under the guise of a regular troop of adventurers from the central continent. Discreetly, they all boarded an airship at a city not far from Phosphorescence Swamp.

Standing on board the deck, Leylin fell silent as he looked at the illustrious symbol of the Fallor Family splashed across the body of the airship,

“They are indeed the rulers of the skies. They single-handedly dominate and monopolize the entirety of aerial transport in the central continent!” From the bottom of his heart, Leylin sighed without any inhibitions.

“What are you looking at?”

A whiff of perfume and seconds later, Kesha walked over, half leaning on the railings and revealing her sensual beautiful body.

Due to the enhanced bloodline of Warlocks, her skin was more delicate and exquisite. Coupled with her slim, shaped eyes and slightly curled cherry lips, she eluded a kind of demonic charm that caused some travellers to have rumblings in their throat and flames burning in their stomach.

Leylin’s eyes naturally swept across Kesha’s body unrestrainedly, paying particular attention to the vital parts.

“Hehe!” Kesha laughed tenderly and without a qualm arched her back and pushed her bosom forward, “The journey is getting rather boring, would you like to go back to my room for some fun?”

Leylin rolled his eyes, lust and illicit sexual relations among the nobles were common. It was even more normal for those who grasped great power and possessed a long life.

Of course, there were some exceptions among the Warlocks. To attain an even more outstanding and pure bloodline, female Warlocks would go all out and embrace craziness. In fact, they had the advantage for seduction.

Leylin smiled and replied, “Pardon me! Not today, you will be the be first to know when I decide to sell my seed, though!”

“Alright then! Such a pity!” Kesha licked a finger, revealing no hint of her humiliation.

“But still! I really do like you, junior!” She placed her finger on Leylin’s chest and with a smile, twirled it in circles.

However, that was the furthest Kesha went and she attempted nothing else. In the end, she appropriately settled for casual conversation with Leylin.

“Do you know Freya and Miranda? Kesha asked out of the blue.

“We have met a few times!” Leylin replied with some uneasiness as he drew out the air from his breath. As far as those two nutjobs were concerned, especially the more powerful one out of the two, he really had a hard time dealing with them.

“Then are you aware?” Kesha smiled mysteriously, with an added crafty look of a little girl.

“They have been spreading the word that you belong to them and you are their prey. Any other female Warlocks who have any intentions of looking your way, will have to go up against them!”

“I…” Leylin rolled his eyes in anger, almost cursing in his rage.

“These two maniacs!” he finally exclaimed with extreme resentment.

“Actually, Why don’t you seriously consider it? Miranda has to-die-for skills and holds the title of the Succubus, as for Freya….”

Kesha moved forward, almost leaning on Leylin and whispered into his ears : ”Freya has never been with a man, so she might be a virgin after all!”

The scent from her hair was pleasantly sweet as it permeated the air. Coupled with Kesha’s words, Leylin was left with a dry mouth.

“Why?” A victorious smile surfaced on Kesha’s face, ”What about now? Do you want me to cease your desire? My skills might be better than Miranda’s!” As she spoke, she stuck out her pink tongue and gently licked on Leylin’s earlobes.

Suddenly, Kesha felt Leylin’s body turned cold, just like a block of ice. “So I see, you knew the both of them?”

She lifted her head in astonishment and saw an emotionless Leylin standing there, both his eyes sparkling and clear, without a trace of sentiment.

“Yes! I know them, and I am just relaying somewhat of a message for Freya, that’s all!” Seeing Leylin’s reaction, Kesha knowingly stepped back, not daring to tease him further.

“Please tell them I will consider it carefully!” Leylin replied nonchalantly.

“Got it! “ Kesha looked intently at Leylin: “Your current state! It’s as if you’re not influenced by the emotional and passionate moods that arise from your bloodline! I finally understand why Freya could not get her mind off you! Such an outstanding bloodline. It is what we Kemoyin Warlocks need….”

Watching Kesha’s back as she was walking away, Leylin stroked his chin and a bitter smile curled the edges of his lips.

Even for Kemoyin Warlocks, deterioration of one’s bloodline cannot be avoided. Looking at the three Black Horrall Snake Warlocks from Kesha’s Clan, it was obvious their bloodline could not avoid the inevitable degeneration either.

Thinking back on her recent temptation, at least half of it were real. If Leylin had agreed to Kesha’s seduction and had multiple sexual escapades with her, she might have even helped herself to obtain his bloodline

Even if it weren’t for the bloodline, according to the emotional state of minds of female Warlocks, as long as the mood and feel were right, they will go ahead and copulate with other Magi.

In the Magus world, other than female Warlocks, the same applied to the female Magi. Those girls who were pure were a rare species.

But Leylin really had no interest at all. He was in the middle of a risky journey and had no mood for it. Even if he needed the company of a lady, his choice would not be Kesha, Freya or Miranda.

These ambitious female Warlocks would do anything for the continuation of their bloodlines. As female Warlocks, they must have done their research on the nourishing of the bloodline with some specializing in techniques and spells to do it. They were well aware of the ways to attain the seed of a male, something which did not surprise Leylin at all.

He was not completely confident in the A.I. Chip’s ability to calm him down, as well as his control over his own body against the methods they deployed to acquire his bloodline.

If anything unthinkable were to happen, resulting in a pile of descendants that were raised and taught by other clans, it would be mind-boggling and Leylin dreaded the idea.

Besides, there was another hesitation in his heart

His bloodline was purified by means of the A.I.Chip and the purity level was exceptionally high, almost equalling the original bloodline. With his own ability and with the help of the A.I. Chip, he was able to conceal his true strength and capabilities from others, but a newborn baby could not.

If his peculiar bloodline were to be discovered, given the greed of those Morning Star Magi, he might have been captured to become a reproductive machine for the next generation.

God knows, they might even be able to extract and strip him of his bloodline!

Therefore, until he was absolutely sure that it was safe, he would not allow the outflow of his bloodline, not to mention having descendants.

“But, nevertheless, if I am promoted to the rank of a Morning Star Magus and I want to start a clan of my own in the central continent, I am afraid those female Warlocks are my only choice!” Leylin stroked his chin.

Being a pure Kemoyin bloodline Warlock, in order to have strong and powerful descendants in the future, it was naturally more suitable if he chose a female Kemoyin Warlock.

As for female commoners and ordinary Warlocks, children he had with them would have their bloodline diluted to half of his, something which was unacceptable.

The quality of a Warlock’s bloodline was known to be the best in the first generation. The more concentrated it was, the better they would be.

These minute details flashed across his mind once before he tossed them aside.

“This is not the right time for me to think about such matters!”

Leylin squinted his eyes, enjoying the natural and pure sunlight from the deck. A look of satisfaction gleamed in his eyes and his thoughts wandered to a faraway place.

……

As far as Warlocks were concerned, long and slow journeys were not torturous. At worst, they might have to stay in their room every day and meditate to pass time. And since the Fallor Family had provided such excellent services in the first class cabin, Leylin was satisfied, especially with the meals provided.

Given how poor Twilight Zone’s environment was, the food and drink of the central continent were worlds apart.

And no matter how long a journey was, it had to come to an end.

The huge airship started descending, casting a huge circular shadow on the ground. The shadow kept spreading until at last, a loud thump was heard.

“This is Sin City station. All passengers who are alighting, please maintain order!”

After the airship had stabilized, a group of workers and slaves opened the warehouse latch and started unloading the goods. A few flights of stairs were unfolded and secured to the ground. The passengers who were going to alight got ready and started forming a queue.

“We are finally here, the border of the Forgotten Land, Sin City! Even the name is unpretentious with no need to cover up!”

After multiple flights on airships and a month of travel, Leylin had finally reached his destination as he mingled among the other tourists.

He fixated his eyes on the orange sun in the distance, and the dilapidated grey and brown walls under it, as he sighed.

The A.I. Chip issued a warning.

[Beep! The energy particle concentration here is about 10-20% lower than the outside world. Please take note!]

The spells of Warlocks and Magi were cast through their own energy which galvanised the surrounding energy particles. Low concentrations of the energy particles would cause a weakening of their power, leading to greater consumption of their spiritual and magical energies. If they were to face such a situation all of a sudden, many Magi would probably be thrown into a flurry.

“The elemental leakage had affected even the Forgotten Land!” Leylin sighed, “The power of Morning Star Magi is too devastating!”

Although the energy particles concentration level was lower than that in the outside world by 20%, it posed no problem to Leylin.

The concentration level of energy particles of his homeland, the south coast, and the Twilight Zone, were less than half of the central continent. Spellcasting with such low available energy was natural for him.

Chapter 419: An Unexpected Situation

“What happens after we enter the pocket dimension? Are we going to be working together or alone?” Leylin asked unhurriedly from the side, taking a bite of the roast meat.

Kesha was gazing at Robin attentively. The reason she was here was due to the temptation of the precious materials in the pocket dimension. It was natural not to choose to work together.

“You can do as you wish!” Robin answered without hesitation.

“I have a general topographic map here, but it lacks a lot of information. Take a look!” Robin had evidently made preparations earlier and produced two maps, giving one each to Kesha and Leylin.

“Of course, after we get everything, I hope we can discuss or perhaps exchange a few things. If anyone here plans to sell their precious materials, the other two shall have the preemptive right to purchase them!” Robin was very thoughtful, and since Kesha and Leylin had no issues with that, they both nodded.

……

A snaking river flowed out from underground, the sound of surging water echoing throughout the cavity in this underground world, making it feel even more oppressive.

In another area, not only were there powerful defensive spell formation set-ups and runes that glimmered, there were even Magi and beings of other races patrolling the area.

Though these people looked pitiful wearing clothes filled with creases and patches, their auras were very powerful and wild.

Leylin and his group all entered Shadow Stealth state and snuck in.

Not far away from them, black bear humanoids—upright creatures with animal skins around their waists as well as other accessories—were standing guard.

“Barbarian Bears!” This was the first time Leylin had seen such a creature.

Unlike the half-beastmen who had escaped from the laboratories, Barbarian Bears were truly from another world. They were extremely intelligent, and their bodies were very resilient.

An adult Barbarian Bears was comparable to a rank 1 Branded Swordsman or Bio Booster, as well as other sub-branches of ancient Magi. After awakening, the power of their totems, elder Barbarian Bears, and Barbarian Bear Shamans could gain the ability to obtain magic with offerings, and turn into frightening magicians.

Just this tribe alone could take on the role as the kings in the Forgotten Land.

In front of Leylin, there were no less than a hundred elite Barbarian Bear warriors, as well as numerous elders and Barbarian Bear Shamans.

And their opponents were not limited to Barbarian Bears.

A few short green creatures strolled past the Barbarian Bears patrol group, holding multi-colour staffs with different ores and gems embedded into them. These staffs emitted detection magic, which caused Leylin to back up.

These green creatures were very similar to gnomes, though their larger heads were like watermelons, large and round. Their skin was a wretched green.

These were the Green-skinned barbarian Magi. Favouring the ability to cast spells, they had abandoned the advantage of strength. Their spiritual force and magic power were terrifying. Every single one of them was akin to a human rank 2 Magus, and some even emanated the strength of rank 3.

“What do we do?” Kesha’s voice travelled into Leylin’s ear.

“Don’t act recklessly. Look!” Leylin pointed in another direction.

At the side of the river, brown vines crawled all over a brown rock. It looked very normal, but this immediately attracted Robin and Kesha’s attention.

“It’s an alarm spell pattern that targets hidden fluctuations in the air. It’s concealed very well. If not for Leylin’s warning, we’d all have been deceived!”

Robin gritted his teeth, “Let’s withdraw first.”

They exchanged glances and left the underground, while the other Black Horrall Warlocks followed closely behind.

*Boom!* Once they got to another safe area, Robin’s expression darkened, and cracks appeared under his feet from his stomps.

“Those wretched traitors to humanity! They must have set up those alarm spell patterns. If not, it’d be impossible for the Barbarian Bears and Green-skinned Barbarians to come up with this technique even if they had ten thousand more years to do so!”

Robin walked in circles, evidently very annoyed. Within the Forgotten Land, besides the Barbarian Bears and Green-skinned Barbarians, there were organisations formed entirely out of fugitive human Magi. There had always been three main forces here.

In order to protect this common asset of theirs that was the pocket dimension, they had obviously teamed up.

“Didn’t we discuss this matter some time ago? Though this is the worst situation, we have made the required preparations. Relax, your emotional state does not seem too good.”

Kesha watched Robin, whose eyes were turning red, and quickly warned, “Damn it. Leylin, Robin’s probably going to have another episode!”

“Hm?” Upon hearing this, Leylin was stunned and turned to look at Robin’s bewitching handsome face. It was now distorted, and bloodlust was beginning to converge.

This was obviously an effect of the emotional instability caused by his bloodline, resulting in Robin losing his senses.

“Wake up! Robin, you might need it!” A high-grade potion of tranquility appeared in Leylin’s hands as he stared at Robin.

Besides Noah and Kesha, the few other Black Horrall Snake Warlocks had retreated a distance.

It was not out of fear of being hurt by accident, but because of the bloodline, Robin’s outburst might even affect their own bloodline and cause them to descend into a state of confusion.

“No, I’ve had enough of that potion!” Robin’s eyes were gradually turning red, dense spiritual particles almost solidifying in front of him.

“Has your uncle been having these episodes lately?” Leylin asked Noah while watching Robin.

“No! It hasn’t been that long since the last episode. With the potion and suppression from the spell formations, it shouldn’t be happening again so soon…” Noah looked helpless.

“What should we do? If he really goes crazy, he’ll definitely kill us!” Kesha stood beside Leylin, now evidently on the same side.

“What else can be done? Hold him down and force him to calm down!”

Leylin’s eyes turned amber, and a pair of vertical pupils produced a terrifying chill.

After a few advancements, Leylin’s bloodline was even more concentrated, and the aura of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent had also risen.

This feeling was most evident to Robin. He took several steps back, his expression alternating between mania and rationality.

“Robin, we’re helping you!” At this moment, Kesha went forward, a powerful aura emanating from her body.

The two of them worked together and evidently gave Robin a terrifying amount of pressure.

At this moment, while he was breathing heavily, the rational expression stayed on his face longer.

“You’re right.” Robin’s voice became coarse and thick, completely different from the gentility it held before.

He produced a high-grade potion of tranquility from his spatial equipment and gulped it down.

A bracelet formed using white crystals was glimmering with tiny white rays, producing a chill that spread in all directions.

“Hah…” Robin let out a long breath, his expression becoming gentle.

He took a look around, eyes clear and wise, “Many thanks, everyone. I’m better now!”

“That’s great!” Noah cheered, while Kesha and Leylin looked like a weight had been lifted off their shoulders.

If Robin really were to act up now, they would have to give up on the plan despite their unwillingness not to.

“Robin, what’s going on? Why did it suddenly happen?” Kesha expressed her disapproval towards Robin.

“My apologies! The outburst of emotion was to sudden, and I could not control it at all…” Robin laughed wryly.

The defect of emotional instability caused by the bloodline had always been an issue for Warlocks. Even with all types of suppression potions and spell formations, they could only ease the issue, not cure it.

This was why Leylin’s potions of tranquility were in such high demand.

‘With Robin’s strength and thoughts, he shouldn’t be stirred up so easily and invoke the emotions from his bloodline. Looks like there’s something he must have from the pocket dimension, which caused him to be so irritated and be made susceptible to those emotions…’ Leylin rationalized.

Compared to other high-ranked Warlocks, he had used the breath of the Icy Jade Scorpion Emperor to treat his bloodline in Twilight Zone. That was why he had experienced no episodes till now.

Based on the A.I. Chip’s simulations and Leylin’s own calculations, he did not have to worry about this until he reached the Morning Star realm. Other Warlocks would not be so fortunate.

Even a rank 3 Hydro Phase Warlock like Robin would often be affected by these emotions.

As for Kesha? Leylin’s eyes swept past her, and he found at least three types of spell patterns that acted as alarms and bloodline-suppressors.

“Alright, now we think about what happens at the end of the plan,” Leylin spoke, gathering Robin and Kesha’s attention.

“Though we are now a distance away from the pocket dimension and have also especially set up a concealing spell formation, an outburst of aura like what just happened could be sensed by our opponents.

“We need to decide on what to do as soon as possible.”

Upon hearing this, Robin looked sorry and embarrassed. This whole situation was caused by him.

Rank 3 Warlocks, merely by using their auras, could generate giant energy undulations, and it was unknown whether their setup was enough to conceal that.

“It can’t be helped. We should enter stealthily, and if it doesn’t work, we barge in!” Robin gritted his head and made his choice.

“Now that they might have discovered the undulations and are coming here, we should just head straight to the entrance of the pocket dimension. As I am the reason for the delay, I will place myself at the back of the group and enter after all of you have done so.”

Robin bowed slightly.

At the rear, he would require much strength to face the crazed counter-attacks from other powers. Even Robin would find this difficult to bear, which made his sincerity clear.

Hence, Leylin and Kesha immediately agreed to Robin’s suggestion.

Chapter 420: Being Discovered

Leylin and Kesha were both unemotional, knowing that it was not the time for any disputes. Their opportunity was fleeting, and could not be wasted.

Approximately ten seconds later, everyone entered Shadow Stealth and left.

A huge formidable energy undulation suddenly broke through the spell and created a violent explosion, just like a prominent bonfire in the darkness of the night.

Of course, this was intentionally set up by Leylin and company.

And with the continuous transmission of the energy undulations, some brilliant rays shone in their direction…

“We’re here! This is the furthest we can go, any further and we might alert the alarms that were set up, even in Shadow Stealth. The spell has too many defects that can be probed.

Robin led everyone into a hiding spot and then stopped his steps.

Leylin looked over and from where he stood, he was able to see to the bottom of the flowing river, In the middle of which was a huge whirlpool. The continuously whirling water sparkled on occasion, and some green Barbarian Bears and human Magi started to emerge from it.

“The entrance to this pocket dimension is unexpectedly just a whirlpool….” Leylin nodded his head. The undulations that were being emitted by the whirlpool did not seem to be fake.

He was deciding on a path of approach.

Leylin took a closer look at the surroundings of the whirlpool. The A.I. Chip was working at full power, forming a 3D map of the area in his mind. The enemy’s defense was naturally strong, with some large structures and a sentry system in place for defense. There were even some rank 3 Magi standing guard.

Leylin shifted his line of sight to the center and shot a glance at a Barbarian Bear. It had a thick neck with a weird looking flag on its back. There was another big headed, very old looking Green-skinned Barbarian. Lastly, there was an unassuming human Mage robed in grey.

“These three…” Leylin’s pupils dilated, ”They’re at least at Hydro Phase. As for the Barbarian Bear, it might already be at the Crystal Phase!”

Leylin and company were nearly equal in power to these Magi, and only held a slight edge in power. Once the patrols were counted in, numbering ten times their own, it would be very difficult to defeat them.

“I will make use of the secret gem to cover up our tracks. Wait for my signal and move together. My men and I will take care of the back!” Robin took out a black ring and spoke in a heavy tone.

Leylin and Kesha both nodded their heads, and walked in a straight line towards the whirlpool in the dark river.

There were some scattered buildings around where they were that looked brand new. It also had a rugged feel to it, most likely made by the Barbarian Bears. Leylin and company were amongst the shadowy construction area and moved progressively towards the centre with the help of the shadows of some patrolmen.

“If they come ten metres closer to us, we will attack!” Robin’s voice sounded out, the tone oppressive.

Rank 3 Magi were very sharp and alert. As soon as they came close, the party would certainly be discovered.

In the midst of the crack in the shadows, the outside world seemed like it was covered with a layer of fog, almost like a starch paste. It was very vague and fuzzy.

However, Leylin could clearly sense them advancing.

One metre… two metres… three metres…

Another seven meters to go and Leylin and the rest of the Warlocks would have the confidence to breach their defence and wipe them out completely before heading for the pocket dimension.

*Woo woo…* At this very moment, something unexpected suddenly happened. The decorative flag on the back of the Barbarian Bear started to flap and shudder.

A strange skull symbol on the scarlet red patch of the flag started to open its mouth, revealing a mouthful of sharp teeth as it wailed loudly.

“Intruder!” The Barbarian Bear stood up and hissed. The sound engulfing the entire area.

“Damn, we’ve been exposed! Charge!” A singular ray of brilliance shone through the hollowness and Robin appeared to take the lead.

“Innate poison!” Immediately, he opened up his poison domain.

In a split second, an invisible and terrifying ripple originated from Robin and started to spread. The surrounding patrolmen immediately started to collapse one after the other, with some dying on the spot and their bodies decomposing thereafter.

“Toxic Bile! You are a Warlock from the Ouroboros Clan!” The average-looking Magus wearing the grey robe clenched his teeth, as if he had some deep-seated hatred with the Ouroboros Clan.

“Activate the rank 5 poison defense spell formation!” He ferociously raised his hands and clapped.

A burst of intense brilliance erupted and a huge spell was cast, rays of green falling on every Magus present.

Like a protective armor, the spread of the green rays enveloped the Magi. Although the armor was trembling continuously, it resisted the attack of the Toxic Bile. As for the rest of the Magi around Robin, they were completely doomed for, even with the assistance of the spell formation.

“All of these sinners deserve death! Do not show mercy!” Kesha and Leylin entered the scene with her yell as she launched her own attack of poison. The rest of the Magi soon followed suit.

In the blink of an eye, the Kemoyin Serpent poison built up, repeatedly overlapping and growing. The formidable power increased to such an extent that even Leylin raised his eyebrows in awe.

*Zi Zi!* The green rays of brilliance were corroding the armor. The other Magi and tribes who were standing behind could not hide their stunned faces.

“Kill!” The huge Barbarian Bear said coldly after a loud roar. The muscles on its body bulged, and the velvet fur stood on end as its physique immediately widened.

As for the big-headed Green-skinned Barbarian, it quickly took out multiple bottles of different sizes, as if ready to cast spells.

“Leave him to me. You deal with the rest!” Robin looked over at the grey-robed Magus with fervour.

“I remember now, he is a Magus from Lone Zither, the sole survivor of the massacre.”

At the mention of this name, the grey robed Magus’ face turned blood red, “Today, I shall avenge the death of my teachers and classmates!”

*Vroom!* A ball of black flame ignited from his body just like a human shaped column and dashed towards Robin.

“Seeing how things have developed till now, I can only go all out!”

Without any other choices, Leylin shrugged his shoulders and, with lightning speed, tossed out multiple test tubes and bottles containing potions.

“Potion combination spell—Divine Prairie Flame! “

A large number of fire snakes swirled and engulfed everyone who was desperately trying to defend against the Kemoyin Poison. Huge billows of smoke rose in the air along with their pitiful cries as a violent and deafening explosion erupted from the blaze.

‘It costs ten times as much to cast a spell here as it does outside. We need to preserve some strength to defend ourselves in case enemy troops catch up with us, so…’ Leylin drew out the black Meteor Sword from his waist.

The grooves on its blade buzzed continuously, as if thirsting for blood.

“Cross Slash!” Leylin grasped his fallen sword and delivered a single forward hack!

A black cross-shaped ray from the edge of the blade streaked across and dismembered a majority of the Magi into pieces. The Kemoyin poison from the blade immediately caused their flesh to decompose.

“We are not here to kill people. We only have to get into the pocket dimension!”

Leylin looked at the surroundings and saw the human grey robed Magus blocked by Robin, while Kesha had picked to go up against the huge Barbarian Bear. He found it puzzling as to why she liked such big challenges.

Noah, on the other hand, led the Black Horrall Snake Magi and continued with the attack.

The entire field was a sea of confusion and chaos. An urgent bugle horn sounded and Leylin could feel the rays of light that chased them making their way back rapidly.

“Foreign human, do you also long for the Forgotten Land’s pocket dimension?”

With a brain that was twice the size of a regular human and a body covered with endless wrinkles, the Green-skinned Barbarian was done with it’s poison concoction and positioned itself in front of Leylin, revealing it’s few teeth that were stained yellow.

“I didn’t expect you to be a Potions Master as well!” Leylin looked intently at the grey coloured alms bowl the Green-skinned Barbarian was holding. In it was a bubbling dense green liquid.

“Get out of my way!” The fallen sword in Leylin’s hand created endless blade rays.

A huge ray of brilliance swiped across the ground and left a long deep gush.

“You shall make a fine addition to my, Modris’, collection!”

The Green-skinned Barbarian laughed. With it’s exceptionally nimble hands and the constant undulations on its body increasing steadily, it seemed as if it was more powerful than Leylin!

*Swish! Swish!* The clever Green-skinned Barbarian split his body into three parts, and in turn each part grew as a whole. It headed straight for Leylin at full speed.

“Just this?” Leylin smiled callously as swiped his sword repeatedly and pierced through two of the phantom images.

The Green-skinned Barbarian’s smile showed a confidence in victory as it swiftly started chanting.

Beside one of the phantom images, the greenish liquid in the grey alms bowl exploded and manifested itself into a gooey monstrous hand.

The innumerable suction pads on the hand started trembling, seeming like it was attached to a tremendously huge body that was attempting to break free from the alms bowl.

Green billows of fog filled the air as if a cage and attempted to trap Leylin within.

But suddenly, the Green-skinned Barbarian’s eyes shot open.

Leylin showed no signs of panic or fear amidst the fog, and on the contrary, took out a potion of his own from his belt. A layer of pink smoke slowly dispersed, enveloping the alms bowl.

The pink smoke neuralized the green gas in moments, and soon droplets of liquid started to form that sprinkled onto the ground.

“How… How can it be…” The Green-skinned Barbarian’s jaw fell wide open.

“Are you surprised your summon mixture has zero effect? Do you think I can’t recognise it?” Leylin looked at the Green-skinned Barbarian, his smile showing his satisfaction.

“With just a potion of clean-jem neutralizing potion, the problem can be solved. You should be embarrassed to use such mediocre potions against me!”

Chapter 421: Sudden Entry

Battles between Potions Masters depended most on their accumulated knowledge and recipes.

For instance, had Leylin not recognised the type of potion that the Green-skinned Barbarian was using, it might have been a hindrance to him.

The winner was determined by who managed to see through the other party’s setup.

When it came to all this information, how could the Green-skinned Barbarian match up to Leylin, who possessed the A.I. Chip?

“You-” The opposite Green-skinned Barbarian’s fingers began to shake, evidently in fear.

“What? Are you planning to use the Star-traced amulet and activate the Icy Frost Potion above your waist, or are you going to use the Corrosive Poison Arrow Potion at your back?”

Leylin measured up this Green-skinned Barbarian, obviously ridiculing it.

“Oh! No, I think you’re doing this as a cover for you to activate your Wind Spirit’s Fury under your feet!”

All sorts of expressions crossed the opposite Green-skinned Barbarian’s face, and it was truly difficult for it to have so many expressions and movements on his creased face. At the end, all this turned into terror.

“Ah! You’re the devil! The devil!”

The Green-skinned Potion Master yelled, and actually abandoned his race and companions, fleeing from the battle area first.

It evidently had a very high status here. After seeing it flee, the other Green-skinned Barbarians were startled, and with some of them shouting at the top of their voices, they rapidly left the area.

“Good job!” Robin, who was not far away, revealed a smile. He was the strongest of the three of them, and the opposite grey-robed Magus could only fend for himself.

Kesha, who was on the other side, was not so lucky.

When she had chosen her opponent, she had had no A.I. Chip and depended on her judgment. She had actually chosen the Barbarian Bear Shaman, which was likely at the Crystal Phase.

This Barbarian Bear Shaman not only had unimaginable strength but also a tough body. Even Kesha’s Eye of Petrification could only hold it for a second and had no other effect.

Rank 1 or two spells that struck it would char the fur, but there would be no substantial harm. As for rank 3 spells? Not only were such models difficult to get a hold of, to use them in the Forgotten Land required that one pay a huge price.

Not everyone was a Potions Grandmaster like Leylin, who could use potions to simulate the effects of a rank 3 spell.

*Wooh wooh!* At this moment, the skeleton flag on Barbarian Bear Shaman’s back suddenly exploded, sounding like a bugle horn.

“Awoo awoo!” The surrounding Barbarian Bears who heard these sounds immediately roared frantically, eyes turning blood-red and their offensive abilities increasing by a large amount. Noah and the other Warlocks were immediately at a disadvantage.

“They’re entering a frenzied state! Even regular Barbarian Bears are affected! How about that one?”

Leylin immediately shifted his attention to the Barbarian Bear Shaman.

Along with the sounds of the horn, the Barbarian Bear abruptly roared towards the skies, slapping its chest.

Thick veins that were like old tree roots occupied its hands, chest, and back.

*Ka-cha!* The skull of this Barbarian Bear cracked open, revealing a muscle similar to a brain that was beginning to glow with warmth.

“Awoo!” Under its crazed roar, this Barbarian Bear Shaman’s body began to expand. Its body that was about two floors high became taller, turning into a gigantic humanoid bear-shaped monster.

Energy undulations typically produced by Crystal Phase Magi burst out from the body of this giant Barbarian Bear.

“Crystal—Crystal Phase!” Kesha looked pained.

The Barbarian Bear monster obviously did not care about that. With its paw that could cover the heavens, it swiped at her!

Under this terrifying might, the air seemed to solidify and began to attack Kesha.

With a boom, Kesha’s figure was sent flying, slamming into numerous buildings.

“Explosive Fireball!”

Countless giant fireballs exploded on the Barbarian Bear’s head, but the groove with what seemed to be a brain was not the least bit damaged. All these attacks successfully incited the fury of the Barbarian Bear monster, and attracted its attention elsewhere.

“Kesha, how is it? Are you dead yet?”

“Who asks questions like that?” Bricks exploded, and Kesha’s figure appeared.

However, she was not in a very good condition. Her clothes were tattered beyond repair, revealing dense snake scales. Kesha was now in her snake form, and not only did her Kemoyin’s Scales cover her entire body, even her pupils had elongated and turned vertical.

Even with the most powerful defensive form of Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks, there was a huge wound on her arm and it was slightly twisted. Even her bones had issues.

“I used a diversion technique and shifted most of the attack to my left hand.” Kesha revealed her mangled left arm and smiled wryly as she explained, “I didn’t expect that Barbarian Bear to be so fierce! It’s very dangerous today!”

To be defeated by a creature that used brute force and its physique, it was a huge blow to her.

Leylin smiled wryly and quickly pulled Kesha aside, dodging a large black foot.

*Boom!* The building from before was smashed, leaving behind a gigantic footprint.

“What we need to consider right now is how to get away from them. Besides, the support troops and Magi who we attracted before are coming this way. The traps we set up can’t hold them for too long, so we need a plan!”

Leylin quickly told Kesha, his words reaching Robin who was a distance away.

“Awoo!”

At this moment, the giant Barbarian Bear monster was already destroying everything, whether it was its ally, the Green-skinned Barbarian, fallen Magi, Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan or even Barbarian Bear warriors, all were attacked without distinction.

“Ah!”

A Black Horrall Snake Warlock was grasped in the palm of the gigantic Barbarian Bear monster, and produced miserable shrieks of fear.

“You monster. Die!” His facial muscles twisted as he yelled, terrifying rays converging in his hands and turned into a large axe, striking down at it.

*Ka-cha!*

The axe, which had the terrifying might of a rank 3 spell made contact with the monster’s chest, and actually produced sparks.

*Boom! Boom!* The Barbarian Bear monster took two steps back, shook its head, and continued roaring.

With a swing of its arm, it threw the rank 3 Black Horrall Snake Warlock into its mouth and began to chew.

*Gachi! Gachi!*

Flesh, blood, organs and bones slid out from its mouth.

The might of those jaws, as well as its physique and sharp teeth turned the Barbarian Bear monster’s mouth into a grinder, turning the Warlock into minced meat.

“Oh no! Alfredo!”

Noah screamed. It looked like yet another Warlock from his family had died, while Robin’s expression turned as gloomy as dark waters. When he saw a few rays about to catch up to them, his eyes revealed a steely determination.

“Quick, get into the pocket dimension. I’ll bring up the rear,” he opened up his hand, “Illusory Terror!”

Formless thin lines like a large web trapped all the human grey-robed Magi within. There were even all sorts of strange laughter being produced in the air.

After that, he stood in front of the giant Barbarian Bear monster and helped Noah and the others stall for time.

“The seal spell formation is completed.” At this moment, a Warlock who had been by the dark river called out.

A scarlet rune launched from his finger and entered the whirlpool of the underground dark river.

*Pila!* A giant blue web immediately appeared on the surface of the river.

“Open!” Leylin’s eyes flickered with blue rays, his Meteor Sword streaking across with a strange arc and slashing at the web!

Black light flashed, and the blue web immediately broke apart, revealing the black entrance to the pocket dimension in the whirlpool behind it.

“Quick, quick, quick! Hurry up!” Many Warlocks immediately jumped into the whirlpool, and immediately disappeared with silver spatial rays.

“Senior Robin, let’s go!”

Leylin slashed at the area with the Meteor Sword and terrifying Kemoyin toxins appeared once more, before he unhesitatingly jumped into the whirlpool.

“Awoo!” The giant Barbarian Bear monster’s eyes glinted with intelligence, and it charged towards Robin in a frenzy.

“What a pity! This is something I only just got my hands on!”

Robin took a look at the monster and tossed a black ball at it.

*Pak!*

Countless vines appeared in mid-air, with green shoots and leaves that formed a large green web that trapped it within.

“Ball of Binding! This is a one-time use magic object passed down from ancient times. Even Crystal Phase Magi will be held back for at least a minute!” Robin sighed, and then jumped into the whirlpool.

Silver-white rays flashed, and he disappeared.

At this moment, a few splendid rays charged to the camp and the lights vanished, revealing the forms of a few people who looked terrible.

“Douglas, stop, you idiot!” A Barbarian Bear with golden fur immediately went forward and roared using a unique method.

This roaring was at a specific frequency that prevented the monster from moving.

“Looks like someone broke into the pocket dimension! I smell the disgusting scent of Warlock blood…”

The Green-skinned Barbarian leader’s nose twitched and he concluded confidently.

“The Ouroboros Clan? Even they have to abide by our rules in the Forgotten Land!” Together with these two Magi was a human Magus with a strange brand on his face that seemed like some kind of symbol.

Chapter 422: The Sun’s Child

“So what now? Do we continue our chase?”

Upon hearing the howl of the Barbarian Bear, the huge monster had already returned to its original state and was currently lying on the floor, depressed.

“Or we could simply destroy this entrance!” the golden-furred Barbarian Bear proposed.

“Are you mad? It would be a waste to destroy such a good pocket dimension. Nobody will agree to it!” The Green-skinned Barbarian shook his head and continued: “Besides, those Magi can completely escape from other small cracks. This is such a silly plan!”

The Barbarian Bear groaned coldly, revealing a big flag on his back.

“Alright! Alright, currently we are allies and we need to discuss as to how we will handle our enemies!” said the human Magus as he was stuck in between the Green-skinned Barbarian and the Barbarian Bear.

“What else can we do? If we have no intentions of letting our enemies mindlessly plunder from our pocket dimension, then we must send people in! But you’ve seen their strength, we’d be sending them to their deaths!” The Green-skinned Barbarian’s eyes flashed with a tinge of helplessness.

“Then we’ll have to deploy Hydro and Crystal Phase Magi! In the worst case scenario, we just abandon our bases. First, we must gather our men here!” the human chief replied.

“Since you said so…” The Green-skinned Barbarian and Barbarian Bear chiefs looked at each other. “Then it’s settled! We will immediately send out the signal!”

……

“Is this the pocket dimension that was established by Quicksand in ancient times?” Leylin said whilst standing on a huge plain that, every now and then, emitted wisps of fog.

Leylin looked at the statistics gathered by the A.I Chip and nodded his head. “From this mapping of energy particles, the concentration here is almost the same as that of the outside world. There isn’t any impact to spells anymore!”

During the battle at the underground river, Leylin and the other Magi could not use their entire strength because of the lack of energy particles. But it was different here.

Of course, there were always two sides to a coin. With this concentration, even the Crystal Phase Magi of the other side would have their strengths restored as well, and become free of restraints.

Robin’s silhouette slowly emerged as silver rays of light flashed. He looked at his surroundings and his expression lit up, “Wonderful! These are the Purple Plains, which are not very far from the Magi buildings in the center!”

“Where do you intend to go? If we have different targets to plunder, we need to separate here!” He asked Leylin and Kesha for their opinions.

“Of course! I want to go to the core of the Magi buildings!” Leylin said with a know-it-all look on his face. The Lamia Hair was likely to be kept in the core of the pocket dimension, why would he go to other places?

“Me too!” Kesha followed. Each pocket dimension had its own set of rules, and the resources were most plentiful at its core. Furthermore, the ruins of Magi are there, so there definitely would be storerooms and laboratories inside, making it the most sought after place.

“That’s good then! We shall go to the ruins of the central continent together, then split and start our mission when we arrive!” Robin nodded his head: “In any case, the ruins there are expansive and we can’t say for sure we won’t run into…”

There could still be remaining Magi and other creatures from the previous three forces that dwelled in the pocket dimension, and not to mention the possibility of armies chasing after them. They ought to move as a group to achieve better security to prevent any mishaps.

To make full use of time, Robin immediately announced the start of the mission.

Although they had lost two men in their lineup, the remaining ten shot out blazing rays of light from their pupils, which transformed into ten black streaks that pierced through the horizon.

*Bang!* A Green-skinned Barbarian Magus was thrown to the ground with no light in his eyes. His forehead had a massive and terrifying hole in it, and one could faintly see a portion of his brain. But it was already thoroughly destroyed and looked like a lump of starch paste.

This Green-skinned Barbarian Magus originally had rank 2 Strength. But because his brain was damaged and he did not deploy a clone seed beforehand, he was actually doomed to die.

As his body twitched, the flames of his life were slowly extinguished.

Kesha, who was beside him, took out a gold-trimmed handkerchief and cleaned her hands of the brain remnants.

“I’ve already extracted fragments of his memory. He is a sage of the Green-skinned Barbarians. This time, he came to gather potion materials and resources. According to his memory, we did not deviate far from our original path and we are almost at the core of the pocket dimension—the Quicksand ruins!” she told a bunch of Magi near her.

Their faces flashed with delight upon those words.

They had taken about two days to get to their current location. All this time, they had not only encountered scattered members of the three forces, there were also Hydro Phase Magi on their tails with orders to kill.

That troop, under the lead of a Crystal Phase Magus, had unhesitantly chased after their group.

Luckily, being Warlocks whose strength exceeded their levels, Leylin’s group had been able to fight them and flee whenever they met, but this had still caused a deviation from their original plans.

“Go there as quickly as possible, find what we need and immediately get out! Our traps will not be able to hold them off for long!”

Robin’s expression sank. The small squads at the back could only grit their teeth and carry on with the mission with no time to rest, not to mention any time to find resources.

Even if a trap was put in place again, with the add-on of Leylin’s spectacular skills, and the difficulty in successfully confining multiple Rank 3 Magi, the effects would not last very long.

Even their whereabouts would be known to their enemies.

After entering the pocket dimension, their ultimate goal was to reach the Quicksand ruins in the central continent. Leylin and company had never tried to conceal this fact — or rather, they couldn’t.

The fiery, blazing sun shone in the sky scorching everything.

Although this was merely a projection of the sun of another realm, the terrible heatwaves were still rising constantly, clambering up the surrounding temperature.

Leylin had draped himself with a white cloak and was standing in a large desert. There was only yellow sand as far as the eye could see. Not even a cactus could be seen, not to mention other plants and animals. It was a scene of death.

“Although this is a desert, the atmosphere and environment here are out of the norm!”

Leylin grabbed a handful of sand and its boiling heat spread to the center of his palm, “This kind of temperature is easily beyond a 100 degrees. Leave alone animals or plants, even a group of acolytes or rank 1 Magi cannot stand this terrible place for too long…”

He opened his palm, letting the boiling sand slip through his fingers. “Furthermore, this terrain is giving off a peculiar vibe. It seems to be from an ancient life form!”

“Did you notice it too?” Robin walked up to Leylin as he asked.

“Mm! Apparently, there are traces of some kind of ancient life form that lived here once, and they have a characteristic of blazing heat.” He said with a firm nod of his head.

Large-scale environmental changes like these, made subconsciously by the ancient life forms, were scaringly similar to those by Breaking Dawn Magi.

“I’ve heard a rumor. Among the ancient Quicksand Organization, there was once the son of a famous Bloodline Warlock who safely returned to his ancestors and really became the ancient Sun’s Child.

Robin looked at the vast desert and could not bear to sigh with sorrow: “We can’t say for sure but if that Sun’s Child was here before and cast his power…”

“The Ancient Sun’s Child!” Leylin’s faced changed slightly as he scanned through the database of the A.I Chip.

This was not just a simple bloodline creature. Its flames could burn in a vacuum, twisting the concepts of time. Even in some small worlds, the sun seen is not the actual fixed burning star, but in fact a grown Sun’s Child!

In the event of a Sun Child leaving the small world, it would bring great disaster to that place.

“Relax, even if the Sun’s Child surpassed Breaking Dawn Magi and entered the unpredictable rank 7, he would have probably died long ago during the ancient war.”

Robin seemed to have confidence and Leylin nodded his head in agreement.

Although ancient Magi were incomparably strong, their enemies, too, knew the rules of survival. And could even wipe out certain Magi via these rules.

Once somebody falls during the war, there was no possibility for them to survive. Even if they cloned their bodies as a backup, it was no use because it would decay the second the main body dies.

Even if the Sun’s Child surpassed the strength of the Morning Star Magus, it would be dreadful if he was made to enlist and die during battle.

‘Everything takes its own course. Even one as strong as the sun cannot escape the fate of death!’ Leylin sighed.

‘So it is uncertain if rank 9 Magi will be able to reach immortality?’ This was his highest pursuit and his greatest ambition, a path to eternal life!

Even if he attained the position of a rank 9 Magus in the highest realm, if he realized that he was unable to be immortal, he would still carry on with his journey, without the slightest hesitation, looking for all hope and opportunities!

Leylin’s pupils burned with desire, but he quickly concealed it.

“We’ve arrived!” Shouted Robin who was at the front.

“Hm? Let’s take a look!” Robin and Leylin looked at each other and walked to the front.

After kicking a small sand dune over, they spotted a huge, black, ancient castle, peacefully standing on its own amidst the yellow desert. The rising heat waves caused the castle to look like an oasis, a scene from a dream. But they could only see a small portion of it, and were able to roughly gauge the size of the ancient castle.

“We’re here! There are traces of Magi here—Quicksand Castle!” Robin laughed out loud.

And surrounding the ancient castle, there were a few people working on temporary construction; a few Barbarian Bears, Green-skinned Barbarians and human Magi forming a harmonious group. At certain times, there were Magi setting off alone, changing into flowy rays of light and entering the ancient castle.

Chapter 423: Defeat

A small white bird landed, and Kesha opened her shut eyes. “From the energy fluctuations at that end, they have, at most, a Hydro Phase Magus overseeing them. What do we do?”

”Even though they have received some information related to us, it isn’t too risky to just barge in. We still have to obtain some sort of guide or map of the area to explore it, though……”

Robin let out a deep sigh, “My subordinates only acquired a part of the information about the outermost region. They have no clue as to the internal structure of Quicksand Castle…”

”Even if it’s a trap, the opponent’s teams have been trapped in the sculptured spell formation. Even if there was a trap set up, they would not have much manpower!” Leylin stoked his chin as he stated this assumption.

”In that case, we have nothing to be afraid of!” Robin’s laughed sardonically.

Having been chased after by their opponents for such a long time, almost to the extent of being chased out of the pocket dimension, he held a lot of pent up anger, a sentiment more or less shared by every other Warlock present.

*Pu!*

A scaly hand suddenly extended outwards from emptiness and grabbed the chest of a Barbarian Bear Warrior, gouging out a still-throbbing bright-red heart.

Drops of fresh blood that had yet to lose their warmth dripped down unceasingly, causing the surrounding Magi to be scared stiff.

”Ah! A beautiful, short, death!” A Black Horrall Snake Warlock robed in black squeezed out of a crack in the shadows, his face revealing a mesmerised expression.

Magi could, more or less, be considered mentally ill, and Warlocks were no exception.

Previously, they had been restricted from acting by the royal bloodlines, but now there was no such thing. Once the orders for an attack were given, the alliance went into complete chaos as six Black Horrall Snake Warlocks, together with Noah, massacred every Magus in sight, regardless of rank. Even acolytes were not spared.

That tragedy had caused some Magi to flee.

*Boom!* The central building exploded. Three magi with gloomy expressions floated in mid-air, their bodies emanating the terrifying energy of Hydro Phase Magi.

“Launch the spells!” the one at the center shouted. A ring of fluorescent light flickered and large runes formed a steel cage, firmly securing the entire campsite within.

”I knew you had some tricks up your sleeves. But where are your Hydro Phase and Crystal Phase Magi? Have they all died?”

Just when the three Hydro Phase Magi were about to go forth to stop them, a spark exploded out of the darkness. Robin, along with Leylin and Kesha, stepped out to block them with a sneer.

There were no Morning Star Magi in the Forgotten Land. Even the major powers of the region like the Barbarian Bears had few Crystal Phase Magi.

To deploy a small team to hunt after Leylin’s team was the most they could do without their tribe leaders. Even for that, they had to give up on many strategic locations.

Were this team to be trapped, this alliance in the pocket dimension would have their overall strength greatly reduced.

After all, this group of Magi was only exploring the place. Nobody had expected them to invade.

“A mere one at the Hydro Phase and two at the Vapour Phase. I, Dominic, will ensure that none of you leave this place today!” The human Magus, who wore black robes with a cross-shaped floral pattern on his face, charged forward as Hydro Phase spiritual force surged forth like a tsunami.

”Oh really? But in the eyes of us royal Warlocks, you are like a lamb to be slaughtered!” Robin’s eyes showed a tinge of arrogance and a horrifyingly intimidating strength erupted fiercely from his body.

The same happened with Leylin and Kesha.

”Rank 3 innate spell—Intimidating Gaze!”

This was the formidable spell that high-level rank 3 Warlocks could master. Moreover, even the strength of this spell in the hands of rank 3 Black Horrall Snake Warlocks could not compare to when Leylin and party used it, even if they had trained in the same spell.

This deterrence strength was entirely attributed to the bloodline. The more concentrated the bloodline, the stronger its ancient roots, the more powerful the effect of intimidation would be.

“Rank 3 spell formation! The Domain of Unity!

The bodies of the three began to glow, the light merging to form a strange triangular diagram.

Under the effects of the spell, the dreadful force fields the three of them emitted actually started to indistinctly complement each other and increase in intensity, forming a force similar to that of the domain of a true Morning Star Magus!

Waves of hissing howls arose, those of ancient predatory Giant Kemoyin Serpents. Space vibrated endlessly and a more than thousand metre tall phantom of a giant serpent appeared. The serpent opened its amber eyes and stared straight at the 3 Magi ahead of it, making them break out in cold sweat.

‘A real domain should possess three basic attributes: weaken the enemy, strengthen the self, and bend fundamental laws!’ Leylin had a deep understanding regarding his own domain, all thanks to the large amounts of information hidden in the library of the Ouroboros Clan.

‘The terror of an individual Giant Kemoyin Serpent can at most weaken its enemies. When we cooperate, the terrifying force fields we generate complement and amplify each other!”’

In an instant, he saw the actions of the opposing Magi slow down. The acolytes fainted while rank 1 Magi could barely move. Rank 2 and 3 Magi could move and even cast spells, but their strength had been greatly reduced.

On the contrary, the Black Horrall Snake Warlocks had an abrupt increase in their aura, to the extent that they could compare to the Vapour Phase now. Under Noah’s lead, the low-ranked Magi unscrupulously massacred the camp.

‘After combination, our powers now both weaken the enemy and strengthen our allies. What a pity that we cannot bend laws, else it would have been a terrifying true domain!’ Leylin could feel the terrifying force field adding to his powers.

An indescribable aura entered his body, exciting his bloodline to a boil and pushing his power to that of the Hydro Phase.

Kesha’s situation was similar to his, but what shocked everyone the most was Robin’s transformation. As the core of this combination, he had received the greatest amplification of power. His aura increased nonstop and began to terrify even Leylin. Only Lucian had managed to inspire such emotion in him previously.

Supplemented by the innate gift of three Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks, Robin had already neared the threshold of the Crystal Phase. With the addition of his bloodline’s strength, he had completely stepped into the Crystal Phase in power!

”This terrifying force field! You are all Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks!” The human Magus, Dominic, squinted his eyes, his body trembling.

The reports had only mentioned that a group of rank 3 Warlocks had invaded the pocket dimension. Because Leylin and the other three had only used their innate poison spells when they entered and not this terrifying force field, the Magi had underestimated them.

Even if they were rank 3 Warlocks, the Black Horrall Snake bloodline and the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline were in completely different leagues. Their strengths were poles apart.

Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks were very rare, and typically never strayed out of the Ouroboros Clan headquarters where they were well-protected. The human Magus had not expected the presence of so many Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks in this infiltrating party.

He could feel a portion of the spiritual force in his sea of consciousness being locked. His inability to use it caused his expression to change to one of bitterness.

A little over ten minutes later, the massacre on the ground had come to an end. Limbs and flesh were strewn about everywhere. Noah and the nine remaining Black Horrall Snake Warlocks had not suffered any injuries, but their clothes had been dyed dark red.

The battle in the sky, too, had reached its climax.

”Ophidian Gnaw!”

Robin had grown even more terrifying, having activated his Kemoyin scales defence. The intricate black scales that covered him were smooth yet elegant, and there were even faint patterns on the surface, forming a complete rune the colour of blood.

He howled, and numerous streams of black air congealed into a large black phantom snake that swallowed a huge Barbarian Bear.

A cringeworthy sound of gnawing was emitted. Several seconds later, there was no longer a hint there of the existence of a Barbarian Bear Shaman.

”Shadow cage!” Leylin, Meteor Sword in hand, combed the area. From time to time, he would cast a few spells which caused the Green-skinned Barbarian Magus opposite him to retreat slowly.

*Boom!* At that time, a hidden trap burst out from behind the Green-skinned Barbarian Magus, morphing into a cage of shadows that trapped the Barbarian within.

”Die!” Leylin rushed forward, his quick steps containing the elegance of a dancer. His sword slashed across the neck of the Green-skinned Barbarian. Green blood spurted out as a head flew across the sky.

”AAAAH!” The human Magus let out a startling cry and distanced himself from Kesha, morphing into a ray of light that streaked into the distance.

The cage from before had immediately made an opening for him as he neared.

”You need my permission to leave!” Just as the Magus was going to rush out of the cage, a black palm blocked his path. Robin made his way there with a smile.

Leylin and Kesha tailed behind him and blocked his retreat. Upon seeing that scenario, the Magus smiled wryly and put up both his hands in an act of surrender.

”What now?” The surrendered Magus immediately fell to the ground and fainted. Robin looked anxiously at Kesha.

“Even though the opponent was very cooperative, but it is extremely troublesome to scour through a rank 3 Magus’ memories!” Kesha opened both her eyes, her face revealing an exhausted expression.

Chapter 425: Ecological Garden

Leylin looked into the information the A.I. Chip had previously recorded.

The three powers had been hanging around for a long time, and they had definitely obtained a few useful items.

Based on Dominic’s information, Quicksand Castle was far larger than it looked on the outside. It was practically a gigantic maze.

The numerous rooms outside were the first layer of defense.

If they did not leave on time, they would travel through countless rooms and later be trapped inside till their death.

The mark of the second layer would first be this illusory corridor.

With the dim yellow lighting, Leylin looked through the decorations in the corridor.

The two walls were mostly white, with some strange patterns of flowers and plants, but there were no portraits of humans. The red carpet on the ground extended until the end of the corridor, with not a speck of dust in sight.

“This drawing technique?” Leylin touched his chin. “It has the style of the ancient era. Looks like it is one of Quicksand’s experimentation areas.”

The strength of the current Magi could not compare to that of ancient times. Leylin even suspected that Magi at the Morning Star Realm or higher had even participated in the construction of this place.

As a mere rank 3 Warlock, , a slight misstep could take away his life!

Leylin glanced at the oil paintings in the corridor vigilantly, he started advancing in a strange pace.

The flower patterns on the two sides began to move in tune to his step. They began to grow, germinate, blossom and then wilt, creating a cycle.

“Rumours have it that the illusory corridor can only be entered with a unique walking frequency. It possesses a strange force that can send a person to any place he would like to go to.”

Leylin remembered this passage, as well as the account at the end, “If there are errors in one’s footwork, the illusory corridor will turn into a life-threatening trap, trapping both their body and soul.”

This specific footstep was discovered through the huge sacrifice from the Magi on the outside, which now made things convenient for Leylin’s group.

“What exactly do I want?”

Leylin strolled along the corridor and constantly asked himself. A unique feature of the corridor was that if one did not have a clear desire, there would be no end.

After a specific period of time, the same mechanism would activate.

“Immortality, strength and all that would be too vague and exceed the abilities of the illusory corridor. I can only mention a place it can communicate with.”

Leylin muttered to himself, “It’s not safe to directly say the location of the Lamia Hair. If such a material doesn’t exist, the illusory corridor will instantly regard me as an intruder!”

This was a test for all who entered. The true owner definitely knew what was at the end of the corridor.

The teleportation of the corridor would only work within the castle. The moment Leylin mentioned an area that did not match what was inside, not only would there be no teleportation, but defensive spell formations would be activated instead.

However, he was unwilling to give up on the Lamia Hair.

‘I would like… to go to a place that will help my bloodline mature!’ A moment later, Leylin made up his mind and constantly repeated this line in his thoughts.

In that instant, the corridor seemed to shrink and the flowery patterns on the walls sped up. In a few seconds, they completed a cycle of growth. A bit of light appeared at the end of the corridor, constantly expanding.

“Let’s go!” Leylin gritted his teeth and calmly headed ahead.

*Swoosh!* The feeling of weightlessness during the teleportation left him feeling dizzy.

Shaking his head vigorously, he took stock of his surroundings.

“Where is this…?”

He was in a large laboratory. He could see plants outside through the glass, as well as many glass vessels and experimental apparatus that were all neatly arranged inside.

“A lab, huh. My luck is pretty good. There’s definitely going to be something here to help mature my bloodline faster!”

Leylin let out a long breath, and immediately recalled the rumours regarding Quicksand. Given that their ranks consisted of Warlocks of various bloodlines, they had a vested interest in the field. It would not be difficult to find something that could help his bloodline mature.

Leylin arrived at a metal counter, and pulled out the first drawer. It was messy, mostly made of thick parchments recording data from experiments. It was all in the Byron language.

Leylin opened the other drawers, and the contents were about the same. There was mostly data from experiments, the counter practically filled by these documents.

“There is so much data, but it’s a pity there’s no information on the receptors and core data. There’s no way to tell the procedure of the experiment at all…”

Leylin found this regretful but quickly saved all the information to the database.

Even if it was mostly unrelated data, it was still very valuable. Who knows, some of these parchments could even hold the data essential to repeating the experiment!

In addition, with all its recent advances and improvement in its abilities, it took little time to record everything.

Everything was organized neatly. It seemed like the Warlocks then had left in an orderly fashion, not leaving much behind.

After recording the information, Leylin turned his attention to the ecological garden outside the giant glass wall.

Large leaves that were like palm-leaf fans covered the sky. Barely any sunlight shone down on the thick roots of the plants.

It looked like a primordial forest.

However, Leylin who had experience from Twilight Zone immediately realised the difference in this sunlight. This was not sunlight from the natural world, but an artificial recreation of heat and light. Though there was a similar effect, it lacked the harmony of nature.

“This place has probably been abandoned for thousands of years. To be able to let this ecological garden achieve a balance like this, it truly is a perfect system achieved with astonishing skill,” Leylin sighed and touched the glass.

[Custom-made reinforced glass. Degree of hardness: 3!]

The A.I. Chip concluded.

A level 3 hardness meant that regular rank 3 Warlocks would be unable to break this glass. Leylin’s eyes brightened at this information.

“Looks like this place was used to hold many powerful creatures.” A giant fireball appeared in Leylin’s hands, the terrifying heat burning even the air around it into nothingness and searing through the void.

“Explosive Fireball!”

Enormous flames smashed against the glass wall, the dazzle of the heat and light incomparably piercing. Even Leylin himself had to close his eyes temporarily.

When he opened his eyes again, there was an indent in a part of the glass, but not much more. It still stood strong.

‘As expected of a material with a hardness of level 3!’ Leylin sighed, as he could immediately tell how much power this reinforced glass could withstand.

Based on the power of his attack, it needed to be used at least ten times before he could completely shatter this glass wall.

‘What for?’ he thought as he stroked his chin. While gathering information, he had also discovered an activating spell which should have been the key to entering the garden. The attack from before was purely to test how strong this laboratory was.

‘Looks like there were at most rank 3 creatures here, so it’s not too dangerous!’ Leylin was now assured. If not, the defence would not be so uncomplicated. Even if there were still spell formations that had yet to be activated, the creatures would still be around rank 3.

He quickly arrived at an instrument that was like a disk. After checking it briefly, he found a groove and placed crystallised magic crystals inside, replacing the previous powder.

After that, Leylin placed both hands atop the disk, rays travelling from his palms and connecting with the disk. “Activate!”

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* The entire glass wall began to shake, great amounts of dust and silt sliding off.

*Rumble!* As it had not been activated for a long time, the mechanism seemed to be aged and produced a loud sound as a glass door opened.

A crack appeared within the glass, expanding in two directions, bringing with it an unusually refreshing breeze.

In that instant, Leylin felt every cell in his body dancing in joy, and his Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline beginning to stir.

“I didn’t notice this before, but it seems like every plant in this ecological garden is an ancient species. Also, they’re quite a few times larger than the species we have now, containing traits of the ancient era…”

Leylin walked out of the laboratory and looked backwards. The laboratory from before was like a giant white egg, set atop a thick stone base. Everything around it looked like a primordial forest.

‘With such obvious traits of the ancient era, and given how lively my bloodline has become, this place is a perfect copy of that period,’ he determined.

Though such an environment may have been the norm at the time. This is very valuable information…’ Leylin revealed an expression of excitement, and immediately commanded, ‘A.I. Chip, record the parameters of the environment!’

[Mission established, beginning scanning. Recording parameters of the atmosphere…]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned, following through on Leylin’s command meticulously.

After giving the order, Leylin walked along a giant plant root, Meteor Sword in hand.

At the end of the root was a berry vine, and atop a leaf the size of a millstone, he found bite marks.

‘An animal eating,’ Leylin looked at the mark on the leaf, ‘It should be omnivorous, these marks are of teeth used to tear flesh!’ The plan was repairing itself rapidly, erasing all traces of the bites.

‘They grow so quickly, which explains how this cycle was constructed here…’ Leylin touched his chin and came to the ground. At the root of the plant was a stinking thick, green goop.

Chapter 430: Activation

The illusion that surfaced was that of an astonishingly beautiful young woman. Her hair was like a sea of emerald green with light curls, flying in the wind like it had a life of its own.

She possessed a pair of mesmerising eyes, coupled with a delicate yet puzzling charm to her face. To Leylin’s surprise, she gave him a baffling sense of familiarity.

Especially after the complete materialisation of the illusion, Leylin’s blood vessels generated a sense of fear, as if he had met a natural enemy. Yet, he felt an amiability within her that tempted him to throw himself into the arms of the woman regardless of everything.

“Lamia?” There were agony and bitterness in Leylin’s tone. From how called out to him just now, he managed to guess some things.

The similarity in temperament and looks between her and the Snake Dowager was especially striking.

The Lamia shared the same bloodline as the Snake Dowager. In fact, it had an even more direct line of descent compared to the Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Thus, on the whole, they could be considered siblings with blood relations.

“My brother! Tell me, why are you here, what are you looking for?” The green haired Lamia asked, her voice strangely charming, compelling him to answer.

[Warning! Warning! Instability detected in host bloodline, possibility of an emotional outburst!]

The A.I. Chip sounded the reminder, snapping Leylin out from the confusion he was in.

This made him unwilling to look at the opposity party, particularly at the Lamia’s eyes.

“Rumor has it that the ancient Lamia has the ability to manipulate any kind of snakes she desires. It seems like this is true indeed…”

It was merely a remnant soul, yet it almost got to Leylin. If the Lamia were to be at the Morning Star Realm, Leylin was afraid he might have to bow down to her.

“Your bloodline, it seems to be extremely pure, and you have a special power enveloping your whole body….” The virtual image of the Lamia bit her finger.

“Who are you, really?” Leylin spoke in a deep tone.

“I was a human once, I had a few names, but I have forgotten them all…..” The virtual image smiled, as if she was narrating a story unrelated to her.

“Are you the soul of the ancient Lamia Warlock?” Leylin made a guess.

According to his intelligence, the ancient Quicksand Organisation once had a Lamia Warlock. And apparently, after her atavism, she became a true Lamia possessing terrifying power that even average Radiant Moon Magi could not match.

“No! She had perished completely. I am just a phantom image formed by the scattered fragments of memories that have evolved together after a very long period of time…” A sense of loneliness could be felt from the green haired woman’s face.

“Even so, for your soul to take such shape, I am sure there is a source of radiation nearby!” Leylin’s eyes lit up and he reached out and grabbed at the fur cushion.

Huge black claws appeared, splitting the fur and metal within and revealing what was underneath the surface.

It was a layer of white fur. Brush that aside and immediately a rich and heavy scent of undulating bloodline spreaded out.

“You can even resist the radiation undulation and the aura of the bloodline!” Leylin kept the white feathers in a flash and thereafter eyed the hollow area intensely.

It was the broken section of a bone, it must have been a part of some bloodline creature.

Although it might have been a long time ago, the horrifying threat and undulations emitting from the bone made Leylin have an impulse to kneel down.

“You are truly the adult form of a rank 5 bloodline creature; even though it is a broken section of a bone, it could still radiate even after your death. Moreover you can induce such a thing!” Leylin looked at the green haired Lamia in amazement.

For Blood Vultures, the remains of a rank 5 bloodline creature was a precious item to that was dearly cherished. No wonder the Blood Vulture had safeguarded it under so many layers, even going so far as to mask its energy with the feather.

“What do you intend to do here, my brother?” she asked again.

Leylin muttered under his breath and finally replied, ”I want to acquire something that will speed up the maturation of my bloodline, for instance Lamia Hair or some such thing.”

“Compared to Lamia Hair, this can help you more!” The Snake Woman smiled and the broken bone was flung out and landed on Leylin’s hand.

“You…. Why are you helping me?”

Feeling the ecstatic joy boiling in his bloodline, Leylin knew the broken Lamia bone in his hands were the real deal. He could already feel the transcendence.

However he did not immediately accept it and instead asked some questions.

“I have been in existence for far too long…. It might be a few hundred years or even thousands. I can never leave the designated finger bone’s radiation area……”

The Lamia shot a glance at Leylin, “Do you know how it feels?”

Leylin fell silent. Such pain, it did indeed have the ability to drive a Magus crazy to the verge of seeking death.

“If you take the finger bone, there will be a shortage of such a radiation environment and I will gradually fade away…..” The young woman’s silhouette became more and more illusionary with a smile of relief on her face.

“Wait. How can I resolve the shackles on the Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock bloodline?

Watching the young woman’s illusionary image gradually fading out until the wall behind her could be seen, Leylin quickly blurted out the question.

“This problem, can only be solved by the Grand Matriarch…..”

Accompanying the fading image, the Snake Woman’s grew softer and softer until she dissipated into thin air.

“Grand Matriarch? Snake Dowager?” Leylin stroked the finger bone he was holding in his hands, his face a sea of infinite obscurity.

“Regardless of that, I better make a move fast!”

With lightning speed, Leylin kept the finger bone well, swept his eyes over the surroundings and launched the Dark Elven Crown.

Thick, black darkness enveloped Leylin completely, and coupled with his magic power he was able to pass through the gate which was guarded by the two Blood Vultures unharmed.

After he reached the foot of the mountain, Leylin looked back at the huge black form of the mountain and its innumerable caves. He looked hesitant.

This was practically a Warlock’s treasure trove, but without a strength at the Morning Star realm, there was no way the entirety of the Blood Vulture could be subdued.

“I have, at most, five more minutes before the King Blood Vulture is back from his patrol. When he realises that the finger bone is gone, I am sure he will definitely launch an investigation into the matter…”

Leylin stroked his chin. He had been hiding up here for so long, the backup plans had to be more than these. But now, the biggest harvest was already in his hand. Whether to continue or not, he had not yet made up his mind.

Since ancient times, it was a common occurrence for an individual to place himself in danger for personal benefits. Leylin did not want to become one of them.

“Forget it! Let’s go!”

With some regret, Leylin turned his head and left the place.

……

“Huh?! You are finally out.”

Not too far away, a temporary underground cave opened up. A female Magus in pursuit ran in with a crystal ball in her hand. On the surface of the crystal ball, a blood-red layer appeared, getting brighter and brighter.

“If you had kept hiding in the nest of the Blood Vultures, I might not have been able to find you. But what about now?”

The female Magus flashed a smile.

She was in pursuit of Leylin all the way and had even used a spell to use a trace of Leylin’s energy to build a tracking item. But after reaching this place, she realised Leylin had hidden in the nest of the Blood Vultures!

The King Blood Vulture there was at the peak of the Crystal Phase! Other than that, there was a big group of rank 3 followers. If she chased in after Leylin and a commotion was created, it would definitely alert the many Blood Vultures to join in for the kill.

Therefore, this female Magus chose to hibernate and wait. To her, Leylin would come for collection of resources, it was just a matter of time. As long as she waited with patience, regardless of success or failure, he would leave and an opportunity would present itself.

“All thanks to you, I was able to discover this treasure place. In return, I shall grant you a quick death…” The female Magus shook her robes and immediately disappeared underground.

[Beep! Warning! Warning! High energy force field undulations detected. Distance 15 kilometers away. Approaching quickly!]

The A.I. Chip gave out this sudden warning, shocking Leylin.

This was the advantage of having the A.I. Chip. Not only did Leylin possess the Magus’ special abilities of consciousness scanning, he also had the A.I. Chip for exploration, probing and throwing necessary warnings.

Moreover, the range of probing by the A.I. Chip was much wider compared to Leylin’s own ability.

“Begin imaging!” Leylin gave the order immediately. Soon after, a red-hued motion picture was sent in front of him.

It was an image of a living creature. There were only heat and radiation readings, without any signs of the gender, however the bright colours were a giveaway. It was a rank 3 Magus, one that had attained the Crystal Phase.

“Ah, the pursuers are finally here!” Leylin had expected this would happen.

*Hoot!* At this moment, from a distance, a high-pitched sound pierced forth, turning Leylin’s face pale white.

“The King Blood Vulture is back! If I turn back now, all that awaits me is death!” As it is, at this point in time, Leylin curled his lips into a smile and commanded his A.I. Chip, “A.I. Chip! Prepare to activate all programs!”

[Command received! Activated!]

The A.I. Chip alerted without any emotion.

*Hoot!* Immediately after the King Blood Vulture had entered its cave in the mountain, a violent cry rang out.

Two Hydro Phase Blood Vultures were pinned to the ground by its claw. Feathers and blood were smeared all over the ground. The King Blood Vulture snarled, creating a whole world of uproar in the Blood Vultures’ mountain.

But that was not all.

*Bang! Bang! Bang!* Following Leylin’s order, in a secret corner of the Blood Vultures’ mountain, hidden spells were activated in series.

One after another, shadow servants manifested themselves at lightning speed, so much so that they appeared right next to the Blood Vultures’ nests. They grasped at many of the bloodline treasures, with some even clasping onto huge Blood Vulture eggs, fleeing the grounds.

Basically, except for the area around the King Blood Vulture’s cave, the rest of the mountain in its entirety was under attack. There were at least fifty such spells placed!

Corresponding with the loud snarl of the King Blood Vulture, multiple shadows of darkness bore through to the center of it all and immediately the whole of the Blood Vultures’ mountain became a huge field of upheaval.

Chapter 431: The Hunt

*Chu!* The King Blood Vulture used its wings and fanned the two Blood Condors in its path away, flying into the sky.

A crimson beam of light struck down, and a shadow servant who could not dodge in time was shattered, scattering multiple bloodline treasures everywhere.

With the commanding high-pitched squawk, the flock of Blood Vultures now had a leader and their formation immediately changed. Many of them flew high into the sky and, like a web, began to circle the shadow servants, occasionally dropping down in attack.

Though this method was effective at killing many shadow servants, the remaining servants’ movements in looting them were much too quick. After paying the price of a large number of casualties, a portion of them still broke out.

*Chu!* The King Blood Vulture roared, bringing with it multiple Blood Vultures as it gave chase.

“Found you!” Leylin met with the person who were chasing after him.

It was a ginger female Magus. Her body was curvy, a golden headband rested on her forehead, and her pair of long and narrow eyes were fixed on Leylin.

“My name is Leylin. May I know yours?” In the face of her gaze that was ready to shoot flames, Leylin smiled slightly and performed a noble’s bow, his movements so precise there was nothing to criticise.

“Tanasha!” This female Magus had not expected Leylin to feel so relaxed. Though her chest was bouncing in her anger, she still had a lot of self-restraint as she announced her name.

“Are you prepared to admit to your sins?” Tanasha glanced at the handsome young man in front of her. Captives could be ransomed in the central continent. In addition, he had not caused too many casualties to her organisation, and was also a human backed by the Ouroboros Clan. Hence, it was not too surprising that he was still calm in this situation.

“Oh, no, you’ve misunderstood,” Leylin’s smile was dazzling, “I just want to ask you this. Do you… like Blood Vultures?”

“What do you mean?” Tanasha’s mind could not process this fast enough. But looking at the numerous crimson figures appearing on the horizon, she suddenly had a bad premonition.

Leylin acted before she could do anything, “Eye of Petrification!”

His eyes turned amber and the pupils became vertical slits, shooting out mysterious, unmeasurable rays of petrification.

Though it was only a rank 1 innate spell, with the addition of his Vapour Phase spiritual force and the strength of his bloodline, its power could not be underestimated.

At the same time, Leylin quickly chanted some incantations, and numerous shadows emerged from all directions, forming a giant cage that trapped her inside temporarily.

Tanasha’s reaction was extremely quick. “Storm!” Almost at the same instant the rays of petrification appeared, her eyes turned silver-white, releasing dazzling light that blocked them.

Meanwhile, a giant storm appeared from behind her, forming a tremendous tornado that stirred up and created chaos in the interior of the cage.

However, Leylin’s sudden attack made her falter. “Lance of Corrosion!”

A dark green lance, tip white, appeared in Leylin’s hand. It shot towards Tanasha, accompanied by a burst of air.

“How confident are you that a mere Vapour Phase Magus dares provoke a Crystal Phase Magus?” Tanasha was expressionless, but her fury was evident.

*Snap!* Tanasha extended her delicate, pale arms and a translucent layer appeared on top of her smooth skin.

Leylin had used all his might when he shot this Lance of Corrosion forth, and yet, she’d caught it just like that.

*Boom!* She viciously crushed the Lance into powder, while Leylin paled as he took several steps back.

However, his smile now was as if he had gotten away with something.

“Hm?” Tanasha’s brows furrowed. Only then did she notice that after the Lance of Corrosion had been destroyed, a white feather had appeared.

*Pu!* The white feather had exploded into powder and lightly stuck to Tanasha’s body.

“This aura? And with a powerful lock-on spell formation…” Tanasha’s brows furrowed and she immediately sneered, “I just need two minutes to-”

However, her expression completely changed.

Leylin, who was opposite her, waved his arms towards her and activated the Dark Elven Crown, and immediately turned invisible.

*Sou! Sou! Sou!*

Numerous black figures appeared. The shadow servants from before quickly pounced towards her, only to be killed by her while heading in her direction.

However, with this opportunity, they threw some bloodline crystals, bones and the like at her legs. There was an especially large egg that had been knocked so hard that it broke, revealing the egg yolk and whites within.

*Chu chu!* Numerous Blood Condors hurried over under the lead of the king, and upon seeing Tanasha, their eyes instantly turned red.

This was especially so for the the King Blood Vulture. It smelt its feather on Tanasha’s body. It was a feather used specifically to protect the Lamia fingerbone and was extremely precious. The smell was extremely unique, and there was no way it could recognise it wrongly!

It now looked like the person who had infiltrated its mountain and looted the area as they wished, was also the thief who had stolen its treasure!

The King Blood Vulture was furious, crimson lightning materialising around it.

“I- I- I!” Tanasha was momentarily stunned. No matter how stupid she might be, she knew what Leylin had planned.

“Wait, O King!” Tanasha was now sending spiritual force waves to the mind of the King Blood Vulture, her final attempt at saving herself.

However, would the enraged King Blood Vulture listen to her explanations? Though it had the intelligence of an adult, it was now in an angered state. Usually, in its territory, it would have what it wanted. Why would it listen to the explanations of a human?

Numerous bolts of crimson lightning struck down, drowning her…

Meanwhile, Leylin had made use of the Dark Elven Crown, and was sneakingly heading back.

*Boom!* Soil upended at an area, revealing numerous bloodline items within. Red gems and white bones were scattered, giving off a dazzling luster.

“There’s even a Blood Vulture egg here! It looks like a pretty good harvest.”

Holding a giant egg in his hands, Leylin looked elated. This was a few times larger than an ostrich egg, and it even had blood-red patterns on the surface, powerful life energy radiating from within. Leylin could even feel a throbbing from the shell.

Blood Vulture chicks could not be tamed, but one still in its egg could.

Not only did it have the ability to find bloodline treasures, it was also very popular for its ability to reach rank 3 after it had matured.

Of course, Leylin had no plans of selling it off. Rather, he wanted to subdue it.

The central continent was vast and boundless. There were many places that even Magi were yet to explore, and the Blood Vulture’s ability to fly was very useful in this area. In the future, he could gain a steady flow of bloodline treasures, which was the best advantage!

“The harvest is quite good!” Leylin quickly kept everything properly.

He had long since ordered the shadow servants to place whatever they had stolen on the road here. Whatever had been flung at Tanasha’s feet was just a small portion. The real treasures had long since been moved away and were all with Leylin.

After checking all his gains, Leylin looked back towards the Blood Vultures’ mountain, sinking into deep thought.

‘The King Blood Vulture has brought all its main forces to annihilate Tanasha. She is a Crystal Phase Magus after all, and it is possible for her to hold them off for some time. Should I go back and rummage through the Blood Vultures’ nests?’

Leylin immediately shook his head, throwing these enticing thoughts out of his mind.

“Forget it. What I now have is more than enough. I shouldn’t take such a risk at the end like this.”

“Besides, my real target is that rank 3 Crystal Phase Magus, not the rest of those bloodline treasures.”

Leylin’s eyes flashed ruthlessly…

“Damn it! Damn it! Damn it! I want to slaughter that wretched Magus and turn his flesh and blood into powder and feed it to a Carnivorous Flower!”

Tanasha was in a tropical rain forest, sprinting hard.

However, she was evidently not in a very good condition. Not only were her clothes in tatters making her seem like a beggar, her entire right arm had disappeared. Her face was pale, with green veins visible on top.

This flock of Blood Vultures was truly relentless. In order to break away from them, Tanasha had to employ a few secret methods that would stimulate the potential in her body in succession. She had even discarded a clone that she had nurtured for a long period of time before she could successfully draw the King Blood Vulture away.

Tanasha was definitely fuming at the mouth, wishing she could eat Leylin alive.

“Tsk tsk, Ms Tanasha, you don’t seem to be in good health. Do you need treatment?” In the quiet rainforest, a voice suddenly sounded, causing Tanasha’s body to stiffen.

She then looked at the young man she would never be able to forget, blocking her path.

“How- how did you get here? I already destroyed all auras and smells that would identify me!” Tanasha gaped, disbelieving.

“You don’t need to know. Right now, you can only answer a question of mine.”

Leylin produced an ink-black cross blade and pointed it at her. “Submit to me, or die.”

He had naturally used the A.I. Chip to scan the surroundings and hunt her down. Though Tanasha had concealed her aura very well, and destroyed all the localizing marks that Leylin had shot out, nothing could be hidden in the face of the A.I. Chip.

Not considering anything else, just the signs of a human passing through on the road would not be able to escape the A.I. Chip’s nanoscopic scanning, no matter how hard Tanasha tried to cover her tracks.

It was only after Leylin confirmed that she was heavily injured that he chased up to her.

Tanasha was at the Crystal Phase, and was multiple levels higher than Leylin. In the past, it would have been a joke if a Vapour Phase Magus had announced his wish to kill a Crystal Phase Magus.

However, a hint of fear had already appeared on Tanasha’s pale face. She had no choice but to admit that Leylin had the strength and ability to kill the current her.

Chapter 432: Subjugation

Rank 3 Magi were categorised into several stages. Leylin, at the Vapour Phase, could compress his spiritual force into a physical, observable fog.

On the other hand, Magi at the Crystal Phase could solidify their spiritual force, even preserving it to sell.

Spiritual force at the Crystal Phase had an unimaginable advantage against Vapour Phase spiritual force.

In other words, even if Leylin, Robin and Kesha had teamed up against Lucian, they wouldn’t be his match.

However, Tanasha’s spiritual force was exhausted long ago, including her Crystal Phase spiritual force crystals.

He wouldn’t be Leylin if he let such a good chance slip out of his hand.

Not only were Crystal Phase Magi powerful, they were considered nobles in the central continent due to their status as the reserve forces of Morning Star Magi.

Under usual circumstances, it was out of the question for Leylin to defeat Magi of this rank. Perhaps only Duke Gilbert, his mentor, would be able to.

But with Tanasha as she was, it would be easy.

“You…” Tanasha’s pale complexion flushed in anger, her fingers trembling, “How dare a lowly Vapour Phase Magus talk to me like that?”

“Looks like I’ll have to help you snap back to reality!” Leylin sighed in disappointment upon seeing her demeanour. His figure transformed into a ray of light and flashed in front of her.

*Thump!* He planted a fist on Tanasha’s cheek.

*Buzz!* A barrier of light was created around Tanasha as a brilliant ruby ring shone. It was, however, too feeble to deter Leylin as he easily broke through.

In the blink of an eye, Tanasha was sent flying, a large red patch on her cheek.

The Meteor Sword has already reached her neck before she could react.

“Now choose… Surrender, or die!” There was a change in Leylin’s tone. Now he demanded with utter disdain, every word pricking with a bone-chilling vibe. He had decided to kill were she to choose it.

He certainly did not wish to leave behind a Crystal Phase opponent.

Tanasha wisely chose to be silent in front of the cold-hearted Leylin.

This feeling of impending death was familiar to her. She felt as if she had returned to times of frailty and weakness, as old memories surfaced and she momentarily became distraught.

“What is with this woman’s mental state?!” Leylin shook his head, Tanasha’s reaction was nothing out of the ordinary since he was aware of the common psychological instability of Magi. There was also her injuries to consider. Moreover, all who entered the Forgotten Land would certainly have a dark past of own.

“I’m only giving you three minutes! Be quick!” Leylin tightened his grip on the sword and brought it closer to Tanasha’s neck.

Other Crystal Phase Magi would probably have a sense of dignity and pride, but things were different in the Forgotten Land. Those human Magi who entered here were mostly those who had reached an impasse, willing to forgo everything for a means of sustenance. It was easy for the mto capitulate.

Leylin’s cold voice caught Tanasha’s attention. The angry flush on her face had already dissipated by then, leaving behind a canvas of ivory.

“I… surrender!” She replied so softly Leylin could barely hear a thing.

As if on cue, Tanasha fell limp to the ground, her backbone losing support the moment she agreed. Her tears were uncontrollable.

The Meteor Sword remained on her neck in spite of everything.

“Make an oath! Also, relinquish your spirit source!” His voice was cold as ice.

“I… Tanasha…” Hesitance crossed Tanasha’s eyes as she fought an internal battle. However, she ended up choosing to surrender.

A sparkling strand of spirit source was released from her forehead and landed on Leylin’s palm.

That was a Magus’ lifeline. Were it not voluntary, it would be completely impossible to offer it to another person. Rules were even stricter in the central continent, to prevent the dominance of one over another. Of course, this didn’t stop people with influence and power from committing it but similarly, it had to be done in secret or they would be boycotted by all Magi.

This was no issue at all for Leylin since he didn’t plan for Tanasha to be seen by others.

“Master…” Tanasha called out in a deep voice and got up to her feet. She resembled a broken puppet, someone that had lost her soul.

“Being forced into the Forgotten Land, you must have your own dark past. But rest assured, I am not going to compel you to do things that are disgraceful to Magi. Instead, I can give you hope. A hope for revenge.”

There was a bewitching tone to Leylin’s offer and Tanasha’s eyes lit up a little as the word ‘revenge’ rang in her ears and a hint of anger rushed through her.

“That’s right! Revenge!” Leylin made eye contact with Tanasha and lowered his voice. “I promise, when I’m strong enough to take revenge for you and not worry about the possible repercussions and retaliation, I will aid you in accomplishing your dream. That is, if you work for me wholeheartedly till then.

“I’m not trying to patronise you. You see, I’ve reached the Vapour Phase at less than a hundred years of age. Moreover, there will be no problems with advancing to the Morning Star realm because of my Kemoyin bloodline!”

Deep down, Leylin was aware that with his method, Tanasha would only be willing to become a puppet to him. To milk her for everything she was worth, Leylin needed to ignite her battle spirit by fuelling her with hope.

And instead of empty promises, he promoted his skills to Tanasha, proving his capability to help her in her revenge.

“One hundred years old! Vapour Phase!” Tanasha gazed at Leylin with a heightened intensity.

A hundred years of age was definitely old for humans. But for Magi, especially those who were at rank 3 and above, it wouldn’t even be considered as puberty.

For Leylin who have both the talent and bloodline of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, his status in the Ouroboros Clan could not be overlooked. All this pointed to one thing: There was a substantial chance for him to become a Morning Star Magus.

Even someone with the capability to escape a rank 3 Crystal Phase Magus would crumble like paper in the face of a rank 4 Morning Star Magus.

“I am at your beck and call, Master! I, Tanasha, will be your most loyal servant as long as my revenge is assured!” Tanasha knelt on a knee and gritted her teeth, a little more willing this time.

Although it was a mere promise without a covenant, what more could a captive like her bargain for?

”Haha…” Leylin cackled.

The addition of Tanasha was definitely a reinforcement to Leylin, given her strength which was more than his.

Plus, she would be hidden from the public since this assistance would be carried out in secret.

That was Leylin’s plan all along, to gather as much of an underground force as he could in case anything unexpected occurred.

“Take these potions quickly and recover!” Leylin showed generosity to the newly-recruited Tanasha and presented her with three tubes of differing colours.

“High-grade healing potion! High-grade spiritual force recovery potion! Sacred regeneration potion!” Tanasha’s face was painted with surprise as she recognised these three potions. Apart from their heavenly price, these potions were heavily utilised by large-scale organisations as their war reserves and could not even be bought with money.

This was especially true for the sacred regeneration potion which could stimulate the regrowth of limbs that were as good as the original with absolutely no side-effects. It was unfamiliar, even to a rank 3 Magus like Tanasha.

“Thank you, Master!” Tanasha bowed and sighed in relief,

“Don’t mention it, it’s just something I made!” Leylin added to his credibility.

Sure enough, Tanasha’s eyes widened at his sentence. She was beyond impressed, advancing to Vapour Phase before the age of a hundred was amazing enough, she did not at all expect that Leylin would be a Potions Grandmaster as well. This was genius at its best and would be considered rare even in the central continent. As long as there were no mishaps along the way, success was pretty much guaranteed.

Hints of hope filled Tanasha’s eyes as she watched Leylin…

Simultaneously, in a clandestine area, Noah was staring at his dish, face drained of colour.

There was an indistinct bloody liver-like substance lying on the white china, emitting a chalky fog.

“Eugh…” Noah slapped a palm over his mouth, resisting the urge to gag.

In his vision, the Barbarian Bear Shaman’s stomach was cut open, and a large amount of yellow grease flowed out from it. There were also visible traces of the skeleton inside.

“Uncle, I can’t do this any longer!” Noah cried through the spaces of his fingers.

Robin didn’t look good either, his body was missing huge chunks of flesh and he was covered in terrifying wounds.

“It was rumoured that this place is dominated by the sin of gluttony, we will be attacked if we stop partaking! We have to keep going, success will be ours if they fail first.”

Robin persisted to his best abilities whereas Noah’s hand trembled as he picked his cutlery. Ultimately, he put them down again. All the food here was created from the sin of gluttony and due to it, all spells would be rendered useless; only their own tenacity could help them withstand the ‘feast’. *Ring ring ring!* The melodious bell rang from afar, but to the trio it seemed like it came from the depths of hell…

Chapter 433: Rescue

Noah made several attempts to reach for the knife and fork but he gave up halfway, letting out an expression of intense suffering.

He collapsed on the dining table with a bang, his teeth clenched tightly.

Similarly, Robin had a pained look on his face as he endured the nausea and swallowed a bloody piece of meat.

Within 30 seconds, the ringing of the bells came to an end, lasting only for a short duration.

*Ka-cha!* Out of nowhere, it seemed as if a huge invisible mouth took a bite. At this moment, Noah let out a deep cry.

A large portion of his flesh was missing on the right side of his head, his ear having completely disappeared. From the side, his ghastly white teeth could be seen. It was a horrifying sight.

Suddenly, a streak of light flashed across. A bloodied ear, still twitching unconsciously, appeared before a dark figure.

“Ew…….”

After a few rounds, Robin and Noah had paled, now resembling corpses. However, the Barbarian Bear Shaman on the other end had finally reached its limit and collapsed onto the table.

*Buzz!* As if a signal was given, the Barbarian Bear Shaman was immediately moved to the 13th chair, which was unoccupied. When this was done, numerous dark figures pounced on it.

“Ah……” The Barbarian Bear Shaman shrieked continuously. Soon after, fur and skin started disappearing piece by piece, followed by flesh, veins and even bones.

*Hoo…* The Crystal Phase Barbarian Bear Shaman no longer had any power to fight back and vanished within the dark figures.

Even up till the very last moment of its life, the Barbarian Bear Shaman was still very much conscious, as could be seen from the expression in its eyes.

After they engulfed the Barbarian Bear Shaman, the many dark figures dispersed and vanished into thin air one after another. At the same time, Noah could feel the strong imprisonment fading..

“It’s finally over…” he sighed, plopping to the ground shortly after. He began to vomit, almost to the point of spewing out bile.

“I swear. I won’t be able to eat anything for at least three months…” Despite his bitter expression, Noah’s bodily wounds were in fact healing quickly.

However, Robin’s fervent eyes were fixed on a particular part of the void. From Noah’s perspective, a presence had already arrived somewhere.

“What reward do you wish for?” An inexplicable voice rang within the hearts of the two men.

“I want…” Robin answered. His voice was deep, but even more so, it carried his unrestrainable excitement…….

At this point in time, Leylin walked out of the ecological garden with Tanasha and they returned to the illusory corridor.

“Master… According to our research, we will be able to get out after passing 3 more spatial points.” Tanasha’s condition seemed to have improved greatly, and even her missing arm was able to grow out again with the help of the potions.

“Yes,” Leylin nodded.

“After we get out, stay in the Forgotten Land for the time being. Wait for an opportunity to sneak out and join me! Do you have any restrictions in your organisation?”

“No! I am one of the leaders in the Alliance of the Exiled, I didn’t agree to any sort of soul-binding contract!” Tanasha responded quickly. It wasn’t surprising given her Crystal Phase strength.

“That’s good…” Leylin nodded. He was about to say something else but all of a sudden, his expression changed and he gave Tanasha a look.

Tanasha acknowledged with a nod before disappearing into a wave of water.

Based on the readings on the A.I. Chip, Magus energy waves were detected ahead. Since Tanasha was a backup plan arranged by Leylin, she could not show herself easily in front of outsiders.

Leylin smiled at Tanasha, who was now concealed behind the water, and walked past a corner.

Then, he saw a warlock dressed in a black robe, slumped on the ground. A puddle of black blood was growing beside him. Leylin knew this warlock well – he was one of Kesha’s men, named Arcus.

“Wake up, Arcus!” Leylin flipped Arcus over and immediately noticed the criss-crossed wounds on his chest as dark blood gushed out continuously.

“Curse power!” Leylin’s expression hardened as he felt an enormous power from the long, narrow cuts.

As a Magus, Leylin was knowledgeable in curses, especially those in the Book of Giant Serpent, left behind by Great Magus Serholm. They inspired him greatly and even led him to develop many new ones of his own. This knowledge helped him to a great extent when he was at the south coast.

However, the deeper his knowledge, the more he understood about the strangeness and difficulty in coping with such power.

In particular, the curses from ancient times were those that Leylin was unwilling to make contact with even now.

It seemed like Quicksand Castle also contained a terrifying curse power, and this power had already found its way to Kesha and her group.

To the unconscious Arcus, whose face was faintly branded with a spell made of dark fumes, Leylin looked at him and said, “Today is your lucky day!” He then smiled and pulled out a tube filled with a green solution from his leather pouch.

Leylin applied the thick, green fluid onto Arcus’ wounds drop by drop.

*Sizzle!* The green fluid immediately went through a strange transformation as it condensed into many tiny green worms, which remained on Arcus’ skin. It was a rather disgusting sight.

After that, the numerous green worms aimed at the dark fumes and pounced on them. They engulfed the dark curse power as if they were having a meal.

As time went by, the dark fumes on Arcus’ face slowly faded away and he opened his eyes.

“M…Master Leylin! Thank you for saving me!” Arcus had realised the situation he was in. He struggled to bow but was stopped by Leylin.

“Did something happen to sister Kesha and the others?” Leylin’s voice was calm and full of wisdom.

“Yes, yes! After we entered Quicksand Castle, we were attacked!” Arcus answered with his pale, dry lips, sounding a little frightened.

“It’s a terrifying monster in human form! Not only are spells and physical attacks ineffective, the wounds inflicted by its scissors cannot heal! It also possesses a frightening ability to enter the void and heal itself!”

“Sir! Please save my master!” Arcus pleaded sincerely.

“Don’t worry! We are an organisation of bloodline brothers and Kesha is also my sister. I will not leave her in the lurch!”

“Rather than that, you……”

“I’m fine! I can leave by myself!” Arcus knew for sure that his presence was a burden thus he made a sensible decision.

“Alright! We are already near the exit, all you have to do is avoid the Magi outside, then leave this pocket dimension!”

Leylin nodded and watched Arcus as he limped out of the place.

“Master, are you going to save them?” A wave swept past the empty space and Tanasha, who had been concealed all these time, appeared again.

“Yes!” Leylin nodded.

Kesha had been good to him and they were relatively close. He had to save her.

Of course, more importantly, through his analysis of Arcus, Leylin had already prepared himself for said curse . At the very least, he could ensure his own safety.

If it was like that, there was no reason to refuse to rescue them while he was here.

“You don’t have to involve yourself with this matter anymore, you may leave first!” Leylin ordered Tanasha.

After that, he immediately handed a large black box to her.

“You have to guard the contents of this box carefully. Do not open it, return it to me when we meet again later!”

“Yes, Master!” Tanasha bowed. After receiving the box from Leylin, a bright light flashed and the item disappeared.

Although rare, spatial artifacts could be found even on the south coast and Twilight Zone, leave alone the central continent.

Tanasha had long since entered the Crystal Phase. A storage artifact was no big deal.

As he watched Tanasha’s silhouette moving away, Leylin turned in the opposite direction and disappeared into the corridor.

……

“Huff……”

Kesha hid behind a large shelf, and her tall chest moved up and down unsteadily as she breathed.

“How is it? Has the trap succeeded?”

She asked a Green-skinned Barbarian beside her. Both Kesha and the Green-skinned Barbarian had long, narrow wounds on their bodies. A pool of dark gas circled above those wounds.

These two Magi were almost entirely drained of their energies and they were at their worst condition.

“The Fogbound Labyrinth can only trap it for 3 minutes!” The Green-skinned Barbarian said bitterly.

“Damn it! That amount of time isn’t even enough for us to recover, not to mention getting past the illusory corridor!” Kesha looked despair.

Being pursued by the man in black, especially after sustaining such injuries, the illusory corridor had refused to transport a cursed person like her several times. They were practically trapped in there while still alive.

By now, both Magi were already at the their limits. They had no more strength to fight back.

“I’d never expected that I would die here, and with a green-skinned dwarf beside me!” Kesha let out a faint sigh.

“What did you say, woman?” Angered after being called a dwarf, the Green-skinned Barbarian jumped up and pointed his staff at Kesha’s nose. “If you guys hadn’t intruded and killed many of our clan members, we wouldn’t have chased after you and we wouldn’t have run into that thing!”

“You…” Kesha wanted to refute further but her expression suddenly changed. She and the Green-skinned Barbarian dodged in opposite directions.

Ka-cha! A brilliant, silver-white light streaked across and the large shelf was split into two. It exposed the silhouette of a man in a black trenchcoat who held a pair of scissors emitting a sharp radiance.

“Oh no! It broke through earlier than expected!” The Green-skinned Barbarian turned pale, looking even greener than usual, and it began to shiver.

“Fuck! I knew it, you green-skinned dwarves can’t be trusted!” Out of her despair, Kesha burst out swearing.

The man in black made an ambiguous howl. The sounds of the scissors echoed as his footsteps slowly drew near.

With her sea of consciousness now dried up, a bitter smile emerged on Kesha’s face. However, the man in black was evidently not one to show mercy even towards a female as he raised his hand and pierced at Kesha’s eyes with the scissors.

“Explosive Fireball!” A massive explosion sounded.

Numerous dark figures gathered to form a cage and bound the man in black.

Chapter 434: Escape

Kesha felt giddy, her head was spinning, but she soon fell into a strong embrace.

“Ley…Leylin!” She was taken aback and called out his name.

“Sister, it looks like you’re in a difficult situation!“ Leylin rubbed his nose and gently laid Kesha down. He then tossed a potion at her.

“This is a purifying potion, it can eliminate the curse energy from your body! Use it as soon as possible!”

“Thank you!” Kesha’s face glowed with a lovely smile. Having just escaped from death, she was especially touched.

“Wait up! That… Can you also give me one…?” The huge Green-skinned Barbarian Magus rolled over like a ball, and he was eager to please.

“Huh?” Leylin looked at Kesha.

“Give it to him! After all, we fought alongside each other!” Kesha nodded her head.

At this moment, countless black shadows exploded forth with a bang. Trenchcoat stood in the center, completely unharmed. He made eye contact with Leylin and started roaring.

“This kind of feeling, it isn’t a common hybrid curse. It’s a gene curse!” Leylin’s face grew absolutely serious.

The so-called gene curse was a high-grade curse. It had the ability to materialise itself which was extremely difficult to cure.

Leylin himself had mastered a few curses. However, even he was not too sure about these gene curses.

“I’ll take care of him. You two, use the potions and leave as quickly as possible!” he said in a deep voice.

As with any curse, there were limitations on the scope of the effect. As for Trenchcoat’s gene curse, it most likely prevented him from leaving the confines of Quicksand Castle. In fact, he might not even make it through the illusory corridor in the outer layer.

Kesha and the Green-skinned Barbarian nodded their heads in agreement and opened the test tubes.

“Right, for such a high-grade curse to make an appearance is fortunate. I have long wanted to study them!” Leylin’s eyes lit up like a spark of fire. He threw out a large number of potions.

*Boom* A flash of jade-green flames ignited and blazed fiercely.

“dkjsklgmnsklm……”

Trenchcoat seemed to have some apprehensions with regards to these flames and muttered some senseless words.

“A.I. Chip! “Leylin ordered, “Compare with every language in the database!“ However, the A.I.Chip had not recorded Trenchcoat’s words and so was unable to find an answer.

“Let’s go!” Kesha and the Green-skinned Barbarian yelled. Both had the black cursed energies from their body expelled successfully by the purifying potions.

As he watched Leylin and his two companions leaving, Trenchcoat standing opposite bellowed loudly and charged at them.

*Crackle!* A copious amount of jade green flames were blazing on his body ferociously. Big patches of black clothing were flaking off onto the ground, revealing the badly scarred skin beneath.

A long hideous wound extended all the way down from his right shoulder blade. It looked like a huge black centipede, a sinister and horrifying sight.

What made Leylin frown was the fact that the profound and brutal power of the curse seemed more pronounced and vigorous on Trenchcoat’s body.

“Run, now!” Leylin waved the Meteor Sword in his hand, bringing forth horrifying poisons and the sharp radiant sword shadows, causing the surrounding structures to collapse one by one.

“Use this!” The Green-skinned Barbarian held out a glittering crystal ball that was radiating beautiful, brilliant rays.

“This is an escape crystal ball. It consists of at least 5 escape charms, enough to get us out of here!” The Green-skinned Barbarian Magus met Leylin’s eyes and explained it to him, seemingly trying to win his favour.

“Good job!” The blue light in his eyes sparkled and the A.I. Chip affirmed the authenticity of the crystal ball and its favourable functions.

He immediately stimulated the crystal ball and the three of them vanished in a blinding flash.

A black shadow whizzed past and Trenchcoat’s pair of scissors slashed across empty space as it produced senseless, incoherent roars.

Inside the illusory corridor, the surrounding walls were filled with images of many plants and flowers. Many of the plants were in a continuous loop of life — from germination, to growth, then blossoming and finally withering.

*Bang! Bang! Bang!* Loud thuds of heavy objects falling were heard. Leylin and the rest were in the middle of the corridor.

“Alright! I can no longer feel the power of the curse at this location. You are all safe!” He shut his eyes and exclaimed.

Hearing his words, Kesha and the Green-skinned Barbarian broke into smiles of relief and joy.

“So, it is now time to discuss how we should ‘handle’ this!” Leylin pointed his finger at the Green-skinned Barbarian, revealing a sinister and calculative grin.

“Oh! No! You can’t do this to me. I saved your companion’s life! And we even fought alongside in battle!” The Green-skinned Barbarian raised both his arms, pleading innocently.

It didn’t adopt any form of resistance as its spiritual force had been drained a few days ago when it was in pursuit. It even needed Leylin to stimulate the escape crystal ball as it wasn’t able to do it on its own.

“But the fact is, you came here to capture us, no?” Leylin saw through his clumsy trickery. Thus, he held up the cross blade and aimed for the Green-skinned Barbarian’s brains.

“Seeing how things have turned out, you have paid the price accordingly. I will spare your life this time!” At that moment, Leylin revealed his true intentions.

Having heard what he said, Kesha, who was initially displeased, suddenly snapped out of her emotional state.

“But…. I do not possess any other good stuff!” The Green-skinned Barbarian Magus pleaded pitifully, but secretly slipped an odd bracelet out of his right hand.

Leylin refused to believe that. Being a Crystal Phase Magus, how could it not have a few aces up its sleeve?

Looking at the current situation, although both parties were seriously injured, they could have mustered up their remaining strength for another fight. Yet, Leylin only wanted compensation and did not want to test the opposite party’s threshold which would have inevitably caused them both to suffer.

“Hand over the compensation! Or do you want to start a fight here?” Leylin’s tone was harsh and intense.

“Sister Kesha! When the compensation is presented, I’ll share 50 percent with you!” Once these words were spoken, Kesha immediately inched closer to Leylin’s side, showing her support.

For this exploration, Kesha had ended up losing her life savings and there was no way she could ever step foot into Quicksand Castle again. She had also lost three capable assistants, who were all feared dead, so now she thirsted for compensation for her losses.

Seeing how Kesha reacted, the Green-skinned Barbarian let out a bitter smile, “All of you human Magi are shrewd and greedy, worse than the devil!”

It resigned itself to its fate, crouched down, and handed a black pouch to Leylin.

“Go ahead and take a look! My treasures are all in there!”

Leylin reached out to received the pouch that seemed to be made from animal fur. Upon further probing, many useful items of brilliant lights and vibrant colours could be seen.

Crystal Phase Magi in the Forgotten Land were not as wealthy as Crystal Phase Magi elsewhere, but it was enough to please the two Vapour Phase Magi.

There were so many precious materials inside that Kesha was dazzled by its extraordinary splendor as she let out a thrilling cry.

Leylin chose some of the most precious ones, including a few copies of notes and thereafter handed the pouch to Kesha.

Kesha showered her delicate charm on Leylin in appreciation, then started choosing gems from the pouch without restraint. When she finally passed the pouch to the Green-skinned Barbarian, it was obvious the pouch was shrivelled and light, with lots of missing items. The Green-skinned Barbarian was heartbroken.

“Alright! Since the ransom has been paid, we shall take our leave!”

Leylin bowed slightly, his lips curled in a slight smile as he walked quickly along the corridor with Kesha. They disappeared at the end, leaving the Green-skinned Barbarian speechless and bitter.

A few days later, at the desert surrounding the Quicksand Castle, in a dim and gloomy underground area.

A wave of bright red brilliant rays flashed past, and the silhouettes of the uncle-nephew pair — Robin and Noah — appeared out of thin air.

“You are both finally here, Leylin and I have been waiting for a long time!”

Kesha stood up, a tone of dissatisfaction in her voice. Soon after, she gazed attentively at Robin: “You…… what happened?”

Using her aura detection abilities, it seemed that Robin had changed greatly, yet she couldn’t tell exactly what changed.

“Huh?” Leylin scrutinized Robin’s face intently.

There was no change in his outer appearance, with an unusually bewitching handsome outlook, but in the space between his eyebrows, there was an additional black symbol imprinted. Multiple blood vessel lookalikes covered his entire forehead.

What amazed Leylin more was that the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline on Robin’s body seemed to be strengthening continuously, with the tendency to purify gradually.

If it weren’t for the extremely pure and concise bloodline in Leylin’s own body, together with the probing of the A.I. Chip, he wouldn’t have noticed such changes.

“It’s nothing. On the contrary, I have never felt better!“ Robin chuckled, rational as ever as he whipped out a huge foreleg and started gnawing on it.

There were scales covering the whole animal foreleg and purple-black blood was still dripping from the severed site. It was clearly a high-energy creature from the vicinity.

Robin wolfed down his food with gusto and finished it up with just a few mouthfuls, meat and bones.

He felt like he could be wrong, but after eating the meat, Robin’s bloodline seemed to have strengthened slightly again.

“Eww…” Noah’s face turned ash-white after witnessing Robin feasting on his food. He turned away, not daring to take another look.

“And what happened to you?” Leylin had a premonition. He was sure Robin had acquired some rare resources from Quicksand Castle.

Of course, he had his own fortuitous encounter and the benefits were not small. Luck wouldn’t shine on only one person, and Leylin understood this theory.

“No…Nothing, it was just a traumatic experience. I might fast for a period, I do not even want to see anybody eating anything.…”

Noah waved his hand weakly. The horrible memories from the previous dinner left a deep horrifying impression on him.

“Noah has experienced too little, let him be! We need to leave the Quicksand pocket dimension immediately! Any objections?”

Robin was evidently clear-headed and wise, not mentioning anything about his experiences in the castle. Leylin and Kesha, as well, were too tactful to ask.

Chapter 435: Demon Hunter

“No matter the profits or losses, it is time to leave.”

Leylin nodded, approving of Robin’s suggestion.

He had gained quite a lot this time, and had long since had the inclination to leave. More importantly, his pursuer, Tanasha, had surrendered into his service. The Green-skinned Barbarian Magus was also heavily injured, and only after being extorted precious materials from was he released. As for the road that Robin had taken, it was evident that it had been disastrous.

These were Crystal Phase Magi! The three powers outside would probably be stamping their feet in anxiety.

By the time they reacted to the situation, Leylin and the others would probably be met with the joint attack from the three powers.

On Leylin’s end, the Black Horrall Snake Warlocks that Robin and Roya had brought were all dead, and those following Kesha were probably in a similar situation. Arcus, who Leylin had rescued, had not met with them here. This would only have happened if he had other plans, or he had met with some unexpected situation, causing his strength to be greatly diminished.

If they did not choose to escape now, were they going to wait to be killed?

“Alright, I agree as well.” Kesha sounded helpless. Out of everyone here, she had gained the least, and it was not even enough to make up for the loss of the three Warlocks from her family. When she returned, this would be a huge blow to them.

Anxiety was apparent in Kesha’s eyes.

“As for the way out, it’s definitely impossible to go through the entrance of the pocket dimension. We should use our original plan and look for the weaker areas of the pocket dimension, and use escape runes to tear through the space and exit!” Robin exclaimed.

The entrance of the secret realm had probably been placed under heavy military guard long ago by the three organisations. Leylin and Kesha would not suggest leaving that way, and they all nodded in agreement.

……

Under the scorching rays of the sun, the moisture in the ground evaporated, cracks appearing within.

Somewhere, many cracks converged and caused a terrifying explosion. A hole opened up in the void, and a few pitiful figures dashed out of a tunnel.

“Based on these energy particles, it looks like we’ve successfully escaped and reached the Forgotten Land!” Leylin commented after sensing the energy particles that were so sparse that they could be overlooked around him as well as the desolate surroundings.

“That’s right! This must be the Tuck Barren Lands close to the Forgotten Land, which is very close to the city of sins, Nefas!”

Robin checked the surroundings, and he looked elated, “Leylin, I didn’t expect your abilities at calculating the areas where space is weak to be so impressive!”

“Yes! Not only did you use the shortest time possible and find the place where space was weak, you also evaded space storms and chose a place that is closest to Nefas City!”

It was no simple task to find the weakest spatial node in a pocket dimension. For Magi, this would require a very precise and meticulous probing ability, and the requirements when it came to calculation were even more terrifying.

“Hehe… What are you saying, that’s only a coincidence!” Leylin rubbed his nose.

All these may seem difficult to a regular Magus, but for the A.I. Chip, it was just a walk in the park. He had even especially chosen a spatial node closest to Nefas City, all so he could leave that place as soon as possible.

He had reaped marvelous gains this time, and he had a bad feeling about this. It was this feeling that prompted him to leave without hesitation, even so going so far as to expose some of his abilities.

“It’s best that we leave as soon as possible. Something feels off.” Leylin furrowed his brows. The resources in the Quicksand pocket dimension were far too plentiful, and just the highly valued pocket dimension, Quicksand Castle, was enough to arouse the interest and greed of Morning Star Magi. A Morning Star Magus was not something any of them could handle.

“I have a bad feeling about this too.” Robin looked grim as he agreed as well.

Hearing this, Noah and Kesha could feel the seriousness of the situation. The premonitions or feelings that Magi had, especially that of high-ranked Magi like Leylin and Robin, were usually accurate. It did nothing to reassure them, causing them to tremble in fear.

“Have the organisations in the Forgotten Land contacted the external world? Or is there any supporter of theirs?” Leylin asked Robin as the group of Magi hurried along lightning-quick.

“Contact? They’re a bunch of vicious criminals, or those who can no longer stay in the central continent. How could there be any communication between them?” Robin scoffed at the idea.

“They can’t even leave the Forgotten Land, and can at most conceal their identities in Nefas City.”

At this point, his expression changed and he immediately halted his footsteps. “You mean…”

Leylin’s expression was grim as he nodded.

“What’s going on?” Noah was baffled, while Kesha seemed to have some thoughts on this, “The organisations within the Forgotten Land and Nefas City have contact with each other? Or…”

She did not dare speak further, but the heavy atmosphere lingered in their hearts.

“But what can we do if we don’t go to Nefas City? The airship station there is the most convenient way to communicate with the external world.” Kesha bit her lips.

“Let’s take the long route.” Leylin let out a long breath.

“This will take more effort. I’ve seen the map, and we’ll pass through a few dangerous areas with rank 3 Magi. However, as long as we’re careful, there’s a large possibility of us passing through, though it might take a bit more time…”

Robin nodded, agreeing with Leylin. Though it was very troublesome to divert their route all based on a conjecture, Kesha and Noah exchanged a few glances and did not object.

The Magus World was filled with danger, and any carelessness could lead to the misfortune of death.

Those who could become high-ranked Magi were very confident in their premonitions, and would prefer to avoid any trouble even if it would cause them to expend more effort.

The moment this group was about to turn around, there was an unexpected situation.

*Ka-cha!* A huge hole opened up in the sky, and countless black streaks of lightning appeared with a thunderous sound..

An incredibly mighty pressure suddenly descended, causing Leylin and the others to stand in a daze.

Suddenly, Leylin felt this whole region being isolated from the surroundings, and the air suddenly becoming heavier, to the point that he could not even move a finger.

“This is… the domain of a Morning Star Magus! I’ve felt it before at my mentor’s. I can’t be wrong!”

Robin turned back, face so pale it was like a corpse’s.

“Found you!” A hoarse voice was transmitted from the black hole in the sky, cold, unfeeling and condescending. It was as if Leylin and his group were a bunch of insignificant little ants.

Numerous black streaks of lightning twined around each other to form a black, giant palm, grabbing at Leylin and the rest.

“Ah-!” Leylin wanted to retaliate, only to find that not only was it difficult to use the spiritual force in his body, even the sparse elemental particles in the external world had disappeared, as if they had become insulators of elemental particles.

[Host body affected by unknown force field. Spiritual force suppressed by 80%. Stats in all areas decreasing.]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded, being distorted as if it was being interfered with.

In terms of Leylin’s own stats, there was a large decrease in all of his abilities, and he had been suppressed to about as strong as a rank 1 Magus.

“The suppression from a Morning Star domain, and its influence, has turned us into elemental insulators!”

A wry smile appeared at the corner of Leylin’s lips, “The terror of Morning Star Magi is something I can only hope to achieve!”

Honestly speaking, he was still in a good condition. Kesha and Noah had already collapsed, leaving Robin and him somewhat able to stay standing. However, in front of the giant black-lightning palm, they were helpless.

“Hmph! Cyril, it’s not up to you to give my students a lesson!” Just as even Leylin gave up all hope, a voice suddenly rang from beside him, a familiar sound immediately perking him up.

“Mentor Gilbert!” Robin and Kesha exclaimed, delighted.

Following that, Gilbert appeared by Robin in loose white robes, his two eyes turning into dangerous vertical pupils.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* Ash gray stone skin extended on the black lightning hand, and it eventually collapsed in mid-air, turning into a pile of powder as it sprayed downwards.

*Po!* Like a soap bubble that had been pierced through, Leylin felt his body become lighter, the region he was in returning to the world. That feeling of being shrouded in a tight membrane disappeared.

The numbers on the A.I. Chip were returning to normal, as was his contact with the elemental particles.

[Beep! Detected reactions from two unknown force fields, resulting in a neutralizing effect.]

The A.I. Chip prompted, and a look of comprehension flashed in Leylin’s eyes. ‘This is mentor’s Morning Star domain, cancelling out the other party’s force field!’

He had also gained a deeper understanding of how formidable Morning Star Magi were.

Without reaching the Morning Star realm, just a Morning Star domain was a torture to many low-ranked Magi. In the face of Morning Star Magi, the concept of strength in numbers was just a joke.

“Giant Serpent Duke Gilbert!” A figure appeared in the sky suddenly, and though he was just standing there, Leylin felt that he was like a high mountain.

“Demon Hunter Cyril!”

Leylin lowered his head, taking a few secret peeks at the sky.

Cyril’s face was gaunt, and his lips were very thin. He had a pair of silver eyes that could inspire fear and the Magus robes he wore, with black threads that formed demonic images and the many chains, axes and torture instruments along with, made him look frightening.

“Wait here. I’ll go have a good talk with him.” Gilbert placed his arms at his back. Wrapped in dense crimson rays, he floated above and, with Cyril, transformed into two shooting stars that disappeared into the horizon.

“Hah…” Robin let out a long breath and dropped to the ground. He no longer cared about his image.

The situation just now could be said to be extremely dangerous. If Gilbert had not reached in time, they would probably be in a terrible state.

Chapter 436: Private Airship

“What exactly is going on?” Noah shook his head, still feeling slightly giddy.

“Demon Hunter Cyril tried to hinder us, but Mentor showed up in time to save us, as simple as that!” Kesha laughed bitterly.

The great name of Demon Hunter Cyril struck his ears like a peal of thunder. Rumour had it that this infamous, ferocious being would make even the most cunning devil burst out in tears, regretting that they were ever born into this world.

Simply thinking about falling into the hands of such a person had her breaking out in cold sweat.

“I should’ve thought of it earlier. Nefas, the city of sins, and the Forgotten Land are in close proximity and there are frequent interactions between their people. It is impossible that the forces in the Forgotten Land are not in contact with the Demon Hunter.” Robin’s face was full of remorse.

In actual fact, what he meant was that those forces were the other party’s lackeys. When they saw that they could not handle their group, they immediately informed their master.

However, there was no conclusive evidence. In addition to that, the Demon Hunter was also a Morning Star Magus, which was why Robin spoke obscurely.

“If Mentor Gilbert hadn’t arrived in time, we would’ve been in grave danger. Oh yes, why did Mentor come here?” Robin asked with a doubtful expression.

“It was me!” Leylin stood out and gave a bitter laugh.

“Before I left, I’d already had a bad premonition. Thus, I gave Parker a letter. If I failed to return within the time limit, he would hand it over to Lucian immediately, who would then pass it on to Mentor… Thank goodness! Brother Lucian is indeed trustworthy. Mentor also didn’t get caught up in a high-level experiment……”

His words were only partly true. As a matter of fact, it was the Coin of Destiny which allowed Leylin to predict the interference of a force at the Morning Star realm. However, he could not bear to give up on the Lamia Hair, hence he adopted such a compromising measure.

From the looks of it, it wasn’t a bad result.

“Sorry! I acted on my own!” Leylin admitted and apologised immediately.

“No! It’s nothing! We still have to thank you for your vigilance!” Robin waved.

“That’s right! Who would’ve known that the Demon Hunter was actually so treacherous? He even tried to snatch away small fries like us!” Kesha spoke with a face full of indignation.

“Silence!” Leylin and Robin shouted simultaneously to stop her.

“Towards Morning Star Magi, even if we are enemies, respect must be given no matter what! This is to respect the truth!” Kesha flushed red from embarrassment and lowered her head.

*Rumble!* At this time, a large wave was transmitted from afar. Leylin looked towards that direction in concern.

“No need to worry! The Demon Hunter may be famed for his strength, but you have to believe in our Mentor. He is also very powerful!” Robin noticed the worries on Leylin’s mind and gave him a comforting smile.

“Let’s hope things will be as such!” Leylin replied a little forcefully.

Getting Duke Gilbert out was already his last resort. Apart from this mentor, he could no longer think of any other ways to make the Demon Hunter give up.

Should their mentor be defeated, the students themselves would not have a good ending as well.

“Strength! It still comes down to strength!” Leylin could not help but clench his fists together as his yearning for the Morning Star realm grew.

*Whoosh!* A scarlet ray of light streaked across the horizon and Gilbert’s silhouette emerged before Leylin and the others.

“Mentor!” Robin and Leylin rushed to bow.

“You rascals, look what trouble you’ve gotten yourselves into, you even provoked Cyril!” Gilbert swept his eyes over before a smile surfaced on his bald, bare face. It seems, that in the battle between him and the Demon Hunter, he was not on the losing end.

After realising that, Leylin heaved a sigh of relief in his heart. At least the worst case scenario no longer had a chance of occurring.

“Alright! You must be exhausted after the expedition, just take a trip back on my airship!”

Smiling, Gilbert waved his hand and a small airship appeared on the spot.

Although it was smaller in size than the public airships, it was evidently more luxurious and ornate. The spell formations drafted on it were also more intricate and powerful.

“This is…” Leylin’s mouth opened wide.

Despite its small size, it was still a proper airship! With enough space to fit an airship of this size, surely Duke Gilbert’s space artifacts must have been at the level of magic equipment at least!

But Robin thought Leylin had lost his senses because of the airship. “This is the ‘Black Scale,’ Mentor’s ship. When he advanced to become a Morning Star Magus, the Fayle clan sent it as a gift. It can use any network of channels and will be treated as an honoured guest at maintenance and rest stops!” he explained with a smile.

“What a lavish clan!” Leylin gasped. The family which had control over the central continent’s airship channels, had a lot of inside information as expected.

“Will they send a gift for every Morning Star Magus after they are promoted?” Leylin suddenly remembered and asked.

“That’s right! Basically, after a Magus is promoted, the Fayle clan will definitely send a private airship as a gift!” Robin nodded.

“What a great scale of spending!” Of course, Leylin knew very well that it was probably not the intention of the Fayles. Instead, the Monarch of the Skies was using the chance to get on the good sides of the Morning Star Magi.

The Black Scale’s interior was very luxurious. Comprising a master room, guest room, kitchen, meditation room and a customized living room, the airship was big enough to accommodate dozens of people without seeming crowded. For a private airship, this was enough.

Gilbert sat on a sofa in the middle of the living room while Leylin and the other 3 stood respectfully at one side. A few clear-winged elves carried the teapot and cups and swiftly poured a cup of red tea for everyone.

“Sit!” Gilbert chuckled. “I am also rather interested in your experiences this time round!”

Leylin’s heart stirred. He knew that whatever was to come could not be avoided, but he showed no dissatisfaction about it.

By the sole fact that Gilbert saved him, it was only right to share a large portion of the reward.

“Tiny energy waves are detected! Identified as Bloodline artifacts’ detection technology! Space artifacts are unable to cut them off!”

By this time, the prompting sounds of the A.I. chip had reached Leylin’s mind. In his vision, he distinctly saw a scanning wave sweep past the 4 of them, not even sparing Noah.

The wave was so obscure that even Robin could not feel it scanning his body, it even went on to scan Leylin’s spatial pouch and ring. Despite that, Leylin’s face remained unchanged.

The few people remained silent for a while before Robin took the lead and spoke up, “Mentor, It’s like this…”

“…….” After listening to his narration, Gilbert looked at the imprint of the spell on Robin’s forehead and took a deep sigh, “I didn’t expect that you would ultimately choose this path!”

“This is my choice!” Robin bowed and replied, “If not for this, I’m afraid I wouldn’t even get the chance to look at the realm of the Morning Star!” He spoke resolutely.

“As your mentor, I can only guide and advise you in your pursuit of the truth and the power of the bloodline. As for your final choice, I will not interfere any further.”

Gilbert shook his head and said, “Since you are insistent on doing this, then so be it!”

“Mentor……” On the other side, Kesha was acting like a little girl, on the verge of crying. She spoke about her encounter extremely miserably.

“Arcus and the other two are all dead…… That’s half the strength of my clan…… Mentor…….”

Towards the end, Kesha’s eyes flushed red and she started crying. Tears flowed out like a waterfall. She spoke nothing about her earnings from the extortion of the Green-skinned Barbarian, which was done in collaboration with Leylin.

“Alright! Alright!” Gilbert said helplessly. “After this, I will give orders for your clan to be taken care of!”

“Thank you Mentor!” Kesha’s face brightened up instantaneously, with such speed that it created a pang of admiration in Leylin.

“Leylin, how about you?” Gilbert finally directed his attention to Leylin, with a slight smile of interest in his eyes.

‘What the hell. Amongst you, one is his former student, while the other is a woman. I, the newcomer, am at the greatest disadvantage!’ In his mind, Leylin rolled his eyes but he kept a calm expression on his face. He patted the space pouch respectfully and a few items appeared on the desk.

“A bloodline crystal!” Kesha covered her mouth and let out a gasp as she saw the blood-red stone.

However, Robin’s focus was on the long-root fruit and a few pieces of large, milky white bones.

As for Gilbert, he looked engrossingly at a large egg which sat in the middle of the desk. As he looked at the blood-red runes on it, he appeared to be deep in thought.

“Leylin, you’ve struck it big this time in the pocket dimensions!” Kesha leaned forward, almost squeezing her whole body into Leylin’s embrace. “This sister’s clan is already so pitiful, shouldn’t you help me out?”

“Haha…” Gilbert, however, made a carefree laugh.

“This is the egg of a Blood Vulture! Blood Vultures in the ancient times were originally well-known for searching for bloodline artifacts. Leylin, I suppose you got lucky and found a nest of Blood Vultures?”

“Yes!” Leylin scratched his head, looking a little embarrassed. “After I found the nest, I hid there for a few days before I finally seized the chance and snuck these things out……”

Upon hearing that, a hint of jealousy appeared on everyone’s face, even Robin’s. Why didn’t such good luck descend on him?

“These items, I’m willing to offer them all to Mentor!” What Leylin said thereafter turned Robin and Kesha’s minds blank.

“It’s not even possible not to offer…” Leylin gave a sincere look, but he was utterly bitter inside.

After discovering that Leylin possessed these items and did not hand them over, Gilbert would not feel good about it. If that was the case, Leylin’s future life in the Ouroboros Clan would be difficult.

“Haha… Good!”

Gilbert laughed out loud…

Chapter 437: Completing the Project

Upon hearing Leylin’s words, Gilbert stared blankly at him for a while, and then started laughing heartily. “I will accept your gift then!”

“Thank you, mentor!” Gratitude was apparent on Leylin’s face as he bowed.

“Sure! Of course, I wouldn’t simply just want to have your things for no reason; after all, Blood Vulture eggs from the ancient times are still very precious!” Gilbert lowered his head in thought.

“How about this? Aren’t you currently accumulating contribution points to buy the scroll that can inject life into constructs? I’ll make an exchange with you directly then; a sealed fourth-grade magic scroll would be sufficient to make up for these items!”

Gilbert swept his hand across the table top. The numerous bloodline treasures vanished, and a grey scroll covered in simple floral designs appeared.

“Thank you, Mentor!” Leylin received the scroll and expressed his thanks again, this time with more sincerity.

“Besides…” Gilbert glanced at Leylin’s ring and smiled.

Leylin scratched his head and displayed his embarrassment, knowing that Gilbert had discovered the items he had hidden in his spatial ring.

……

After nightfall, Leylin lay on his bed and examined the scroll in his hands, satisfaction written on his face. “Exchanging those items for a fourth-grade scroll is indeed a fair trade, I didn’t suffer!”

He then looked at the ring on his hand and collapsed onto the bed, looking as though he would fall into deep sleep soon enough.

Bu in actual fact, he was sneering secretly. What Gilbert had discovered was actually what Leylin purposely wanted him to.

Inside the ring, there was only a single Bloodline crystal and a few remains from ancient times. Gilbert did not value them exactly because there were only a few items, thus he silently agreed to Leylin’s secret stash.

In actual fact, what Leylin had handed over today was not even ten percent of his real loot, much less the fingerbone left behind by the fifth-grade Lamia from ancient times.

The temptation of such an item was too huge, and even Leylin was not willing to take it out. If not, it would be hard to pass Gilbert’s checkpoint.

No matter what happened then, it would not be a situation that he would want to see. After all, Gilbert was rather nice to him, and he didn’t want to fall out with his mentor and the Ouroboros Clan.

Benefits are the greatest reason why people are divided, and Leylin did not want to use the fingerbone to put the bond between master and disciple to the test. Might as well avoid it for the better good.

Yes, the real loot, including the Lamia’s fingerbone, were not on Leylin himself! Therefore, no matter how strict Gilbert was with his inspection, there was no use at all!

“However, although this journey was dangerous, I finally attained the items I wanted, and the other loot is not bad…” Leylin thought as he lay in bed, quickly falling into deep sleep for real.

The Black Scale travelled at high speeds. Initially, Leylin and company took more than a month to travel from the Ouroboros Clan to Nefas City, but the return journey only required about ten days or so.

After returning to headquarters, Leylin, his mentor and a few seniors gathered together and returned to Onyx Castle to check on the Magus Tower in his territory.

“Welcome, Lord Leylin!” Parker stood in front of the black Magus Tower and saluted respectfully to Leylin. His voice still sounded old as usual, and was strangely mismatched with his youthful face.

“How is the construction of my Magus Tower going?” Leylin stepped forth and gently caressed the black tower, admiring the exquisite runes on it and the faint but powerful energy waves it emitted. A smile spread across his face.

“The entire structure of the Magus Tower has been completed, we’re just left with a few cores and most importantly, the activation of the spirit of the Tower! These are awaiting your completion, Master!”

Parker’s response made Leylin satisfactory. He was serious when working too; the previous task that Leylin had given him was performed well. He had successfully delivered a letter to Duke Gilbert and helped Leylin avert his misfortune.

“Excellent! Leylin nodded, “Bring Snoopy to my lab someday. I haven’t taught him anything new in a long while too!”

He, of course, knew that age was catching up to Parker and he had no ambition, so he placed all his hopes on his grandson Snoopy, whose importance surpassed any reward.

Of course, after hearing what Leylin said, Parker was slightly excited and his bow almost reached a right angle, “Thank you on his behalf, Master!”

“On my way back from this trip, I obtained the Scroll of Life. Under my orders, prepare to begin work. I would like my Magus Tower to be completed immediately!” Leylin gave his orders indifferently.

“Your wish will be executed!” Parker replied. All the preparations for construction were already complete, and the other core materials had already been prepared too. All was left was to wait for Leylin to return and take the lead.

Wandering in his own Magus Tower, Leylin examined every corner carefully.

The interior of the Magus Tower was very spacious. Leylin created all of it according to the highest standards, with a complete set of facilities that looked refined and luxurious.

Leylin looked at level after level, especially the positive and negative energy reactive pools, along with other places such as the laboratory, the binding room, and the ecological garden.

“A.I. Chip! What are the results of the scan?” While looking around his tower, Leylin did not forget to let the A.I. Chip fully scan and record the decorations and spell formations that he saw before conducting an inspection.

The A.I. Chip sent [feedback] faithfully.

8% of the main structure of the Magus Tower has been scanned. Defence spell formation operation intact, areas that can still be further optimized: 2!

As the blueprint of the structure was originally done by Leylin himself, using the A.I. Chip’s perfect deductions, the decorations of the entire Magus Tower were perfect, almost to the point that no fault could be found.

The remaining areas that could be further optimized were only small problems that resulted from improper construction and other reasons. No matter how perfect his plan was, as long as it was executed by humans, accidents were bound to happen. Leylin had long prepared for this.

‘The rest is alright, but the previous ecological garden can be altered a little by adding in the data I collected about the environment in the ancient times while at Quicksand Castle!’ Leylin stroked his chin.

Since the Magus Tower was yet to be completed, he could still take the chance to amend it now. If he waited until the defensive spell formations were activated, especially after the tower genie had been awakened, then he wouldn’t be able to amend anything even if he wanted to.

“A.I. Chip! Design an improved version of the blueprint according to what I said earlier!”

Leylin had always liked to put the A.I. Chip in charge of the nitty-gritty things, while he himself was responsible for directing the big picture.

[Task established, adjusting original blueprint! Adding in simulated environment parameters from ancient times, beginning formation of the blueprint…]

The A.I. Chip operated swiftly and projected a new blueprint in front of Leylin within a few minutes.

Leylin scanned the blueprint many times, satisfied with the blueprint made by the A.I. Chip. “Yes! To maximize the use of the original resources and set-up, I just have to add a few items and spell formations! This will do!”

He now had numerous subordinates and a huge number of Stone tribe slaves. Once he handed down the task of amending the place, it would only take a small number of people working in shifts day and night for ten days to complete it.

Leylin stood at the side of the negative energy reactive pool on the lowest level, and examined the complicated spell designs. At the radiance of the pure gold, silver and other precious materials, his face showed no signs of sadness or joy, maintaining tranquility.

[Simulation of the spell formations of the entire Magus Tower complete, 341 dummy runs, number of malfunctions: 0!]

The blue glow of the A.I. Chip flashed in the depths of Leylin’s eyes.

“Begin!” Leylin exhaled gently, and placed a piece of compressed energy crystal that was emitting immense light rays and heat, much like a miniature sun, into a groove at the heart of the spell formation.

*Brr!* The entire spell formation started to shake, and ring after ring of runes appeared out of thin air. Traces of light circulated on the spell formation.

“Start!” Leylin’s spiritual force extended and connected with the spell formation.

In the instant when the spiritual force came into contact with the spell formation, Leylin felt as though he had opened a valve, causing a multitude of energy particles to be frantically absorbed by the spell formation, before passing through a complex conversion channel and flowing into the negative energy reactive pool.

Meanwhile, outside the Magus Tower, Parker, Kubler, Snoopy and Leylin’s other subordinates had all gathered to watch this scene, their eyes all brightly lit.

A huge elemental wave seemed to form a vortex that was absorbed by the black Magus Tower.

One by one, the magical runes on the body of the Tower lit up, bringing about frightening and yet stable waves, firmly connecting to one another.

Only Leylin was in the Magus Tower at that moment. He ran to the top of the Magus Tower at the speed of lightning and saw that the external appearance was almost the same, but the spell formation and storage pool gave off an entirely different vibe.

“Next, the positive energy reactive pool!” Leylin pushed the same high energy crystal into the groove, and the same activation spell appeared from Leylin’s hands, merging into the four walls.

*Boom!* At the top of the Magus Tower, a huge elemental wave practically condensed into a physical substance, energy particles of various colours emitting brilliant lights and vibrant colours.They quickly subsided into two rainbows, one bright and one dark.

Soon after, the bright rainbow was absorbed by the peak of the Tower, while the rainbow with a hint of gold submerged into the ground.

The positive energy reactive pool buzzed continuously, the elemental liquids within accumulating further and further until it finally reached the middle mark.

Two spheres of light that resembled stars emitted from the peak and underground of the Tower, spreading continually across the structure. Numerous runes lit up one by one, and finally converged at its centre.

[Magus Tower spell formation fully activated! Currently operating well!]

The A.I. Chip pointed out.

At that point, Leylin was standing on the point of intersection of the positive and negative energy reactive pools. An unadorned scroll covered in bizarre floral designs appeared in his hands.

“Fourth-grade magic— the Scroll of Life!”

“A.I. Chip, prepare to inject knowledge into the being!”

Leylin ripped open the grey scroll, and rays of light burst out. Suddenly, a terrifying attractive force was transmitted from the scroll. The Vapour Phase spiritual force of his consciousness was consumed in huge quantities, and the process only came to a gradual stop when it was close to being exhausted.

Chapter 438: Tower Genie #1

Of course, with how much of his wealth Leylin had expended on this, the power of the activation spell was not to be belittled.

A circle of sparkling starlight shrouded the tower. Numerous runes flickered in sync and breathed at the same rate, as if having lives of their own.

A faint blue figure began to form in front of Leylin. “Master, this tower genie is here to serve you!”

This tower genie had been branded by Leylin’s spiritual force upon its birth.

In addition, it was one with the Magus Tower, and could help Leylin take care of any minute details that might be difficult to find.

“Alright. Here’s my first mission. Accept this and fuse with it!” A blue seed shot out from between Leylin’s eyebrows and quickly entered the blue tower genie’s figure.

A multitude of data flowed across the tower genie’s eyes, and a tremendous amount of complicated information even caused the newly-formed tower genie’s figure to flicker, as it eventually turned into a ball of light.

By the time everything had stabilised, the A.I. Chip’s robotic voice was produced from within the blue ball of light.

[Digitization complete. The A.I. Chip system is now serving you. Please choose the exterior appearance.]

“A tree elf!” Leylin had never had anything against humanoid managers.

The blue ball of light shook, and eventually formed a blue elf the size of a human head, with a pair of wings formed of starlight.

“I’ll call you Number 1 in the future.” Leylin nodded, very satisfied with this intellectual body’s external appearance.

“Understood. Number 1 greets Master!” The blue elf bowed, though its facial expression looked mechanical.

[Beginning networking.]

Such an expression actually pleased Leylin more. What he needed was an absolutely rational manager, and from the very beginning, he had not built in any emotional functions.

With this command, a data interface connected Leylin’s A.I. Chip with the elf using a stream of spiritual force.

[Beginning synchronizing of data. In the midst of tidying up]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded.

[Discovery of inharmonious spiritual force waves at three areas. Beginning elimination.]

[Fusion with tower genie completed. Activation of anti-probing spell formation at full force.]

One after another, these prompts popped up, and the smile at the corner of Leylin’s mouth grew wider.

Regular tower genies definitely lacked the terrifying calculation abilities of the A.I. Chip. The area that it could manage would only include the interior of the Magus Tower.

However, with what he was doing, not only could he control the interior of the Magus Tower from a distance away, he could even completely eliminate any damages that would otherwise have been hidden.

After fusing with the program that the A.I. Chip had duplicated, the tower genie had now become more intelligent, able to autonomously search for holes and repair them, and even take care of a few flaws or defects that had originally been there.

It could be said that even if Grand Duke Gilbert had done anything to the rank 4 scroll, it would have been pointless.

This was because Leylin had already modified the tower genie’s structure with things of his own.

“Hah…” Leylin took in a long breath.

The construction of the Magus Tower, particularly the completion of the positive and negative energy reactive pools, now allowed the interior of the Magus Tower to have ten times the elemental particle concentration as outside.

The concentrated energy particles could even be seen with the naked eye, and for Magus eyes this was even more apparent. Leylin felt like he was surrounded by an elemental ocean.

The particle concentration in the central continent had already been very high, and that of this Magus Tower far surpassed that..

It could be said that in this environment, Leylin’s progress in his meditation technique would not be too slow even if he did not use any potions. What was more frightening was that even trashy acolytes with a level 1 or 2 aptitude could break through their own limits and become official Magi if they studied and meditated here!

After recognising this, Leylin immediately made a choice. Unless there was anything terribly important, he would stay and settle down in the Magus Tower.

Outside the tower.

Parker and the others could not feel all this as keenly as Leylin, but after there was a rumble from the entire Magus Tower and it started emanating faint light, everyone still began to cheer. Even Kubler had shining tears at the corner of his eye.

A Magus Tower was a representation of strength in the central continent.

With a Magus Tower, and a Magus like Leylin who was viewed highly, regular Magi with Crystal phase spiritual force would not dare trespass in this area. In addition, with the large-scaled monitoring abilities of the Magus Tower, the rate of crime would definitely be lowered.

This signified that Leylin’s power was secured, whether among mortals or Magi.

As a result, all the vassals who depended on Leylin were extremely moved.

*Boom!* At this moment, with the sound from a power switch, the entrance to the Magus Tower opened up, revealing Leylin’s figure.

“It’s finally done. Come in and take a look!”

“Many thanks, Master!” A few Warlocks immediately bowed. They had contributed to the construction of the Magus Tower, and naturally wished to take a look at it.

“Ah! The concentration of the particles!” Upon entering through the entrance, they were immediately shocked by the terrifying concentration of particles in the Magus Tower.

“As expected of the Magus Tower that my lord personally constructed. If I had studied in this place from my youth, I might have been able to break through to the Hydro Phase spiritual force stage by this time…” Parker carressed the cold and rigid walls, almost feeling like sobbing.

“Based on your contributions, I will give you different amounts of authority within the Magus Tower, as well as assign you your own bedrooms, laboratory and the like.” Seeing all his subordinates, Leylin immediately made a promise to reward them.

“Many thanks, Master!” Numerous Warlocks were immediately touched. They had never even dreamed of having a place in such a high-grade Magus Tower.

This was especially so for Parker. Though he had little hope of advancing, all he wanted was to pave the way for Snoopy. He had never expected this treatment at any point in his life, and was immensely grateful.

Leylin thought nothing of it. These Warlocks were all his subordinates, and ought to be given rewards. With the tower genie supervising, they wouldn’t be able to do anything anyway.

He would only open up the guestrooms, living areas and a few laboratories to them. The core areas, the positive and negative energy reactive pool as well as control room were safely in his control.

As it was very likely that they would live and perform research here, Kubler and the others had a different reaction and emotion to this.

Leylin brought them to look at the few levels in the middle, passing by the living room, bedrooms, library, and all the way to the Magus Garden.

Leylin had set up this Magus Garden like those of ancient times. Though he had yet to transplant any plants here, some vegetation and precious plants were already growing lushly.

A green light shone down. All this was the accumulated life energy that had come from activating the Magus Tower, giving the vegetation a huge boost in nutrition and vitality.

“With the positive energy pool, the entire Magus Tower’s water circulation uses the purest water elemental particles and turns them into water that is purified to the highest degree. The yield from this Magus Garden would be enough to provide for thousands of people if the incoming energy stays at its peak,” Leylin introduced, sounding a little proud.

With the bonus from the Magus Tower, he could obtain a strength comparable to a Magus with Crystal Phase spiritual force, and even provide for over five thousand people in the tower!

With this ability and self-sufficiency, it would be considered an extremely frightful large fort in times of war.

The Magus Tower was a terrifying war machine, and its amazing strength was enough to obstruct any attempts at spying on them.

“This is my future base!” Leylin sighed in his heart, but a smile then appeared on his face. “To celebrate the completion of the Magus Tower, I will hold a feast in Onyx Castle tonight. Let us all revel!”

An intoxicating clamour spread throughout the room.

……

Night fell and Onyx Castle was filled with scenes of jubilation, with many female singers, dancers and entertainers presenting their art with all the energy they could muster. Waves of delicacies and fine liquor were constantly sent to the feast like running water.

As this was in the form of a family banquet, the rules were lax, and even regular nobles were invited.

Though the Warlocks had formed a circle of their own, they were not repelled by the clamour outside. All faces were brimming with smiles, full of hope for the future of their territory.

With Leylin’s status, nobody dared disturb him. He drank a few glasses and encouraged his subordinates with a few words, and then secretly left the castle.

The moon hung high in the sky, silver moonlight spilling down. The night air held a chill to it and was just right for those who had consumed alcohol.

Of course, with Leylin’s body, there were few wines that could get him drunk.

He came to the side of the Magus Tower. Here, due the superb detection abilities of the tower genie, the original guards had all been transferred out.

A ring-shaped rune suddenly brightened on Leylin’s hand. “I’m here. Come over!” Leylin said, his tone holding within a command that was difficult to ignore.

A black figure appeared from the air, and came to stand silently beside Leylin. “Come with me.”

The entrance to the Magus Tower opened up with a rumble, welcoming its master.

They went all the way to the reception room, and only then did Leylin’s facial muscles relax as he took a seat on the sofa.

“Sit! You don’t need to conceal yourself anymore here. My Magus Tower has powerful detection spell formations. Even the spying of Morning Star Magi can be recognised!”

The person in black robes hesitated, and then threw back her hood, revealing a pretty female face with a golden headband on her forehead.

“Master!” She exclaimed in a low voice. This female Magus was the fugitive Magus leader that Leylin had subdued, Tanasha!

Watching Tanasha taking a seat, Leylin asked slowly, “I hope there weren’t any troubles on the way here.”

Chapter 439: Deceit Seen Through

The Forgotten Land was very infertile and could be said to be a desert of the Magus world. Magi who travelled there were all fugitives who had been driven to desperation in the central continent.

Of course, Tanasha was no different. If her identity was exposed, it was not just her, but also Leylin who would be in deep trouble.

“No, I have been very careful so far. I didn’t leave behind any information about my appearance or scent, and I did not use an airship!” she stated.

“Very well!” Leylin nodded. “Where are my things?”

“Right here!” A large black box appeared on the table with a swish of her hand.

Seeing the seal still perfectly untouched, Leylin gave a look of satisfaction. He opened the box, in which was a thick layer of soft white fur.

This was the King Blood Vulture’s feathers. It contained the miraculous ability to conceal a bloodline’s aura, and it had even fooled Leylin previously.

After brushing these white feathers aside, the energy waves of many bloodline treasures radiated out, surprising Tanasha.

A mountain of bloodline crystals and many strange bones, as well as fruits, rhizomes and such containing the power of bloodlines, were piled up messily, as if they were not of any monetary worth.

However, deep inside, Tanasha knew that once these items were revealed, it would greatly impact the Ouroboros Clan. Every single item in there could make a high-ranked Warlock go crazy!

Although she brought them over as per Leylin’s orders, it was also by his order that she did not open the box. It was only then that she became aware of the contents of the box.

This was obviously Leylin’s plan. When he acquired the loot in the pocket dimensions, he had already considered ways to get them past Gilbert.

After all, as the person who had sent out the information, he had already known long ago about Gilbert’s arrival. How could he not have prepared for it?

Morning Star Warlocks’ ability in detecting bloodline treasures was far exceeded Leylin’s expectations. He had no confidence in hiding them at all. Hence, Leylin chose not to bring them with him.

Even if Gilbert monitored Leylin’s spatial pouch and ring, he could only find some of the things that Leylin left behind intentionally. The real loot was all moved away by Tanasha.

With regards to this set up, it certainly was a decision that Leylin had made with determination.

Firstly, Tanasha had not only sworn her loyalty to him, but also allowed a part of her spirit source to be held by Leylin.

For a Magus, this kind of restriction was practically fatal. If Leylin destroyed that part of her spirit source, Tanasha would lose her mind even if she did not lose her life! On top of that, he deliberately won her over previously and agreed to take revenge for her. The assigned mission was just to transport an item. Leylin had some confidence in her.

For safety’s sake, not only did he cast a sealing spell on the black box, but he also used the King Blood Vulture’s feathers as a cover in order to conceal the bloodline energy waves of the treasures.

It seemed like the plan had succeeded.

Leylin looked at the pile of bloodline treasures, nearly laughing. Among the many bloodline energy waves, a fingerbone lay there quietly, yet majestically like a king. It made the other treasures seem less appealing.

Tanasha stared at the fingerbone as if she had seen her enemy, “What is this thing?”

Evidently, the aura of the fingerbone made her uncomfortable. This was unfathomable for a Crystal Phase Magus.

Even though it was just the remains of a creature, it had the power to make her so uncomfortable. How powerful could the living creature have been?

Tanasha fixed her eyes on Leylin. Now, she began to find this young Magus increasingly unpredictable.

“The Lamia fingerbone!” Surprisingly, Leylin answered the question directly.

“Tower genie, keep these items safely!” Leylin picked up the fingerbone and ordered the small blue elf beside him.

“Yes, my master!” The small elf held its chest and bowed. After that, a mechanical puppet walked over and took the black box to be stored in the treasury.

“Tanasha, come with me. I might need you later on!” Leylin called out to Tanasha with a downcast face.

Subsequently, he brought Tanasha all the way down to the room binding room before he came to a stop.

Powerful binding runes, energy-isolating runes, the power of corrosion, the weeping of vengeful spirits, gravity runes…

Tanasha looked at the runes on the walls as her expression darkened. With so many binding spells, even Tanasha, a Crystal Phase Magus, would have difficulties struggling her way out.

This led to an even deeper understanding of Leylin’s financial capabilities.

“You set up such strict bindings. Do you intend to summon the great devil?” Tanasha asked, with a slightly provocative tone.

“No! This is only set up in case of an emergency. You know it— the astral plane is filled with all kinds of strange creatures. A little more preparation never hurts!”

Leylin’s face carried an odd smile, “But never did I expect that the first subject that it would be used on, would actually be this!”

As a light shone from his right hand, the Lamia fingerbone in Leylin’s hand immediately appeared at the center of the bindings. A strong sluice gate made of reinforced glass dropped and the many runes began to flicker.

The Lamia fingerbone lay there silently like a dead creature.

Tanasha held her breath. She knew that Leylin was probably going to show her something unusual.

“Tower genie, begin first-level operations of the bindings!”

Following Leylin’s orders, the circle of lights in the binding room lit up all at once. An invisible power lifted the Lamia fingerbone.

“Start purification!” As per the tower genie’s emotionless command, two small lightning clouds grew above the bone, streaks of lightning crackling as they burst towards it.

“I know you’re still there. There’s no need for the pretense! Come out!” Under the lightning, the white fingerbone appeared to be unaffected. However, Leylin had a straight face, with an expression as cold as ice.

After a few minutes, there was still no sign of any anomaly, causing Leylin to sigh deeply.

“Begin the next level of purification!”

“Authorisation verified! Inputting energy!” Upon hearing the tower genie’s voice, the original two clouds began to transform immediately.

Dark, black clouds suddenly soared above the area, and the lightning acquired a subtle red hue. Thick bolts swept across the bone mercilessly, causing narrow cracks to surface on it.

“If you continue doing that, you’ll destroy the fingerbone!” Tanasha looked at Leylin, but his expression did not stop, indicating he had no intentions of stopping.

Under the lightning that had been strengthened tens of times, the bone began to vibrate, as if it was going to explode into dust anytime.

*Ring!* Just when Tanasha thought the fingerbone was about to explode, a strange scene suddenly appeared. A ring of green light burst out violently, with such a strong power radiating that it split the dark clouds apart in a second.

*Hiss!* A touch of green light emerged. It then transformed into a phantom of a young, green-haired woman, now lunging towards Leylin.

Compared to what Leylin had seen previously, the image of the young woman was not only more illusory, but her face had also become a lot more complex, with rhomboidal scales. Her eyes were a sea of green and her pupils had become vertical slits.

As the Lamia’s phantom swept her glance across with her pupils, Leylin’s entire body became a little sluggish.

“Begin binding!” This time, the tower genie responded swiftly and gave an order.

*Bang!* A loud sound echoed as the young woman’s phantom crashed into the clear reinforced glass, causing the runes to flash.

Soon after, an enormous gravitational strength emerged and pinned the woman to the ground.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* A chain of runes appeared one after another, binding the green-haired Lamia’s phantom.

After coming back to his senses, Leylin, who had broken out in cold sweat, could not help but draw a deep breath. “That was really close!”

Although he tried his best to overestimate the opponent, the terrifying feeling of having his mind being snatched had given him a fright all of a sudden.

This was the definite control that a high-ranked bloodline had over a low-ranked one. In face of the great gap between the ranks, all efforts were to no avail.

“You dare oppose me? The Grand Matriarch will not let you off, bloodline traitor!” The green tongue of the Lamia’s phantom forked as she spoke.

“Sorry! I don’t have the habit of obeying orders that’ll cause me to lose my life!” Though Leylin apologised, he showed no sign of remorse on his face.

“The Giant Kemoyin Serpent is a rank 4 creature. It needs to obey the Lamia’s bloodline, which is of a higher rank. This is branded deep into the inheritance of the bloodline and is not able to be changed!” The Lamia’s phantom glared at Leylin and asked, “How did you escape?”

“How would I know?” Leylin swished his hands.

In actual fact, he had guessed that it might have a connection with his bloodline. Not only was the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline in him extremely pure, there was a great possibility that through the A.I. chip’s purification, his bloodline differed from the original.

“What is this?” Tanasha stared at the Lamia with a look of curiosity surfaced on her face.

“The owner of the fingerbone. Just a projection of a destroyed, shattered and unwanted memory fragment!” Leylin spoke with disdain.

“When did you find out?” After seeing Leylin like that, the Lamia calmed down.

“I knew from the beginning!” Leylin said calmly.

“I am not someone who would sit and wait for rewards. I only believe in achieving things through my own efforts. Seeing how you took the initiative to come to me, there’s no way I could let my guard down!”

Frankly speaking, Leylin basically believed the part about the other party being tired of staying in the King Blood Vulture’s nest, but he could not believe that it would be so boring and despair-inducing that one would seek death.

Ancient Magi had strong mental endurance, and on top of that, she was an extremely powerful Warlock. How could she possibly be cowed by a long period of solitude?

Perhaps her true intention was to get out, or to seize a corporeal body with the help of Leylin!

A Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock which is suppressed by the ancient Lamia, was definitely a first-rate target to seize control of!

Chapter 440: Destroy

The moment Leylin used the Lamia fingerbone and fused with it, her remaining memory fragments would also fuse into his Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline, secretly lurking within.

When the time was right, the Lamia’s sea of consciousness would burst forth. How could Leylin be a match for her?

It was not just the large gap between them in terms of their knowledge and experience. The inborn control in terms of his bloodline, as well as issues of how she would try to gain dominance over him would definitely put Leylin at death’s door.

Having thought this through, Leylin’s murderous intent towards the Lamia was at its boiling point.

However, he had not flared up but instead, pretended that he knew nothing. He waited till the Magus Tower was built, and once his most capable subordinate, Tanasha was at his side and increased his power to the maximum, he then lashed out on his home ground.

It looked like it had been a good idea to be so meticulous. If not, his opponent could have easily taken care of him.

“Shall we make a trade?” The scales on the Lamia phantom’s face faded, returning her face to that of a young girl. Her delicate and pretty face even enchanted Tanasha, who was also female.

“What trade?” Leylin’s voice was low.

“Help me find a flesh body. Anything is fine as long as they have the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline, and it’s best if it’s a female Warlock. In return, I can give you all my knowledge. Though you’ll only obtain a portion of the knowledge that my main body possesses, she is a rank 5 pure-blooded Warlock. Just a small bit of her memories is enough to make you strike gold…”

Calm words rang from the mouth of the phantom Lamia, causing Tanasha’s breath to become rough.

Inheritance from an ancient rank 5 Warlock? Perhaps even Morning Star Magi would go crazy in want over this.

The price he had to pay was a mere female Warlock, and with just a bit of effort, he could find them easily in the Ouroboros Clan.

*Clap! Clap! Clap!!*Leylin applauded, a slight smile on his face. “Good suggestion! What a great suggestion! Even I am tempted.”

“Good! You can first—” The Lamia phantom’s words stopped halfway, and a look of fury suddenly appeared on her face. “You!”

Countless chains tightened, binding her to the spot.

“Tower genie, use all stored energy and prioritise the bindings. The aim is to exterminate this person!”

“Tanasha, help me!” Leylin’s face suddenly changed, and he made to deal the fatal blow.

Great amounts of thunder clouds were produced, lightning washing over the phantom time after time, causing her figure to become even more illusory.

Tanasha obeyed Leylin’s order subconsciously, and her Crystal Phase spiritual force emanated, reinforcing the runes of binding.

“Traitor! The Grand Matriarch will not let you off! Hiss…” The phantom image eventually turned into a half-human, half-snake and hissed, her expression incomparably fierce.

“Let’s talk about it when she finds me.” Leylin’s expression was resolute, constantly urging on the runes and spell formation of binding.

The inheritance from an ancient rank 5 Warlock was indeed very tempting, but Leylin had his own considerations.

The other party was merely a remnant spirit, and might even be the combination of a few memory fragments. How much could she remember?

And just for this, he would bring her around and let her scheme against him?

Though he was somewhat confident in his scheming abilities, Leylin was not certain that he could win over this ancient freak, especially when she could suppress his bloodline and was so enticing.

The ancient Lamia had started out enticing various giant serpent species, and Leylin did not want to unknowingly let her suggestions affect his mind.

For him, it was most practical to be able to take in harmless things. Everything else was an illusion!

“If you don’t die, I can never be at peace.” Leylin stared at the Lamia phantom behind the glass, a determined look in his eyes. “Maximise power!”

[Runes of binding operating at excess of 120% capacity. This is the most powerful attack.]

Along with the tower genie’s voice, a streak of thick red lightning struck the phantom.

*Rumble!* The Magus Tower began to tremble, and fine cracks began to appear in the binding area.

The phantom image of the Lamia seemed to have given up all hope as she dissipated to nothingness under the red lightning.

*Pak!* A fingerbone with cracks all over its surface fell to the ground.

“It’s over.” Tanasha heaved a sigh of relief and glanced at Leylin as if she was looking at a freak, “That’s inheritance from an ancient rank 5 Warlock! You actually…”

“I was, of course, tempted!” Leylin shook his head, “But it wasn’t to the point that I would become muddle-headed in the face of it. Ancient Magi have too many methods. I wouldn’t dare bring a disaster waiting to happen along with me at all times.”

As he spoke, the tower genie constantly scanned the fingerbone in the binding room, streams of electric light moving across its surface.

[Level 1 scanning complete. No remnant spiritual force found.]

[Level 2 scanning complete. No abnormal reactions found.]

[Level 3 scanning complete. Confirmed total extermination of remnant spirit of Lamia.]

Red, green and blue rays shot out and scanned the fingerbone to and fro, not missing any spots.

A streak of blue flashed in Leylin’s eyes, and he waited till the A.I. Chip gave the final confirmation before he issued the command, “Open up the protective layer!”

*Shoo!* The tempered glass split apart. Bathed in milky-white light, the slightly cracked fingerbone floated to Leylin’s hand.

Though it looked like a mere fragmented bone, the rejoicing of his Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline told Leylin that the moment he digested this bone, his bloodline would become so pure it would be unimaginable, and might even be able to help him advance!

‘If Mentor Gilbert were to know about this, he would immediately fall out with me in order to obtain it. What ties we have as part of the same clan, our mentor-student relationship or ethics would mean nothing at all.’ Leylin sighed inside. If not for the isolation by his Magus Tower, he would not dare take it out now.

‘Though it’s best if I use it right now, it has too much research value! Besides…’ Leylin glanced at the data recorded by the A.I. Chip.

[Activity of Host Body’s bloodline increasing. Maturation period of bloodline estimated to be in 124 years, 4 months.]

Though it was just some physical contact with his skin and the waves and energy radiation from the fingerbone, it had the legendary effect of Lamia Hair, allowing Leylin’s bloodline to mature by a large amount.

“Based on the situation, I don’t even need to absorb the bone. I can make use of the radiation to increase the rate of my bloodline’s maturation by nearly tenfold!’

“Looks like I’ll need to stay in the Magus Tower as much as possible from now on…’ Leylin touched his chin and ordered the tower genie, “Keep the Lamia fingerbone well. Store it based on all procedures for special grade 1 materials.”

[Understood, master.]

The little elf quickly took the Lamia fingerbone and vanished.

There was no other way around it. Bloodline Warlocks were extremely sensitive to this type of item. If Leylin brought it with him, not counting Lucian and the others, Gilbert would definitely sense it.

The only way was to make use of the powerful energy isolation abilities of the Magus Tower and conceal the undulations from its aura.

After taking care of all these matters, Leylin looked back and revealed a kind smile to Tanasha, “Alright. Tanasha, welcome!”

After going through such a secret matter together, he evidently had a better relationship with Tanasha.

Making use of this opportunity, Leylin invited Tanasha to have a look around his Magus Tower. Glancing at Tanasha, who was immersed while glancing at the Magus Tower constructed with top-grade materials, the corner of Leylin’s lips quirked up in a smile.

“Can I know more about your past?”

Leylin asked after the tour of the living room, where the tower genie had a few puppets deliver hot cocoa and desserts to them.

“Since I am now with Master, I have nothing to hide…” Tanasha held her mug with both hands and looked pained, as if immersed in some memory.

“I am of the Madie Lands, in the Dark Lunar Forest at the western region of the central continent.”

Leylin listened closely. It was just another story about profits, women and other things that gave rise to blood and hatred, which he was familiar with. He learned the name of Tanasha’s enemy.

“Some large family in the Crescent Moon Zither Alliance?”

“Yes! If Master could take revenge on my behalf and extinguish the Swaine family, my body, spirit and everything will belong to Master!” Tanasha promised, looking determined as she delivered her oath.

After hearing Tanasha’s story, Leylin did not agree immediately, but sank into deep thought.

Crescent Moon Zither Alliance was a small organisation in the central continent, but since he had heard of it before, there was definitely a Morning Star Magus in charge. However, that Magus was not of the Swaine family, so there was a way to interfere in this.

“I can agree to this, but it might be a long time till then. You need to be prepared.” Leylin watched Tanasha’s eyes attentively and spoke slowly.

Tanasha ran her fingers through her hair behind her ear, a wry smile about her lips, “I understand! I am already very happy that Master agreed.”

Leylin was surprised. It looked like this was her only wish.

“Alright! As for your identity, I have no way to solve that issue yet. I’m afraid you’ll need to stay out of sight or return to the Forgotten Land. Do you have any plans?” he asked.

She lowered her head and pondered over it, “I still have a few things to take care of in the Forgotten Land.”

“Alright.” Leylin nodded.

“One more thing. In the Forgotten Land, there is a Kobold tribe. I’ll need the blood essence from the stronger ones, meaning rank 3 or above!” The Kobolds were rumoured to have the great giant dragon bloodline, and Leylin was very interested in this.

“That’s not a problem. There are many powers with conflicts amongst each other within the Forgotten Land. Battles are common!” Tanasha nodded and agreed.

Chapter 441: Guest

Leylin holed himself inside the Magus Tower after its completion.

This was because the elemental particle concentration here far surpassed that of the outside, allowing his spiritual force to grow much. Furthermore, there were many high-level experiments that could only be done in the Magus Tower. Many of his previous theories could finally be put to the test.

More importantly, the Magus Tower could block out the probing of high-ranked Magi, turning into an elusive location which could hide Leylin’s many secrets.

With those factors coming into play, it was natural that Leylin almost never left the tower, and had neglected both sleep and food to focus on his meditation practice and research.

Many top-notch results had been actualised with the A.I Chip’s assistance, which had increased Leylin’s own knowledge reserves.

In the gigantic library, Snoopy was trying his best to chain up a hysterical, screaming copper-coloured book that had pages filled with fangs, and properly settled it on a bookshelf made of black pinewood.

The library of a Magus was naturally extremely enriching, and represented the accumulation of its owner’s knowledge.

Even though Leylin had the A.I Chip, he had previously collected many books from the south coast and Twilight Zone; the books were so plentiful that all the space was practically filled up. Now, they would have to tidy the books up and sort them out according to their different genres.

Other than that, the central continent was vast as well. Its accumulated knowledge was even more shocking. Leylin had always been actively purchasing books related to magic and a steady flow of such books were sent to the Magus Tower, which further enriched his collection.

His apprentice Snoopy was sent here to sort out and manage the conservation of the books.

Even if it was tough, he cherished this opportunity. Not to mention the stiflingly high concentration of energy particles in the tower, the chance to read so many books freely made him so happy that he could die.

Even if he had his head buried in books day in and day out, he would only have covered an insignificant portion of Leylin’s collection.

Only now did he realise the depth of his Mentor’s knowledge. Just the terrifying accumulation of information was enough for him to look up to Leylin.

At this time, in a room within the library, Leylin was sitting before a giant study desk, quill in hand, as he wrote with lightning speed.

Every second, tens of characters were jotted down, one after the other.

His astonishing speed as well as the coordination of spells allowed Leylin to perform a miracle unthinkable in his previous life.

A blue light glowed in his eyes as rows of words appeared unceasingly. He was actually trying to replicate all the information the A.I. Chip had recorded.

“All done!” Leylin looked at the messy yet seemingly organised documents on his desk, and his face revealed a satisfied expression.

“The entirety of the ecological garden’s experimental data has been replicated. As for these…” Within the Quicksand Castle, Leylin’s biggest gains were what he’d appropriated from the Blood Vultures. However, he had also found large amounts of miscellaneous data in the laboratory.

Due to the lack of the core information and the receptor model, the data could not be replicated at all.

But the other gains thereafter had allowed Leylin to see a glimmer of hope. In the spatial pouch of the Green-skinned Barbarian Magus whom Leylin had saved from a curse, Leylin had found some flawed research data and notes. From the looks of it, the forces in the outer circle had also obtained some data from their explorations.

Even though the other party had not managed to analyse any information, Leylin’s deductive ability was very strong with the support of the A.I. Chip. He had instantly realised the connections between the data and the experimental information he had collected.

If he was not wrong, the torn and tattered journal he obtained from the Green-skinned Barbarian Magus was the core data that was missing in the laboratory!

Even though the Green-skinned Barbarian’s collections were not complete, as long as Leylin had some form of data, albeit flawed, he would be able to derive the other information through deductions and simulations. It was only a matter of time.

After interactions with Tanasha, he had further improved the core data.

With his research, he gradually deciphered the experiments that were conducted in the gigantic laboratory.

“Studies on transferring and combining bloodlines?” Leylin held out a part of the deciphered content and muttered to himself.

Quicksand was undoubtedly an alliance of various Warlock organisations, and their research on bloodlines had never ceased.

Their experimental data was actually more in-depth and concrete than the research of the Ouroboros Clan, which had allowed Leylin to reach a whole new level.

‘I have a premonition that if I finish analysing the experimental results and add them into my own A.I Chip’s system, my research in bloodlines would advance to an unimaginable stage, even to the extent that I can directly extract genes from rank 1 and 2 bloodline creatures and assemble them into an ancient bloodline!’ Excitement flashed across Leylin’s eyes.

Bloodline shackles were the greatest pains to a Warlock. Those that had advanced to the peak of what their bloodlines would allow and reached a dead-end would normally choose to turn their attention to research on bloodline modulation and combination.

That was also the main direction of the research of the Ouroboros Clan.

While the three elders were looking for the Purgatory World, they were also trying to manufacture an even stronger bloodline by building upon the foundations of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline, and from there onwards, break their own bloodline shackles.

Of course, until now, the experiments had made no progress to speak of, not to mention any hopes for success.

“From the looks of it, in this area, the ancient Warlocks have greatly surpassed us…” Leyin sighed as he held the data tighter in his hands.

If he did not experience a breakthrough after being promoted to a Morning Star Magus, or if his search for the Purgatory World were to fail, this would perhaps be his last hope.

“Tower genie! Store the bloodline research data well, at level 1 confidentiality!” Leylin issued the command.

Nowadays, he felt that it had been extremely worth it to construct the Magus Tower. If he didn’t have one, let alone experimentation and information storage, how would he hide such a valuable object?

Just after Leylin had consumed some food and was about to start research, the tower genie suddenly appeared before him.

“Master! A strong radiation has been sensed south-east of the Magus Tower, about 200 kilometres away. Estimated to be a Magus of rank 3 or above!”

In terms of range of detection, the Magus Tower far surpassed the A.I. Chip. That was also one of the reasons why many Magi liked to construct a Magus Tower in their territory. The feeling one got when in complete control of their territory and that nothing could escape their eyes was extremely desirable. More importantly, they were able to protect their own interests.

Of course, in terms of accuracy, the Magus Tower could not measure up to the A.I. Chip. Currently, it could only scan for energy spikes, and could not concretely tell him how many people there were or even their genders.

Leylin was not too worried about that. Even when compared to all other Morning Star Magi, his Magus Tower was one of the best in the entire central continent.

As the enemies inched closer, the accuracy of the Magus Tower’s scans would increase until it could project a proper image.

“It’s them! I’m afraid I’ll have to go out for a while.” Leylin looked at the two silhouettes in the image and stood up, feeling a headache coming on.

At the same time, Kesha had arrived at Onyx Castle with another female Warlock.

Kubler, who was in a butler uniform, lowered his head, “Distinguished Marquis Kesha, my Master is currently conducting experiments in the Magus Tower. If you could rest here for a while, I’ll inform him immediately!”

As a Mankestre Bloodline Warlock, his position in the Ouroboros Clan was very low, and he could only admire the highly-ranked Magi like Kesha. If he wasn’t Leylin’s vassal, he would not even have a chance to speak to her.

“There’s no need for that. He’s already here!” Kesha waved her hands, and a shadow from afar waved back.

“Hehe… How did Senior find the time to visit me here?” Leylin landed on the floor, his robes flowing in the wind. He nodded to Kesha as a form of respect, and looked at the other female Warlock.

The Warlock had jet-black hair that gushed like a waterfall until her waist. This was an effect of the darkness elemental energy particles in the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline, but it matched Leylin’s standard of beauty very well.

Her fair skin, gentle facial features and voluptuous body were what made many men find her unforgettable, but what left a deep impression on Leylin was her wild and reckless personality.

“Welcome to my castle as well, Marquis Freya!” Leylin’s smile was a bit forced. Kesha, however, disregarded all societal expectations and came forward, giving Leylin a passionate hug.

“Leylin, I haven’t thanked you for saving my life the other time! Originally, I had wanted to subsidise the construction of your Magus Tower, but from the looks of it now, you are so much richer than I am…” she remotely sighed, and appeared to be jealous as she stared at the splendor of the Magus Tower not far away.

“Keke… That’s only some savings from a lifetime of risks!” Leylin touched his nose and said unabashedly.

“Alright. Freya and I came here today specifically to see you. Aren’t you going to show us around?” Kesha curled her mouth. In front of close friends, she behaved in a feminine manner, and was sometimes even childish.

“Of course, of course, it’ll be my pleasure. Please!” Leylin wryly stretched out his hands and locked arms with Kesha.

Inviting close Magi to take a look at one’s Magus Tower, or even to reside and perform research there, was something many Magi used to strengthen their bonds with them. Leylin, of course, was not an exception.

Thanks to the manipulation abilities of his tower genie, things that he did not want found would be hard to discover while inside the tower, even for Morning Star Magi. Hence, there was no need to fear his secrets being exposed.

Chapter 442: The Trade

Leylin led Kesha and Freya around his Magus Tower.

Kesha oohed and aahed at everything, while Freya was much quieter, as though there was something on her mind.

“Whew… Junior Leylin, I take back what I said earlier. You’re not only much richer than me, you’re a lot richer than even Senior Lucian!” Kesha said, pleased. She was half-lying on the sofa in the living room without the slightest care about her wardrobe malfunction.

“In my opinion, even Lucian’s Magus Tower might not be as luxurious as yours, Leylin! I’m afraid that only a handful in the entire central continent would be as fancy!”

“Senior! Don’t say such things!” Leylin laughed wryly as he raised his arms in defeat, “Why are you here today?”

Seeing his mentor conversing with guests, Snoopy served refreshments and quickly retreated, behaving like a waiter that had been groomed with utmost care.

“We are here to thank you, junior, for your care in the pocket dimension. We’d initially planned to compensate you with resources, but by the looks of it, you aren’t short on them, so we’ll have to make it up to you through other means…” Kesha licked her lips, “How about letting me keep you company for few nights? Any position works…”

“Hmm! Let’s talk about this another time…” Leylin laughed and changed the topic.

“Hmph! You’re still as boring as ever!” Kesha shook her head regretfully, “On Freya’s end, she’s here to ask a favour of you, hoping to make a trade with you!”

“A trade?” Leylin had his doubts, and instantly recalled the previous incident at the trading hall.

“Not that kind of trade! Of course, if Lord Leylin is willing to sell his seed, I will offer a high price!” Freya giggled with her hand over her mouth.

“I don’t have any plans in this area just yet!” Leylin said with a straight face, realising that speaking to these women was indeed very tiring.

As though afraid to anger Leylin and cause the trade to fall through later, Freya was very obedient and didn’t dare tease him.

“Actually, I’m offering a high price for a certain material that you possess.”

“Which material?” Leylin put his guard up in a split second.

“Bloodline crystals!” Freya took a deep breath and looked at Leylin expectantly.

“Oh, that!” A look of understanding flashed in Leylin’s eyes. Bloodline crystals had the potential to strengthen bloodlines, and even had the powerful effect of purifying them. Although they did not have much effect on Leylin, a Warlock whose bloodline was already purified to its limit, it was a priceless treasure to Freya whose family’s bloodline was showing signs of degradation.

“But… how did you know about them?” Although the question was posed to Freya, Leylin’s eyes were fixated on Kesha.

Under Leylin’s gaze, Kesha couldn’t help but feel uncomfortable, before sitting up and saying arrogantly, “That’s right! I told her. You still have leftover bloodline crystals from the time when you performed the exchange with Mentor, right? You don’t have any family, so you don’t need them urgently. On the other hand, Freya is a good friend of mine, and the price she’s willing to pay will definitely satisfy you!”

Leylin stroked his chin. What he handed out on the Black Scale previously was only a portion of his possessions. He still had a secret stash of a few pieces in his spatial ring.

Of course, this was done on purpose for Gilbert to see. Otherwise, even a regular human would be suspicious of such a generous student.

There was no way sly old Duke Gilbert would believe him to be without a trace of selfishness, especially as a Magus.

Thankfully, everything went as Leylin had expected. Although Gilbert knew that Leylin had a stash in his spatial ring, he didn’t pursue the matter, and instead was more assured.

Leylin’s secret stash was not tempting enough for Gilbert.

From the looks of it, Gilbert didn’t care about it, but that didn’t mean that other high-rank Warlocks didn’t. He must have been spreading the news, or else Kesha would not have known either.

“Bloodline crystals… I still have one remaining piece, but you should be very clear of its value. How much can you pay for it?” Leylin muttered, tapping his finger on the table rhythmically, as though struggling with the thought.

In actual fact, he had already decided to sell off all the materials he had shown, or else many people would have their eye on these items.

This time, it was Kesha and Freya, who were close to him. In the future, however, if crazier people like Miranda or Senior Lucian came over, what should he do?

Freya and Kesha exchanged looks of joy.

As long as they were willing to offer a price, everything would be settled. Their families had profound backgrounds and possessed much that was enticing to Leylin. Since Freya had made special preparations before coming, the items must be even more tempting.

“A set of the Hydro and Crystal Phase spell formations that have been passed down the generations in our family. They can increase the success rate when compressing your spiritual force by 10%!” Freya’s first sentence made Leylin’s eyes light up.

The compression spell formations inherited by such high-ranked Warlocks could not be compared to the normal goods exchanged in the Trading Hall of the Ouroboros Clan.

Furthermore, the other party was also a Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock, so the spell formations developed would be even more appropriate for bloodline Warlocks.

“That’s not enough!” Leylin kept a straight face.

“And this!” Freya pushed a red box before Leylin.

The box was small and had a grainy wooden texture, likely made from some bark. A loop of fiery red energy particles surfaced on the box, forming multiple seal patterns.

“What?!” Leylin furrowed his brows and blew lightly on the box.

*Whoosh!* Powerful yet fine black darkness elemental energy particles whizzed by, and the seal on the box started to disintegrate, tearing apart inch by inch.

“As strong as a Crystal Phase Magus!” Kesha gasped in awe, “The amplification from your Magus Tower is really terrifying!”

Freya was also shocked. She had purposely left the seal on the box as it was, with the intention of testing the waters, but it looked like Leylin’s abilities in his Magus Tower were far beyond her expectations.

As a matter of fact, within the amplification boundaries of the Magus Tower, Leylin could not only display strength comparable to a Crystal Phase Magus, but could even manipulate the energy particles in the positive and negative energy reactive pools to replenish what had been depleted. His magic power was endless.

If any average Crystal Phase Magus were to enter, they would waste all their spiritual force against him.

It could be said that within the range of his own Magus Tower, the only ones that struck fear in Leylin were Morning Star Magi.

In response to the exclamations made by the two women, Leylin’s expression did not change, as he opened the box.

At the bottom of the box was a thick layer of soft, pure white velvet.

And right in the centre of the velvet cloth was a red octagonal gemstone. A few intricate gold runes were swirling around in the jewel, much like tadpoles.

[Hall’s Jewel. Rarity: One of the three ancient wondrous items. Has the ability to greatly boost the compression of a bloodline Warlock’s spiritual force, and can increase the success rate of advancement to the Hydro Phase by 50%.]

The A.I. Chip swiftly transmitted the corresponding information to Leylin’s brain.

‘It’s actually Hall’s Jewel!’ Leylin was unable to mask his excitement. ‘Haven’t these materials been lost since ancient times?’

With this gemstone, coupled with the Hydro Phase spell formation, his spiritual force would naturally enter the Hydro Phase without a bottleneck once he had sufficient spiritual force.

It was obvious how important this object would be to him.

Leylin took a glance at his condition that was presented in his consciousness.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 3 Warlock (Vapour Phase). Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 23.6, Agility: 20.1, Vitality: 39.1, Spiritual force, 251.7; Magic power: 251(Magic Power synchronized with spiritual force)]

‘The minimum spiritual force required to enter the Hydro Phase is estimated to be around 300!’ Leylin recalled the statistics he had obtained from many simulated experiments through the A.I. Chip.

‘And with the Lamia fingerbone, if I artificially strengthen my bloodline, the rate of increase of my spiritual force wouldn’t be too slow either, and I may attain it in a few decades!’

The two obstacles in a Magus’ progress would be accumulating spiritual force and breaking through the bottleneck.

Now that the problem of a bottleneck had already been solved by Freya, what’s left was to slowly accumulate spiritual force. How could this not be a cause for joy?

Although Leylin tried to keep a straight face, Freya managed to catch a glimpse of happiness flicker across his face.

“It seems that Sir Leylin has taken a great liking to this item!” she smiled sweetly.

“Yes, the Hall’s Jewel is enough to make any Vapour Phase Magus go crazy!” Leylin nodded.

“If it’s appropriate to ask, may I know where you found it? The Hall’s Jewel should have been wiped out with the extinction of the Sea of Gemstones!” Leylin stated his doubts.

“The Sea of Gemstones did vanish a long time ago, but it still existed in ancient times!” Freya smiled in response, “As long as you find more ruins from ancient times, it is still possible to find these gemstones.”

‘So this was the aim of their previous expedition…’ Thinking about how they returned full of severe injuries previously, and how even the Second Elder was forced to take action, Leylin felt his scalp go numb, and the gemstone even heated up.

“I initially wanted to give it to you without any conditions, but…” Freya expressed her regret, but Leylin was secretly afraid.

Thankfully, he owned something that she wanted, or else he would have a hard time deciding if he should accept the Hall’s Jewel should she have really sent it over as a present.

Once he took the bait, the other party would tempt him with more benefits in the future, landing him in a trap until he willingly married into her family.

Sadly, in the history of Magi, many with shockingly excellent inherent skills but yet without a background or much status were enticed into marrying into other families in this manner.

Although both parties would be satisfied in the end, Leylin was different from them.

Chapter 444: Century

After settling the troublesome matters, Leylin’s life sank into complete serenity.

Everyday, other than meditating at fixed times and using the Lamia fingerbone’s radiation to mature his own bloodline, he was cooped up in the laboratory. He had already completely recovered the information on bloodline combinations. Besides that, he would patrol his territory and mentor Snoopy on occasion.

Such peaceful days were hard to come by. With the passage of time, his strength was slowly increasing, and was something worthy of rejoicing over.

Before anyone knew it, Leylin’s authority had been firmly set in place in his territory. The gigantic Onyx Castle towered on this piece of land, becoming the nucleus of power in this world. With the years rolling by, it left its mark on history.

Apart from being indestructible, the castle now had some history to it, which was something only the castles of true nobility could accumulate.

The only constant was the huge Magus Tower nearby, its everlasting glow seemingly eternal.

Inside the tower, Leylin lay on a huge experimental desk half-naked, his firm muscles visible. A few robotic arms were holding a translucent crystal ball above him, releasing blood-red rays that swept across his body. His eyes were closed, as if trying to sense something.

If one looked through the surface of the crystal ball, they could faintly see a milky-white fingerbone suspended at the center of the crystal ball, emanating a mysterious light.

The entire process lasted for a total of two hours before the robotic arms retreated back into their valves. Leylin then opened his eyes.

However, his pupils had now turned amber, still containing an ominous glint.

The moment he opened his eyes, the tools in front of him all became ash-grey, turning into stone. The alarms from various apparatus began to ring unceasingly.

Leylin lowered his head, deep in thought, ‘The bloodline is too rich… that can be a problem as well.’

When he raised his head once more, the amber in his eyes had faded, instead replaced by a pair of bottomless black pupils.Yellow skin rustled as he tore a layer of his body and threw it aside.

The skin still had fluids and traces left behind by the scales.

Leylin continued to tear off his dead skin, as though he was a molting like a snake.

“This is already the third time I’m undergoing molting!” Leylin looked at the molted skin as helplessness flashed across his face.

Warlocks’ advancement was done through meditation and transforming the body, progressing towards becoming ancient creatures.

It could be said that the higher-ranked the Warlock was, the less human they would be. The same held true for Warlocks of the Ouroboros Clan.

Since Leylin’s bloodline was that of a Giant Kemoyin Serpent, he naturally would undergo molting periods in his growth. However, under the radiation of the Lamia fingerbone, the molting process had been greatly expedited.

“Tower genie, prepare warm water for my bath.” The tower genie acted quickly under Leylin’s order. Before he’d even reached the designated bathroom, steaming hot water had been prepared.

Water elemental particles had been condensed into a pure liquid, and had been made extremely suitable for the bodies and skin of Warlocks through specialised proportions.

Leylin lay contentedly in the bathing pool made of black marble. As he looked at his fair and smooth skin, his eyes faintly phased out.

Every single time he molted, his strength would see a rapid increase. The rate of his advancements recently had been truly terrifying.

Leylin looked at his palm. Who would have thought that these ordinary slender hands could hide such extraordinary power?

‘How time flies. This leisurely life of mine has gone on for a century now?’ Leylin sank into deep thought.

Indeed, nearly a hundred years had passed since his foray into the Forgotten Land.

Such a long period of time was enough for commoner families to have passed between four to five generations, yet all this did for Leylin was make him look more mature. Given his life expectancy as a high-ranked Warlock, he could be said to still be in his teens.

In this last century, Leylin had maintained a low-profile lifestyle, immersing himself in research and drawing links between his own knowledge base and that of the central continent. He had even reached the boundary in multiple areas.

The A.I. Chip’s data had also been updated several times.

[Leylin Farlier: Rank 3 (Hydro Phase) Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent; Strength: 30, Agility: 30, Vitality: 45.5, Spiritual force: 315.6, Magic Power: 315 (Magic power in synchronization with spiritual force)]

Through the Lamia fingerbone’s maturation of his bloodline, even without the consumption of spiritual force potions, Leylin’s spiritual force increased day by day, up to the point where he fulfilled the requirements to advance to the Hydro Phase.

20 years ago, Leylin had used the Hall’s Jewel and Hydro Phase spell formation to finally condense his spiritual force, breaking out of Hydro Phase.

There were, even more, merits to the maturation of his bloodline. His strength and agility, which had stagnated for a long time, experienced an exponential growth, while his vitality steadily increased as well.

Once both strength and agility reached 30, Leylin knew that even the Kemoyin Giant Serpent bloodline could not lead to an indefinite increase in these areas. This was probably his current limit.

Similarly, the increase in vitality from every consecutive molting was diminishing. It seemed like it, too, would slow to a crawl.

Leylin clenched his fists, feeling the surge of strength within. ‘Just the radiation from the Lamia fingerbone could bring about so many benefits,’ he muttered to himself as he felt the increase in power from the molting, his blood bursting with vitality.

Outside the bathroom, two pleasant voices similar to that of an oriole sounded, “Master, it’s time for lunch!”

Leylin smiled and exited the bathroom.

Two teenage girls in maid costumes were kneeling on the two sides of the bathroom. They showed not a tinge of bashfulness when he walked out stark naked, using a large white towel to dry him and dressing him in a loose robe.

It was clear that these two emitted energy waves unique to rank 1 Magi, and they possessed a special charm.

They were actually Warlocks! Even though they were only rank 1 and did not have a pure bloodline, they were still hard to come by.

They were Warlocks under Leylin’s guidance. The two were actually sisters who came from the same family tribe of Giant Mankestre Snake Warlocks. Due to the restrictions of their bloodlines, their position in the Ouroboros Clan was very low. Once Leylin had released news that he was hiring, the family had immediately sent these two sisters to serve him in his tower.

The Magus Tower was extremely dangerous. Even its living quarters had large amounts of radiation, and commoners would not be able to live on the premises. Only Magi were suited to stay within.

Leylin’s Magus Tower was naturally only open to a few of his acolytes and subordinates. Even though they were only given access to the living areas and a few laboratories, it was more than enough for them to be moved to tears.

“Mentor!”

In the dining hall, Leylin saw Snoopy. That kid had already advanced to become a rank 2 Warlock. For his Black Horrall Snake bloodline and meager natural aptitude, it was considered a great feat.

“Mmm!” Leylin nodded his head lightly and sat at the head of the table. The two twin sisters immediately served delicious food.

“How’s the cleanup of the library going?” Leylin asked Snoopy while eating.

During the organisation and influx of books into the library, Leylin had noticed Snoopy’s passion for them and decided to just hand the entire place over for him to manage.

“It’s going well! Only area B-3 has experienced some mild oxidation, but I’ve already asked the tower genie to isolate the region and deal with it.” he humbly answered.

“Also, the captives locked up in the experimental areas have become more irritable, and the rate of energy consumption of the binding rooms has risen by 1.9%…” This next bit caught Leylin’s attention.

After lunch, he went to the basement of the Magus Tower.

*Boom! Pow!* The intermittent noises he heard after entering the area caused him to frown.

He came to the area outside the binding room. Through the reinforced glass, he could see a large red-eyed Kobold. Large amounts of drool were dripping from his mouth as he rammed his head into the walls repeatedly.

Every time he did that, a thick blue electric current would shoot at the Kobold’s body, burning its reddish-beige scaly exterior to a charred black.

Leylin frowned and ordered, “Retrieve its information!”

The tower genie projected a screen in front of Leylin’s eyes. The densely-packed words and figures of the surgical journal and surveillance footage were laid out in front of him.

‘After the initial bloodline strengthening experiment, symptoms of hysteria appeared on the eighth day?’ Leylin stroked his chin.

“This Kobold has no more observational value. Get rid of it and send its carcass to the dissection room!”

“Authority verified! Getting rid of the Kobold!” The tower genie answered without emotion. After all, it had been programmed to put Leylin’s orders as the first priority.

*Swish!* A black light streaked across the sky, and the hysterical Kobold that was confined immediately fell to the ground.

In the blink of an eye, this terrifying Kobold, who had been so close to reaching rank 3, completely perished, without being able to put up a fight at all.

The prison gates then opened, and a few adamantine puppets carried the lifeless Kobold carcass out on a stretcher.

Chapter 445: Precipitation and Strength

After seeing what happened, the Kobolds bound in the center huddled up together, fearful of the demonic Leylin.

Looking at the fear in their eyes, Leylin nodded his head, “The rest of the experiments look alright!”

The fear represented sanity, which meant they were still worth keeping alive. These Kobolds being here was naturally Tanasha’s handiwork.

After receiving Leylin’s order, not only had she collected a large amount of high-grade Kobold blood, she had even captured a group of captives and sent them to Leylin.

In the midst of working on Quicksand’s bloodline experiments, Leylin gladly accepted these gifts with pleasure and used them in his research.

Right now, the results were rather positive.

Leylin looked at the rest who were bound in the center. Their general was well-built at over two metres of solid muscle covered with a dense layer of scales. The horn on his head was also thick and bulky.

“I did not expect the rumors about the Kobolds possessing the giant dragon bloodline to be true after all…” Leylin took out a tube of golden blood from his pouch.

The tube of blood carried a powerful aura. Even the cowering Kobolds who were covering their heads in the corner raised their head unanimously and looked at the tube in his hands, their eyes filled with desire.

“The quintessential bloodline of the Ancient Red Dragon!” Leylin gasped. As long as he was willing to give up this ancient bloodline, with the high-grade meditation technique of Dragon King’s Mystic Might that he’d obtained in the subterranean world, he could have turned any of the Kobolds into a terrifying first generation Dragon bloodline Warlock in a flash.

But before he’d conducted more research on methods of restriction, such a thing would be equivalent to Leylin creating unnecessary trouble for himself, which he didn’t want.

Even though his bloodline was already finalized, the experiments of the ancient Quicksand Organisation did inspire him tremendously.

For instance, one of the fields he was interested in was the ignition of another bloodline to strengthen himself. He had constantly paid attention to that area of research.

Upon confirming that all the hubbub was raised by that one crazed Kobold, Leylin soon left the place and reached the experimental area for spells.

After molting, he urgently needed to train his control of his powers.

The Magus Tower’s spell experimental area was built with the strongest alloy, and had specialized registers and targets for testing. The strength and durability was high enough to withstand any spell at rank 3 or below.

“Beginning with rank 1 innate spell, Kemoyin’s Scales…” Leylin’s entire body was soon covered with exquisite black scales, this time slightly differing from before. Multiple decorative designs extended across them to form a symbol. The outer layer had another bright membrane on top, forming a second layer of defense.

This was the advantage of an innate spell. When a Magus attained enough power, their innate spell would improve with them and become stronger, displaying the power and effects of higher-grade spells.

The same went for the bloodline inherited spells of Warlocks. The stronger the bloodline, the greater the amplification of the innate spell’s power.

“Initiation of test!” The tower genie hovered next to Leylin

Ever since he had the tower genie, Leylin had allocated most of the A.I Chip’s tasks to the tower genie instead. The freed-up processing power of the A.I Chip were then accumulated and used by Leylin to be spent on deducing more important tasks.

The elemental rays dazzled. Numerous elemental particles appeared and coagulated, ready for attack.

It started with the commonly seen earth, fire, and water elemental attacks. After which, there were attacks by special light and darkness elemental particles, followed by various fused spells.

Lightning, hail, blades of wind, and balls of fire all burst onto Leylin’s body, their power unceasingly rising.

*Buzz buzz!* A black radiance emitted from the Kemoyin scales and formed a layer of defence around Leylin’s body, which had repelled those frightening attacks.

The violent energy particles had a sustained attack of ten minutes or so. After which, the tower genie’s voice intonated once again, “Spell resistance test completed. Physical defense test initiated.”

The moment the words were spoken, the attacking spells vanished and the ground crackled as it split apart to reveal an entry valve. Adamantine puppets appeared from within, wielding huge steel swords, hatchets, heavy hammers, and other large weapons. They started attacking Leylin.

For the next half hour, an unceasing rumbling could be heard.

The tower genie flapped its invisible wings as it flew towards Leylin and reported, “Kemoyin’s Scales defense test completed!”

A numerical report was then clearly projected forth.

[Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock rank 1 innate spell — Kemoyin’s Scales (Augmented: Rank 3) Spell Resistance: 160 degrees. Physical Resistance: 175 degrees.]

“With this sort of resistance, I’m basically immune to the common rank 2 spells,“ Leylin nodded with extreme pleasure.

Next was the testing for the Eye of Petrification and Toxic Bile. After comparison, the degree of power of the Eye of Petrification had reached the apex of rank 2, although there wasn’t any other strengthening of the foundation.

On the other hand, Toxic Bile’s terrifying poison attack had quietly crept passed its boundary and reached the rank 3 realm.

“This bloodline strengthening has benefitted me so much!” Witnessing his own innate spells getting more powerful, Leylin couldn’t help but sigh in pleasure.

For an average Warlock, they depended on their own bloodline to spur on their advancements to the next level, whereas for him, he had advanced too soon in the past and his Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline couldn’t keep pace with his strength. This had resulted in a lack of advancements in his rank 1 and 2 spells.

And now? He had finally caught up with the other Warlocks who had progressed over many years, enabling his innate spells to match, if not exceed, theirs!

After testing several of his own innate spells, Leylin asked in silence, “A.I. Chip, how did the simulation go?”

[Rank 3 spell derivation progress currently at 98.9%!]

The A.I. Chip’s response was swift and got Leylin smiling, “It’s almost done! At the current rate of progress, it’ll only take a short while to completely derive the spell!”

Although rank 3 spell models were very valuable, Leylin had gotten his hands on quite a few. As he recalled his previous battles, he realised the same problem recurring.

Although he had many tricks up his sleeve, the majority of his battles had him dependent on a combination of potions, spells and the Meteor Sword to successfully defeat his opponent.

It may have seemed straightforward, but in reality, if the other party had surpassed him in any one of those factors, he would’ve found it difficult to succeed.

To put it simply, he lacked a sure-fire killing move.

Such a strategy could arise from a huge demonic weapon, an earth-shatteringly powerful spell or a deadly potion. However, Leylin realised, he had no such thing on hand.

Manufacturing a huge demonic weapon would be way too troublesome. The same went for a deadly potion. There were material costs and they had limitations to them. As such, after much deliberation, he decided to bring forward the A.I. Chip’s derivation of a powerful spell, which was tailored for him.

In order to see this matter to completion, Leylin gave his full attention and had stopped himself from many other missions. He even had the tower genie share the burden of the A.I. Chip. He wanted to maximize the use of the the A.I. Chip’s processing power.

As such, everything had progressed smoothly.

“According to the latest estimates, this new spell will have at least 300 degrees of power. Common Crystal Phase Magi will not dare underestimate me, and it’ll be useful enough below the Morning Star realm…” At this juncture, the light faded from Leylin’s eyes and was replaced by a hint of gloom.

In his previous expedition to the Forgotten Land, they had offended the Morning Star Magus, Demon Hunter Cyril. Although Cyril didn’t declare any intentions to seek revenge, there were many rank 3 Magi who wanted to get in his good books, and quite a few of them were at the Hydro and even Crystal Phases.

Therefore, under such tremendous pressure, Leylin had withdrawn and holed himself in his territory for a long time, coming out only when necessary.

Every once in while, there would be a few ignorant trespassers who would gallantly cross the border. They were almost always discovered immediately and brought to Leylin. Under the amplification of his strength by the Magi Tower, Leylin had powers parallel to that of rank 3 Magi. As a result, he managed to defeat the few trespassing Magi easily, the deaths of those Magi affording him some bit of reputation.

Over time, fewer and fewer Magi tried to trespass.

Additionally, with the ability to deduce spells, Leylin’s confidence soared. Relying on those trump cards, he could fight on par with Crystal Phase Magi without relying on the tower. He felt that the time was right.

Truth be told, it was frustrating for Leylin to be cooped up for close to a hundred years in a single territory.

‘Before this, I’m afraid I would still have to make a trip to the Ouroboros Clan to see if there’s anything profitable for me. Phew, astral stone…’ Leylin plotted in his mind, and could not help but sigh again.

Normally, once one had their own Magus Tower and had been promoted to Hydro phase, they would have the ability to conduct early-stage experiments on the astral gates independently. Unfortunately, Leylin had not taken any actions for a long time to come. The only reason behind that was because he lacked the key ingredient, the astral stone.

It was the base material for the construction of an astral gate, and at the same time a core battling resource held by Morning Star Magi. They were rarely circulated in public, and required a trade with other rare or valuable items.

At the moment, Leylin did not have the connections to carry out such exchanges. In fact, Leylin could not even make up his mind even for the trading of mundane objects.

It was not due to the fact that he did not have enough enticing treasures to put forth, but that many of the objects he possessed were better off not being exposed to others. For instance, the essence of the ancient red dragon bloodline and the yield from the Blood Vulture’s Nest.

He could have easily exchanged any of these objects for astral stones. However, he could also have attracted unnecessary attention from other Morning Star Magi. Leylin had enough trouble from provoking the Demon Hunter, he certainly did not want any more eyes on him.

On the other hand, Kesha had secretly been in touch with Leylin and had informed him on an arrangement for astral stones. He looked forward to it eagerly.

Chapter 449: A Test

An incorporeal ‘death-god’ had solemnly descended on the rebel camp.

On the ground, innumerable rank 1 and 2 Magi started collapsing with their acolytes in tow, dying despite multiple layers of protection, potions, magic artifacts and other defenses.

Even the surrounding buildings were not spared. They creaked and swayed as they crumbled down like sand faced with water.

Formless toxic ripples took aim at the three rank 3 Magi in the air and started attacking them, leaving them helpless as they watched their apprentices and the other members of their organisations fall.

With a single attack, except for a handful of Magi who managed to escape using their secret treasures, the rest had been turned into corpses that decayed rapidly.

“YOU!” Toram roared as she rushed ahead.

The terrifying power of a Kemoyin Warlock’s toxic attacks was common knowledge. However, Leylin’s ability had reached a level that allowed him to exterminate nearly everything on the ground, which was abnormal.

This attack of his was sudden and unexpected, which resulted in huge losses. Witnessing the deaths of their own apprentices, friends, and even families at Leylin’s hands, the two other rank 3 Magi hardened their gazes and dashed forward with tearful eyes.

“Phantom Hologram!” Multiple phantoms of gigantic creatures started appearing from behind an old rank 3 Magus. They surrounded Leylin and opened their huge, ferocious, and menacing mouths to trap him in their midst.

“Crimson Throne!” An illusory image of a bloody red throne appeared behind Toram, emanating a strong stench of blood.

The throne was simple and unadorned dull gold with marks on it from various swords and hatchets. It seemed as if it had gone through a lot of trials and tribulations, giving it an almost lifelike appearance of cruelty.

Under the illusory throne, the three of them donned a red armour, their auras having been raised to a level.

“Hmm! Aura amplification and removal of suppression… so such spell models exist!” Leylin’s blue eyes sparkled with excitement. He diligently recorded the opposite party’s domain into the A.I. Chip, intending to research it further.

This was the characteristic of the incomplete domain of a rank 3 Magus. Once Toram completely comprehended the strength of this domain, she would step into the Morning Star realm.

Of course, the current Crimson Throne only provided a limited amplification to Toram and the rest. It could not compare to Leylin’s own Intimidating Gaze.

However, under the brilliant glow of the throne, the eyes of the huge phantoms became bloodshot, and they dashed towards Leylin with full force, not an ounce of hesitation in them.

“Such a weak retaliation! Toram, I’ll be utterly disappointed if this is all you have…” Leylin sighed. The terrifying energy undulations from his body overflowed as the terrifying innate spell of a rank 3 Kemoyin Warlock, Intimidating Gaze, enveloped the region.

*Hiss Hiss!* It seemed as though an ancient Giant Kemoyin Serpent had been reborn in all its savagery. A tyrannical surge of dark energy descended on the ground, bringing with it a rather unusual and wild aura.

The force field immediately took over the territory previously under the Crimson Throne, almost instantly countering its effects.

Even though Leylin had suppressed the energy on his body, his abilities had been exposed to the huge phantoms and they went absolutely crazy, as if they had seen something horrifyingly bizarre. They roared in confusion, brutally attacking one another and even sprinting towards their original owner.

“Oh! A nice chance to witness the effects of the confusion!” Watching the opposing Magi fumbling about, Leylin smiled indifferently.

His innate domain had been steadily strengthened by the Lamia fingerbone, something that extended to the regions of energy amplification and suppression. If not for the fact that he’d experienced the bending of rules by a true Morning Star Magus’ domain, he would’ve thought that his had already been formed.

Still, even if it was a mere force field, its effects were already unimaginable.

The phantom image of the Crimson Throne started to retreat in defeat, as if stripped of its previous glory. And before the two other rank 3 Magi could retaliate, their force fields had been suppressed and defeated.

Toram was the only one who qualified to match Leylin in a collision of force fields.

As for those lower-level force fields used by the others, they could certainly not match those of these Hydro Phase Magi.

Due to the differing depth of understanding of a domain at different levels, there was a vast difference in their strengths. Thus, the force fields of Magi below the Hydro Phase were considered effectively useless.

The Magus with the tiger skull wore a look of defeat. He understood and admitted the huge disparity between Leylin and himself.

Yet, he roared ferociously, the muscles in his body tensing and swelling up as his gorgeous fur shone with a colourful radiance.

The joints on his bones popped loudly and soon his body swelled and expanded from a normal figure to a hulking three meters.

“You punk! I’m going to kill you! I will break your bones one by one, inch by inch without mercy!” He roared thunderously and delivered a high intensity punch, as strong gusts of wind hit him right in his face. The surrounding air seemed to have been so compressed by this punch that it became a substantial crystal body which surged towards Leylin like a projectile.

“A human Magus with a reinforced body, what a rare sight!”

Leylin became serious, growing cautious of the man. Magi with reinforced bodies were known to belong to the barbarian beast clan. As for other types of Magi, they would generally be glad to use spells for the destructions of enemies.

As such, seeing how the tiger skull Magus transformed himself into such a powerful creature, he was sure there were some in the central continent that could do it, although it would be rare.

Generally speaking, Magi did not place much emphasis on strength and agility. Instead valuing the quality of the physical form more, as the corporeal body was the part that bore the foundations of any magic power.

Also, different Warlocks inherited different abilities from their elders, hence it highly depended on which area each ancestor placed their emphasis on. Leylin understood this and strived to polish all factors of strength and agility in himself to the maximum.

“Heh!” In a rush of excitement, Leylin drew his Meteor Sword and skillfully exhibited his cross blade techniques.

“Cross-blade Slash!” A big black cross shone and sliced through the sky, carrying with it terrifying Kemoyin toxins. The projectile shattered to tiny bits in the air, even as the aftermath traveled towards the enraged tiger skull Magus.

“Awooooo!” The tiger skull Magus covered his head with both hands and dashed forward.

*Crackle !* The sound of breaking glass could be heard as the gorgeous colourful shine from the tiger skull Magus burst forth in a flash and collided head on with the black cruciform, smashing it into a million pieces.

*Zzzz!* A slight tear appeared on his arm, and from it one could hear faint sounds of something decaying as white smoke arose.

Without hesitation, the tiger skull Magus dashed towards Leylin in a moment.

“Very high vitality indeed!” To be able to withstand the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s poison, other than possessing excellent spell resistance, one’s vitality needed to be at least a hundred points and above.

In addition, the opposite side’s strength and agility had exceeded his own value of 30 by leaps and bounds. Seeing how he was able to use simple techniques to deal deadly blows, Leylin’s eyes brightened.

“Die now!” The right arm of the tiger skull Magus had morphed into a huge tiger claw, striking down on Leylin.

The huge tiger claw looked like a small millstone. The shiny sharp claw was glossy and menacing, with spell runes visible in the brilliant light it emitted.

*Bang!* The tiger claw was stopped abruptly mid-air by a palm.

Although Leylin’s build was tall and lanky, when compared to the tiger-headed creature, he was rather petite and his palm was equivalent to that of a baby.

Yet, it was this insignificant palm which had managed to tame the sharp tiger claw, disabling his ability to advance forward.

“How can that be?” The old man yelped in surprise. He had just defeated his phantoms a distance away.

He was absolutely certain of his friend’s strength.

The tiger skull Magus had mercilessly killed a rank 3 creature in this beastly state.

Even when he recalled it now, it had been shocking. Yet, a full attack from his friend had been blocked by a single palm, something that made no sense. What’s more, looking at the opposite party, it seemed to be effortless.

“Even for a Warlock, it is not possible to possess such terrifying power, unless you are a also a Magus who practices body reinforcement techniques?” The old man scrutinized Leylin, trying to analyze but unable to read him.

“How… How is that possible ?” Other than the shocked old man, the tiger skull Magus was speechless himself.

He had been extremely confident in his ability. Even in the face of several magic alloys put up by other Magi, he only needed to use his claw and they would have cracked and crumbled like soft sand. But now…

“There is nothing that is not possible!” Leylin tightened his grip, and cracking sounds rang out as the tiger skull Magus’ arm twisted abruptly into an odd, distorted curve.

“The difference between humans and animals lies in the usage of your strengths, be it for exploitation or as a tool. If you do not even know this, regardless of how strong you are, you are just a fool!” Leylin looked at the whimpering tiger skull Magus and he felt a tinge of pity.

Behind him, the black shadows of two arms appeared, attaching to his right hand and injecting a steady flow of energy into it.

Although Leylin’s strength was only thirty degrees of power, he could use his spells to break through that limit and massively increase his strength for a short period of time.

After all, his innate character was that of a Magus, not a competitive knight.

“Those who cannot keep up with the times, you will be abandoned like trash!” Leylin heaved a sigh, grabbed the tiger skull Magus’ arms, and raised him up.

“This is bad! We have to save Borgin!” The clash had happened too quickly. After all, both Leylin and the tiger skull Magus were agile, with at least 30 degrees of ability in that respect. From the initial assault, to Leylin drawing his sword, to the retaliation and counter-attack, everything had happened in a matter of seconds.

Even Toram did not have the chance to react, nor would she have expected Leylin to so easily defeat a rank 3 Magus.

“Shadowflame Plague!” Leylin was not going to show any mercy. He was completely ready to take everyone out.

A scarlet-black wall of fire appeared and, in a flash, the two rank 3 Magi that had charged forward were drowned in its blaze.

Chapter 450: Seal of the Dark Corrosion

The corrosive black flames were like a chasm which separated Toram from the rest.

As for the other rank 3 Magus? The flames had inflicted him with heavy injuries, and he had escaped to the side while letting out blood-curdling screams.

”What… What are you trying to do?” At that moment, the tiger skull Magus was truly terrified. He felt the increasingly horrifying strength emitting from both of Leylin’s hands, and the savage spiritual force which had sealed his sea of consciousness. For the first time, he felt terror from the bottom of his heart.

He began to regret not escaping immediately upon Leylin’s arrival. Because of that, he had landed himself in his current circumstances.

”What I’m trying to do?” Leylin’s lips curled up. Shadow arms emerged from his back in rapid succession. Enormous muscles emerged indistinctively, and fused onto both of Leylin’s hands.

*Creak! Creak!* First, the skin ruptured, then the muscles, then the bones.

The tiger skull Magus had a twisted expression, and was in so much pain that he could not even make a sound. His entire being seemed to have been stretched apart by Leylin.

”Let him go! Wait! NOOOOO….” Amidst Toram’s blood-curdling screams, the tiger skull Magus was ripped into two. Large amounts of bloodshed could be seen everywhere.

”Don’t you think it’s too late to say these things only now?” Leylin expertly avoided the blood, a skill he’d acquired from experience. His body had not even been tainted by a smidgen of it.

As if tossing out the garbage, he threw away the two segments of the corpse before turning towards Toram, his face emotionless. “You should have come to your senses before you decided to rebel against the Ouroboros Clan!”

”You’ll perish here today! This is my promise to Borgin!” Toram’s face instantly calmed down. Still, Leylin could very distinctively see the desire for vengeance in her eyes.

This was not a hot-blooded vengeance that arose merely from this one incident. It was rather a collective response to the extended period during which they were hunted down like prey. Many of Toram’s friends and family presumably died amidst the massacres conducted by the Ouroboros Clan, and Leylin’s actions earlier had fully evoked her wrath.

”Even now, you refuse to learn!” Leylin shook his head.

”Currently, you don’t seem to be fit to be my opponent. Let me give you a hand!” Just as he finished these words, a Magus dressed in a black robe, who looked identical to Leylin, suddenly emerged before the rank 3 Magus who had been seriously injured by the Arm of Vengeance.

A few multi-coloured potions were thrown out by “Leylin”, as he kept a straight face. They collided in mid-air and emitted terrifying energy ripples.

”Rank 3 potion combination spell— Divine Prairie Flames!”

The endless flames instantly swallowed the rank 3 Magus, even spreading so far as to include the “Leylin” in the area of effect.

”Leylin” who was surrounded by the many flames suddenly laughed hysterically, and morphed into many shadow chains that confined the rank 3 Magus in the flames.

”Master Toram! Save me!” The rank 3 Magus’ face was full of dejection. He did all he could to seek help, and him looking to Toram for help was his last hope.

But Leylin had blocked Toram’s path, and mercilessly dashed that last hope.

”You must be the only high-ranked Magus left in the stronghold now?” Leylin looked to Toram after the rank 3 Magus’ life aura had completely dissipated in the sea of fire.

”If you don’t use your remaining time to make me happy during our battle, I’m afraid I’ll continue to hunt down and kill all the other Magi below!”

”That female Magus must be your apprentice? The two of you might even be related by blood. Don’t even think about lying to me. Both the bloodline ripples on your bodies and the spiritual force frequency have revealed your relationship…” Leylin shot a glance at one of the corpses lying around, and what he said caused Toram’s facial expression to change.

Just when Leylin’s gaze shot across the area, the female Magus with a childlike face who had been lying behind the remains felt as if she was stared at by a fierce ancient creature. Her limbs began to shake uncontrollably.

”It’s… It’s too terrifying!” Upon realising that she had been discovered, the female Magus tried to escape.

A light green wind dissipated from her body and carried her to the depths of Doray Forest.

”Other than Nina, even Master Borgin has….” As she started to sprint, tears streamed down her face.

At the instant when Leylin had released his deadly attack, the low-ranked Magi were all exterminated. Other than the three rank 3 Magi, almost everyone else had instantly perished.

No antidotes or defensive runes had any effect on the attack. Before the terrifying toxins of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, everyone else was feeble and weak.

Toram’s innate defensive spells had not in the least bit affected Leylin’s attack. If not for the protective charm she’d obtained from her mentor, she would have perished as well.

The female Magus that was lucky enough to survive had hidden herself behind a wall, witnessing Leylin’s cruelty and terror. The two powerful rank 3 Magi had perished at his hands one by one, and from the looks of it, Leylin had not even unleashed his full power. Now, he was even using her life to threaten her mentor!

After hearing her mentor’s hurried whisper, the female Magus could not take it anymore, and started sobbing out loud.

Even so, the energy particles below her feet had not once stopped shining, as if escaping from that area was instinctive.

In the depths of her subconscious, she did not want to return to face the horrifying monster anymore.

”That’s not too bad of a suggestion! Looks like you care for her a lot!” Leylin watched as the rank 1 Magus escaped, with no intentions of giving chase.

On the contrary, he turned to Toram who was ahead of him, and a taunting expression flashed across his face. “However, I’m afraid you’ll have to try to buy time. If not, she won’t be able to make much headway…”

”Lunatic! Monster!” Toram cursed. A majority of Warlocks had anger management issues, something that was only exacerbated by battle.

Compared to Magi, Warlocks prefered to ruin their opponents or even vent their desires upon them.

Toram had previously witnessed similar scenarios. It was painful to see dead Magi, and many female Magi subjected to horrible violations.

And now, she thought of Leylin in the same light as those crazy Warlocks.

”Even if I have to put everything on the line, I will stop you at all costs!” Toram announced as she ripped the silver necklace off her neck with eyes full of determination.

”Haha! Excellent! That’s the mindset!” At that instant, Leylin felt like the big villain from the movies of his previous life.

”Seal of Dark Corrosion! Release!” Toram performed some gestures and, in that instant, the silver necklace exploded.

In a flash, the energy waves on her body strengthened significantly. Drops of blood even started seeping out of her pores.

The detailed black runes instantly crawled all over her body. Coupled with the scar on her face, she looked even more terrifying.

Leylin could sense that she’d already reached the peak of the Hydro Phase. In fact, some of her spiritual force had already formed traces of crystals from repeated attempts at compression.

Once completely solidified, Toram would reach the Crystal Phase.

Of course, her rash actions put her in grave danger. However, right before her body completely fell apart, she’d stepped one foot into the Crystal Phase realm!

This was definitely her trump card, some sort of mysterious spell that would put everything at stake.

Strangely, Leylin did not try to stop Toram’s actions, instead allowing the aura on her body to rise slowly as he let out a hearty laugh, ”Haha… Good! Indeed, with this sort of mysterious spell, you won’t disappoint me!”

From the very beginning, the entire reason why Leylin had adopted such abusive methods was to force Toram to use a spell that would exhaust her vitality and allow her to temporarily increase her strength.

Although he’d accepted it as a task from the organisation, he also intended to experiment with his newly developed rank 3 spell— Fatality’s Tip.

Even though its ability to break through the defensive spell formation spoke volumes of its formidability, he ultimately lacked the physical data to affirm its full capability. Especially with regards to its ability to clash with Crystal Phase Magi, something that engendered his resentment.

He had discovered that with his strength, he was the best of the best among Hydro Phase Magi, and even a peak Hydro Phase Magus like Toram could do nothing to him. Only a Crystal Phase opponent would cause him trouble.

And the A.I. Chip lacked data specifically regarding Crystal Phase Magi. Given the fact that Leylin would have to deal with Magi of that rank, he desperately needed a standard to measure his own capabilities.

And now, Toram had become such a standard.

When he’d probed her during the previous battle, the A.I. Chip had detected that not only had her strength become feeble, she had even seemed to be injured, something that resulted in her not performing to her fullest potential.

And so Leylin took such drastic measures to compel his opponent, to incite her her will to live on so as to battle him.

And from the looks of it, he’d achieved his goal.

Originally a peak Hydro Phase Magus, Toram indeed possessed the formidable ability to partially crystallise her spiritual force using this mysterious spell, even if she’d pay for it with her life.

It was rare to experience a fight against a Crystal Phase Magus. After all, the Crystal Phase Magi he’d previously come across were mostly his seniors, and he could not fight them.

Magi like Toram, who had a probability of losing control when they forcefully entered the Crystal Phase, were even more scarce.

Leylin immediately ordered: “A.I Chip, record this battle in detail!”

[Orders received! Scan scheduled!]

The A.I Chip intoned.

A pale blue screen was projected ahead of Leylin’s eyes, and Toram who was in the screen was engulfed by strong radiation.

The mysteries of Crystal Phase spiritual force were also slowly being uncovered by the A.I. Chip and presented to Leylin.

”The madmen of the Ouroboros Clan should not even exist in this world!” Having advanced to the Crystal Phase, Toram’s strength now was a far cry from what it was before.

Just the suppression of the aura in the atmosphere caused Leylin to feel discomfort.

Chapter 456: Wing of the Sun

Behind the introductions were several other rows, each describing the items following the first.

“…… Now, please allow me to present the first item of this year’s auction: a treasure produced from the Fiery World, the Fiery Gemstone!” The host announced loudly, lifting the gauze from the tray behind him at the same time.

*Boom!* In a flash, 3 pieces of translucent crystal emerged before Leylin’s eyes. An unceasing flame seemed to be burning in the cores of the crystals.

“Treasures from another plane!”

Numerous Magi gasped. In order to start off the auction successfully, the Azure Mountain auction house had indeed put in much effort. Evidently, the first auction item was unexpected for many of them.

“The Fiery Gemstone is rumoured to be a treasure of the central Blazing World. Containing heavily compressed fire elemental particles, it can help break through and upgrade a fire-attributed Magus’ spiritual endowments, and is even an essential item the advancements of many high-grade fire elemental meditation techniques…” the host continued.

However, very few spared the attention to listen to him anymore. They had all averted their rapacious gazes to the Fiery Gemstone on stage.

Even Leylin was slightly tempted by this item, leave alone the other Magi.

Resources from other planes, could only be obtained by Morning Star Magi due to the requirement for an astral gate. For rank 2 and rank 3 Magi like them, they were an inaccessible existence.

It’s small-degree spiritual endowment enhancing effects especially drove many of them crazy.

“Alright. Now we will begin the auction for the compressed blazing gemstones, with the starting bid at 5 million magic crystals!” The host reported a figure, which was soon drowned amongst a cacophony of bids.

Huge figures appeared on the screen, which was refreshed again and again with the highest quoted price.

Leylin speechlessly watched the numbers spike on the corner of the screen, exceeding ten million in a flash and going all the way up to around 50 million before slowing down. He could not help but smile bitterly.

“I originally thought that the more than 90 million magic crystals from the Azure Mountain auction house was already a large fund. Now it seems it will be really difficult to win the bid for the astral stone…”

Leylin extinguished all thoughts of pressing the bid button. Although he had many items that he could use as payment and winning the bid for the compressed blazing gemstone was not hard, it was too ostentatious. Furthermore, his funds were limited, they had to be saved for later and were not to be wasted on this.

Because he had already decided to give up, Leylin was able to relax and engrossedly watch the group of high-ranked Magi fight furiously over these treasures.

The value of otherworldly treasures still exceeded Leylin’s expectations. Not only were the VIPs in the VIP lounge going all out, even Magi seated at the regular auditorium began quoting prices to fight for the items as well.

“Possessing the financial ability to compete for the Fiery Gemstone yet withdrawn within the regular auditorium crammed with all those low-ranked Magi, he is also a rascal pretending to be weak!” Leylin looked at a red-haired youth and assessed monotonously.

“Bidding closed, the three people who quoted the highest price will obtain the rights of attribution to the Fiery Gemstone!” The host, who stood on the central elevated platform with a slightly flushed face, spoke with an obvious excitement.

Now, on the screen, the large figures stopped in a moment. The highest bid had reached a shocking 85 million magic crystals! The second and third highest bid merely differed from the first by not more than 1 million magic crystals.

“This is crazy!” Leylin shook his head.

Clearly, the quoted price this time had been overshot by a lot, even exceeding the original expectations of the auction house. The host calmed down and began introducing the next auction item, “Magic equipment – Aphopis’ Scepter! Starting bid: 38 million magic crystals or resources of equivalent worth…”

An entirely golden, magnificently crafted scepter instantly appeared within Leylin’s sight. At the head of the scepter, many gold tassels and decorations formed the shape of a sun’s corona, emitting light and heat continuously.

“40 million magic crystals!”

“50 million magic crystals, and 3 moonstones on top of that!”

Evidently, this piece of magic equipment was already renowned among this group of Magi. Even before the host finished speaking, the Magi below had already begun quoting prices.

Leylin rested his chin on his hands and as he watched, he suddenly felt that he was actually considered poor.

Compared to these central continent Magi who took possession of rich resources and had long-spanning inheritances, even if he plundered the entire Twilight Zone, he would still only be considered slightly rich.

If not for those few incidents of huge profit, and if he was not a Potions Grandmaster, he definitely would not have dared to participate in the auction for the astral stone.

Shortly after, the piece of magic equipment, Aphopis’ scepter, was bought by a Magus in the VIP lounge at a high price of 90 million magic crystals. Many Magi could not help but take note of the VIP lounge number.

The Azure Mountain auction was no doubt the top power in this area. What followed next was a large quantity of rare Magus treasures, information on high-grade meditation techniques, and also a great amount of valuable resources appearing on the stage one after another, something which many Magi pursued.

The high-grade potions that Leylin initially sold were in there too. Although there were only a part of it, they were still sold at sky-high prices. The desires of Magi for high-grade potions could never be satisfied.

This made Leylin rather happy but at the same time, he secretly rolled his eyes.

He originally thought that the Azure Mountain auction house undertook a definite loss when they purchased his potions, but now it seems this transaction greatly profited the other party instead.

“Ladies and gentlemen, today’s auction is approaching an end, our Azure Mountain auction house has specially decided that the biggest treasures of this time’s auction will be up for auction at the last moment!” The host’s words piqued Leylin’s interest uncontrollably as he fixed his gleaming eyes on the stage.

“This time’s auction will continue on for 3 days, which means to say, there are 3 extremely valuable items to auction! There are few opportunities!” The host’s voice carried a hint of temptation.

“Next, please allow me to grandly introduce the first treasure: the ancient advanced meditation technique—Wing of the Sun!”

Following his words, the curtains on both ends of the stage were drawn, exposing the precious object behind it. It looked no different from the common large swords. Its model was full of antiquity and the middle section of its blade had obvious cracks on it, with the tip of the sword missing.

Even more so, what caused Leylin to slightly lose his spirit was the drop of golden blood on the blade of the broken sword, which looked as if it contained a life of its own. It took the form of a spiral and shone with radiance continuously.

“As you all know, once a Magus surpasses the Morning Star realm, reaching an even scarier and more unpredictable state, their lives will begin to sublime. Even the smallest cell of their blood will contain a deep secret about themselves, so much so that they may achieve blood reincarnation…”

The host’s voice carried a slight excitement, “And this broken sword, had once been in contact with a little bit of the blood of the ancient Sun’s child! Through our appraiser’s verification, although the blood on the broken sword has completely lost its life energy, this sole drop of blood holds the information about the meditation technique of the Sun’s child from that time!”

“Sun’s child!!!”

As soon as the host spoke, Leylin somewhat lost his cool.

It wasn’t rare for the relic of such a powerful person from ancient times to contain some fragments of information. Even the Lamia fingerbone could forcibly catalyse the formation of a soul by the means of its own radiation. But to contain the complete information about the meditation technique was extremely rare.

Based on Leylin’s conjecture, the Sun’s child must have had a premonition about his death when he was facing his enemy and thus deliberately left a legacy behind.

Only, what amazed Leylin was that he had never expected to see a relic of that Sun’s child, who was amongst the ranks of Quicksand, in this place.

Somewhere, he had a feeling that maybe, his fate with the ancient bloodline Warlocks—the Quicksand Organisation, was not so short-lived.

“We can guarantee that the meditation technique—Wing of the Sun—is absolutely complete! The ancient top meditation technique is still a great reference for us even if we are unable to practise it! Moreover, although the bloodline of the Sun’s child on the sword has completely lost its life energy, you never know, there may still be certain spells that can restore its vitality. If it’s like that, I’m afraid the Warlock structure of the entire central continent will be revised……”

The host was trying his best to delude them, “For this auction item, the starting bid—200 million magic crystals, or other equivalent resources!”

After the host finished his sentence, the scene became calm and actually fell into a short, temporary awkward silence.

The numerous Magi, all stared at the broken sword and its golden spiral which was on the elevated platform, with unknown thoughts.

“Huff…” Leylin gave a long sigh, “If Mentor Gilbert was here, he’d buy this at all costs…”

Of course, Leylin was sure of one thing—the auction would be conducted for three days and a valuable item would be revealed every day at the last moment; this advanced meditation technique was only the cheapest among the three precious treasures.

The advanced meditation technique, Wing of the Sun, was similar to Kemoyin’s pupil—a technique specially customised for individual Warlocks. The criteria to practise it was to possess the bloodline of the ancient Sun’s child. According to Leylin’s intelligence and knowledge, ever since the ancient Sun’s child of Quicksand died, there had not been any news of the birth of similar bloodlines in the entire central continent.

Hence, the Wing of the Sun meditation technique was at most useful for Magi as a reference, causing its worth to plummet.

Also, the blood on the sword had lost its life energy and could not be used as a bloodline to be introduced into Magus bodies and passed down. Even though it looked very precious, its real worth was in fact not much.

Of course, the relatively low worth of this item was only when compared to the other two treasures. To Leylin, the price of this treasure was still too high to afford.

Chapter 459: Peeping

The third day of the auction commenced with much flair. The lower ranked Magi had been suppressing their enthusiasm and saving their magic crystals to the best extent of their abilities, hence once the pressure was diffused, they exploded into action.

Every item was sold for a high price, so much so that Leylin was quite surprised by the number of wealthy Magi that emerged. Some were in the VIP lounges, but there were also others amongst the crowd. It seemed like although he was very rich, he did not belong to the group of the most wealthy.

Leylin witnessed one of the Magi in the crowd buy a treasure for more than 100 million magic crystals nonchalantly. The cause for this transaction was the ever-so-common jealousy of a love rival!

When he began socialising with others, Leylin learnt that this young kid was the direct descendant of a Morning Star Magus who possessed a lot of resources and influence. It was natural for there to be a lot of magic crystals at his disposal.

However, he hadn’t dared to be arrogant in the face of the two Morning Star Magi present, and had hence only revealed himself now.

Leylin also saw Vance, the patriarch of the Rolithe Family, successfully buy a spell formation that was optimized to increase the chances of advancing to the Crystal Phase by 20%. At the same time, he’d also bought a lot of other supplementary materials for the process. It seemed like he’d reached the bottleneck and was ready to advance.

Leylin stole a glance at their party. According to the Coin of Destiny’s guidance, the item he needed to acquire now was probably in their possession.

The last great treasure up for auction was top-grade magic equipment— the Tri-Python Ring!

It was rumoured that the bodies and souls of three ancient cold pythons were extracted to cast this piece of magic equipment. Not only was its spatial storage boundless, it could even withstand three full attacks of a Morning Star Magus!

A full-power attack from an ancient Morning Star Magus was known to be able to kill anything under that level. Such spells had the ability to blot out all light; they could crush mountains and destroy rivers!

To possess the ability to withstand up to three such attacks, this Tri-Python Ring was undoubtedly the most precious treasure up for auction this time.

Even Morning Star Magi would be envious of its ability. This piece of top-grade magic equipment would be a great advantage in a battle between Magi of the same rank. It could flip the heavens and the earth for its user’s sake.

Its value climbed steadily up to the last bid of 8.6 billion by a Magus from a VIP lounge.

According to Leylin’s estimates, that party could be a Morning Star Magus. In fact, it might even turn out to be the Azure Mountain King.

In spite of the hiccups along the way, this Azure Mountain auction had concluded successfully. The emergence of the Tri-Python Ring had created strong waves that continuously spread even to the surrounding areas.

Some lower ranked Magi began to leave the city, heading back home to continue with their own research or embarking on another journey. With the decreasing number of Magi, the city seemed to have regained some order. The original chaos had considerably eased up, and the situation became peaceful.

Leylin and some other high ranked Magi, on the other hand, were waiting in silence.

To them, this auction was similar to an appetizer. The actual main course was yet to be presented.

On the surface, it looked like the Oakheart Clan had recalled their elite patrol. However, the actual fact was that the level of caution had increased threefold. It was only that the security concerns were now internal.

Everything was set up for the anonymous barter. The anonymity of the event meant that many Magi were now disposing of stolen goods. Hence, there were going to be many precious high-quality treasures offered for an attractively low price.

The Oakheart Clan would guarantee safety and confidentiality of both parties. On the other hand, they would not be held responsible for the consequences and disputes that would arise after a successful transaction.

In a room in a small hotel, Leylin who was in the midst of meditation opened his eyes. A flower-shaped secret imprint emerged from his contact book, bringing with it the voice of Serene. “Sir Blood Rogue! The anonymous barter will take place tonight. As for the venue…”

This woman had been attempting to rope Leylin into the Oakheart Clan, and had kept a close tab on his whereabouts. Still, Leylin would not let her have her way. Not only had his past been hidden flawlessly, his attitude towards her left him neither close nor distant, causing her great distress.

Finally, he had even changed his accommodations. The only way to contact him now was via the secret imprint, which left her helpless.

When night fell, Leylin changed his outward appearance once again. Following the directions he was given, he arrived at a spot outside Azure Mountain City.

Unexpected incidences were not rare at such private events. Even under the watchful eyes of the Azure Mountain King, the Oakheart Clan did not dare hold the event within the city, choosing an outside venue instead.

As such, even if anything were to happen, the damages would be reduced to a minimum.

‘Huh? There are other Magi too?’ After his descent, Leylin noticed another Magus who had also just arrived a step ahead of him, walking towards an unremarkable cave.

“Welcome!” Two old men wearing the Oakheart Clan uniform emerged. Without any questions, they handed over a black mask.

The Magus nodded his head without replying, accepted the mask, and headed in.

Without the need for a number, command, or even an invitation card, any Magus would be granted access as long as they knew of this entrance. In addition, they would be given items to help conceal their identities. It was this persistent and tight secrecy that allowed the anonymous barter to be successful for so long.

According to Serene, the entire location had been masked by a cover-up spell formation. With these matching face masks and their own identity concealment, even their genders were difficult to make out. Even Morning Star Magi could not see through these disguises.

Leylin’s mouth curved into a bitter smile.

“In reality…” He stopped mid-sentence, and stepped over to take the mask from the old man before proceeding to head inside.

Both these old men were at the Crystal Phase, and yet were stationed to guard the entrance. The Oakheart Clan had indeed invested heavily into this event.

‘A.I. Chip! Mobilize the atomic microscope and begin scanning!’ Leylin commanded in silence.

[Beginning Scanning! Microscope engaged… *Beep!* Abnormality detected!]

The reply from the A.I. Chip was swift. Leylin noticed within his line of sight that on the black mask were innumerable ladybugs flooding the surface. These were the same creatures that he’d seen at the auction.

In fact, their numbers far exceeded what he had seen previously. They were even cautiously entering Leylin’s body.

‘Hehe… This is the true Oakheart Clan!’ Leylin shook his head.

The spell formation enveloping the entire barter was genuine. The concealment runes on the mask were also genuine. Otherwise, it wouldn’t have by-passed the inspection of the many Magi. However, the Oakheart Clan had secretly planted these ladybugs all over the event area, including on all the masks.

They hadn’t dared to tamper with the spell formation for fear of being discovered by Morning Star Magi. However, with these ladybug spies, which were ten thousand times smaller than a speck of dust, everything that every Magus did, and all other matters regardless of importance would ultimately be known by them.

‘I’m afraid even Morning Star Magi won’t be able to detect these… ’ Leylin sighed, and a layer of fine black powder appeared on his hand.

As if drawn by some unknown attractive force, the ladybugs advanced in the direction of the powder, and soon lumped together into a ball.

‘A.I. Chip! Begin imitation of the organism’s energy signature, issuing misleading information!’

The A.I. Chip’s feedback was immediate.

[Mission received. Beginning…]

Leylin had been low-key for these past three days, and hadn’t bought anything at the auction. He had held back due to fear of the espionage of these bugs.

However, he hadn’t been idle at all. He’d made use of the A.I. Chip’s abilities to continuously scan and collate data about these bugs, learning all there was to know.

Knowing the tendencies of large organisations, if they’d rigged the auction to their advantage, there was no chance they wouldn’t do the same with the anonymous barter. In fact, the surveillance would even be much stricter. Therefore, Leylin had prepared well with his own customized potion on top of his disguise.

After the powder took effect, Leylin could see through the microscopes that the ladybugs had slowed to a languid crawl. Soon, they all moved back to the mask.

Leylin was pleased and smiled. Walking in, he slid the mask on. At the same time, a mysterious current and fine undulations emitted from his body.

At the huge barter event, in the centre of a hidden area.

“Reporting to Grandfather! According to feedback from the stardust bugs, everything is working normally!” The present chief of Oakheart reported respectfully to a middle-aged Magus with blue hair.

“Hmm! There are rumours about some convicts from the north heading towards us here. They had stolen some local treasure with intentions to trade and dispose of their stash. Be alert and pay special attention!” The blue haired Magus spoke indifferently, without the slightest degree of power and influence, yet it made the chief of Oakheart nod his head ceremoniously.

“Do not worry. Under the strict surveillance of the stardust bugs, nothing can stay hidden, regardless of the methods they use!” There was a reason for the chief’s confidence.

This species of stardust bug was a unique find from another plane. The Azure Mountain King had stumbled upon it during one of his interplanar experiments.

Thereafter, through intensive research, not only had he successfully tamed this organism, he had also given it the ability to work as a probe, becoming the secret trump card of the Oakheart Clan. In the entire clan, only the Azure Mountain King and the current elders knew of this.

Given their minuscule size, their energy undulations could not be detected without a special instrument. Thus, even Morning Star Magi couldn’t find out about them as they were spread everywhere undetected.

The knowledge that these presumptuous Morning Star Magi had the impression that their concealment skill was flawless, not knowing that everything was being exposed, made the chief smile heartily.

Of course, armed with such stardust bugs, he had even used them for his own benefits, to peek at the naked body of female Magi and had even kept the images. However, he was careful not to reveal such details for risk of angering the other Morning Star Magi, and having them turn on the Oakheart Clan and razing the entire clan to the ground.

Chapter 460: Assassin

“You’re in charge of this. The opponent is merely a Magus at the Crystal Phase; with your secret guards, you must take him down,” the Azure Mountain King spoke nonchalantly.

“Understood, Grandfather!” The chieftain nodded before bowing and leaving.

After acquiring all the information, he would first let these fugitives dispose of their goods before he went forth to hunt them down and receive the bounty. This method of taking advantage of both parties was not a foreign concept to him.

If wealth was being accumulated quickly, it would usually involve bloodshed. Even if the Azure Mountain King was a Morning Star Magus, the Oakheart Clan would not have been able to develop so quickly without these methods.

The Oakheart chieftain’s heart was aflame as he impatiently arrived at a control room, rubbing his fingers. “How many Morning Star Magi will come to the anonymous barter this time? I”m looking forward to it…”

“This is the central control room. Commanding all daughter elements to transmit gathered images,” he pressed a crystal and ordered.

Quickly enough, numerous fragmented projections formed a screen with many little squares on it. On the surface were the outer appearances of the Magi participating in the barter, as well as their true appearances.

Beside the images of some of the exceptionally beautiful female Magi were even full-body images. Of course, they were without clothing. The chieftain’s eyes widened, and he looked excited.

What he did not notice was that in one of the parts in the corner, Leylin’s character had a completely foreign face.

The barter was held in a large karst cave underground. The ground was filled with powerful runes and brands, emanating formidable energy waves.

The mask Leylin had on gave off a black layer of light that resonated with the spell formation on the ground, hiding his body in darkness.

From the outside, all the Magi who entered were black blobs of light, and it was difficult to even distinguish their sexes.

In addition, the strength of the spell formation was something Leylin had never seen before. He could not help but order the A.I. Chip to record the pattern down.

It was evident that this was a spell formation that only Morning Star Magi were able to set up. It was even able to ward off the probing of other similarly-ranked Magi.

This had been verified by the many Magi who had participated in such events in the past.

It was a pity, though. Even if the Oakheart Clan hadn’t tampered with the spell formation, they had surreptitiously placed a deadly spy on all their bodies.

Bugs that were ten thousand times smaller than specks of dust would not be discovered even if on someone’s body. On top of that, these stardust bugs had the innate skill of concealing themselves.

With the Oakheart clan’s nurture and specialised training, these stardust bugs had already turned into dreadful spies that could tell the identities of every single Magus in the trading event.

“So sad…” Leylin strolled along with the numerous black blobs of light, feeling regretful.

He had yet to do much research on this type of bug. He could only achieve the effect of hiding himself, but it would require a lot of time to trace the origin and even steal the others” footage from the central control room. Perhaps, he might need to even develop his own stardust bugs and sneak them in to achieve that goal.

All this required time! However, he only had three days at the auction. It was already amazing to be able to accomplish what he had done. Wasn”t that obvious from how the many Morning Star Magi here had yet to realise the secret of the stardust bugs and how their identities were completely exposed?

When the black blobs of light in the cave increased in number, a crisp bell sounded, attracting the attention of multiple Magi to a circular stage at the centre.

Light began to flicker there, revealing a blond middle-aged Magus.

“The many of you may or may not know me. Please allow me to introduce myself. I am Leo Oakheart, the host of the Azure Mountain auction. I shall also be the host of this anonymous barter…” Leo’s expression was brimming with a warm smile.

“I”ll cut to the chase. As the anonymous barter only takes place for one night, I shall not waste any more of your precious time. There are two parts to this event. First, the Magi who need to trade items can come onto the stage in order to show the item you wish to sell, and declare what you hope to obtain in exchange. Each person is limited to three items! When the time for the public exhibition is over, next will be the trade. Everyone may communicate privately, but this place does not permit any fights, and once you are out of range of this cave our Oakheart clan will not be held responsible for any of the items you have traded!”

Nearing the end, Leo’s voice became stern. As if to complement his words, a large pressure emanated from within the spell formation on the ground like a huge mountain.

“Please do not worry. All of us are aware of the Oakheart clan’s rules,” a low voice sounded from within the surrounding Magi. It was evident that some of these Magi had been here a few times.

“Good!” Leo nodded, and yielded his position on the platform.

*Swish!* The moment he left the stage, three streaks of black darted forth.

It was obvious that these Magi were all experienced. They knew that it was most advantageous to go up first, since what they needed might very well be in the hands of the next Magus. The sooner they went up, the easier it would be to obtain the items, and their own items would not be traded off so quickly as well.

“Hehe… my apologies…” The black streak in the middle was lightning-quick, and reached the platform a moment before the other two. A robotic voice sounded from the black streak, and it was difficult to identify the gender of this person.

Upon seeing this, the other two streaks of black light hesitated and could only retreat. They knew the rules of the Oakheart clan, and that if they did not obey they would be in trouble. Hence, they did not have any plans of doing things by force or arguing.

“Ladies and Gentlemen, what I have brought to exchange here is an ornament, the “Forbidden Ancient Clock”. In exchange, I require…” The moment he spoke, the audience was in an uproar.

“The forbidden clock? Isn’t that the inheritance of the Lucca clan in the north? Why is it here?”

“Rumours have been circulating recently that a few fearless Magi snuck into the clan and stole it, and then scattered till they were near the Azure Mountain. He can’t be one of them, can he?”

Leo, who was watching on, was also slightly surprised. He had not expected the other party to make their move so quickly.

With a thought, countless stardust bugs crawled all over the Magus” body in secret. With them on his body, that Magus would definitely be unable to escape from the Oakheart clan.

“The Forbidden Ancient Clock? A.I. Chip!” Leylin, who was under the stage, was similarly startled and quietly issued a command.

[The Forbidden Ancient Clock. One of the mysteries inherited from ancient times. Said to hold the power of time, and is the treasure of the northern Lucca clan.]

The A.I. Chip quickly came up with a paragraph and a picture. It was a vivid image from a piece of parchment paper, within which was a giant black wall clock. The clock hand was twisted, and gave a strange sense of confusion.

“The power of time?!” Leylin’s eyes widened. “This is an extremely advanced power. How can low-ranked Magi control it…”

There were many who knew about the rumours surrounding the Forbidden Ancient Clock. Many Magi stared at the black blob of light onstage with fiery gazes.

Or to be precise, they were staring at the item the Magus was displaying.

It was a round ornament. It looked exactly the same as the picture of the ancient clock that the A.I. Chip had shown. The surface was the colour of dark copper and did not seem the least bit special.

“A.I. Chip, scan!” Knowing something was off, Leylin commanded the A.I. Chip to perform a scan.

[Mission established. Beginning scanning. Beep! Interrupted by an unknown force field. Scanning unable to proceed.]

On the interface of the A.I. Chip, Leylin saw a strange blank region at the sides of the black item, preventing the A.I. Chip from scanning.

After advancing to become a rank 3 Warlock, the A.I. Chip had also been upgraded. Issues like this, where there was interference from a force field that prevented it from scanning, hardly happened anymore.

The only possibility was that this Forbidden Ancient Clock was the real deal. The A.I. Chip was still unable to draw data on the power of time.

“However, what the A.I. Chip might be unable to probe might not be the clock, but some other mysterious item that causes a similar reaction…” Leylin touched his chin and continued watching the platform.

As expected, that Magus continued to demonstrate a few tricks, proving the authenticity of what he held.

A unique treasure, especially one that was related to the domain of time, was more than enough to be highly sought-after by Magi, even if it was merely a small component.

On top of that, this Magus had not quoted a very high price. Not only could it be exchanged with some precious materials, he even accepted magic crystals. This immediately caused the eyes of all the Magi present to go red in desire.

This was an anonymous barter event. Even if they obtained the item, the Lucca clan might not be able to find them. The number of Magi who had this thought in mind was definitely not small.

At the end, another Magus shrouded in black light used an astronomical price of 15 billion magic crystals as well as numerous precious materials and put pressure on the other competitors, finally obtaining this item.

After obtaining this item, the Magus knew that he could not stay for much longer and quickly left in a hurry. The Magus on stage did the same.

In order to protect customers, the Oakheart clan had even set up a random teleportation formation. Customers leaving would be transported to any area near the Azure Mountain, which even the Oakheart clan would not know. Hence, there was no need to worry about being followed.

However, these things were all just to prevent any attention. Leo had long since planted stardust bugs on their bodies. Not just the seller; even the Magus who had obtained the item was now under his eye.

This feeling of being in control of another’s fate was truly intoxicating.

Chapter 462: Rob and Kill

Leylin had long guessed what Leo was thinking.

Since they had already dispatched stardust bugs to find out the background of all the guests, the Oakheart Family had probably done their fair share of killing and seizing treasure. They hadn’t been discovered only because they had concealed it well, and the targets they chose were mostly those without power and support.

What interested him more was the other party’s obvious desire for the Dark Elven Crown.

‘The concealing effect of this magical device has a large range. Although it is sufficiently extensive, for a Magus, a range that is too large might become a burden to them, making the concealing function less favourable.’ Leylin stroked his chin and squinted.

‘The only reason why this could attract Leo would be its use in war…’ Only a sneak attack in such a wide area would be the place for this piece of magic equipment to be put to use.

Therefore, whatever purpose the other party had purchased this magic equipment for would be revealed soon. Leylin absolutely did not believe what he said about giving it to his cousin or any rubbish of the sort anyway.

‘However, having gained something here, Vance…’ Leylin looked over at his empty stall, and glanced outside at the corner of his eye.

Indeed, the sphere of light that represented Vance had left together with the Magi who were crowding around to watch the scene earlier on.

Although Leylin still did have items of a higher value, it would evidently be inappropriate to put them up.

However, merely letting him go was clearly not Leylin’s style of doing things. He had now completely understood the rarity and scarcity of astral stones. If he had the chance to obtain one more, he definitely wouldn’t mind.

As time passed, the anonymous barter had come to an end.

Groups of Magi left on the teleportation spell formation one after another, rays of light flashing repeatedly. The entire cave quickly became quiet.

At this moment, Leo appeared, along with 7 or 8 Magi behind him. There seemed to be both old and young Magi, but what remained the same across all of them were their frightful energy waves and astonishing murderous aura.

“I will personally handle the Magus that sold the Forbidden Ancient Clock. Number 6 and 7 will be in charge of the buyer! The other party is only a small fry with little power. As long as we kill him and destroy the evidence, there wouldn’t be any consequences…” Leo swiftly delegated missions, occasionally throwing out a locating crystal.

“As for Number 5, you’ll go after the fellow that took the astral stone and kill him. That is his actual appearance, don’t worry! He only has the strength of an initial Hydro Phase Magus!” They were the secret elite force of the Oakheart Clan, and every Magus was in the Crystal Phase. To Leo, dispatching even one of them to deal with Leylin was already thinking too highly of him.

Number 5 was a bulky middle-aged Caucasian. Upon receiving an image, he discovered that Leylin was a young man with brown curly hair and nodded.

“Also, if possible, try to catch him alive. Our clan’s underwater prison has been short of prisoners of a sufficiently high rank…” Leo laughed coldly, sending shivers down the spines of the other Magi.

The Oakheart Clan’s underwater prison naturally would not be any average place. Even rank 3 Magi in the Crystal Phase that entered would surely face death, and would even be sentenced to the cruelest penalty before dying; even their corpses would be an unbearable sight to behold.

‘Looks like this youngster has greatly offended Sire!’ number 5 secretly thought. He slapped his chest and guaranteed, “Rest assured, Chief! I will definitely arrest him for you to punish!”

“Alright! Excellent!” Leo nodded.

“Is everyone clear about the rules of our Clan? If something goes wrong, immediately destroy all evidence. I’d rather you commit suicide than divulge any information about the clan, or else…” He watched the Magi indifferently. The icy-cold look in his eyes made them sweat profusely.

Although they had already risen to Crystal Phase, as long as they were human, there was bound to be something or someone that they cared about or was their weakness. And all of this was secretly controlled by Leo and the clan.

While every single one of them was strong rank 3 Crystal Phase Magi, they did not dare to disobey Leo’s orders because they were deterred by the Morning Star Magus.

“Great! Let’s set off!” With a wave of his hand, the numerous Magi instantly transformed into rays of light, launching in all directions.

……

At this moment, Leylin was following closely behind Vance.

He had already set his eyes on the other party at the auction venue. There would only be one outcome when a scheming Leylin and a clueless Vance come together: an easy target. With the aid of the A.I. Chip, he immediately marked Vance.

He wasn’t far from where Vance’s transmitted location was and had promptly followed him.

“Hmm?” Leylin then discovered that the stardust bugs on him had sent him information.

“Someone is chasing after me, and he’s just a mere Crystal Phase Magus? What a pity Leo didn’t come himself, or else I might be able to take the Dark Elven Crown back…” After the experience with Toram, Leylin now had confidence in his combat capabilities.

If an average rank 3 Magus in the Crystal Phase tried all the tactics possible, there still might be a possibility of defeating the enemy.

However, if the other party had more than 3 people, then his only option would be to ditch the plan and run.

If Leo alone came for him, he thought of making him stay here forever, but since it was just a Magus in the Crystal Phase…

“Since I can’t kill you, I’ll annoy you. A rank 3 Magus in the Crystal Phase probably wasn’t easy to nurture…” Leylin stroked his chin, and an evil look flashed in his eyes.

‘However, I will first have to settle with Vance, or it will be an unexpected factor that could easily result in consequences I can’t have thought of.’ After much thought, Leylin used the Transfiguration spell to transform into the image of Blood Rogue that he had used in the auction venue, and stopped Vance in his tracks.

“Who is it? Oh? Mr Blood Rogue?” Vance examined the Magus in his way, stunned. Even after recognizing that he was Blood Rogue, he did not seem relaxed, but instead became more alert.

“I wonder why Sire is blocking my way?” Vance stared at Blood Rogue in fear.

His ability to randomly transmit spell formations and find out his whereabouts was definitely something worth being cautious about. Vance’s heart beat rapidly, and he had a premonition that something bad was about to happen.

“I am the Magus that was selling the Crown of the Dark Elves previously. It seems that you, Sir, seem to have information about astral stones, so I followed you with hopes of obtaining it…” Leylin spoke politely.

“Oh! It’s you!” Having made a great realization, Vance patted his head, but his expression suddenly changed, “But, how did you recognize me?”

At that time, he had been using the concealment spell formation, and had even put on a few layers of disguise!

“About this, of course…” Leylin smiled, keeping an enigmatic expression. But before he could complete his sentence, he turned behind and his face changed.

There, Number 5 had hidden his face and was swiftly coming after him. using up to them.

“Such waves? It’s a Magus in Crystal Phase. You went so far as to provoke someone of this level?” The old man’s eyes widened, and deployed a few layers of defense in succession.

“He came too quickly, what a waste! With a bit more time, I could lower Vance’s defense levels and attack in one go!”

Leylin glanced at Vance, “I’ll have to get this done and over with!”

*Whoosh!* Both of his hands abruptly turned blood red, and huge claws grabbed at Vance, making loud sounds.

“I knew you were up to no good!” Vance hollered, as layers of soil made their way onto his body, forming a humongous clay giant that was more than ten metres tall.

“Kill!” Leylin’s face was expressionless, his eyes filled with a piercing look that was sharp enough to kill. His spiritual force, which was already in Hydro Phase, flowed into the Claws of Blood without end.

The massive clay giant roared, raising his fist to greet the strange bloody claws flying towards him.

*Bam!* The blood red claws were sharp beyond comparison, and instantly scratched the other party’s fist, even leaving a deep groove in his chest.

“Hmph!” Vance’s stifled snort came from within the clay giant, his voice filled with dismay, “Such strength? Aren’t you a Magus in Hydro Phase?”

*Boom!* With that, the clay giant immediately turned and hurriedly escaped.

But why would Leylin let him run off? Numerous potions flew in mid-air, and terrifying elemental particles converged, taking the shape of a jet black sickle.

“Rank 3 potion combination spell—Death’s Blade!” Gigantic black sickles slashed through the giant silently, without a single wave.

The clay giant’s entire body trembled and he suddenly came to a standstill. Soon after, along with the loud rumble, the clay giant disintegrated in all directions, revealing Vance within.

It was just that Vance now had a more pitiful appearance. Both legs were broken at the knees and blood was gushing profusely, but no matter what spells or healing potions he used, it was still useless.

“No! Don’t come over! I can give you anything you want, I… I still have some clues about astral stones… You’ll definitely need it…” Seeing Leylin inch closer step by step, Vance started to panic, promising a whole heap of things.

He didn’t wish to die. He treasured his life, even more now that he had already collected sufficient materials and was about to advance to the Crystal Phase.

“Blame Jessia if you wish!” Leylin was apathetic. He had never believed in intelligence that was revealed in the face of death, and the Crystal Phase waves that were getting closer also meant that he was running out of time.

“I have enough astral stones, the intelligence means nothing to me. If you don’t have any on you, at most I’ll think of it as doing all of this for nothing!” Leylin had thought this through clearly. He had gone on the trip with the intention of giving it a try.

He didn’t need the intelligence, because with a piece of astral stone with him, there wasn’t a need to risk his life for another imaginary desire.

Therefore, Vance’s fate had actually been set from then.

“Jessia?” Vance paused, recalling his grandson’s cheeky wife.

“What has anything got to do with her?”

But he didn’t have to think any further, as a blood-red ray of light threw him into darkness…

Chapter 466: Astral Experiment

Numerous heatwaves congregated within his sea of consciousness.

Leylin saw the silvery stream of Hydro Phase spiritual force circulate wildly. Even the core nucleus body glowed with strange crimson runes. It had only lacked just that little bit in the centre that would render it complete!

“Activate Crystal Phase spell formation!” The Crystal Phase spell formation set up at the center of the room immediately rumbled, the crimson runes on it lighting up one after the other.

Leylin began to shiver uncontrollably. Compared to the previous few spell formations, the feeling that came from this Crystal Phase spell formation included a terrifying compressive force, as well as a chill that dug deep into his bones.

Streams of icy air flowed into Leylin’s sea of consciousness, combining with the boiling spiritual force.

On one end, there were waves of heat, but on the other end, streams of cold. Leylin felt like his brain had expanded and seemed on the verge of exploding.

With the alternating cold and heat, a huge transformation happened in his sea of consciousness, the boundaries constantly stretching outwards.

Much of the liquid spiritual force shrunk under the immense compressive force, and was refined further by the constant waves of heat and cold, glimmering with sparkles. This led to the formation of crystals, marking a shift from the Hydro Phase to the Crystal Phase.

Crystal Phase spiritual force was unique to each Magus, and Leylin paid attention to his own. It was made of dark, nearly black crystals, that held a hint of the crimson of fire inside them, denoting his affinity with these elements.

The liquid spiritual force turned to crystals, and decreased in size by several folds. The warm rush of the Diamond Jellyfish stimulated the generation of even more spiritual force, filling up the gaps.

[Beep! Host body breaking through current gene limitations. Stats in all areas increasing.]

The A.I. Chip’s voice rang. It had been monitoring him as per usual.

After entering the Crystal Phase, the entire body would experience a complete transformation as a foundation for advancing to the Morning Star realm, and this was only one of the changes.

“As expected, it’s an advancement that affects even the genes,” Leylin’s expression revealed his elation. Amongst lower-ranked Magi, there were few opportunities to break through the limits of one’s genes, and it was thus very precious.

[Beep! Host body’s spiritual force has exceeded threshold, advancing to Crystal Phase Magus. Recalculating stats!]

The A.I. Chip’s prompts came one after the other, and by this point, the waves of heat and cold had calmed and gradually disappeared. Within Leylin’s sea of consciousness, a black crystallised spiritual force covered the area, seemingly indestructible.

His stats had been refreshed once more.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 3 Warlock (Crystal Phase). Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 35, Agility: 35, Vitality: 50, Spiritual force: 351.7, Magic power: 351.7 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force).]

Leylin observed the newly refreshed stats that the A.I. Chip had come up with, and nodded in satisfaction.

“Strength and agility have both increased by five points in one go, which is already pretty good. As for my vitality, if not for finding precious materials such as the blood dragon fruit, I wouldn’t be able to achieve these numbers…”

His spiritual force had completely broken through the threshold of 350, allowing him to enter the Crystal Phase.

Leylin raised his arms. He could sense the modifications Crystal Phase spiritual force would grant his body. This was just the beginning, and though the effects had slowed and were not as obvious as when he had broken through, these imperceptible changes would result in a terrifying accumulation of strength over time!

‘Senior Lucian advanced to the Crystal Phase when he was five hundred, and that speed is already considered rather quick in the Ouroboros Clan. Senior Robin is now only three hundred, and his advancement had shocked the clan, earning him a reputation as the most powerful bloodline talent in the last three hundred years!’ Leylin tidied up the room while forcing a smile.

‘I’m only two hundred and am much too young. If my speed of advancement is let out, it will definitely cause another huge ruckus!’

A Magus who had advanced to the Crystal Phase a hundred years before Robin did, without the help of external influences, would definitely shock even Gilbert. But what Leylin urgently needed now was strength, and he had no choice but to break through.

‘I need to wait for a while longer. When the war begins, everyone will be focused on the battles. Though my speed will still cause a commotion, it will definitely be smaller than if news were to leak now.’ With his mind made up, Leylin decided on not leaving for a while, holing himself up in his tower.

With the concealing spell formation he had set up, as well as the amplification from his Magus Tower, nobody would know that he had secretly advanced to the crystal phase unless Gilbert himself came and checked.

This hidden strength would definitely cause enemies who had misjudged his abilities to be in for a huge shock!

At this thought, a smirk rose about Leylin’s lips, “I really am quite curious as to who will be the first to barge in…”

……

The underground of the Magus Tower was separated into many little rooms, forming many laboratories. The facilities were first-rate even in the central continent, and Leylin had only been able to achieve this by spending many magic crystals and resources. He even owed quite a few favours.

In the past, a few less important laboratories were open to a few high-ranked Warlocks that were under Leylin.

Now, however, this layer was empty. The Magi who usually remained in the Magus Tower had followed Leylin’s command and left for a while. Even his disciple, Snoopy, had been chased out.

In the innermost, largest and most advanced laboratory, Leylin stood silently, drawing a rune on the floor.

Though he had simulated this activity a great many times with the A.I. Chip, he was still extremely focused while he drew, concentrating on the rune and lines on the ground.

Compared to the other spell runes used in the central continent, what he was now carving evidently held the style of another dimension. Some parts were even a mess of disorganised figures and lines, but closer inspection revealed that they were strangely three-dimensional.

Only when the last stroke was done did Leylin sigh slightly, looking at the spell formation that had no mistakes. “It’s finally done!”

The long time he’d spent on carving had resulted in a thin layer of sweat on his forehead. With his current vitality, this should have been almost impossible.

[Scanning completed, confirmation that there are no errors.]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded at this moment.

‘Then, the preparations for interplanar experiments are complete,’ Leylin thought as he stroked his chin.

He had gone out and went through the trouble of finding an astral stone. Was it all not for the purpose of preliminary astral experiments? Hence, after he advanced to the Crystal Phase, he had been impatient to begin his research.

All experiments related to the astral plane were dangerous, and this held true even for preliminary ones. Hence, Leylin had no choice but to disperse all the Magi in the tower. This was to eliminate all external influences so that he could concentrate on the experiments here.

Interplanar experiments were a high-level research that only Morning Star Magi could conduct. They were connected to the glory of the ancient era, and Leylin ambitiously hoped to make use of this research.

Hence, this preparatory research work was vital.

Even this research had very stringent requirements. A high-grade Magus Tower, Hydro Phase strength and astral stones were the most basic requirements..

Though the requirement for the Magus was merely to have reached the Hydro Phase, Leylin wanted to be on the safe side. He waited till he had advanced to the Crystal Phase before he began the research.

The more powerful he was, the safer he would be. This was indisputable.

The information for the preparatory work regarding the astral gate obviously came from Duke Gilbert. By aiding him in many experiments, Leylin had gained valuable experience.

At the heart of this giant interplanar spell formation was the smaller astral stone that he had gained from Vance. The blue lustre on its surface seemed more powerful.

Leylin took in a deep breath and checked everything once more. Only after ensuring was fine did he issue the command. “Tower genie, begin charging!”

[Confirming authority. Magus Tower preserving 10% of energy as base reserve. Remaining energy will be used on the spell formation.]

The tower genie rapidly reported.

The Magi outside watched this marvellous scene. The runes on the giant black Magus Tower dimmed one after the other. Besides a very dim glow, it had basically stopped operating.

After its construction over a hundred years ago, this was the first time that this had happened. It immediately gave rise to the panic of residents who knew nothing. This Magus Tower was a safeguard to them, and was the thing that could preserve their lives and safety.

Kubler, who had stayed behind in Onyx Castle, had no choice but to dispatch patrolling officers to put down these worries.

“Grandfather, will Mentor’s experiments be successful?” Snoopy seemed to know more and asked Parker.

“How can the mysteries of the astral plane be something we can pry into? As long as we successfully activate the spell formation, the lord’s experiment can be counted as a success!”

Parker forced a smile, “The energy required to probe into the astral plane is much too terrifying. Regular Magus Towers cannot withstand it, but don’t worry about that. The lord’s Magus Tower uses a top-grade set up of positive and negative energy pools, and there shouldn’t be much of a problem in terms of resources.”

*Buzz!*The giant Magus Tower trembled, and terrifying elemental tides formed two large rainbows, one dark and one light. One disappeared into the crest, the other into the base.

“Tower beginning charging, and positive and negative energy pools are revolving!” The genie reported.

Snoopy was no stranger to this scene, but now he could only silently pray, hoping that his mentor’s experiment would be a success.

He felt a hint of pride at this.

Out of the entire continent, there were few Magi who could do even some of the preparatory experiments into probing through the astral plane alone as a rank 3 Magus. His mentor was one of them!

Chapter 467: Power of Destiny

Within the Magus Tower.

Leylin gazed steadily at the giant interplanar spell formation. With the positive and negative energy pools working at full strength, the runes atop the spell formation lit up one after the other, causing terrifying waves of spatial undulations to converge on the spot.

[Spell formation working as per normal. 67% activated. Gaia cuvatures stabilised.]

The A.I. Chip constantly monitored the spell formation, reporting to Leylin occasionally.

With the spell formation slowly activating, the blue rays from the astral stone right in the middle condensed, giving off a resplendent light.

The spatial undulations that had been on the verge of going berserk fused with the blue light and quickly stabilised, surging in a single direction.

At the same time, Leylin sensed that a frightening energy was surging out of the astral stone, supporting the operation of the entire spell formation.

[Spell formation activation increasing in speed. Progress at 75%, 80%, 85%, 90%, 100%!]

The A.I. Chip rapidly intoned.

When all the runes within the spell formation lit up, the spatial energy followed a channel and converged before Leylin, forming a silver mirror the size of a fist. At the heart of the mirror was a small vortex, its destination unknown.

Leylin had seen this situation multiple times at Gilbert’s. This meant that he had now made contact with the astral plane!

However, this spiritual force channel of his was much smaller than Gilbert’s. Furthermore, he could not open a few simultaneously, and could only allow the entry of spiritual force seeds to find coordinates. Physical beings could not pass through.

It was naturally impossible for there to be a similar situation as the first time at Gilbert’s, where a creature of the astral plane had passed through the mirror and attacked them.

Though he had lost the chance to fish for benefits, it was good that his safety was not compromised. In a way, the gains balanced the losses.

Leylin carefully appreciated this feeling. There was large difference between helping with someone else’s experiments and performing one alone.

For instance, Leylin now sensed that with the assistance from the spell formation, especially with the energy from the astral stone in the middle, his own spiritual force seemed to be able to peep at the edges of a frightening dimension.

This was a confluence of time and space, the peak of the universe. A higher dimension which had an unexplainable existence!

Even just the aura that was given off was dazzling and glorious, going on for eternity and stimulating his desires to explore.

“Just becoming aware of all this is enough payoff from this experiment…” Leylin sighed.

The opportunity to see the astral plane was a very rare opportunity for Magi. They might not even need other advantages; just observing the astral plane every day would bring about indescribable benefits.

Of course, this was impossible. Experiments on the astral plane everyday? Even Morning Star Magi would go bankrupt!

[Beginning projection of spiritual force onto the astral plane. Recording data.]

The A.I. Chip instantly intoned under Leylin’s guidance.

A thread of Crystal Phase spiritual force, with the gleam of actual crystals, appeared from Leylin’s forehead and formed a spiritual force seed before quickly disappearing into the silver mirror, and into the vortex.

“Begin localisation support, activate navigation mode!” Leylin commanded.

Immediately after, his spiritual force seed seemed to find its way in the chaotic space, and went head on dauntlessly, even going against the current.

The A.I. Chip quickly began to calculate, and numbers began flashing before Leylin’s eyes..

[Spatial turbulence estimated to happen in 0.34s. Suggested directional change is 34 degrees to the left.]

This spiritual communication happened in an instant, and Leylin’s spiritual force seed immediately moved in a different direction, accurately avoiding the spatial turbulence. It even joined an undercurrent that headed east, floating further away.

Compared to Gilbert’s experiments where he depended on luck, Leylin’s method was evidently more effective, and he would find it easier to obtain results.

It was a pity that Leylin was the only one with support from the A.I. Chip, and it was not as if he could expose his secret.

Hence, while he was at Gilbert’s, Leylin tried to familiarise himself with the A.I. Chip’s functions, but did not dare use it at will. He could only go through with his plans when he was conducting his own experiments.

“As expected, with help from the A.I. Chip, chances of my spiritual force seed being destroyed are much lesser than average!” A hint of excitement appeared on Leylin’s face.

[Warning! Warning! Spatial storm generated ahead. Time to impact is 0.0000001s. Retreat is suggested!]

The A.I. Chip’s voice sounded once more.

However, it was much too late. Though Leylin’s spiritual force seed tried its best to retreat, its struggle was like that of an ant’s against the flow of time. Besides, time was scarce, and the horrifying spatial storm was generated instantly in front, whirling the seed within.

Leylin fell two steps back, feeling dizzy, but he quickly recovered.

He was no longer a newly-advanced rank 3 Magus, and was now at the Crystal Phase, preparing to enter the Morning Star realm. Injuries that could harm his spiritual force then were now nothing to him. Even condensing ten or so spiritual force seeds at one go was not a problem.

“The support system of the A.I. Chip also has its limits. At most, it will allow me to go further than other Magi can.” A wry smile appeared about Leylin’s lips.

The dangerous spatial turbulences were extremely terrifying and unpredictable. Even with the frightening calculation abilities of the A.I. Chip, it was difficult to completely establish a pattern and understand them.

In addition, even when knowing there was danger ahead, once held by the spatial turbulence, Leylin’s spiritual force might not be able to escape.

However, even so, Leylin was already content. ‘The A.I. Chip can increase my chances of success from one in a million to one in ten thousand,’ he thought.

One in ten thousand! As long as he persevered and continued trying, he would definitely gain benefits. In actuality, these odds were enough for Morning Star Magi to go green in envy, not considering the other methods Leylin had as well.

“In matters like these that depend on probability, the Coin of Destiny might be useful!” Leylin flipped over his palm, and a dim golden coin appeared in the middle of it. As this was his own experiment and nobody was around, he could use all of his methods.

A spiritual force seed was formed once again. Leylin rubbed the coin on the seed, and a layer of dim golden luster appeared on its surface.

*Ka-cha!* Meanwhile, a huge crack appeared on the surface of the Coin of Destiny once more, almost breaking it in half.

Seeing the Coin of Destiny on the brink of complete destruction, Leylin felt piteous before he stored it carefully.

The Coin of Destiny was able to predict anything as long as it did not deal with the Morning Star Realm. However, the moment it did, there would be frightful repercussions.

As for the turbulence in the astral plane? This was even more dangerous than Morning Star Magi.

Based on the situation, the Coin of Destiny would probably be completely destroyed after being used like this a few more times.

For the period of time that Leylin had been in the central continent, he had not seen any children of destiny such as Baelin and Longbottom. His instincts also told him that it would be a long time till he could make another Coin of Destiny.

What happened the last time was merely a coincidence. If he wanted to do it again, things would not be so simple.

“I hope the power of destiny will be able to help me proceed forward…” Leylin sighed and sent the dark golden spiritual force seed in.

[Monitoring. Vortex estimated to appear on left, recommendation to move far away.]

Leylin’s eyes were now emanating blue light. The A.I. Chip’s abilities were being utilised to the fullest as large amounts of data appeared before him.

He was like a helmsman who had gone through gales and waves. Amidst the storms, he continued to guide the seed forward, dodging in impossible ways and avoiding spatial turbulences.

Within the gigantic spatial crack, the golden ray was like a little boat passing through gaps in the turbulence, its movements unbelievably agile and smooth.

*Awooo…* At this moment, a giant black figure suddenly appeared in the air, pouncing towards the golden spiritual force seed.

“A creature of the void. I didn’t notice it!” Leylin was extremely annoyed. Creatures that lived in these spatial cracks usually had terrifying spatial abilities, and the A.I. Chip was much too far away to scan and notice it.

“Dodge it immediately!” The dim golden spiritual force seed quickly evaded, but the black figure roared, refusing to let up. A sharp, giant mouth formed on its stomach, hot on the seed’s heels.

[*Beep!* Warning! Warning! Spatial turbulence estimated to happen in: 0.00023s!]

The A.I. Chip’s prompt sounded again.

“Shit!” Leylin’s eyes were now slightly bloodshot, and he was doing all he could to avoid that region.

*Rumble!* Berserk spatial undulations swept through, and Leylin’s spiritual force seed was caught within.

*Awooo…* That creature noticed that its delicacy had been swept into the spatial turbulence, and could only roar at the boundaries before disappearing into the darkness.

“Is it going to die out again?” Leylin was full of agony.

At this moment, the golden rays on the seed flickered.

*Rumble!* An even more powerful spatial turbulence formed at the side. The two spatial storms collided, wreaking havoc on space itself.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* Countless bolts of silver lightning crashed into each other, tearing open numerous spatial cracks.

Leylin’s spiritual force seed actually followed along a crack and, despite the alarm it had caused, fell in without harm.

“The power of destiny!” Leylin, who had seen this scene, suddenly sighed, holding more reverence for the mysterious, unmeasurable power of destiny.

Chapter 468: Blackrain World

In a wasteland where little red grass with serrated edges filled the seams of rocks, which were decorated with strange images of humanoid faces, droplets of black rainwater generated within the cracks in the ground, quickly rose, and rained into the horizon.

　　

The rain here was actually black, and moved in the opposite direction.

　　

A dim golden spiritual force seed lay atop a blade of red sawtooth grass, giving off spiritual force undulations and scanning the surroundings. Leylin admired the sight.

“In that case, I’ll name this place the “Blackrain World”. I never thought I’d be so lucky and find a plane without a protector, and I wasn’t even discovered…

　　

“If Duke Gilbert found this place, he’d definitely go crazy in elation, right? However, it’s much too extravagant for me!”

　　

A complete different plane represented boundless top-grade resources, as well as much information regarding different dimensions. It was more than sufficient to make a Morning Star Magus go insane in envy.

　　

When it came to places like this which held traces of life and were possible to reside in, Leylin believed that Duke Gilbert would immediately hold no qualms and open the astral gate to arrive here, no matter the cost.

　

However, all this was much too early to Leylin. What he had opened up was merely a spiritual force channel that could not transport physical objects, much less his own body. That was a function of an astral gate, and still in the remote future for him.

　

“If not for this seed being formed from Crystal Phase spiritual force, it might long since have dissipated. However, at this rate, this merely slows down the process…”

　　

The rays from the golden spiritual force seed were very weak. In this environment, it seemed on the verge of being extinguished.

　　

“I can only transmit information here, so what’s most valuable to me here would be the coordinates of this world, high-grade meditation techniques or information regarding the path to power and the like…” Leylin now urgently wished for a high-energy energy creature to take him away.

This was merely a spiritual force seed, and if it dissipated, then so be it. However, if he could make a trade with another party, that would be a frightful profit.　　

Even if it was just the simple exchange of information, that would be the most beneficial for him.

　　

Ancient Magi had walked the path of glory through studying and imitating the paths of other worlds. If Leylin wished to restore the glory of the ancient era, he would definitely need to go along this road.

　

[Unable to determine world’s location.]

Leylin frowned. With the connection to his spell formation, he could feel that his spiritual force seed had reached a very remote area, and this connection was only faintly discernable, and seemed to be on the verge of breaking down.　　

　　

“One way of sending out the coordinates is to project a localising mark there. As long as it isn’t destroyed, it can send out waves of information infinitely, and then allow me to infer the coordinates. However, that’s impossible for now.” Leylin furrowed his brows.

　　

How many benefits could be obtained from a new world? It was enough to cause Morning Star Magi to go crazy. Even Breaking Dawn Magi would go green in envy and work to obtain it! Before all that, what was needed were the coordinates.　　

　

This method of calculating the coordinates was very complicated. It could not be obtained so easily just by sending a spiritual force seed over. A series of meticulous, complicated calculations had to take place, as well as coordinating with the seed in that world.　

However, the seed was now unable to hold on for long.

　

Being able to reach the Blackrain World was completely coincidental, and a repeat was impossible.

　　

“There’s another method. I can bewitch the intelligent inhabitants here and get them to set up some sort of altar, which in actuality would be a coordinate projecting device. I’ll then determine…” As long as the coordinates were confirmed, the Blackrain World would not be able to escape his grasp.

　　

Leylin had never heard of the terrifying ability to teleport himself into different worlds, even in legends.　　

　　

In addition, without a protector, Leylin’s spiritual force seed was not destroyed at the outer layer of the world. This meant that the Blackrain World lacked Magi who were at or above the Radiant Moon realm. At most, their highest battle might would be at the Morning Star realm, and therefore they lacked any defence!　　

　

“What I lack now is time…” Leylin gave a wry smile. His spiritual force seed could not be replenished in the Blackrain World, and was on the verge of dissipating.　　

　　

The moment it dissipated, it would be a complete loss. How could he take it lying down?　　

　　

A one in a ten thousand chance of finding a world was not so easily found. The Coin of Destiny had already been damaged to this point, and could no longer be used unless it was crucial.

　　

At this moment, Leylin’s brows twitched, “There’s something there!”

……　　

　　

Meanwhile, in the Blackrain World, Leylin’s spiritual force seed lay in the plains, while two dark green humanoid beings approached.

　　

These two creatures could somehow be said to look human. They had human torsos and two legs, but their bodies were filled with scales, and their eyes held blood-red pupils.　　

　

The arms were rather terrifying. On one side they had four, and on the other, three. There was even a horn sticking out from their heads.　　

　　

“Since they have so many arms, let’s call them the “Multi-Armed Race!” Leylin did not hesitate as he named this race, looking as if he was the conqueror of the place.

“…”　　

　　

The two members of the Multi-Armed race gathered a type of green fruit while they conversed in a language that Leylin could not understand. Their language was not sounded with their throats, but information was relayed through something like electrical currents projected from their horns.

　　

Even if he identified that information, Leylin still did not understand.　　

　　

[Discovery of information regarding language of a different plane. Recording!]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned.　　

　　

All methods of communication were definitely practical and universal. With enough samples, simulating them would merely be a question of time.　　

　　

At this moment, Leylin noticed how frightful their physical strength was. It even exceeded that of a few rank 1 high-energy creatures.　　

　　

“If this isn’t the usual standard in this world, then their strength must be exceptionally high…” Leylin sighed, ordering the spiritual force seed to make a move.　　

　　

“Hello!” Information in the ancient Byron language through spiritual force was transmitted into the minds of these two Multi-armed beings.　

“p”　　

　　

These two were obviously scared by the sound and immediately retreated, on their guard.　　

　　

“The ancient Byron language is a languages governed by rules, and also one that is common to many worlds. I didn’t expect it not to work here!” Leylin sighed. Though Magi of the ancient era seemed to have taken over many dimensions, and forcefully implemented their language and words, the number of different worlds out there were like the countless stars in the sky. It was very possible for some to have been overlooked.　　

　

“It’s going to dissipate anyway. Any changes in the situation are better than none at all!”

　

*Buzz!* With Leylin’s control, the dark golden spiritual force seed began to vibrate, giving off a dim radiance.　　

　　

This strange situation immediately attracted the attention of two other Multi-Armed beings. They gathered in front of the seed and began to gesticulate at it. When they realised the dark golden seed posed no threat, they began to argue.　　

　　

At the end, one of them seemed to have persuaded their comrade, and used a white animal skin to carefully pick up the spiritual force seed that was already looking weak, and darting in a direction.

　　

The wind whooshed on both sides, the scenery blurring, and Leylin had to recalculate the strength of this race.

　　

Tens of minutes later, these two Multi-Armed beings brought Leylin to a large tribe.

　　

In terms of its appearance, it looked very primal. There were few houses, all built of bulky rocks that had been piled up, seeming very boorish.

　　

Many beings of the Multi-Armed race moved around the tribe every once in a while, even greeting these two after seeing them.

　　

Leylin obviously did not let this chance slip by and carefully observed everything in the tribe. He immediately made a discovery.

“Not considering the elderly and children, there seems to be only two types of looks for the Multi-Armed race.”

　　

The Multi-Armed beings had two types of looks. One was three arms on the right, and four on the left, while the other was the exact opposite, with four on the right and three on the left. The latter was usually larger, and their scales were more firm.　　

　　

Leylin inferred that this could be a difference that indicated their genders.　　

　　

The two Multi-Armed beings did not seem to have a low status in the tribe. They proceeded forth with Leylin and came before a giant cave.

　　

“Hm? This place?” Leylin was immediately wary.　　

　　

From within the cave, he could feel energy particles converging. This meant there was an existence that dealt with magic, and there were even undulations similar to those of spell formations. However, compared to the Magus World, it had a different style.　　

　　

Outside the cave were hung all sorts of materials. Some were from animals and plants, such as the roots and fruits.

　　

“Looks like I’ve been brought to the a place where offerings are made, or where the tribe leader resides. That’s good too, since these people are usually more open…”

　

The two Multi-Armed beings firrst kowtowed outside the cave devoutly, and then yelled.　　

　　

“Sknglk…” An answer resounded from within the cave.　　

　　

The two Multi-Armed beings immediately placed the hide that carried Leylin within on the ground. Respectfully bowing, they then left.　　

　

The moment a sound entered Leylin’s ears, he was instantly shocked. “Morning Star!!! There’s actually a Morning Star-ranked being here!”　　

　　

*Tok! Tok! Tok!*　　

　　

Giant footsteps were heard, and immediately after, a being that was two times larger than others of its race appeared before Leylin.

　　

It stared at Leylin’s seed, giant blood-red eyes shining as it immediately grabbed it before its figure disappeared into the cave.

Chapter 469: Multi-Armed Race

This was the result of the natural radiation of a creature which had achieved the Morning Star realm.

The space in the hillside was even larger, and many creatures’ remains were casually abandoned at one side. The remaining energy waves on them made Leylin feel suffocated.

In the middle the platform, the livers of all kinds of animals were casually laid out at one side. An entirely black boiler foamed with white bubbles, making Leylin feel as if he was seeing a shaman of his old world.

Be it the insignia on one side or the totem, they were all decorated with bloody brown symbols.

This was Leylin’s evaluation: the entire hillside seemed just like an unsophisticated laboratory, but it already possessed a certain ability for research.

In a flash, the large Multi-Armed Race being threw Leylin’s seed onto an altar in the middle as the surrounding blood-red emblems immediately emitted a faint radiance.

Leylin suddenly felt as if he was isolated from his surroundings, and even if he wanted to explode, he could do nothing at all.

“Spell formation of a different tribe? Pretty interesting!” With the seed in their hands, the worst thing that could happen was just to lose it, hence Leylin was not especially afraid.

“The other… world’s… spiritual force seed?” At this time, the Multilimb Clan member spoke. Using the ancient Byron language, he stuttered slightly, but Leylin managed to understand his words.

“Yes, honourable sir! I am a space traveller, and I accidentally ended up here!”

Leylin’s heart soared. Being able to communicate meant that there was hope for a transaction. “Do you know the ancient Byron language?”

“Yes! Although we of the Quark tribe have already experienced 3 extinctions, our civilisation’s legacy has never been gone!” The large Multi-Armed Race being seemed very proud.

Leylin nodded. In such a brutal tribe, the clan leader, witch doctors and leaders always had deep knowledge. This was a rule that held true in almost every world.

“As you have seen, I am currently only a spiritual force seed, which has nearly dissipated and poses no threat. May I know if it is possible to make a deal with you?” Leylin told him his requirements.

The spiritual force seed needed the person’s own spiritual force to work, and now, it could be said that time was counting down to its annihilation. Even if the other party had a way, they could only delay it at most, without being able to solve the root of the problem.

Moreover, the journey to the Blackrain World this time was entirely accidental. It was impossible to create a space passageway even if he wanted to. Thus, he needed to obtain some valuable items immediately.

From Leylin’s point of view, the Multi-Armed Race member who had already achieved the strength of the Morning Star realm largely fulfilled the requirements.

“Are you really doing this just for a deal?” The Multi-Armed Race member’s eyes were full of distrust, and even more of cautiousness. The blood-red runes on the insignia twinkled, and it actually emitted energy waves similar to that of a lie detector.

“Of course!” Leylin answered without hesitation, almost believing his own lie.

“You are only left with a little bit of spiritual force, I’m afraid we have not much to discuss. Moreover, the previous disasters were all brought about by you all…”

The large Multi-armed Race member evidently showed distrust towards Leylin. The entire altar began to rotate, almost wanting to destroy Leylin’s spiritual force seed completely.

‘Bitch. Which bastard came first? They’re making things hard for those of us who came later…’ Leylin scolded in his heart. Still, he immediately shouted, “Wait, you don’t need my things, but I’m sure your clan members do. I have a lot of remarkable information from different planes, including lots on organisational systems, planting, smelting, alloy-making, even potion-making and alchemy. I believe they will definitely be helpful to you and your clan…”

“I can obtain these items directly from you…” The large Multi-Armed Race member laughed coldly. Streaks of blood-red lines emerged on the altar, even scheming to penetrate the spiritual force seed.

“So it’s this kind of soul-searching method!” Leylin’s spiritual force seed suddenly shook, emitting a great dark gold radiance.

The streaks of blood-red spiritual force were drowned in the bronze radiance in a flash. Right after that, Leylin’s spiritual force seed seemed to be more illusory, as if it would be forcibly destroyed in the next moment.

“As you have seen, this method is ineffective on me. Even more forced methods will not benefit us both in the end…”

Leylin was secretly relieved. This Multi-Armed Morning Star being only broke through to the Morning Star Realm based on his body strength. Similar to that male scorpion in the Icy World, it was a representation of power. Hence, its experience with regards to the spiritual world was still very feeble.

Such a creature could use its strong strength to beat up Leylin, but its power was inadequate to carry out a complicated job like soul-searching.

Should Leylin’s spiritual force seed end up in the hands of a similar Morning Star Magus who concentrated on spiritual force, he would only be left with the road to annihilation, even having many of his memories opened up for the other to see.

But with Leylin being at the Crystal Phase, it was still possible to somewhat confront a barbarian with Morning Star strength. In the worst case, he could order the spiritual force seed to self-destruct, leaving the other party with nothing to gain.

“What exactly do you want?” The Multi-Armed Race member’s expression turned sour.

”Simple. An equal exchange—both parties will provide valuable information, and as the outsider, I am willing to offer a portion first!”

Leylin’s spiritual force seed vibrated, and sent a few books of information written in the ancient Byron language over shortly after.

In those were some primitive introductions of systems, and simple agriculture and alchemy techniques. Although it was not of much help to a matured Multi-Armed Race member who was at least rank 1, it was still enough to use as reference.

Furthermore, at the end of the information, Leylin specially attached some information on methods of setting up spell formations to refine their physical bodies, as well as knight-training manuals that were commonly seen in the central continent. Although it was just a starter, it was still valuable.

The Multi-Armed Race, a bunch which concentrated on physical strength, would definitely be more interested in items in this aspect.

Indeed, towards the agricultural techniques and other information that Leylin sent earlier, the large Multi-Armed Race member did not show any interest. Instead, he appeared very intrigued by the proposed killing techniques.

“ An interesting item!” the large Multi-Armed Race member nodded, “The body refinement spell formations in here is enough to strengthen our children slightly. As for the last part about the killing techniques, although the structure is different, it can still provide some insights. I need the last part!”

“Then may I ask what you have in exchange?” Leylin was no longer anxious now that he had proven his worth. All that was left was for the other party to make his offer.

“You…” The large Multi-Armed Race member growled, but Leylin was not the least bit bothered.

If he were in his original body, he would naturally be very polite to the other party to protect his life. However, the worst case scenario was only losing a spiritual force seed. It was not a big deal, and hence, he was not anxious.

“What do you want?” Evidently, this Multi-Armed Race member also knew that now, Leylin was not afraid of him at all, and would not succumb to threats. If he still wanted that information, he could only give in.

“I am very interested in your training methods. Maybe…” Leylin tried asking. He was there to search for a way to increase his strength. Anything in that regard would definitely be very valuable.

A person such as this Multi-Armed Race member seemed to show hope for his own body to break through.

“We Quark tribe people are born warriors. Our strength is not trained, Instead, we are born with it!” The large Multi-Armed Race member proclaimed proudly.

Leylin rolled his eyes, “Then why is there still a great difference between you and your clan members?”

Creatures that had achieved Morning Star level in their adulthood, were all abnormally terrifying species. This Multi-Armed Race was not worthy to claim itself as the Quark tribe.

At the very most, they were only capable creatures with hopes of breakthrough to the Morning Star level. This piqued Leylin’s interest, and he wanted to conduct research on it.

In fact, the Multi-Armed Race were also bloodline creatures. However, they were able to advance continuously, to a point that such monsters with Morning Star strength existed. This lifted Leylin’s spirits.

If he studied their ways of obtaining strength, would he be able to find a method to break through the bloodline shackles?

“That is a top secret of our Quark tribe. How can we reveal that?” The large Multi-Armed Race member rejected straight away without hesitation.

“I don’t need it to be in-depth. Just the simplest and most basic explanations will be enough. What do you think of that? As long as you give me this information, I can give you all of the missing parts about the spell formation, as well as the next chapter of the killing techniques from before!” Leylin tempted enthusiastically.

To the A.I. Chip, these most basic things were the most important, because they represented the foundation of the system! As long as the foundation was complete, based on the deductive ability of the A.I. Chip, there would be a day when this Multi-Armed Race’s hidden secrets would be laid bare before Leylin.

”You give it to me first!” The large Multi-Armed Race member said.

Leylin pondered for a while before giving a proposition. “From the current situation, none of us will trust the other side. How about each of us hand over the information to the other party at the same time?”

“Alright!” The large Multi-Armed Race member agreed helplessly.

A huge wave of energy was emitted from its horns and entered Leylin’s spiritual force seed.

[Detected influx of spiritual force, accept?]

“Accept!” Following Leylin’s order, the curtains to the path for evolution was slowly unveiled.

Leylin did not go against his words as well. While receiving the information, he transmitted a large amount of information simultaneously.

When the transaction was over, both parties were relatively satisfied with their gains.

“Very well, visitor from the other world. You didn’t deceive me!” The large Multi-Armed Race member was evidently delighted.

“Of course. This transaction marks the beginning of our trust, and hopefully in the future, we will still…Oh damn!” Leylin spoke halfway and his tone suddenly became exasperated.

The spiritual force seed that represented his existence suddenly became illusory, exploding into a ball of light shortly after and vanishing without any trace…

Chapter 471: Neutralization

“Was that an illusion?” Leylin muttered under his breath and turned his attention to the A.I. Chip’s records.

[Unknown forcefield interference detected! Host has entered a state of confusion.]

[Interplanar spell formation engaging countermeasures, charging!!”]

[Magus Tower prepared to eradicate interference, beginning.]

[Host has successfully been restored to normalcy. Alert ended.]

The red records made Leylin feel gloomy.

In the middle of all this, the spiritual force seed that he had sent into the astral plane had vanished without a trace into a spatial rift.

“Tower genie!” Leylin called out.

“My Lord!” The green genie immediately flew towards Leylin.

“How much of our energy reserves are left?”

“Energy currently at 1.9% of maximum. Energy boost has been initiated,” it replied instantly.

“What led to such a huge consumption?”

“Records are in chaos!” the tower genie expressed a rare puzzlement.

“Indeed! What happened a moment ago was real. It wasn’t an illusion!” Leylin drew a deep breath.

He’d always known interplanar research was risky. Still, what he’d experienced just now was possibly his greatest research crisis to date.

‘Fortunately, the three astral laws are unbreakable. Hence, the other creature was unable to pass through and could only create an illusory projection!’

Leylin stroked his chin, pondering about the events that had happened one more time, ‘It was merely an illusory projection and yet it was that menacing. Had I opened an astral gate and allowed the other party to enter, perhaps my entire territory would have been destroyed…’

With such thoughts, he felt his lingering fear wash over him.

“Fortunately, it lacked the power to do anything. The situation was resolved by the countermeasure of the dimension spell formation!”

He exhaled a deep breath and turned his head around.

“Do you know—” A huge decapitated goat head with yellow liquid flowing out of it, appeared behind him.

Two huge lifeless pupils locked onto Leylin’s.

“…….”

In a split second, a layer of black scales surfaced on Leylin’s body and both his eyes turned amber.

“Petrifying Gaze!” Rays of mysterious light hit the opposing wall, and a layer of whitish-gray stone covered it.

The goat head disappeared into thin air.

“This matter is not finished!” Leylin’s face turned gloomy, “A.I. Chip, start scanning!”

[Beep! Mission established! Beginning scan!]

It took but a few seconds for it to respond with its findings.

[Remnants of an unknown force field have been detected. Confirmed to be interplanar contamination.]

*Buzz!* He stopped the whole interplanar spell formation with a wave of his hand. And then, with a blast at the center, the astral stone turned into smithereens.

The energy from this astral stone that he’d acquired from Vance of the Rolithe Family had been exhausted completely.

Seeing the course of events, Leylin took a deep breath before stepping up to the middle of the room.

In the library, multiple sprinklers that were fixed to the ceiling and connected to an enormous pool in the center started spraying a fragrant whitish-green liquid.

“Rank 5 purification pool! I hope it’s of help!” Interplanar defense was a compulsory course for anyone performing research in the area. Leylin had gotten Gilbert’s own purification system a while ago and built an enhanced version for himself.

Green liquid dripped from the nozzles, its antiseptic scent strong and sharp. Soon, Leylin was completely drenched.

As the green liquid washed over him, green fur started to appear on the surface of his clothing before being washed off by the same liquid again.

“This is so troublesome!” Leylin assessed his situation and furrowed his brows. He stripped himself naked and jumped into the pool in the center.

*Zi Zi!* An enormous whirlpool formed of pearl-white liquid started bubbling lightly.

Traces of black liquid oozed out of Leylin’s pores, visible to the naked eye.

After several rinses, Leylin stepped into another purification room. Inside, many human-sized flowers and plants were blooming. They opened up their petals and revealed their scarlet red tongues with suction pads…

After multiple purifications, Leylin wore a brand new loose-fitting robe and relaxed on a recliner.

‘I’ve sent many seeds into the astral plane in the past three months, but unfortunately I didn’t have help from the Coin of Destiny. There’s no way to find the Blackrain World again. Not only did I suffer an irrecoverable loss, I have even provoked such a heinous creature…’ Leylin weighed his gains and losses.

He had run many experiments on the astral plane, and had gotten some substantial gains. Yet, compared to his engagement with the Multi-Armed Race, it was all worth nothing.

With the A.I. Chip’s help, he had figured out the secret spell, and named it Multilimb Strength.

The A.I. Chip’s simulations had proven that such a secret spell had the ability to break apart one’s genetic limitations. So much so, that it could enhance Leylin’s current vitality by five to ten points.

To Leylin, such temptations were irresistible.

The more powerful one’s vitality, the harder it was to advance further. When his vitality was at ten to twenty points, he hadn’t bothered much about raising it. But now, to advance further from his base was an uphill task.

If word leaked of his Multilimb Strength, it would drive body-refining Magi crazy and cause them to act.

Even this one gain was enough to offset all his losses in the past three months!

This was the main attraction of the astral plane. There were both sides to a coin, no profit without loss. After becoming unable to use the Coin of Destiny, Leylin’s experiments had been at a bottleneck, with multiple attempts to proceed resulting in failure.

Especially today. He’d unexpectedly drawn towards himself a completely unknown living creature. It was, in fact, not an organism. Just a formless being with consciousness.

When it flared up, it was potentially more horrifying than an ancient curse.

“My luck had been average, I think it’s time to stop!” Leylin had a bad premonition about the dangers he had been facing.

“…….”

He shut his eyes lightly, and when he opened them, the same decapitated goat head appeared in front of him again. Its eyes were filled with death and traces of ridicule.

Leylin sighed. Facing the goat head eye to eye, his face was expressionless.

Ten seconds later, the goat head once again disappeared without a trace, as if what had just happened was another illusion.

“So troublesome!” Leylin was evidently annoyed, ”How dare it!”

He got up in a flash, grabbed his clothes, and went to the center of a restricted room.

Grasping the knob of the door, another illusion appeared as the yellowish-bronze knob morphed into a familiar goat head, glaring at Leylin, and giving him a sinister smile.

Such circumstances would drive any Magus crazy, and cause many other repercussions as well.

Upon opening the door, a cold mechanical voice was transmitted, “This is the core room! Only host Leylin Farlier is permitted entry. All trespassers will be executed.” Soon after, horrifying spell energy locked onto Leylin’s body.

Rays of red, green, and blue scanned his body. “Scanning has begun. Authority verified. Alarm lifted.” With the last sound, his body felt a rush of relief.

This was a small core room. There was only an experimental table with a crystal ball, and on top of it were intermittent images of a white bone.

Leylin laid down on the experimental table. Soon, he could hear noises from all around. First were some animalistic growls, and then there were the pitiful cries of someone in the throes of death.

Leylin was unmoved and nonchalantly gave the order, “Begin radiation!”

“Beginning radiation!” A mysterious energy appeared from the Lamia fingerbone, streaking across Leylin’s body. Slowly, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline in his body was roused to a gentle boil.

Given any other time, he would have enjoyed this process immensely. However, this time he felt different. Streaks of ash-grey fog appeared all over his body, enveloping him like a huge callous. It made him feel like he was struggling on his deathbed.

[Remnants of an unknown force field have been detected in the host. Confirmed to be interplanar contamination.]

The A.I. Chip repeated, and then added something else.

[It is advised to stop the Lamia radiation.]

“No! Increase the radioactive level. Raise it by 10 times!” an ambitious glare burned in Leylin’s eyes.

The A.I. Chip only had the rights to suggest, not to execute anything. Acting on his will, rays of blue currents radiated from the Lamia bone, causing huge energy undulations. It broke through the grey fog and shone onto his body.

Leylin groaned as he clenched his teeth, both hands holding tightly to the experimental table, using so much strength that he left imprints on it.

Purplish-black patches started to appear on his body, looking similar to sunburns.

[Epidermal cells are now 39.78% damaged! Host is suggested to abort the radiation!]

The A.I. Chip sounded once again.

“It seems to be insufficient! Increase intensity, adjust to 50 times!” Leylin locked his jaw tightly and hissed.

*Zi Zi!* The enormous radiation tangled with the ash-grey fog, turning it into a liquid that dripped down.

The noises surrounding Leylin began to intensify in both volume and chaos.

The white goat head once again appeared in front of Leylin. This time, the fur on it started to be shed one by one and the two horns started to shrink back into its skull, resulting in a huge change in its appearance.

After numerous alterations and transformation, the original goat head had morphed into a female human head. Her eyes were all-white, and were streaming blood.

Chapter 474: Obstruction and Ambush

”Thank you very much!” Leylin smiled widely as he expressed his gratitude.

Freya pulled on Leylin’s arm as they moved to sit on a long sofa. Leylin’s eyebrows furrowed, but not taking such intimate actions to heart.

”What exactly did you ask me to come here for?” Leylin thought Freya was not one to look for him because of a small matter— Miranda would be more likely to do that.

Once a serious topic was mentioned, all other expressions left Freya’s face as she turned solemn,“Do you know about the events related to the Purgatory World?”

”As far as I know, the elders seem to have acquired some clues, and now they should be searching for the specific coordinates!” Leylin said with an equally strict expression.

“Actually, the search has almost been completed. According to my master’s plan, I’m afraid we’ll all have to go to the headquarters to participate in the experiments!” Freya added, smiling bitterly.

”This is a responsibility we cannot shirk!” Leylin seemed solemn.

”It’s just that… I have a really bad feeling about this…” worry surfaced on Freya’s face, “Even in the ancient era, the Purgatory World was a tremendously powerful world, so how is it possible that it would be so easily found? Even if it is found, how would anyone then go past the protectors to enter?”

“I’m sure the mentors have already considered these questions…” Leylin considered his own words as he spoke.

“Well, I sure hope so!” Freya breathed a long sigh, then suddenly remembered something else, “These days, the outside world does not seem to be at peace; you must be careful. These are for you…”

Freya pushed a box over to Leylin. Leylin opened it to find numerous glittering and translucent crystals neatly placed inside.

“Spiritual force crystals? Those that have had their markings completely removed?”

Leylin was taken by surprise. A Crystal Phase Magus could naturally store and preserve his own crystallised spiritual force, and leave these crystals for future use.

But for such a pure colour to appear meant that Freya not only washed away all the spiritual force inside her crystals, but she also eliminated all her spiritual imprints.

To a Crystal Phase Magus, this was no different from reducing their own spiritual force. Although it wasn’t impossible to replenish them, it was still extremely troublesome.

Such crystals with their marks removed could be given to other Crystal Phase Magi to use, and could quickly replenish spiritual force. They were rare treasures, and had always been a top-class resource that was only circulated among Crystal Phase Magi.

For Freya, someone who had just advanced to the Crystal Phase, this gift was extremely precious to give.

Freya stopped Leylin before he could say anything. “Don’t decline it, this is what you deserve. I have yet to thank you for the bloodline crystals from last time…”

Leylin remained silent for a while, but eventually, managed to speak to express his gratitude, “Thank…thank you…”

……

A black horse-carriage slowly exited from the Ancient Blood Serpent Castle’s main gate..

Inside the magnificent carriage sat Leylin. He was looking at the box in his hand, a bitter smile on his face.

“She’s very considerate…” He sighed lightly. During this period of an unknown crisis, Freya was still able to remember him. This thought inevitably led Leylin’s heart to flutter.

“In the future, if I have the means, I will definitely help you!” Leylin firmly decided in his mind.

“Are you certain the target is inside?”

Not far away, there were tremors felt on the ground surface. Two shadows dressed in yellow appeared. “It is confirmed, inside that carriage is the Ouroboros Clan’s Marquis, Leylin!”

The other figure had a scratchy voice.

“Hehe…this is the Magus who the Demon Hunter put a high price on… And he has Hydro Phase strength!” The person who spoke first immediately laughed coldly.

“Everything is already prepared. Once our target enters the ambush, we spring into action at once!” There was a hint of bloodthirst in that scratchy voice.

“Hmm?!” Leylin, who was just resting on the carriage, abruptly opened his eyes, revealing a cheeky smile.

“Someone wants to attack me?” Although he had not heard the conversation between the two shadows, the A.I Chip’s detection clearly showed that, in the forest not far away, there was a trap.

Even if the other party had already carefully set up three layers of aura-concealing spell formations, from Leylin’s point of view these spell formations were like sieves that were filled with holes.

Especially the radiation from the Magi hidden within— that was as obvious as a burning torch in the night.

“Julian!” He called in a low voice.

“What’s the matter, Lord Marquis?” the coachman from outside replied immediately.

“Maintain the speed, there’s a group of friends ahead of us waiting for a greeting!” Leylin spoke in a low voice, and he was certain the Magus had already understood what he meant..

“Yes, my lord!” Upon hearing this piece of news, Julian’s voice was still ever so steady, like he was not in the least bit worried.

The grand horse-carriage proceeded at a constant speed, moving along on the road by the forest as if unaware.

A yellow fireball boomed as it crashed down on them, ruining the walls of the carriage and causing it to break apart. The giant rut and the wheels of the carriage flew out.

A waft of smoke rose just outside the area, isolating this piece of land from the rest of the world.

A few men dressed in black immediately pounced towards the carriage. One of them held a huge hammer up high, and smashed down on the carriage directly.

The land rumbled as the huge hammer mercilessly crushed the remains of the carriage and created a gigantic pit, as if by an earthquake that sent out strange ripples.

“Eh? There’s no one?” The person who spoke was someone with the voice of a child, and the body of a seven- or eight-year-old. Yet, he was holding a hammer that was bigger than his own body, making him look a little ridiculous.

“Blacksmith Mia? I don’t recall there being any grudges between us.” Several black tendrils covered the whole area, and Leylin carried the trembling coachman as they walked out of the shadows.

“Hehe! Do I need a reason to kill you?” Mia lifted her hood, revealing a face befitting the body. A face that should have been filled with the joy of a child was instead warped with bloodlust.

Blacksmith Mia was the central continent’s most infamous bandit, a peak Crystal Phase Magus with countless crimes to her name. Under the guise of a little girl hid a vicious, scary monster. She’d once used a metal hammer to kill an entire family of Magi. Male, female, old, young; no matter who it was, they were simply added to the mountain of flesh.

“And I reckon these people are courting death too?” Leylin looked around at the other few black shadows. Numerous elemental particles transformed into shields and appeared before him.

“Assassin Hill! Brutal Bear Fein!”…

A few of the Magi reported their names successively. They were all characters whose names were known far and wide for their notoriety.And they all emitted waves of Crystal Phase energy.

“You sure do think highly of me…” Leylin said, smiling while shaking his head. Without warning, he sprung forth violently.

“Go to hell!” He whirled the coachman who was in his arms upwards, smashing him towards Mia as if he were a sandbag. The numerous potion bottles on him scattered outwards.

“Rank 3 potion combination spell, Divine Prairie Flames!” Burning flames immediately formed a wall of fire in front of him, isolating Hill and Fein to one side.

On the other end, the coachman who was thrown by Leylin changed in a bizarre manner. Mia, who was standing in front of him, whirled the heavy hammer without regard for anything, trying to smash the coachman into pulp.

He pulled out a golden dagger in mid-air, and his whole temperament instantly changed. The originally timid man turned sinister and crazy, as if a cowardly rabbit transforming into a tiger.

“Blacksmith Mia?” He laughed coldly. His whole body seemed to have become as flexible as a snake’s, and he moved his body in a way no ordinary person would ever be able to as he avoided the huge hammer. In the same instant, he stabbed the dagger right into Mia’s chest.

*Weng!* An aura of gold was emitted from Mia’s body, but even that was shockingly dimmed as it was stabbed firmly by the dagger.

Mia’s body went stiff for a split second before her innate defensive spell shattered into pieces under the dagger’s attack.

Swiftly after, the sharp dagger mercilessly slashed at Mia’s skin and its sharp blade entered right through her chest, ripping through flesh and entering her internals.

Seeing the fresh red blood spurting out, the coachman’s face instantly revealed joy. And yet, the moment he saw a crazed expression on Mia’s face, his heart froze.

“Die!” Mia let go of the hammer. Holding on to a dagger, she crashed forward.

The sound of bones breaking came from the coachman’s body. His face revealed his astonishment as blood flew from his mouth onto the street.

“Boneless Snake Julian?” Mia’s body constantly wiggled, covering and repairing her internal organs and wounds immediately. She looked at Julian with eyes filled with hatred.

“As expected of the legendary Magus with body refinement, who soaked in the Corrosion Swamp! To think my strength and magic equipment isn’t enough to kill you in one shot!”

Having been revealed, there were slight alterations to the coachman’s face, and Hydro Phase waves were emitted from his body. He was a Magus as well!

Or rather, an advanced Magus who had already reached Hydro Phase.

The Boneless Snake, Julian, was one of Freya’s family’s most powerful warriors. He was notorious for assassination ability, causing enemies to be terror-stricken at the thought of his existence.

“Damn it, I knew those bastards’ plan was not reliable!” Mia’s face changed. “Retreat immediately!”

Hill and Fein glanced at each other, doubt surfacing on their faces.

Even if Julian and Leylin stood shoulder to shoulder, they were merely two Hydro Phase Magi. On the other hand, their group had a bunch of Crystal Phase Magi who had been famous for a long time, how could they run away from them with their tails tucked between their legs?

But subsequently, their facial expressions drastically changed.

“Pssssst!”

A menacing Blood Serpent’s shadow abruptly bombarded the surrounding haze. The whole spell formation was immediately breached.

Warriors wearing dark red Magus robes with Giant Kemoyin Serpent tattoos surrounded the area, and covered Leylin who had just been promoted to the Crystal Phase.

“Ouroboros Clan Warlocks?”

Hill cried out beneath his breath, knowing that today’s business would be hard to handle…

Chapter 475: Explosion and Encirclement

“You lot knew our plans from the very beginning?” As Mia looked at how they were heavily surrounded, her face turned grim.

The fighting strength of high-ranked Warlocks, especially that of Warlocks like Leylin and Julian, could without a doubt compare to ordinary Magi in the Crystal Phase.

The Blood Serpent Warlock Organisation was the elite force of Freya’s family, not something to be trifled with. They were actually dispatched all at once, and were even led by Freya herself, a Crystal Phase Warlock!

Due to the additional power from their bloodlines, Warlocks were usually stronger than ordinary Magi. Once they advanced to the Crystal Phase, they would immediately be able to compare to peak Crystal Phase Magi.

Given all this, it was no wonder that Mia’s face looked glum.

“All of you have been wreaking havoc near the territory of the Ouroboros Clan! How can we let all of you go so easily?” Freya wore a tight-fitting hunting suit, and looked extremely heroic. Of course, that was only if one ignored the childish face.

“River Agu’s warehouse robbery, the extermination of the Rolithe Family, and Count Oakta’s disappearance. Who exactly is the mastermind behind all these?”

Freya stared at the three Magi, and an extreme feeling of danger overwhelmed her.

To subdue and order three vicious Magi in the Crystal Phase was not something that could be done by any ordinary power. With the addition of the chain of events that had occurred recently, Freya had a bad premonition.

“Just the Ouroboros Clan?” Mia’s group of three Magi all registered smiles of disdain.

“Watch out! Lest they…” After seeing that smile, Leylin’s pupils shrank, and he quickly gave a reminder.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!* Three other rays of black clashed with the Blood Serpent Organisation like lightning, overcoming the strong obstructions before arriving next to Mia’s group.

“Three… Crystal Phase!” Freya grit her teeth, and she sounded bitter.

Little did she expect that the opponents had reinforcements, which obviously meant that they had made preparations with regards to the plan of hers.

She was already at the limit of her current strength in subduing three Crystal Phase Magi. But now that there were three more? Freya felt her heart sink.

“What now? If you don’t wish for the elites in your family to perish here, then release us now!” Mia’s voice had a tinge of complacency.

“That’s not enough! He needs to stay!” The three Crystal phase Magi who’d appeared afterwards pointed at Leylin.

“What? Why?” Leylin touched his nose.

“The damage you’ve done to us is not light, and only the Demon Hunter’s rewards can make up for it!” Hill shot Leylin a look before glancing at Freya.

“He is not a Warlock from your family. Miss Freya, I presume you wouldn’t want to simply treat us as your enemies just for a member of your organisation?”

Leylin rolled his eyes internally. It would be impossible for discord to be sowed with such simple tactics. However, due to the fact that personal interests were involved, this could bring about more trouble.

Thankfully, Leylin had not planned to put his own safety in the hands of others, and had backup plans already.

“The Demon Hunter?” Freya muttered to herself. She had heard of how Leylin and a few others had offended that particular Morning Star Magus. If those Crystal phase fugitives were under the Demon Hunter’s wings, it would be understandable.

Many of the Warlocks thought of that point, and after hearing Hill’s words they looked at Leylin in a different light.

Even though they belonged to the same organisation, and they’d had some friendly interactions before, Leylin was simply not important enough for them to offend a Morning Star Magus without hesitation.

Morning Star Magi in the central continent had power and status, and their dignity could not be infringed upon lightly.

Even though the two organisations were hostile, they hadn’t yet completely fallen out with each other. As a result, many of the Warlocks thought that it was worth it to give up Leylin to get on Cyril’s good side.

A few Warlocks immediately distanced themselves from Leylin. This included the very Julian who had been fighting at his side all this while.

Freya’s face immediately registered a change. She grit her teeth as she looked at the numerous Warlocks from her family.

“Leylin is a Marquis of our clan, we will never hand him over!”

“Master!”

A clamour was started amongst the Warlocks. From their point of view, their family did not have to do so much for an outsider.

“My decision is firm! All of you, quickly get out of my territory, or else you’ll come to regret it!” Freya said firmly.

“The one who’ll come to regret it will be you!” Mia said furiously, and together with the five figures behind her, turned to leave.

“Wait a minute!” Just when the Blood Serpent Organisation had made a path, an ill-timed voice sounded that caused both parties to look around.

“Leylin, don’t do anything rash!” Freya’s voice betrayed her anxiety.

Even though they were related by bloodline, the Ouroboros Clan was divided into many factions that competed with each other. This was the most she could do for Leylin. Were he to go and provoke them without discrimination, Freya would not risk the danger of her family’s elimination to accompany him.

She looked at Leylin’s back, and bit her lips.

“What? Youngster, you’re lucky today to be able to hide under the skirt of a woman. Next time, you won’t be so lucky!” Mia raised her giant hammer and threatened him.

“Three Crystal Phase Magi for the ambush, and another three as backup… this should be the limits of your strength!” A blue light shone in Leylin’s eyes as he sighed, “Don’t use the Hunter as a facade, he’s not fit for that!”

“Hmmm? What did you just say?” Fury appeared on the faces of some of the Crystal Phase Magi.

“What I’m saying is that you have to stay here today. There’s no escaping from that, even if you’re using the name of a Morning Star Magus!” Leylin’s tone was light, but seemed to emphasise his words. At the same time, a mountainous might instantly erupted from his body.

“Crystal… Crystal Phase! How long have you been…” Freya covered her mouth in extreme shock.

Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks would typically depend on the accumulation of time to make a breakthrough via their bloodlines. Freya’s own breakthrough to the Crystal Phase at her age had deemed her a genius.

But Leylin? He was only 200 years old, and yet had already broken through the bottleneck to the Crystal Phase!

Freya immediately thought of the changed situation on the battlefield after Leylin revealed his strength.

The other party had a total of six Crystal Phase Magi, and Freya’s side had two with the addition of Leylin Julian and the other members of her organisation could at most resist the attacks of three Crystal Phase Magi. Overall their strength was still lower than that of their opponents.

Of course, in that case, for the other party to want to cause great damage to Freya’s team, their chances at succeeding would be greatly minimised.

With the small disparity in strength and the apprehensions about damages on both sides, ordinary threats would have no effects.

“I’ll deal with these three Crystal Phase Magi! You can settle the remaining ones right?” Leylin had undone the pretense of the transfiguration spell, and had released his entire strength without any qualms as he pointed to Mia’s initial group of three.

“No problem!” With Freya’s Crystal Phase strength and the addition of Julian and the Blood Serpent Warlock Organisation’s support, to annihilate the three Magi would not be a problem. It would only be a matter of time.

“But, are you sure you’re up to it?” Freya glanced at Leylin, and in her eyes was worry that she could not conceal. After all, the enemies were Crystal phase Magi as well.

“Haha… Don’t worry…” Leylin laughed, and numerous black flames shot out like arrows as they trapped Mia, Hill, and Fein within.

He actually wanted to, in one move, deal with three Magi that were similar in strength to him together.

“I’ll grant your death wish! Just nice, my Bloodthirsty Hammer lacks the spiritual wailing of a Crystal Phase Magus!” Mia smiled coldly as she rushed forward with the metal hammer.

*Bam!* The heavy hammer rippled with terrifying amounts of energy, creating a huge crater on the ground.

“A lass who only uses brute force! I happen to detest beings like these lately!” Leylin’s silhouette grew translucent, giving off a glow which swiftly appeared before Mia.

“I cannot stand you, but it’s a piece of cake to subdue you!” Leylin’s eyes registered coldlness, a black ray slowly appeared from his hands.

“Fatality’s Tip!” The black ray of death tunneled through the hammer and the innate defensive spells, shooting at Mia’s forehead like black lightning. When it exited, it brought with it a large amount of blood as well as brain matter.

*Bang!* It was not until Mia’s corpse fell to the ground that Hill and Fein reacted to it.

What had they seen? The famed Mia who was known for her hammer, someone at the peak of the Crystal Phase, died at the hands of her opponent. The two had not even dueled for a few seconds.

‘Could it be that he has already advanced to the Morning Star realm?’

All of a sudden, an idea that shocked the two appeared within their thoughts, which instantly caused their limbs to become colder.

Leylin himself had not expected the effects of the sudden attack to be so successful as well.

He had originally already reached the state of a rank 3 Hydro Phase Magus, and with his bloodline strength matured to an extent, he had managed to prematurely reach his limits now together with the help of the Lamia fingerbone.

Currently, he not only had a terrifying spiritual force, his other credentials had far surpassed that of ordinary Crystal Phase Magi by a huge margin.

This terrifying strength had the support of the powerful spell tailored for him by the A.I Chip— Fatality’s Tip!

All the factors had come together, and perhaps with the help of Mia’s complacency, he had managed to achieve such success. Even Leylin himself was grateful for this stroke of luck that arrived just in time.

“It seems that in my current state, few can match up to me unless they’re at or above the Morning Star realm!”

Leylin looked at the venue which had instantly quieted down, and let out a sigh of relief.

“What are you looking at?”

Freya was distracted for only a short while before she instantly ordered the gathering of the Blood Serpent Warlocks. Leylin’s terrifying outburst had allowed her to see hope for subduing and annihilating the opponents here!

The thought of her earlier humiliation seemed to have triggered the adventurer in her.

Chapter 478: Annihilator

Glancing through the many pieces of magic equipment and precious materials, Leylin set his gaze on a pile of crystals.

These were all pure spiritual force crystals. On their surfaces, he could faintly feel the energy of elemental particles.

Crystal Phase Magi had the tendency to stockpile their crystallised spiritual force. In times of need, they would use them to replenish their own spiritual force, or trade them for something else due to their value.

Leylin’s move had been quick and violent, leaving no opportunity for the opposite side to use such tactics.

Compared to the spiritual force crystals gifted by Freya, these crystals were obviously unclean, and had to be processed before use. “Crystal Phase spiritual force crystals…”

Leylin stroked his chin, and a tube of golden blood appeared in his hand.

“It’s unexpected that I managed to gather these two items so quickly. I guess I’ll just go ahead and carry out Quicksand’s experiment!” Leylin sighed, and his eyes flashed with a dark solemnness.

His harvest from Quicksand Castle had been much greater than just the Lamia fingerbone.

After he finished deciphering the experimental procedures, the great amount of data became useful for his own bloodline research. Over the past century, he’d digested it all, and even improved on some of it. The technique of preserving his genes was just a marginal result of the experiment.

In fact, Leylin felt that his research into bloodlines was amongst the best in the entire Ouroboros Clan, just below that of the elders.

And one of his experiments involved a method of igniting a Warlock’s bloodline to strengthen them.

Leylin had kept this experiment top secret, unwilling to perform it even after he advanced to the Crystal Phase. The effect of the first ignition would be the best, and subsequent ones would progressively decrease in value. Hence, Leylin planned to use his first ignition to break through the bottleneck to the Morning Star realm.

Of course, one measly experiment would not be able to propel him to rank 4. Moreover, he was only at the beginning of the Crystal Phase, so he hadn’t even reached the threshold for advancement.

There was an enormous gap between rank 3 Magi and those at the Morning Star realm. There was an abundance of Magi in the central continent, yet Morning Stars remained few and far between, their positions envied by all.

Igniting one’s bloodline had the potential to boost one’s strength greatly, and even that had slim chances of facilitating a breakthrough.

Still, this bloodline experiment wasn’t the only trick Leylin had up his sleeve.

“My cumulations to advance to rank 3 have been progressing well! I have to start considering the next stage—Morning Star…” Leylin stroked his chin, evidently pleased.

The central continent was currently in a dire state, especially the Ouroboros Clan. Not only were there disturbances on the borders, many families had perished and core members had gone missing. These disastrous events were a bad omen for the future.

Amidst such chaos, the best defence one could rely on was their own ability!

“I’m sure Mentor Gilbert and the other two have already been alerted about the circumstances. Why are they yet to make a move?” Leylin muttered under his breath. Suddenly, he thought about his own appointment as an enforcer. “Perhaps they were aware of it and had secret plans of their own that I might have missed noticing it…”

Time crawled on as he waited in silence.

Later, Leylin welcomed the presence of his own bodyguards. Boosting his own confidence was the presence of Lucian.

“Do you really wish to do that?” Lucian stood in front of Leylin, unable to mask his astonishment.

After finding out that the current Leylin had advanced, and was on par with him at the Crystal Phase, he sighed in his heart.

This junior only needed a hundred years to catch up to his level. His talent exceeded any member the organisation had ever seen even in Morning Star seeds. And yet, compared to the temperamental Robin, Leylin whose potential was much higher remained humble and earnest. Lucian found this extremely admirable.

“If we investigate further, the number of people implicated in this will increase… Although Mentor ordered me to assist you…” Lucian, after seeing the current Leylin, felt that this junior ought to have wholeheartedly entered seclusion, waiting for an opportunity to break through the Morning Star bottleneck instead of focusing on such small matters. He wondered what his mentor was thinking.

Thoughts about Gilbert made Lucian heave a big sigh.

To these high-ranking Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlocks, the allure of the Purgatory World was much too huge, and they couldn’t help but be engrossed in their search.

Thinking about the recent situations and Leylin’s terrifying military power, Lucian heaved another big sigh.

“I’m in charge of information in the clan. I can give you anything you need. My only wish is for you to not get yourself involved!” Lucian smiled bitterly, took out a translucent crystal ball, and handed over to Leylin.

“As an enforcer, it is imperative that I locate the rebels and all the disruptive elements hidden in the Ouroboros Clan and get rid of them!” Leylin smiled faintly, as if he was not affected by Lucian’s words. But once his spiritual force entered the crystal ball, his face changed.

“The situation has deteriorated to such an extent?” He looked up in disbelief and glared at Lucian.

“Yes…” he answered after a heartbeat, “The chaotic power struggles are not confined to the border regions. Even internally, some ambiguous problems have cropped up. Some of the clans and families especially, their betrayal is pretty much confirmed…”

This top secret information was only available to Leylin because he currently held the position of an enforcement officer. If it were in the past when he only held the position of a Marquis, he wouldn’t have access to such things.

‘What exactly is Mentor doing?’ The thought left a bitter taste in Leylin’s mouth.

“There’s no need for excessive worry. As long as we don’t lose our main base at Phosphorescence Swamp, given the presence of the three elders, we of the Ouroboros Clan will never be vulnerable and weak.”

Leylin let loose a long sigh before he stood up.

“I want the list of confirmed traitors!”

“Alright, I’ll ready them immediately,” Lucian promised, “What do you plan to do?”

“No matter what, since they have the audacity to betray the Organization, they will have to pay the price!” Leylin spoke with a steely voice. With his men behind him, he headed out.

…….

“The Stuart Family at the Stuart mountain range!”

Black fires were blazing furiously. A large number of high-ranking Warlocks were surrounding a huge mountainous brutal bear.

Behind the bear was a fort that was half-built into the cliffside.

“Enforcer Leylin, I demand an explanation for this!” In the middle of the castle, the silhouette of an old Magus appeared. It entered the sky, becoming a huge projection.

“Even though you are an enforcer, you do not have the authority to besiege the castle of a Marquis!” The illusory image of the old man roared in his hoarse voice.

“Authority? Only the weak will abide by such rules and regulations while wishing that their predators would abide by them in this way too. By placing your hopes on such enforcements is truly foolish!”

Leylin sneered. Still, on the account of the other men that went on this mission with him, he decided to explain further, ”If I have to give you an explanation, it would be your betrayal of the Organization. That is why all these Warlocks are out to kill you, and that is why you cannot escape your fate!”

“Rubbish…” Having his biggest secret exposed, the Magus acted like he knew nothing and was hearing it for the first time. Veins popped out of his flushed neck and he fumed with anger.

“True or false, we’ll know after you surrender.” Leylin’s face was emotionless. A brilliant ray of black ripped through the vast sky and streaked across the brutal bear’s head mercilessly.

*Bang!* The huge mountainous brutal bear’s head was cracked open like a watermelon.

“So long as they are from the Stuart Family, we have orders to kill them without exception. Property and assets will also be confiscated. We’ll be given bonuses of equivalent value!” Parker ordered clearly. Those Warlocks thirsty for achievements, and those who longed for the huge payout from the mission, howled and dashed forward.

Seeing Snoopy taking the lead and defeating one Magus after the other, some even dying on the spot, Leylin couldn’t help but nod his head.

The reason he’d taken on the job of enforcer, other than to acquire the huge wealth of the rebels, was for him to bring his men together for a round of actual field training.

The bloody battle of magic and death carried on for a short while. Ten or so minutes later, Parker grabbed the Magus that had been speaking from the fort, and pulled him out. With the matter settled, he stood in front of Leylin and reported like a loyal long-time butler.

“Except for this old man, all surviving members of the Stuart Family had been wiped out!”

“Well done!” Leylin looked at the high-ranking Warlock on the ground. The opposite party evidently had the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline in him too, yet when he saw Leylin, he began to shiver.

“Do you feel resentment? Desperation?” Leylin stepped up, provoking the old Magus.

“Hopefully, the next time, before your soul is destroyed, you should use some brains!”

*Thud!* After Leylin was done speaking the chief’s head fell to the ground, staining it red.

“A total of three Giant Kemoyin Serpent Families have been wiped out, along with their supplementary small-scale families and other influences. I think we’ll have some peace for a while now…”

Standing at the edge of the overhanging cliff, Leylin glanced at the result of the destruction caused by many Magi, involuntarily heaving a sigh of relief.

“Only a while?” Standing by the side, Parker smiled bitterly.

After numerous episodes, Leylin’s reputation had spread everywhere. With his formidable strength that could even slay Crystal Phase chiefs, he’d immediately established his status.

Soon after, through the ruthless means of wiping out entire families and clans, Leylin’s fame as an enforcer became even more widespread. Thus, he was labelled ‘Annihilator’.

Chapter 479: 3 Helpers

No matter what, with Leylin happily going on a killing spree, the internal affairs of the Ouroboros Clan stabilised despite the general unrest.

Leylin guessed that this had more to do with how the opposing Morning Star powers had yet to make their move.

Without these insider spies, it would take more effort to create chaos within the inner circles of the Ouroboros Clan which was currently already on the alert.

With these achievements, his reputation soared not only within the Ouroboros Clan, but even in the nearby regions.

‘After the Stuart family is destroyed, we can take a small break!’

Leylin sighed and asked Parker, “How is it going at Senior Robin’s side?”

After taking on his role as an enforcer, Leylin was stunned at the realisation that this senior of his had accepted the responsibility from Gilbert before him, and was leading his family and pushing down all rebellions.

In addition, there were rumours that Leylin’s senior had a large change of personality. Not only did he like to torture his enemies, he even enjoyed eating human flesh.

Upon hearing this, Leylin’s heart sank.

Though it was terrifying when bloodline issues acted up in high-ranked Warlocks, Robin’s behaviour had surpassed the pattern of any problems arising from bloodline.

‘Mentor might have wanted to capitalise on his insanity, which is why he arranged for him to purge the inner regions.’

Leylin took in a deep breath.

Compared to him, Robin was going too far. Leylin had merely destroyed families where there was conclusive evidence against them, but Robin went even further. If he had the slightest suspicion at all, the entire family would be purged by him mercilessly.

Even a few bloodline noble families who had a deep connection with Robin’s own thus lost their inheritance.

Through the list of families Robin had destroyed, Leylin made a discovery. Robin seemed to only to have an interest in pure-blooded families, and the higher the purity, the more pitiful their deaths were. Even their corpses were not complete.

Knowing all this, Leylin felt a chill as he put two and two together.

Though he knew he wasn’t the best person in the world, he was still better than Robin. He wouldn’t do anything so disgusting.

“Complaints against Robin are becoming more widespread. Who knows, we might need to stop him next!” Leylin smiled wryly at Parker.

“Robin is master’s senior. I believe Duke Gilbert wouldn’t do this,” Parker consoled him.

“I hope so!” Leylin sighed. A distance away, many white dandelions fell down like snowflakes, flying freely atop the ancient castle that had already been ruined.

Night fell, and outside what had been the castle, Leylin’s vassals set up simple tents. Iron pots bubbled with meat soup and large amounts of mushrooms, giving off a tempting aroma.

A merry atmosphere permeated the camp; the plan had gone quite well, Though Leylin planned to train his vassals this way, he still made his move when the casualties were about to be too high.

Hence, they had not suffered much, and instead reaped massive gains. For this reason, they were motivated to continue striving on.

Even the most ferocious Warlock was full of admiration when gazing at Leylin’s tent at the heart of the camp.

They had been with Leylin for the longest period of time, and could be said to be the people who knew Leylin the best out of everyone in the Ouroboros Clan.

It was because they knew the terrifying strength of their master that they held reverence for him.

Of course, he did not put too much thought into this. As long as he maintained his crushing strength, these vassals would follow him for their entire life.

Within the tent, Leylin was half-lying on the ground, dressed in tight black clothing. His hands were held behind his back in a strange position.

There were a few strange runes written on his body with blood.

Buzzing sounds were produced from Leylin’s lips from time to time, his entire body slightly moving along to a rhythm.

During this process, threads of mysterious energy seemed to be pulled from the air, disappearing into Leylin’s limbs.

This process continued for almost an hour. Only then did Leylin stand up, taking a look at his hands.

A prompt popped up at this moment.

[Host body completed a cycle of Multilimb Strength. Vitality increased by 0.5, no changes to strength. Estimated that in 20 days and 13 hours, host body’s vitality will increase by 6.7, and strength by 2.1…]

“This progress is not bad!” Watching his stats that were refreshed again, Leylin couldn’t help but nod.

Multilimb Strength was a cultivation technique he had gathered from the race in the Blackrain World. Though the Morning Star realm chief had purposely left out a lot of things, the complete version of this path to strength was completely deduced, with the A.I. Chip organising the data and making inferences.

Toughening his body with this method, Leylin found that his body, which had already developed to the maximum, now held the possibility of advancing even further.

Though this increase was small, it was enough for him to be happy.

Furthermore, with Multilimb Strength, the toughness and coordination of his body had increased by a whole level. He could even launch a physical attack similar to that of an ancient giant beast.

This coordination, when paired with the Knight techniques Leylin had previously learned, turned his body into a frightful killing machine.

Still, these were all just serendipitous. What Leylin focused on was the increase Multilimb Strength gave to his vitality.

The corporeal body sustained the spirit. If spiritual force was said to be water, then a Magus’ body would be the cup. The larger and sturdier the cup, the more liquid it could contain.

Leylin was still unable to peep at the Morning Star realm, but after reaching the Crystal Phase, what he needed to do was continuously increase his vitality and accumulate spiritual force. Once enough had been gathered, his crystallised spiritual force would eventually condense to form point mass.

The point mass represented everything to a Magus. It represented their journey, bloodline, strength, and even soul!

Hence, this process was irreversible. The moment the ascension to the Morning Star realm failed, and the point mass grew unstable, a terrifying explosion might occur.

If a Magus encountered such a situation, they would be left without a corpse.

Historically, the Magi who failed to ascend to the Morning Star realm and fell far outnumbered those that had succeeded.

Wondering about his future path, Leylin’s expression changed as he asked the A.I. Chip a question, “How is the simulation of information regarding the Morning Star realm going?”

[Simulation is 13.5% complete. Unable to process deeper calculations without concrete data]

The A.I. Chip robotically answered.

If he could gain an understanding of the Morning Star realm now, it would be incomparably useful to Leylin’s advancement.

However, it was difficult to meet with Morning Star Magi, and even more impossible to perform research on them.

It wasn’t as if Leylin could look for Gilbert and tell him that he wanted to do an experiment, and ask him to be a specimen.

It would be a wonder if Gilbert did not destroy Leylin in that instant!

“Perhaps the corpse of the Scorpion Man in Twilight Zone will be useful to me!” Leylin touched his chin. The Scorpion Man was truly a Morning Star creature, and his corpse would definitely be useful as a reference for the A.I. Chip’s simulations.

Immediately after, Leylin overruled his own thoughts. “There’s not enough time. It isn’t the volcano’s dormant period. Furthermore, based on the predictions of the Coin of Destiny, rank 3 Magi will meet with dangers that cannot be predicted in the Icy Cave. Only those with Morning Star strength can be safe…”

Leylin steeled his expression and let the A.I. Chip continue research.

Leylin was counting on the Lamia fingerbone and the bloodline ignition experiment as well as the A.I. Chip’s analysis of the Morning Star realm to advance.

As long as he did persevered in that regard, he would definitely be able to reach the threshold of Morning Star.

If he was a regular Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock, just obtaining one of those would be difficult. However, Leylin had everything, and even without assistance all these would increase his chances of reaching Morning Star by a lot when compared to other Morning Star seedlings.

Leylin had no doubt about this.

……

*Sha sha!* The pendant at Leylin’s waist suddenly emitted bright light.

Leylin’s brows furrowed, and he tapped on a secret imprint.

“Is this Marquis Leylin, Sir Enforcer?” A low, hoarse voice was produced from the secret imprint.

This was the communications officer that the Ouroboros Clan had specifically allocated to him. He was in charge of contacting Leylin alone, and just by hearing his voice, Leylin could guess that something terrible had happened.

“I am Leylin. Is there anything wrong?” His voice was calm and steady, even causing the voice from the other side to become gentler.

“Headquarters has received a denouncement. Marquis Miranda is accusing Marquis Robin of attempting to kill her. There is also a large amount of evidence! Based on the information, something has also seemingly happened within Robin’s family.”

“Get to the point.” Leylin raised his eyebrows.

The voice on the other end hesitated, but still presented the news. “According to the order of the Elder Committee, Marquis Leylin is to head to Robin’s family immediately, and send Marquis Robin back to headquarters.”

“They want me to capture Robin? Do you know that he’s Mentor Gilbert’s student and my senior?” Leylin’s expression became serious.

“I know. This is Duke Gilbert’s order!” The voice was silent for a while, and then transmitted a black runic imprint.

This was similar to a person’s signature and could not be forged. This black rune was Gilbert’s own symbol, and Leylin definitely would not misidentify it.

“I understand.”

Feeling jittery, Leylin ended communications and fell into silence.

“Mentor, what are you thinking?” A long while later, a low voice was sounded in the tent.

Chapter 481: Bloodline Detector

The excitement dissipated with distance from the banquet hall, and the sounds were inaudible from the castle’s dungeons.

Dim light shone against the murky walls and reflected numerous shadows that looked like talons. The place reeked.

“We’re getting there!” Leylin knitted his brows and sized up the rooms and walls of the castle.

The dungeons of Magus castles were, more often than not, laboratories or storage rooms. He had yet to discover anything of value.

Most of the preventive and detective spell formations were unable to discover Leylin, allowing him to strut through the castle without being realised.

And the Leylin that everyone perceived in the banquet hall was obviously just a clone. Anyway, nobody would want to provoke him, and with a clone and the abilities of the A.I. Chip, a double was no problem.

On top of everything, Leylin could move freely without obstruction in the castle due to his Crystal Phase abilities. He could weaken the effects of many detective spell formations, stopping them from locating him.

‘Robin’s sudden emotional outburst wasn’t all that it seemed to be…’ Leylin rubbed his chin in deep thought. ‘Moreover, if the situation outside and this were linked, it would spell even more trouble…’

Robin, despite everything, was still his senior and cared a lot for Leylin when they first met. So it’d be unwise of Leylin to make a move before finding concrete evidence.

And Robin’s attitude was upright. If Leylin continued to be so unwilling to spare him, his reputation would likely go down the drain. ‘Biting the hand that feeds him’ would probably top the list of derogatory comments that would be made against him.

‘A.I. Chip! How’s the progress of the scan going?’ Leylin’s figure was engulfed by the pitch black as he looked at the walls and questioned in his heart.

[Blueprint of the castle established, spell array formation analysed: 58%, simulation in progress…]

The A.I. Chip intoned.

A three-dimensional image was projected in front of Leylin, showcasing the structures of many castles.

The castle of Robin’s family was comparable to Freya’s impressive Ancient Blood Serpent Castle and there were countless spell formations and bizarre phenomena caused by radiation.

Robin himself might not even know all the secrets within the castle.

The scanning of the A.I. Chip undoubtedly took a while but if Leylin stepped in to explore himself, he would be pretty much familiar with the whole internal layout after walking around so many times.

As for those sections which were yet to be analysed, it was unfortunate that the current capability of the A.I Chip was unable to compute them.

But all this was enough for him.

Under the gigantic projection, Leylin saw another empty construction buried deep underground. And its outer layer was the most Leylin’s A.I. Chip could reach.

The blank spaces were marked out by crimson symbols that prevented any forms of peeping, which surprised Leylin.

The core secret of the ancient castle must have been located there. Leylin followed the directions of the map and came face to face with a huge mural.

The mural depicted a grand historical scene—a horned demon skull was guillotined by armoured cavalry and robed Magi, bloodstains and burn marks painted all over their bodies as evidence of war.

It was realism at its best with a distinct sense of style. The 18 eyes of the demon were wide open and glaring at him, as if it was still alive.

‘The existence of this cellar is barely brushing the surface of Robin’s family’s secret. The true secret is hidden behind this mural…’ Leylin’s eyes lit up as he stroked the mural.

He felt like he could smell the stench of blood and fire as he moved close to the painting. It was as if he was facing the remains of an actual war, where the blood had yet to dry.

[Beep! Ahead is a rank 1 bloodline detector. After thorough scanning, it has been identified to be one that requires a specific incantation and bloodline to pass through.]

The database of the A.I. Chip as of now was as vast as the ocean, just a mere scan could send detailed information to Leylin’s memory.

‘Bloodline detector?’ Leylin touched his chin in deep thought. Since they’d chosen such a defensive measure, it definitely required the bloodline of Robin’s family, or even Robin himself, in order to get past it.

But, of course, Leylin was ahead of Robin in terms of his knowledge on bloodlines for he had dedicated more than one century towards the study of the bloodline experiments of Quicksand. His current situation might have been an unsolvable problem for other Magi, but it was a piece of cake for him.

[Beep! Data is being collected, probing for removal measures]

The A.I. Chip operated at Leylin’s command, and numerous blue symbols floated before him, forming countless dots before entering the mural.

The whole mural began to quiver and buzz as layers of dust collapsed, distinguishing the characters and making them appear more realistic than ever.

Especially the skull of the demon; an eerie green light seemed to be projecting from its eyes.

“Under the ultraviolet rays, the approaching descendant bloodline will come together and return to its origins…”

Leylin chanted a medieval incantation and a strand of black hair flew from his hand.

It was something that Leylin had stolen from the maid, Edda, when they fooled around, and was specially saved for situations like these.

Warlocks possess the most in-depth knowledge with regards to the power of bloodlines and were thus the most confident as well. So, when they set up traps or other preventive measures, all this would be taken into consideration.

Leylin had thus collected a strand of hair from a direct line of Robin’s family for his use.

*Hiss!* A ball of scarlet light wrapped the strand within itself under Leylin’s incantation.

The hair disappeared as the light dispersed, leaving behind a droplet of purplish-red blood that possessed a savage aura unique to Giant Kemoyin Serpents.

“That’s not enough!” Leylin shook his head vigorously and threw out a handful of crimson rocks. These rocks turned into a fine powder in midair and congregated with the droplet.

The powder transformed into a bright silver liquid upon contact with the droplet, helping it expand even as it diluted the colour of the blood to a washed-out red.

Leylin’s eyes glistened all the more as he watched this.

The incantation sounded more mournful with time and the faded red had agglutinated to a dark red blood clot, emitting a dangerously powerful aura.

If the previous bloodline was only Edda’s—a low-ranked Magus—then the current ball of blood had already reached the level of a Crystal Phase, and its aura was highly similar to Robin’s.

If Robin had installed this bloodline detector, then the key to it wouldn’t be as simple as the bloodline of a Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Otherwise, it’d be easy as pie for any Magus to uncover the secret here.

Surely, Robin would only use his own DNA as the key.

Therefore, Leylin was trying to generate a bloodline aura similar to that of Robin’s through that of his relative.

Though the DNA couldn’t be imitated, Leylin believed that it would be almost undetectable by the spells here given the supreme abilities of the A.I. Chip.

[Beep! Deduction completed for the removal of the spell!]

The A.I. Chip alerted and Leylin’s face lit up as he sang the incantation.

[Beep! Wrong aura, starting automated matching!]

The deep red ball of blood underwent some changes before changing into the aura of another Warlock.

“This is..” Leylin was confused for a moment. He quickly shook his head and sent the blood ball straight into the mural causing the two to fuse.

A layer of red started rippling on the surface of the mural and it was frightening. The characters in the mural, especially, took an eerie turn and started changing under the crimson light.

Thin scales and cysts started getting embedded their bodies and some of the cavalry even had horns growing on their heads and enormous wings on their backs. The mural had transformed into one of monsters.

The demon head, however, still had a sinister smile painted across his face that made Leylin’s hairs stand.

“There must be more to this mural, this seems foreboding…” Leyin muttered to himself and looked at the demon head again.

“A.I Chip, scan the mural! Find a similar specimen in the database!” Leylin ordered.

[Beep! Mission received, starting scan! Matching similar specimens in database…]

The A.I. Chip replied almost immediately while scanning through the database furiously.

[Beep! Similar image found!]

The A.I. Chip projected an oil painting in front of Leylin.

Within the painting was the huge image of a demon, its horns and eyes shockingly similar to the one in the mural.

“What is this?” Leylin looked into the information of that particular section almost immediately.

[The year 2315 of the Holy Calendar, a night where crows wept, the clone of Beelzebub arrived in Verdant City and cause a holocaust before being eliminated by an unknown Breaking Dawn Magus…]

The information presented by the A.I. Chip was very simplified. It was a mere few sentences and the image had a few missing portions on the edge.

These were the defects on the ancient book scanned earlier.

“Beelzebub, who represents gluttony?”

Leylin covered his mouth in shock, “Even if it’s just a clone, the only people who could eliminate it were Breaking Dawn Magi!”

Though details weren’t mentioned in the ancient book, the marked calendar system belonged to the ancient era where Morning Star Magi reigned, and there were definitely some in the Verdant City too.

“Amongst those who were injured, exactly how many were at Morning Star or even Breaking Dawn…” Leylin sighed.

And right at this moment, both the incantation and bloodline were stimulated and a crack split the mural from the centre, revealing a passageway that led underground.

The bloodline detector was broken by an outsider in a situation that did not alarm the owner.

Chapter 482: Prison Cell

Cries and howls sounded.

Indescribable noises echoed past Leylin’s ears as he stepped foot into the passageway. The secret that Robin had kept so tightly was about to be revealed to him.

‘There must’ve been something more to that expedition we did.’ Leylin thought about other matters as he took note of his surroundings.

‘Robin was evidently impatient when we last explored the Quicksand pocket dimension. And the information he held about the dimension was definitely not possible for someone who only worked internally. He’d probably known all the secrets within Quicksand Castle long ago, and went there specifically for it…’

Leylin’s guess was confirmed by the mural.

‘Robin’s family clearly inherited something important, and it might even be linked to the Quicksand Organisation.’

As his journey in the long passageway came to an end, he found himself between two rows of small prison-like cells.

The walls in these cells were covered in complex runes—many of which were familiar to Leylin—that were identical to the bindings of his own Magus Tower.

“The number of cells is crazy,” Leylin sized up the rows of cells that seemed to have no end to them, and caught glimpses of shadows within.

‘Exactly how many people is he planning to imprison?’ he thought as he came in front of a cell.

“Outsider detected, warning dispatched! Destroy!”

A deep voice masculine voice sounded as Leylin entered Shadow Stealth mode, the man was a formation genie in charge of this area, holding a position similar to that of his own tower genie.

“A.I. Chip,” Leylin lightly called out.

[Spiritual force interface discovered, forcefully manipulating data!]

The A.I. Chip replied mechanically, without an ounce of emotion.

The voice started to change in an instant, becoming hoarse.

“Invasion by outsider’s spiritual force! Activating first layer of defences!”

“Defence broken, activating level 2 firewall and alarms! Beginning self-destruction!”

“Invasion of outsider’s spiritual force into centre formation genie. Warning! Warning!”

“Destruction imminent in T minus 3, 2… Warning dispersed! Operation normal! Outsider’s spiritual force intercepted. No information has been leaked.”

Its voice that was initially submersed in fright and hoarseness became choppy. Light shone everywhere, illuminating the surroundings distinctly as it turned into a unique robotic one, that of the A.I. Chip.

An intelligence of this standard was nothing in front of Leylin’s A.I. Chip, it was only a matter of time before it was breached.

The administrator of this region had already changed from the formation genie to Leylin’s A.I. Chip.

After he successfully took it over, the place had become Leylin’s backyard. Even Robin would fail to detect him.

Of course, he had to thank his luck that he took care of the formation genie in a short time. Most formation genies would have self-destructed in time, and alerted their owners, landing Leylin in a heap of trouble.

Thankfully, Robin’s formation genie was of a lower rank. If it were a core formation genie set up by a Morning Star Magus, the A.I. Chip would have faced a lot of difficulties.

Now, Leylin was in control.

“Activate the observation window of cell 0023!” Following Leylin’s command, a white ray of light shone in the cell, ridding it of the darkness, the prisoner appearing in front of Leylin.

And the prisoner appeared in front of Leylin.

“Huh?! This is…” Leylin’s pupils dilated. “I’ve seen him somewhere…”

It was a Warlock; more accurately, a Giant Kemoyin Serpent Warlock.

This sense of familiarity between bloodlines was always accurate. The Warlock in front of him looked plaintive; not only was he almost naked—only clothed in pathetic rags—his whole body was riddled with large wounds.

Some granulation tissue could be seen squirming on the wounds, they were repairing themselves. It looked revolting.

“Don’t… Don’t come any nearer. You monster!” A low voice rumbled from the Warlock’s mouth.

“I’m not Robin!” Leylin cleared his throat and said.

“…” The Warlock raised his head and Leylin could see his goblin-like face. As if on cue, hope filled his eyes, replacing the dread and despair that existed before he saw Leylin.

“Sa- Save me! Please save me, Lord Leylin!”

He was like a drowning man that was grasping at the last straw as he crawled to the middle of the cell,

It was then that Leylin realised that both the legs of the Warlock were missing. He was completely disabled.

Though it could be healed using limb regeneration spells or other high-grade potions, Robin wouldn’t have been so nice.

“Tell me, what happened? Why are you here?” Leylin looked dreadfully displeased, and his voice was low as ever.

“It’s Robin! He captured me, my wife and my children and caged us here right after he attacked my family! He- He’s a demon!”

He seemed to have undergone an overly traumatic experience that caused him to stumble over his words.

“Master! Master! Take me away please, I’m begging you!” He shouted himself hoarse as his eyes watered.

Leylin could only shake his head at this scene. Though the advancements of Warlock were largely a result of their bloodlines, making moving up the ranks easier, to see such low willpower from a Warlock was still very rare.

High-ranking Magi usually had tenacious spirits, and could compose themselves quickly even in huge events.

“Tell me, what exactly did he do?” Two rays of lights shot from Leylin’s eyes, and made the Warlock speechless.

“He- He-” The Warlock sobbed and hugged his knees close, coiling into himself as he trembled endlessly.

“He- How dare he eat my Gwen! Oh Lord, she was only 7…”

“And Hugo, and Ron…” He could not stop listing name after name and looked absent-minded. He ended up wrapping his arms around his head, refusing to think anymore.

“A drastic change in temperament, imprisoning people, rumours of cannibalism, a mural to Beelzebub, the prince of gluttony!” Leylin let out a long sigh. The pieces came together to form a complete picture in his head.

“Wow, this is…” He did not know what to say. Robin’s desire for power had already reached such sick levels.

Though Leylin didn’t label himself a good guy, he would never go as far as Robin had.

Just then, the A.I. Chip relayed a piece of information to Leylin.

[Beep! Scan of underground laboratory completed! 341 prisoners: 34 Giant Kemoyin Warlocks, 22 Rank 3 Warlocks…]

“Other matters aside, things will be over for Robin the moment he gets exposed…” As Leylin went further, he saw that the cells on both sides were full of all kinds of Warlocks. Most of them had portions of their bodies missing, and he even saw a few elders from Robin’s own family.

It seemed like the elders who disappeared were all captured by Robin and locked up here.

Upon seeing Leylin, all the Warlocks went mad; some were wailing, some were bellowing in fury demanding that Leylin punish Robin for his sins. Even the eyes of the elders from Robin’s own family were filled with hatred and rage; they had evidently given up on Robin long ago.

“These Warlocks, most of them should be from the families that Robin eliminated…” Leylin sighed. Who would know that Robin would have the guts to seize his enemies and lock them up in a secret cellar like this?

And judging from their faces, Leylin bet they would rather have died on the battlefield.

Though Leylin pitied them, he didn’t order the A.I. Chip to deactivate the defence in the cells and allow them out.

After all, there were still many prisoners here that could cause chaos if let out.

Furthermore, Leylin still had more tasks to be performed that needed to be hidden from Robin.

“The core cell! Who is the one imprisoned there?” At the end of the passageway was a large cell. A few sparks could be seen jumping along the blood red electrified cage every now and then, firmly caging a Magus inside.

[No information found within the formation genie’s data, this place is marked top secret!]

The A.I. Chip sent back.

“Who are you?”

Standing beside the cage, Leylin was curious about the shadow inside. As the criminal who was under the tightest form of imprisonment in the entire cellar, this person could not be simple.

The prisoner raised his head after hearing Leylin’s voice, and Leylin’s pupils constricted in an instant before he broke out in cold sweat.

“Ro– Senior Robin?”

The person in the cage possessed a face that was bewitching, but malnourished beyond recognition. It was as though all flesh and blood had been drained from him. Robin could only force a smile before calling out for Leylin.

“Leylin, you’re here?”

“What is going on? Who is that ‘Robin’ out there?” Leylin’s expression was dark.

He felt an unusually familiar aura from this Robin who was in front of him, his smile unforgettable.

When he’d first entered Phosphorescence Swamp, Robin wore this exact same smile when welcoming Leylin as he stood by the entrance to the Ouroboros Clan headquarters.

“You should be able to guess by now,” Robin was very weak and had to pause after every other word.

All muscles seemed to have disappeared, leaving Robin a sack of bones.

If not for his features, Leylin would have thought the person in front of him was a skeleton.

Chapter 484: Cage of Gluttony

“Can you control them?” With regards to unforeseeable situations, Leylin was always more cautious.

He looked at Robin. After all, Robin was the clan leader and should have had some tricks up his sleeve.

“I’m afraid not! Noah’s taken away my authority. Moreover, once the Devouring Corridor is engaged, even the clan leader himself can’t control it…”

“Then what was the point of me saving you?” Leylin rolled his eyes and pulled Robin along, sprinting at a much higher speed.

Soon Robin proved that, as a clan leader, he was still very familiar with his castle. Under his guidance, after rushing through three rooms, Leylin managed to jump down from a window pane.

The moment before he left the window ledge, numerous tongues swiftly climbed forward and filled the entire room, but had not followed through their attack to the exterior of the castle. It was as if there was a chasm at the fringes of the castle that was difficult to pass through, or even barriers outside.

Only at that point in time did Leylin have the leisure to look at his secret imprint.

“Master… they’ve gone on the offensive! The situation here is extremely chaotic!” an impatient Parker transmitted even as the rumble of explosions from spells could be heard in the background.

“Today’s banquet is extremely lively!” Leylin looked at the ancient black castle. Through one of the windows in the living room, he could see explosions and flames being set off in the room.

“Put your own safety as the priority, and escape as soon as you can!” Leylin did not have the plans to return once more. After all, those still inside the castle were his subordinates. Subordinates fought to the death for their masters, not the other way around.

“Your nephew seems to be coming over!”

After they escaped, Robin’s head had been hanging low, his thoughts a mystery. Leylin indifferently set him down under an oak tree.

After hearing his tone, Robin raised his head and saw a black figure rushing down from the ancient castle, with a terrifying aura on his body.

That was the terrifying power of a Crystal Phase Magus. Coupled with the fact that he also possessed the ancient Gluttonous Desire, these had caused even Leylin to furrow his brows.

*Boom!* A figure landed in front of Leylin, and revealed a face that was mostly covered with runes.

“Noah!” Leylin let out a long sigh. Relatives Noah and Robin had very similar face shapes and auras. But with the influence of the gluttony imprint concealing and obscuring things, even Morning Star Magi might not have been able to realise the difference. However, there was no way Leylin would not be able to recognise him.

“Uncle…” Noah’s voice was low as he gazed at Robin who was seated on the ground. Complex emotions whirled across his face.

Shortly after, the black runes on his face started to move about, causing changes to its shape.His nose became sharper and eyes wider.

It took only a few tweaks for Noah to look drastically different, as he regained his original appearance.

“You’ve changed a lot…” Robin said after a moment of silence.

“I have not changed! Was this not always your wish anyway?” A vicious look flashed across Noah’s face. He bowed to Robin, his etiquette perfect to the point that nobody could nitpick about it. He was the perfect example of royalty.

“Very soon, the aspirations of our clan will be realised. I can feel it. Under the radiation of the sin of gluttony, my Kemoyin bloodline has been purified. I’m only one step away from becoming a pureblood Kemoyin Warlock!”

Mysterious rays shot out of Noah’s eyes as he bit his own finger to show Robin and Leylin the pure purplish-red blood.

Immediately, he greedily sucked the same finger which he’d previously bit, even as his face was immersed in pleasure.

“Crazy! You’ve completely gone insane!” Robin grabbed his head in pain and regret, “I should not have allowed you to inherit the imprint to begin with… No, I shouldn’t even have gone to Quicksand to uncover it!”

On the other side, Leylin looked at Noah proudly showing the purity of his bloodline, and was rendered speechless.

From what he saw, even though the Kemoyin bloodline of the other party was extremely pure, but compared to the first time Leylin had purified his Kemoyin bloodline, there was still an obvious difference.

Just based on the luster, if Leylin’s bloodline was initially a diamond, Noah’s bloodline was at most coal, or even worse than that.

And after having absorbed large amounts of radiation from the Lamia bone, his bloodline had been purified to an unprecedented level, and might even have surpassed the ancient Giant Kemoyin Serpent!

“I’m not crazy! For those trash to be the foundations to allow for our clan to flourish is definitely an honour for them!”

Noah lifted his hands in despair, his eyes bloodshot, “I have a feeling that if only I were to eat him, my bloodline would advance to an unprecedented level, and I could even advance to the Morning Star realm!”

Noah pointed at Leylin and his eyes widened, as if he was a plate of some delicacy.

That gaze made Leylin uncomfortable, especially when the other party started to contemplate on where he should start devouring him.

Leylin kept the Memory Crystal Ball that would be the evidence for later before he swiftly asked Robin, “Since he has already confessed, there shouldn’t be a problem if I start killing here in my name as an enforcer, right?”

“….” Robin’s face looked pale, and he did not utter a single word, only waving his hand.

After getting Robin’s approval, Leylin had no more misgivings.

In actual fact, just based on what Noah had done previously, Leylin would not hesitate to kill him. Still, it would be better with Robin’s understanding.

After all, the other party was his senior, and he would have to take note of the potential aftereffects.

“Tsk tsk! He actually dared to utter such words to me!” Noah licked his lips, and the imprint on his face went into action. “It’s decided! I’ll make sure you don’t get to leave this place, and I’ll slowly devour your meat, a kilogram a day!”

There were many ways for Magi to regenerate their muscles, a natural product of their high vitality.

As a result, even though the flesh might have been cut off, it would grow back in a designated amount of time. That was a characteristic that Noah had made use of when he imprisoned many Magi and left them in circumstances where they were better off dead than alive.

“Devour you! I’ll devour you!” Noah’s face warped as he went berserk, and he rushed towards Leylin like a beast. Black blood vessels rose from his body, and like tentacles, covered Leylin’s face.

At the tips of the blood vessels, needle-like structures appeared. Should it penetrate one’s sick, the bone marrow could even be sucked away in an instant.

“Gross!” Leylin shook his head, and a black ray erupted from his waist. The Meteor Sword brought with it the terrifying Kemoyin venom, and formed a black wall in front of Leylin.

Numerous blood vessels were immediately chopped off by the sharp edges of the Meteor Sword. The horrifying venom even started to corrode them, causing them to rot and fall loudly to the ground.

“Grrrr…” Noah opened his mouth, and large amounts of saliva dropped to the ground.

The current him was already under the absolute control of the sin of gluttony, and he had become a beast that moved around merely based on instinct.

Robin had turned his head, and dare not look at the miserable scene.

*Buzz!* During the attack, Noah’s body had been shrouded by a layer of black light. After the light dissipated, numerous pieces of black armour could be seen on his body.

No matter what, Noah was still a Crystal Phase Magus, and Leylin would not dare to belittle his abilities.

“Shadowflame Plague!” He swiftly chanted, and black flames shot forth from his robes like an aura, aiming for Noah who was rushing over.The black flames burned the crystal defence, heating up the surroundings so much that the air distorted.

Noah yelled and, like a beast, rushed out of the sea of fire and appeared before Leylin. The movement was almost instantaneous.

“What a shocking physicality!!” Leylin squinted his eyes as he saw the other party’s injuries almost instantly recovering on their own. As he saw the skin patching up, he couldn’t help but feel a little fearful.

After which, without any hesitation, he held his Cross Blade and hacked down from Noah’s head.

Sharp sword rays were created with the action as the terrifying venom was dissipated carelessly.

Leylin’s Toxic Bile had far surpassed other rank 2 innate spells, achieving a horrifying power. It was an effect entirely brought about by the maturation of his Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline under the effects of the Lamia fingerbone.

“Crossblade slash!” Black light in the form of a crucifix slashed down upon Noah’s body, causing a large vertical wound.

“AHHH!” Noah’s face flushed with blood, but he actually grabbed the blade of the sword.

Large amounts of white mist were emitted as his hands started to rot under the horrifying venom. The scene made Robin feel uneasy.

But Noah instantly revealed a smile that suggested that he had gotten away with something, and his eyes were no longer bloodshot.

“You actually were sane all this while!” Leylin cried out. That astonished him more than Noah inheriting the gluttony imprint and replacing Robin.

“It’s too late now to realise it!” The injuries on his abdomen and chest were all covered by a layer of black blood vessels, and his aura increased exponentially to a peak.

“Arcane Art, Cage of Gluttony!”

A black fog engulfed Leylin and Noah, and Robin’s face changed as he heard the gnawing sounds from within.

“The Cage of Gluttony?” On the other hand, Leylin who was shrouded in darkness casually waved both his hands forth in a bid to size up the strength of the formation.

“This isn’t the energy system of our world. It must be a formation from the path of another realm, a result of the inheritance of Beelzebub’s clone!”

Even as Leylin spoke, numerous mouths with ivory teeth surrounded him.

Chapter 486: Discovered

The threatening words only caused Leo’s hands to tremble a little, and the scroll remained tightly in his grip.

Relationships were based on strength, and this was something even more pronounced in the world of Magi.

Why would anyone be threatened by an ant? These could affect Leylin even up to the Morning Star realm, and at this point?

Leo sneered, his spiritual force continuously seeping into the scroll. At worst, he could just kill the opposite party and invite his Master to take part as they slew the rest of the Magi who could possibly know the secret.

The only powers that could restrain the Oakheart Clan were those at the Morning Star realm and above. The current Leylin didn’t even qualify to bargain.

Leylin understood this principle. What he sought was not a withdrawal, he just needed that moment of pause.

The moment Leo froze when Leylin’s voice was transmitted, he sprung into action.

“Kemoyin’s Scales!” “Toxic Bile!” “Intimidating Gaze!” Acting on the chant, all 3 innate spells immediately took effect.

Compared to the other methods of using spells or potions, a Magus’ innate spell would take effect in the blink of an eye. Thus, in times of danger, every Magus would first choose to use their innate spells, and Leylin was no exception.

A layer of shiny black scales immediately enveloped his entire body. The two domains of poison and Intimidating Gaze was launched in his attack without any reservations. At this critical moment, Leylin had burst forth with all his power.

Without any apprehensions, the Toxic Bile poisoned Noah who was standing by his side. Thereafter, the ripples struck the surrounding Crystal Phase Magi, creating countless waves.

After absorbing the Lamia bone’s radiation, the power of Leylin’s Intimidating Gaze had swelled by a few folds. The pressure was immense even for similarly-ranked Crystal Phase Magi.

“Such strength of the domains? Even average Crystal Phase Kemoyin Warlocks are not this strong!” The enormous amounts of life force caused the iron chains to start trembling.

The surrounding Magi, numbers 1 and 2, immediately cried out in alarm.

“Fatality’s Tip!” At such a juncture, Leylin did not show the slightest reservations. The black rays of death, aimed at the weakest link, number 3. It was like a vicious viper baring its ferocious teeth at its prey.

“Number 2, number 4, support!” Number 1 yelled immediately. As the leader of the team, he needed to help stall for time as Leo launched his rank 4 spell.

*Swoosh! Swoosh! Swoosh!* Multiple chains appeared like a wall, blocking Leylin’s advance.

“Cross Blade Slash!” Leylin held onto the Meteor Sword, its black blade dazzling. The iron chains started to break apart into pieces, dropping to the ground one after the other.

The remaining unbroken ones started to erode away, revealing multiple tiny holes.

*Pak!* The iron chain was split apart. The rays of death appeared before number 3.

”You want my life?” Number 3 looked like a kindly old man, and had extremely thin and long lips. At that moment, he lost all self-control and started howling as his face warped.

“Thunderstorm Shield!” Sparks of blue electricity danced around, forming a massive blue shield in front of him. On top of the shield were flickering multiple streams of current.

*Rumble!* The death rays clashed with the blue shield. Two different streaks of brilliance collided in midair.

Although the shield was showing signs of being unable to endure for long, it bought him enough time for backup to arrive. Seeing the support, number 3 broke out into a smile.

But the next moment, his face froze. With a flash of his body, another identical Leylin appeared in front of number 3 and dashed forward.

“Lightning Spear!” Number 3 waved his hand and two shafts appeared in his hands that were bathed in arcs of blue electricity. Following his command, the two long spears darted towards the two ‘Leylin’s.

*Crackle!* One ‘Leylin” was pierced by the long spear, and the slight explosion caused darkness to fill the whole sky. The same happened to the other Leylin.

“No!” Panic washed over number 3 and he turned around.

Yet, it was too late. Leylin emerged from a crack in the darkness and dashed directly towards him.

“Multilimb Strength!” A strange, unusual image manifested behind Leylin. It was a huge, tall humanoid covered in green scales. It had three thick and bulky arms on the left, and four on the right. It gave off a thunderous roar.

Leylin’s muscles swelled instantly, bringing a kind of shiny luster to his muscular curves. Rays of green and black combined, forming a terrifying energy.

“Innate defense spell!” Number 3 revealed his last trump card. Numerous currents covered his whole body, forming an armour made wholly out of blue lightning.

“Break!” Bolts of lightning were flung at Leylin’s body. However, they were absorbed by the Kemoyin Scales. Leylin’s hands violently moved forward and grabbed the opposite party’s lightning armour, tearing it in half!

*Zip!* With his terrifying prime body quality and under the enhancement of Multilimb Strength, the lightning armour was torn apart like paper.

The wild electric current destroyed Leylin’s defences, and branded his skin and muscles in a horrifying black. Yet, Leylin did not even bat an eyelid.

Although he had other ways of breaking through the other side’s blockade, he was in a race against time to succeed. Thus, he believed the best course of action would be this that was simulated multiple times by the A.I. Chip.

His innate defences screeched as they were ripped apart, and number 3 turned pale, trying to flee. But how could Leylin let him do so?

With a huge earth shattering punch, number 3’s head was cracked apart, sending splashes of red and white liquid all around.

“Number 3!” Number 1 and number 2 helplessly watched this execution. Now, with one member absent, their formation wasn’t whole.

Numerous iron chains grouped up into a cage, but Leylin broke through easily with its instability.

The moment he escaped, horrifying white rays of light grazed through the entire region. A large amount of soil, rocks and even corpses were vaporised, forming a long, deep, ravine.

A rank 4 spell wasn’t comparable to a Morning Star Magus’ Arcane Art, but a Crystal Phase Magus would not be able to withstand it. If Leylin hadn’t escaped in time, he would have perished under the horrifying white light.

“Garbage! You’re all a bunch of garbage!” Seeing Leylin’s silhouette disappearing in the horizon, Leo immediately chided number 1 and 2. They hung their heads low, with pain and sorrow in their eyes.

Leo was breathing heavily. It took a lot for a rank 3 Magus to use a rank 4 spell.

If it had been put to used by a rank 4 Morning Star Magus, things wouldn’t have been so slow, and Leylin wouldn’t have escaped.

“Get him!” Leo vented his anger. He brought along the remaining Magi and gave chase.

“Do not let him get away!” Wild whistles and screams sounded from both sides. Leo’s eyes burned with an unmasked hatred.

This was the same Leylin that made him suffer a huge loss with that astral stone!

If it was just that one single incident, all that would happen would be a scolding from his grandfather and it wouldn’t be a big deal. What infuriated him was the fact that Leylin had discovered the secret of the stardust bugs!

My goodness! If his private collections were discovered, he would be brutally torn to pieces by the enraged female Morning Star Magi!

The methods Morning Star Magi used in tormenting others were unbearably cruel, and feared by even the most savage of devils. Naturally, Leo felt the same way.

Unfortunately, the opposite party had managed to destroy all traces, and Leo had been left with no leads to follow.

As such, his grandfather, the King of Azure Mountain, personally made a trip to locate a Morning Star realm Prophet. After paying an enormous price, they obtained Leylin’s definite identity.

As for the enormous price, his grandfather was still working on paying off the debt.

The prophecy showed that Leylin was just a newly advanced Crystal Phase Magus. Hence, the job of hunting him and silencing him fell on Leo.

In order to succeed, he’d brought along a large number of men. He even called upon his spy in the Ouroboros Clan, Noah.

Coincidently, while he was in the Ouroboros Clan’s territory in the midst of discussions with Noah, Leylin showed up and bumped into them.

If the location had been Leylin’s Onyx Castle, with the presence of the Magus Tower, Leo and his men would not have been able to hide. Furthermore, without any insider help in the Ouroboros Clan’s core territory, Leylin was sure Leo wouldn’t have dared make any opposing moves. But now? They would never give up this golden opportunity!

Leo’s eyes reddened with anger. At that moment, he noticed Leylin stopping. Watching Leylin descending on a bare rock on top of the hill, he and a few of his men immediately followed up and surrounded him.

“Why? With nowhere to hide, are you now seeking death?” Having surrounded Leylin, Leo raised his brows and jeered at him.

Leylin shook his head. He’d been secretly conversing with his A.I. Chip.

[Beep! Scan completed! Articles detected on the opposite side do not exceed the Morning Star realm. No other Morning Star realm undulations detected in the surroundings!]

Leylin was pleased with the conclusion and he secretly sighed a breath of relief, “No. You flies are disgusting, it’s about time I cleaned up.”

Previously, when he’d fled in disarray, what caused him more worry than the rank 4 spell scroll in the opposite party’s hands was the possible presence of the Azure Mountain King.

However, thankfully, he hadn’t appeared, only sending forth some Crystal Phase Magi instead.

With Leo leading a team of elite Magi and the use of the rank 4 scroll, it would’ve been no problem to deal with an average Crystal Phase Magus, even one from the Ouroboros Clan. However, Leylin wasn’t your average Magus. Even Morning Star seedlings would be tossed around by him!

“Flies?” Leo’s face swelled as he flushed red, ”Wait till I catch you. I’ll use a magic scroll and turn you into a red-eyed fly!”

‘A.I. Chip! Probe the surrounding space and establish a model. Begin charting the best path for a massacre!’ Leylin’s eyes glinted with a dangerous light.

Since the opposite party had discovered his identity, there was nothing to hold him back anymore. This matter had to come to an end.

Chapter 487: The Pursuit and the Appearance

Leylin was extremely offended by the attempt on his life.

Furthermore, Leo was the chief of the Oakheart Clan. If he was killed here, it would be a huge blow to the Azure Mountain King.

The chase with Leo previously had not been merely for his entertainment. It was for the A.I. Chip to gather vital data and create a plan.

Right now, with the data compiled, the A.I. Chip had come up with a large number of plans. It filtered through them continuously, leaving only the most feasible ones.

[Model establishment completed, simulated combat victory rate: 67.9%!]

It reported.

“Enter supplementary mode!” Leylin’s voice was laced with a lethal aura.　　

[Target number 1 is condensing energy particles. Determined to be the rank 3 spell Aurora Beam! Dodge to the right by 3.7m immediately!]

The A.I. Chip warned.

As per the simulation and the A.I. Chip’s deductions, target 1, Leo, activated a necklace of colourful gems in his hands. A powerful aurora burst forth, immediately attempting to swallow the entire area up along with Leylin.

Leylin dodged to the side in a flash at the same moment the enemy made his move.　

“Aurora Beam!” Leo triggered the high-grade magic artifact in his hand. Immediately, a powerful multicoloured torrent drowned out the stone that Leylin was standing on, causing the terrain to cave.

[Target defined as Number 3 is undergoing transformation. Estimated to be a descendant of the Banu Tribe. Bloodline activated, morphing into a Barbarian Bear!]

“Aaaooo…” The moment the A.I. Chip ended the report, one of the men standing by Leo’s side let out a thunderous roar and started ripping his clothes apart. He morphed into a brutal bear with stiff white fur. 　

Countless shards of sparkling ice circled around its body, emitting a freezing chill that formed billows of white fog around it.

“Kill!” Leylin’s eyes gleamed blue. He danced gracefully, and lightheartedly managed to dodge from under the huge bear’s palm, sliding up in front of it instead. The Meteor Sword traced a beautiful arc as it flitted across the bear’s body.

The white fur was slashed apart, revealing bright red flesh and an outline of the internal organs. Blood splattered all around.　　

Unable to believe its defeat, the enormous creature howled loudly at first, but soon its voice tapered away until it fell silent.

The earth rumbled as the carcass of the white bear resembling a large mountain collapsed onto the ground, causing large amounts of dust to fly. The fur of the bear started to shrink back into its pores, and soon returned to its original form of a Magus.

“Number 4!” Number 1 and number 2 cried out in alarm, their eyes fixed on their dead comrade.

They clearly knew the abilities of number 4, and the fact that after his transformation, he would be able to resist a rank 3 spell easily. And yet, he’d died this quickly!

Number 1’s eyes darted towards the Meteor Sword in Leylin’s hand. His eyes narrowed and his pupils dilated, “Be wary of his sword! There’s something strange about it!”

The Meteor Sword was originally a high-grade magic artifact, but through multiple improvements and optimisations, its quality had improved to that of a piece of magic equipment. Additionally, with the supplementary power of Toxic Bile, the current Meteor Sword could be considered a big threat to any Crystal Phase Magus! 　

Leylin enjoyed handling foes like the bear, all brawn and no brain.

“Hocada Beast!” On the other side, witnessing Leylin’s explosive retaliation, Leo’s face hardened and he yelled for his trump card.

Howls rang out as a creature manifested out of thin air that had the upper body of a wolf and the lower half of an octopus. It landed right in front of Leylin. The countless suction pads on its arms looked like magnificent blooming flowers. 　　

“It’s no use!” Leylin muttered in a low voice, his silhouette dodging in a flash, avoiding the multiple arms’ attack. He stopped in front of the Hocada Beast.

“Multilimb Strength!” The silhouette of a Multi-Armed Race member appeared behind Leylin, formidable power seeping into his body.

[Ding! Multilimb Strength in operation. Host’s power is increasing!]

The A.I. Chip reported.

Leylin grasped his sword firmly, and hacked at the creature’s brain. The beast started cracking apart as fissures arose on its body as if it was breaking glass. They spread all over its body, before pieces of flesh began to simply fall apart.

By the end, the creature’s body had been sliced into ruin, eventually crumbling apart like dirt.

“Damn, ho… how are you so strong?” After executing the Hocada Beast, Leylin turned to look at Leo, the killing intent in his eyes causing the Oakheart Clan chief to feel a chill down his spine.

“You’re next!” Leo could faintly make out what Leylin mouthed, and could see the mockery in the eyes that were staring into his.　

Having never experienced these circumstances before, it was a huge blow to his self-esteem.

“Number 1, number 2, follow me!” Leo roared ferociously.　　

“Stormwall!” A pale green whirlwind emerged from the short black staff in his hand. The huge whirlwind then formed a terrifying barricade that seemed to be made of sharp blades as it rushed towards Leylin.

Number 1 and 2 nodded their heads, and simultaneously cast their own spells.

“Water Elemental Rite!” A huge blue ball of water appeared on the ground under number one’s chant.

“Arctic Draft!” Number 2 summoned a huge bout of chilly air and had it adhere to the ball of water.

The icy wind sucked away the heat from the ball of water, causing a huge reaction as a frightening ball of ice was formed.　

“Combination spell—Iceberg Torrent!”

The huge ball of ice was like a meteorite as it darted towards Leylin, smashing onto the ground.

“Impressive!” The blue light in Leylin’s eyes dimmed. His body was covered in frost, and yet the Meteor Sword did not deviate even slightly from its trajectory, forging ahead and crashing into it to open up a pathway.

The cold could freeze the average rank 3 Magus to death. To Leylin, though, all it could do was slow him down.

“Shadowflame Plague!” A huge amount of dense black flames clashed with the whirlwind that had now developed into a hurricane. The two clashed, each trying to destroy the other.

“Compared to combination spells, it’s wiser to rely on magic equipment. That way there won’t be anything to worry about!”

Leylin tore through the hurricane and stepped in front of Leo, his eyes glistened with a piercing chill that gave the other man goosebumps.

“Fatality’s Tip!” Black rays of death streaked across the vast sky, reaching Leo in a flash. Just as they were about to strike, a black wooden cross on his neck immediately flashed and formed a rune that represented new life and regeneration.　

The barrier shattered as the rays of death dissipated. A majority of the attack had been blocked by the defensive runes, but even then it had only diverted the attack as a thumb-sized hole appeared on Leo’s body, bleeding profusely.

“How…. How can this be?” Leo glared at Leylin, the fear in his eyes palpable.

He let out an odd cry, turned his head and fled. Number 1 and number 2 fulfilled their duties as bodyguards faithfully, blocking Leylin from giving chase.

“Giving up after encountering such trivial problems, you certainly deserve to be called a descendant of a big family!” Leylin shook his head and laughed as his gaze on Leo was filled with mockery.

Seeing the blood-covered Leylin, number 1 and 2 both felt a chill down their spines. In their time accompanying Leo, they had seen their fair share of slaughter. Yet, this was the first time they’d met someone as valiant and ferocious as Leylin.

Both of them had cursed Leo umpteen times for provoking Leylin, but Leylin had what they needed, so they had no choice but to take action.

“Get out of the way, or else you will die!” Leylin drew his sword and pointed at them. Number 1 and number 2 exchanged glances. Determination in their eyes, they both shook their heads.

“Pity!” Leylin had no sympathy for the suicide fighters of large families. Moreover, these two from the Oakheart Clan had no means of defence remaining. Armed with the determination to die in battle, they stood in front of Leylin and blocked his path.

……

“Damn it! Why? WHY?” Leo was fleeing madly, his heart in absolute turmoil.

Not only had he brought along a rank 4 spell scroll for this, he’d even brought with him a large number of potions and magic equipment. He’d even had four Crystal Phase Magi accompanying him!　　

With such power, to deal with a newly promoted Crystal Phase Magus ought to have been a simple matter. And yet, the opponent was unfathomably terrifying, practically wiping out his entire team

*Krrich!* Suddenly, the sound of two crystals cracking was emitted from his chest.

After hearing the sound, the blood drained from his face and he panicked. He sped up as he dashed along. “Number 1 and Number 2 are also dead? Useless indeed!”

Soon after, he ground his teeth and retrieved a communication device. He punched some secret code on it and the message was sent from his hand. 　　

　　

“I still have a chance! I am the chief of the Oakheart Clan, so long as I make it back, grandfather will absolutely not turn a blind eye to…” Leo cut a sorry figure as he fled in disarray, speaking words of encouragement to himself.　　

“Got you!” a voice was suddenly transmitted from behind him. He turned his head, only to see Leylin rushing towards him at the speed of lightning, a brilliant black streak. At this rate, he would catch up in about a mere ten seconds.

The new blood on Leylin’s body was obviously from number 1 and 2.

“No! You cannot kill me! I am the chief of the Oakheart Clan! If you let me go, I can give you whatever you want…..” Leo ran madly, his voice turning hoarse as he yelled out terms of surrender.

“I only want your life!” Leylin knew promises made under such circumstances were not reliable. Hence, without emotion, his killing intent increased. He speed increased threefold, and he was but an arm’s length from Leo and his petrified face.

“Die!” Leylin drew his black Meteor Sword.

“Stop!” An extremely imposing voice spoke directly into Leylin’s mind.

Chapter 488: Confrontation with Morning Star

‘This voice… a Morning Star Magus?’ Leylin’s pupils narrowed. If someone were to be named as the Crystal Phase Magus with the greatest knowledge of the Morning Star realm in the central continent, it would be himself. Through the A.I. Chip’s simulations and deductions, as well as previously collected information, he already had a deep understanding of the Morning Star realm.

The owner of this voice could not be disguised, the words emanated power and a slight aura of rules… This was not imitable by Magi below the Morning Star rank.

“Grandfather! Save me!” Leo suddenly smiled, and slowed down ahead of Leylin.

In the presence of a Morning Star Magus, Leylin absolutely could not harm him. He completely trusted his grandfather, as well as the strength of the Morning Star realm.

“Hmm?!” However, Leylin noticed something different. ‘Although the nature of the aura has not changed, its power is only at the Crystal Phase at its peak… Could it be a puppet… or some sort of clone?’

This was, after all, within the boundaries of the Ouroboros Clan. If Morning Star Magi from other clans stepped in, it would be seen as a provocation, leading to war.

But the restrictions on this kind of clone seemed unclear.

After all, it was very difficult for Morning Star Magi to create a clone of equal strength. Very few succeeded because most of them were limited to the strength of rank 3 Morning Star..

With Leylin’s sharp eyesight, he could already see a streak of blue rushing there from afar.

“Haha… You’re done for!” Leo laughed carefreely. But shortly after, his smile faded as his surroundings swiftly shrunk and grew again. A scene swept across like a parabolic curve and he ended up looking at a patch of yellow ground.

“My head, my head was chopped off…” he said with the last of his consciousness.

Leo then fell into eternal darkness.

Space shook as a blue shadow suddenly emerged before Leylin’s eyes, looking at Leo’s headless corpse with an angered expression.

“I told you to stop just now!” His voice was deep. It seemed to carry an irresistible compulsion to obey every word of his.

This majestic aura could only be developed after obtaining absolute power and being in a high position for a long period of time.

Leylin was also analysing this Morning Star Magus. Although he had not seen the Azure Mountain King before, he had read up on him. The other party looked exactly as in the portraits— a head of blue hair with eyes that twinkled like stars.

Yet, those eyes were now blazing in anger. This was the rage of a Morning Star Magus! It was enough to burn Leylin to ashes.

Yet, Leylin simply shrugged his shoulders, “Sorry! I killed him!”

If this was his main body, Leylin would have no chance to flee. However, it was only a clone, and there was still hope for escape.

“Do you know who he is?” The Azure Mountain King’s eyelids drooped. Someone familiar with him would know that this was a sign of irrepressible rage.

“The chief of the Oakheart Clan…” Leylin shook his head and stared at the Azure Mountain King, “I don’t care who he is. Someone who has bad intentions towards me can only repent with death!”

“Then let me tell you something too. The last Magus who dared to offend the Oakheart Clan still has his ashes buried below the steps of Azure Mountain City!” The sparkle in the Azure Mountain King’s eyes had reached a limit.

A circular mirror appeared in front of him, reflecting Leylin’s figure.

“Strip!” The Azure Mountain King gently pointed to the Leylin in the mirror.

A hum sounded and, as if he had been rejected by the world itself, Leylin immediately felt the elemental particles that were in complete harmony with him previously leave him one after another, as if stripping him down to an ordinary person.

The domain of a Morning Star Magus displayed its terrifying power once again!

“That’s not it!” Leylin was a Magus who had previously experienced a true Morning Star domain when he’d been caught by Demon hunter Cyril. He naturally noticed the difference between this domain and that of a Morning Star Magus.

The situation this time was much better. His connection with the elemental particles was still barely holding on. As long as he used more spiritual force than usual, he would still be able to communicate with them and invoke his spells.

This was just equivalent to his spiritual force being suppressed to a fifth of its normal amount.

A bitter smirk appeared at the corner of Leylin’s lips. Even if the other party was only a clone whose total amount of spiritual force and magic power was around the same as his own, he was no match for him in the understanding of spells and laws. Even this simple suppression had immediately put him in a dilemma.

With over half his body’s strength being suppressed, how was he to fight a peak rank 3 Magus? Leylin shook his head, feeling that he had been too optimistic previously.

‘However, this is also an opportunity! An opportunity to confront a Morning Star Magus head on, and to gather data!’ Leylin’s eyes sparkled. If he wanted to advance to the Morning Star realm, he could not be lacking in knowledge of it. Although the A.I. Chip had previously used the data he had to simulate some experiments, the lack of samples meant that its progress was still less than 20%.

And now, a Morning Star Magus’ clone had appeared in front of him! He had no need to defeat it; he needed only to stall for time as the A.I. Chip gathered data that would be greatly beneficial to him.

‘The A.I. Chip should be able to collect enough data from this fight.‘ Leylin’s eyes blazed brighter. He pulled out the Meteor Sword, a metallic hiss ringing from the blade.

At the same time, a layer of dark Kemoyin Scales covered Leylin’s body. The phantom of a huge Multi-Armed Race member appeared behind him as well.

‘Since my elemental particle connection has been suppressed, I can only rely on my physical strength!’ With Multilimb Strength in full effect, Leylin’s entire body enlarged and numerous muscles swelled up as a dark green membrane emerged on the surface of his body.

Following a deep shout, Leylin’s Meteor Sword emitted numerous rays of light that shot towards the Azure Mountain King like a rain of arrows.

“You actually dare to resist?” The Azure Mountain King frowned.

How many years had it been since such a low-ranked Magus provoked him? 200 years, 300? He had never encountered this situation since he’d advanced.

After a momentary daze, the Azure Mountain King was overcome by boundless anger. The sound of metal striking metal rang out as a translucent spherical film appeared around his body. Despite seeming like a mere bubbly layer, it actually blocked all of the black rays.

“Die!” Leylin’s figure emerged just as the rays disappeared. He suddenly jumped up, and the Meteor Sword slashed across the void, bringing with it a ferocious wind that was aimed at the Azure Mountain King.

Black gases shot out of both sides of the blade, so corrosive that it seemed like even the surrounding void would melt. The ground was continuously eroded.

*Bang!* The blade, which contained a terrifying poison, was blocked by an aged palm. Although this palm seemed extremely old, with green veins popping out of the skin, it was unmoving like a hill. Even the skin hadn’t been pierced through.

The Azure Mountain King raised his right hand with a mocking smile, watching Leylin’s expression change.

“Abandoning elemental spells and switching to physical strength, this method is not bad when under elemental suppression. Unfortunately, your tricks are too low-levelled…”

“Impossible, your body can’t be this strong!” Leylin blurted out.

The Azure Mountain King chuckled, “Do you know what point mass is? And the meaning of the Morning Star realm? The power of the point mass, soul force, is the only power a Morning Star Magus has! However, it greatly surpasses spiritual force and physical strength, having achieved a terrifying qualitative change!”

A layer of crystal-clear light emerged above the Azure Mountain King’s palm. With his right hand grabbing the Meteor Sword, he mercilessly punched the blade with his left.

The Meteor Sword howled out a sad cry as the blade cracked. The mere physical attack of a Morning Star Magus could actually damage the Meteor Sword, which was comparable to magic equipment!

“Although I don’t specialise in physical attacks, as long as I have the amplification of soul force, my vitality will be able to break through the boundaries and ultimately allow me to attain the perfect body of Morning Star!

“This strength of yours, and your spiritual force, will only collapse in front of soul force!”

As if confirming the Azure Mountain King’s words, a large number of crystal-clear light blades appeared before Leylin, drowning him within.

The power of the point mass, also known as soul force, was the next evolution of spiritual force. Only Morning Star Magi could possess such a thing, and it was the first time it had shown its terror in front of Leylin.

As he watch Leylin being drowned by the light blades, the Azure Mountain King smiled.

The light blades, which were composed of soul force, were not only powerful in physical attacks. They could even attack the spiritual sea within a Magus’ sea of consciousness!

Magi who were below the Morning Star realm, without a soul force defence of equivalent power, did not have the slightest chance of resisting these blades.

This was the reason Morning Star Magi had almost no enemies at rank 3. Soul force was just too terrifying!

Yet, the smile on the Azure Mountain King’s face only lasted a moment, and his expression immediately hardened.

With his soul force, he sensed that Leylin might have sustained injuries all over his body, but he had survived the slashes from the soul light blades.

Soon after, the Azure Mountain King felt the weight on his hand fade as the Meteor Sword landed in them.

*Bang!* A dark green shadow rushed out of the sea of blades, its scaly body covered by a raging dark green film.

“Multilimb Smash!” Leylin had thrown away the Meteor Sword, and as the physical strength of his hands surged, he threw his fist at the Azure Mountain King’s defence. The mere power of this punch could shake space itself.

The soul force of a Morning Star Magus surpassed spiritual force in terms of quality. Due to this enormous disparity in strength, most of the methods of Magi were rendered ineffective.

But Leylin was not limited to the methods of Magi. He possessed a secret technique from another world— Multilimb Strength!

A large phantom of a Multi-Armed Race member appeared behind Leylin’s body, growling into the sky.

Chapter 489: Breaking through the Defense

Spiritual force was fundamental to a Magus.

In the beginning, as acolytes, all Magi would start with meditation. They would begin to meditate in a willpower rune of their own, and construct a core spirit body, together with a sea of consciousness.

After advancing to the realm of official Magi, they would have a conversion of elemental essence amounting to 80% or more, in order to advance into rank 2.

After materialising spiritual force in rank 2, and then passing through the three stages of Vapour, Hydro, and Crystal in rank 3, the point mass would finally be formed.

The point mass was fundamental to Morning Star Magi. It was the path for everyone, even spirits! Once they broke past this bottleneck, the spiritual force in a Magus’ sea of consciousness would sublimate to form soul force.

This was a threshold in ancient times, used to mark the difference in strengths between Magi. Only those who were capable of using soul force would be considered to have stepped foot into the world of ancient Magi!

As soul force had a horrifying suppressive power, low ranking Magi would lose their ability to communicate with the elements, and would end up disconnected from the elemental particles. Those who were suppressed would be unable to resist or escape. Many Morning Star Magi liked using this trick in their domains. Hence, over time, they successfully enhanced the prestige of a Morning Star Magus.

Since his normal powers had been suppressed, Leylin had no choice but to use another system of power instead. Luckily, he indeed had such a thing on hand, a terrifying secret from another world— Multilimb Strength!

Leylin had relied on the dark green membrane to avoid injury and death when drowned in the sea of light blades.

A booming sound rang out, as if a tall mountain had collapsed to crashing waves. The phantom stood behind Leylin, performing the same moves as him.

Formless streams of air started developing a pressure as even the ground behind the Azure Mountain King started caving in. The wind continuously rolled in, coagulating to form a substance that was stronger than granite.

*Po!* The defensive layer on the Azure Mountain King deformed completely as a look of disbelief took over his face.

“Even for a Morning Star, you’re merely just that!” the blood-soaked Leylin burst our laughing. He then threw his fist forward, aiming for the Azure Mountain King’s face.

*Boom!* The Azure Mountain King slid across the floor like a train hurtling through, leaving long tracks on the ground.

“The skin of a Morning Star is thick indeed!” Leylin flung his clenched fist without any traces of excitement on his face.

He’d definitely felt it when his punch landed, A barrier with a starry radiance appeared on the Azure Mountain King’s face, blocking his attack. Hence, he was only shaken up slightly by the attack and did not sustain any major injuries.

“Soul force defence?” Leylin scrutinised the dull-faced Azure Mountain King as he stood up, secretly conversing with his A.I. Chip, ‘How much data has been collected on the target?’

[Data collection at 12.1%. Further interaction with target needed, it is suggested to break through the soul force defences!]

The A.I. Chip responded.

‘You still want me to try breaking through soul force?’ Leylin smiled bitterly and shook his head. If it weren’t for the purpose of gathering intelligence, he would not be so silly as to clash with a Morning Star Magus in the first place, ‘Begin simulations, calculate a path of retreat!’

Seeing how things had turned out to his disadvantage, he immediately made plans to retreat. But at the current moment, it was no longer up to him to decide if he could leave. Leylin saw that the Azure Mountain King wasn’t seriously injured. A huge amount of the blaze continued to surround him, burning wildly.

Traces of black smoke streamed from his nostrils, eyes and ears. He was really fuming mad. Morning Star Magi had always been placed on top of a pedestal, much like kings. At the current moment, he felt like a king who’d been bitten by an ant as he was walking down the street.

In the Azure Mountain King’s eyes, as long as one had not reached the rank of Morning Star, their existence was similar to that of an ant. To be bitten by an ant, and even be humiliated by it, how could anyone bear it?

“You… How. Dare. You. Insult. Me…” The Azure Mountain King’s face scrunched up, his rage-filled words staggered apart.

“Such plaintive whines of defeat, I’ve heard them too often…” Leylin did not give the opposite party a chance to rebuke him, dashing forward.

Even in a simple match of speed, Leylin would be lacking compared to the opponent. Therefore, the only way for him to escape successfully would be to slow him down by inflicting some degree of injury.

“I want to incinerate your soul for a hundred centuries!” The Azure Mountain King bellowed loudly, the imposing aura emanating from his body. Even the sky started to darken, revealing the sparkling of stars.

Only a Morning Star Magus could thoroughly grasp the power of a domain. In any case, the current Leylin had reached his rank 3 limits, infinitely nearing to a rank 4. Hence, he was able to portray a portion of the power of his domain.

Being enveloped in the Morning Star domain, Leylin felt like he had fallen into a swamp. Every single move was tedious.

“Soul Armour!” A layer of translucent, full-bodied armour appeared on the Azure Mountain King. Judging from his attitude, it looked like he was ready to take on Leylin with pure strength to erase the humiliation.

[Multilimb Strength operating, estimated remaining time: 3 minutes 57 seconds!]

Noting the hint of the A.I. Chip, an unrestrained Leylin amplified his power to the maximum. He struck the Azure Mountain King head on.

The earth shook as a silhouette of dark green and another of translucent blue collided with each other continuously. Their every punch and kick seemed to rip the sky apart, creating countless tremors on the ground.

Sharp, ear-piercing explosions boomed continuously from where they struck. Once the dust was dispelled, an entire huge region would’ve been knocked off the map.

*Bang!* A translucent fist from the armoured body smashed Leylin’s chest viciously. Multiple scales cracked and flew with explosive lights of dark green radiances.

Leylin’s face turned red, and some black rays of light appeared on his hand, “Fatality’s Tip!”

As if the reaper himself had descended to the earth, a terrifying explosive light sprang forth. With how close they were, even the Azure Mountain King did not even have the chance to dodge.

Although the other party had suppressed his elemental connections, he was merely a clone after all, and his main body was not on site. Thus, Leylin could still break through the opponent’s soul force, forcefully converging elemental essence. All it required was a huge spiritual force consumption.

Leylin had held back on his trump card until now. Firstly, there had been no real opportunity to use it, and secondly, he was biding his time, waiting for the Azure Mountain King to take the bait.

As for the data on his opponent, he’d constantly kept that in mind.

“You did not abide by the rules!” The expression on the Azure Mountain King’s face said it all. Leylin clearly understood what he meant, yet he didn’t care. There hadn’t been any agreements on the usage of spells in battle. Furthermore, the opponent was a Morning Star Magus who had made the first move. In a matter of life and death, who would abide by rules?

Leylin’s pretence of having supreme bodily strength had successfully tricked the Azure Mountain King.

The most terrifying thing about a Morning Star Magus, and also the fundamental of their power, was soul force spells!

Watching the flustered and exasperated Azure Mountain King getting ready to retaliate, Leylin almost couldn’t hold back his laughter.

The rays of death reached the Azure Mountain King in a flash, clashing with the translucent armour.

“AAAHH…..” The Azure Mountain King yelled, the void and stars behind him shook as a huge amount of blue light converged on his armour.

Explosions sounded as the A.I. Chip reported to him, [Multilimb Strength at full power!]

How could Leylin miss this golden opportunity? He immediately yelled, releasing all the power remaining in him. Feeling the steady flow of energy seeping into his body, Leylin charged wildly towards the defence of the Azure Mountain King.

An enormous iron fist landed on the armour mercilessly, and the translucent layer shook.

The Azure Mountain King couldn’t believe his eyes as his armour cracked, blasting apart in a loud explosion. The black rays of death arrived at his chest, and pierced through him like arrows.

[Target’s soul force defence breached, data being collected!]

The A.I. Chip took the opportunity to collect massive amounts of data while it was available. Leylin too, had unknowingly absorbed some residual form of data from the Azure Mountain King.

“Shadow Prison! Dense Fog Frontier!” Watching the Azure Mountain King cut a sorry figure while retreating, Leylin continued to launch his spells.

A menacing black fog spread continuously, swallowing the Azure Mountain King up. The ground split apart as countless yellow bars extended upwards, forming a gigantic dungeon that sealed the fog inside.

“The doubled spell of dense fog formations with the addition of a secret composition makeup should be enough to delay the opposite party by at least three minutes!” Not in the least bit zealous to continue with the fight, Leylin turned around to leave.

Fatality’s Tip did not cause any major injuries to the Azure Mountain King. Adding the fact that he was a Morning Star Magus, he definitely had some trump cards hidden away. After multiple provocations, he could become hysterical, and if that happened Leylin didn’t want to face him head-on.

As such, his silhouette immediately morphed into a black shadow, and faded out rapidly in the midst of battle.

*Rumble!* About two minutes later, a huge blue sword streaked across the width of the dungeon, and it collapsed like a mountain that had its summit shaved off.

Dust flew and rocks flew everywhere. When the dust cloud dispersed, two bloodshot eyes appeared out of the darkness.

“Leylin! Leylin! LEYLIN! I’m going to KILL YOU!” he yelled at the top of his voice. When he couldn’t locate signs of Leylin, he started to roar furiously.

Following his hiss, massive blue energy waves swept forth, wreaking havoc on the region. Soil rumbled and stones rolled as the very earth split apart. It looked like armageddon had arrived.

Everything that had happened had nothing to do with Leylin anymore. After escaping to a safe distance, he’d immediately changed course, ordering the A.I. Chip to clean all traces and marks on his body.

After multiple rounds of purification, Leylin came upon a newly established cave.

“My Lord!” A ray of light shone in the middle of the cave. A beautiful woman with a slender, proportionate body curtsied, behind her standing Parker and the other men.

“Hmm! Looks like you have successfully saved them all. Well done!”

Chapter 490: Large Crisis

Naturally, this female Magus was Tanasha. As a Crystal Phase Magus from the Forgotten Land, she had a sensitive identity and served as Leylin’s hidden force.

Tanasha also participated secretly in several battles. As soon as he’d noticed the sudden change in the Parble family, Leylin had sent her to rescue his Magi in the castle.

”Parker, how are the casualties?” Even so, injuries and deaths couldn’t be prevented, although it was still better than being wiped out.

”Master, we lost two rank 3 Magi this time, one of them at the Vapour Phase…” Parker didn’t look well, and the big loss this time could be seen on his face.

After listening carefully, Leylin sighed.

The Magus world was full of danger. Death was common in fights between Magi, so those who fought in battles seldom cared about it.

But as an enforcer, he couldn’t say this out loud.

Leylin pointed three fingers to the sky. ”I swear on the name of Leylin Farlier, every Magus who fights to the death for me will be adequately compensated.”

His vassals followed him for different reasons. Some of them wanted to further improve themselves, but many worked for their families like Parker. Thus Leylin’s oath successfully relaxed them.

”What happened in the Parble Family was very complicated. Prepare a room for me, I need to contact the headquarters.” Knowing there were great dangers, it would be foolish to make further movements.

Leylin had his own forces to back him, and it was time he put them to good use. This clone was only rank 3, and this was his only chance to kill it.

He was very confident in the strength of his forces.

”Your room has been prepared, please follow me!” Tanasha led Leylin deep into the cave.

Although this secret base was temporary, it wasn’t a big problem to construct several rooms using spells.

Parker looked at Tanasha whose face was covered by a black cloth, moving his mouth but finally said nothing.

Only now did he learn that another Crystal Magus served his master! Rich in experience, he felt an aura of danger from the cold-blooded aura of that Magus.

How many hidden powers did master have?

Although he was used to his master performing miracles, Parker felt like he was shrouded with another mysterious veil.

Of course, this was just his imagination, he would rather die than inquire about his master’s secrets or even the woman’s identity. This was how a subordinate should behave.

Not only him, the other Magi accepted the existence of Tanasha immediately as well, as if she had been with them all this time.

And with the help of Tanasha, their base was quickly tidied up.

When facing great danger, great power could give people confidence. This wasn’t limited to ordinary people; even Magi felt the same way.

In a cave dug with earth elemental spells, Leylin found the secret imprint of his communications officer. He pressed his hand on the imprint, and soon the device was covered in black light.

After several minutes, Leylin’s face turned dark, ”It can’t get through!”

He pressed down on the imprint once more, ”Headquarters! Is anyone there?”

After several attempts, he couldn’t help but admit that the liaison assigned specifically to him, who was expected to be ready for his message any second, had deserted his post.

Knowing this, Leylin frowned. He had no other backing in the central continent except the Ouroboros Clan, and he would be in danger if something happened in headquarters. The pressure from Azure Mountain City alone would force him to hide in the underground of society, with the dregs of the Magus world.

”What the hell happened?” Leylin searched the other pages. There was no feedback from Kesha. Lucian was there but he didn’t say much, just that some accident had occurred and all outer-ring movements were cancelled.

”Cancelled? Now?” Leylin smiled coldly, directly ending contact with Lucian. Judging from his tone, something must have happened in the headquarters that caused them to lose their ability to react.

And from his secretive manner, he still didn’t take him to be a core member, and was suspicious at this key moment.

It was too dangerous without accurate information. Leylin considered calmly for a moment, and flipped to another scale-shaped red imprint.

After a short while connecting, a response finally came in, “Is this Leylin?”

”It is!” Leylin spoke in a low voice, ”Freya, are you in the headquarters now?”

”Yeah, I’m here. Leylin, it’s now an emergency! You better come back immediately and not go out!”

Leylin was surprised about her panicked voice. She hadn’t acted like this even when the bloodline of her own family was deteriorating.

”I have trouble here too. The Parble Family colluded with Azure Mountain City, and even the clone of the Azure Mountain King is here!” Leylin related the information he hadn’t told Lucian just now.

”The Parble Family, a clone of the Azure Mountain King?” she cried out in surprise. Anyone would be nervous if a Morning Star Magus, even if just a clone, appeared in their hinterland.

”I knew it!”

”Knew what?” Leylin asked.

Freya seemed to notice her slip of tongue, and after a while she spoke in a low voice, ”Are you in a safe place?”

”Absolutely safe!” Leylin moved his fingers, and black light covered the whole room.

”Wait a minute, I need to change into an encrypted channel!” As Freya’s voice arrived, the light on that brand first vanished and then returned, now brighter.

”Things don’t seem good…” Leylin listened carefully, he knew that what Freya was going to say definitely affected his life.

”We can’t make contact with Mentor or the other two elders…” Freya’s nervous voice came from the brand.

”Can’t make contact? What does that mean?” Leylin was confused.

”My teacher said they were about to find the coordinates of the Purgatory World, and they needed to conduct detailed experiments and couldn’t be disturbed! Thus, they cut off all connection with the outside. Yesterday, I found that the spiritual flame my teacher gave me was about to die out, so I broke into my teacher’s lab…and…”

”What did you find?” Leylin’s voice also became nervous.

”Nobody was in that lab, even the astral gate had stopped working!” Intermittent sobs laced Freya’s words.

”The same thing happened in the labs of the other two elders!”

”I…I…I…” Leylin was about to curse, so he took a deep breath to calm himself down.

Experiments on the astral gate were very dangerous, and if you didn’t return before the astral stones ran out of power, the Magi who passed through would be trapped in another world.

As Freya said, the astral stones had run out, and even the spiritual flame was extremely weak; they were trapped in another world!

The three Morning Star Magi were the backbone of the Ouroboros Clan. Once they lost them, it wouldn’t be long before the whole clan was destroyed. No wonder the headquarters was in a mess, and even Lucian was thrown into disarray.

”Are you sure?” Leylin felt his throat tighten, but he still held on to hope.

”We have tried everything to contact them, even projecting the spiritual flame. Nothing worked… My Mentor… I’m afraid they’re lost in another world…”

On the other side of the brand, Freya couldn’t restrain her choking sobs.

When someone was lost in another world, it wasn’t as simple as not being able to come back. Big worlds always hated outsiders, and once you were unable to return in time, the Magi stuck there would have no good end.

Nibble away from the safety of the astral gate, and finally reverse the attitude of the world, that was the best way to seize another world.

Now, the three Morning Star elders were like ordinary people lost in the boundless ocean, surrounded by bloody sharks.

Nothing could be worse than this.

After she wept for a while, Freya’s voice finally grew firm, ”Do you know why the Azure Mountain King is here?”

”I have no idea, I thought it was for the Parble Family or me, but now I’m not sure…” Leylin smiled bitterly.

If it was just an experimental accident, there was still hope. But what if the whole thing was set up by their enemies?

Thinking about the omens of war recently, and the abnormal behaviour of the Azure Mountain King, Leylin thought this was very possible.

After thousands of years, why did they find the Purgatory World at this exact time? It made sense if this was their enemies’ plot.

”Good job! Good job! One astral coordinate trapped three Morning Star Magi…” Leylin took a deep breath, if he was right, after the Morning Star Magi of the Ouroboros Clan disappeared, they would be dealt with as fast as lightning.

If they couldn’t settle this matter, from now on, whether the Ouroboros Clan would continue to exist in the central continent was a question.

Cutting off the connection, Leylin fell into deep thought.

Chapter 492: Killing the Clone

“So you’re relying on this?” the Azure Mountain King laughed coldly, “Do you think you can control this hurricane? It may be possible if I came with my main body…”

Nonetheless, his face was full of fear, and he unconsciously took a few steps back.

“If you don’t try, how would you know?” Leylin chuckled, and suddenly rubbed the ring on his hand. A strange energy wave seemed to pass by at the speed of light.

Miles away, Parker looked at the communicator in his hands with a stern expression. He then ordered, “Activate!”

“Beginning operation! Preparing number 1 energy reactor!” Snoopy shouted immediately.

“The elemental particle gathering device is complete, beginning ground vibration!”

Many Warlocks, as hardworking as ants, began to get busy, and one by one, strange symbols were lit up on the surface of the huge pyramidal reactor.

*Rumble!* At this moment, the surface of the ground seemed to come alive as a large amount of energy was bound and transmitted towards Leylin’s direction.

This violent earthquake did not cause much trouble for the warlocks, as expected. Snoopy wiped away the cold sweat on his forehead and went to his grandfather’s side with an evident look of worry on his face, “Grandfather, will Mentor be able to succeed? I’ve never heard of this idea before… No! I wouldn’t be able to think of this even in my dreams! Once any node goes wrong, I’m afraid what awaits Mentor will be…”

Before he could finish speaking, a thick, muscular palm pressed down on his shoulders, “Snoopy! You have to believe in your mentor!”

Parker’s eyes did not mask his respect for Leylin, “He is the most profound scholar and the strictest Magus amongst everyone I’ve met! Once the lord makes a decision, it will definitely be correct, we only need to follow and execute according to the plan devised by the lord!”

After interacting with them for more than a century, be it in force or knowledge, Leylin had long ago subdued these men of his.

“Yes!” Snoopy nodded repeatedly, and his previous worries disappeared immediately.

At another place, Tanasha was also doing the same thing.

A perfectly straight lightning rod, almost piercing through the horizon, stood firmly on a pile of black rocks.

Thunder roared and lightning flashed. Many blue electric waves growled and rushed towards the black needle, before diverging in all directions through the path that was laid out.

“Sir! I Hope you will succeed!” Tanasha grew a little excited in her heart, praying silently.

……

“Preparations for node 1 completed, review of node 2 completed, preparing to charge node 3…”

Data kept pouring out from the A.I. Chip continuously and many fluorescent-blue information windows flashed past Leylin’s eyes.

*Rumble!* The howling hurricane that was brewing in the sky seemed to be controlled by someone, and it slowly began to transform and pack together, converging behind Leylin.

The windstorm roared, dissipating the dark gas and silently turning the rocks and plants on the roadside to dust. It then wrapped the Azure Mountain King within.

“How… How is this possible? Why can you……” The Azure Mountain King’s eyes almost popped out.

How could a mere rank 3 Crystal Phase Magus possess such enormous power?

After he came here, he had definitely tested with his soul force that there were no other Magi lying in ambush. There were also no signs of any spell formation!

“I am unable to hide anything from soul force scans, hence I did not plan anything here…” Leylin stood above the hurricane, as if he was a deity from another world.

“Thus, the closest spell formation that I’ve set up is 45 kilometers away. The underground hurricane is being manipulated through redistribution points and could be temporarily kept under control! I call this spell formation—farcast support spell formation!”

Using the superimposition of small influences from other areas, he ultimately gained control over the hurricane!

It was easier said than done. To do it, the calculations needed were terrifyingly complex, fit to be described as perverse.

Even if there was a slight error the data, there was a possibility that the hurricane would ultimately lose all control. As the one to bear the brunt of the damage, Leylin would be the first to die without any remains.

Such horrifying calculations, even the Azure Mountain King felt giddy from just simulating them in his head.

Leylin had done something even Morning Star Magi could not thanks to his A.I. Chip, a scientific chip from his previous world which possessed incredible abilities after numerous extreme transformation and advancements!

“The hurricane can destroy anything under rank 4, you are destined to die today!” Leylin’s expression was calm, his face showing no signs of sadness or happiness.

But the hurricane, which was under his control, suddenly screeched. A large gust of strong black wind surrounded the Azure Mountain King and began to spin around him, as if it wanted to drag him into the eye of the hurricane.

“No! I have not fallen yet!” The Azure Mountain King’s eyes flushed red, and his facial muscles twitched as he suddenly growled.

Explosions rang out as the crystal clear soul force transformed into a defensive film on his body. Terrifying accessories, which had reached the level of magic artifacts, began to explode one by one.

The massive explosion caused a horrifying driving force, and even the hurricane was momentarily blocked out.

Using this hard-earned chance, the Azure Mountain King immediately dashed out to break through the barrier.

“You can’t escape!” The large Multi-Armed Race phantom thrashed and growled behind Leylin. The hurricane gathered in Leylin’s hands as he stood before the Azure Mountain King and threw out a sudden punch.

*Boom!* Like the roar of an ancient giant snake, along with the accompanying howls of the many hurricanes, a terrifying energy instantly extinguished the explosion from before, breaking through the Azure Mountain King’s body.

Even if it was soul power, under the the besiegement of the hurricane, it was exhausted too quickly. The protective film immediately crackled and broke.

Cracks began appearing one after another, and due to Leylin’s attack, the Azure Mountain King was once again pushed back into the eye of the hurricane.

While watching Leylin, who stood outside like a war god, a hint of despair surfaced on the Azure Mountain King’s face…

*Rumble!* It was as if the world exploded, reaching its end.

Among the many dark storms, a touch of blue light suddenly exploded. It immediately intensified, offsetting the dark storms persistently.

The terrifying energy waves dissipated as streaks of silver cracks in the space emerged endlessly.

The dark storms howled, but it also seemed to weaken under the blue radiance as time passed. At the same time, the blue radiance slowly began to dim.

The earth rumbled, and after what seemed like a sky-shaking and violent magnitude 9 earthquake, everything finally calmed down. Only, the surroundings had already been destroyed beyond recognition.

Even a part of the West Sea Canyon was totally wiped out, becoming a large, ruinous rocky plain.

“Master!”

This was the scene that Tanasha and Parker, who had rushed over, saw. Their faces seemed to search for answers anxiously, until they saw Leylin who was standing on a large rock proudly. Their faces were immediately overcome with delight.

“Yes!” Leylin nodded.

Currently, he was in a very bad condition. Not only were there blue wounds all over his body that were bubbling and corroding it, there was also an obvious dent on his chest.

In his hands, there was an already prepared crystalised test tube, in which laid a piece of burnt flesh. Surrounding it were some squirming tentacles.

“I’m fine!” Leylin waved, stopping Tanasha and Parker’s greetings.

“I give you all an hour’s time, search this area immediately and look for bloody pieces of flesh like this! No matter what the outcome is an hour later, we will leave immediately!”

“Yes, Sir!”

Watching his men busy themselves, a bitter smile emerged on Leylin’s face.

The Azure Mountain King was indeed a Morning Star Magus, with an extremely determined mind. After he realised that there was no hope of escaping, he immediately cast some sort of secret spell, detonating his clone.

The self-destruction of a rank 3 Magus’ clone would cause major damage.

Not only was Leylin’s spell formation utterly defeated, he himself had sustained serious injuries. This could be said to be a loss for both parties.

‘But as long as these things can be obtained, it’ll be worth it,’ Leylin put away the pieces of flesh safely, before his heart lightened.

Although the Azure Mountain King had self-destructed, losing him the opportunity to collect his complete body, the tissue structures of these bloody pieces of flesh and such were enough for the A.I. Chip to study for a long time.

And after obtaining these, the A.I. Chip’s deductions on the Morning Star Realm would be able to advance to at least 50% and above!

“If it’s like that, the conditions are more or less all set! We only need to prepare for the Azure Mountain King’s counterattack!” Leylin stroked his chin.

Originally, he and the Oakheart Clan were prepared to give their lives to achieve their goals. Now, the other party’s Morning Star Magus had lost his clone at his hands. Surely the Azure Mountain King would be going crazy.

‘We cannot stay in this territory anymore, we must hurry back to the organisation and evacuate as soon as possible…’ Leylin was stuck in thought.

Although it still seemed peaceful at his Onyx Castle in the core of the Ouroboros Clan, with Robin’s Parble Family reduced to their sorry state, was it really?

Perhaps, as of now, only the area at the headquarters of the Phosphorescence Swamp could forcibly maintain stability.

Although they lacked Morning Star battle power, under circumstances where outsiders were still unsure, keeping it a secret for a period of time was no problem at all.

Furthermore, based on the Ouroboros Clan’s arduous accumulation as well as the spell formations, defence installations and such by the Morning Star Warlocks ancestors, hindering a certain Morning Star Magus for a duration was still not an issue.

What Leylin needed most right now, was time!

This was because the headquarters of the Ouroboros Clan was definitely a point of attack for many enemies in the future. Once it was confirmed that the battle powers of the Morning Star were gone, there was a high chance that they might face a siege from numerous Morning Star Magi.

By that time, the headquarters would be a deathtrap!

If they lost the other territories, without advancing to the Morning Star level before the Phosphorescence Swamp was attacked, all of the Warlocks at the headquarters could only accept death!

Chapter 493: Distractions

“All in all, Phosphorescence Swamp is going to be the safest right now, but the most dangerous place in the end……”

Leylin smiled reluctantly, ”It’s just that… do I have any other choices?”

At this time, he was sure the Azure Mountain King was hot on his heels. Once he left the Ouroboros Clan, he feared he would not get to live another day.

Unlike his rank 3 clone, the Azure Mountain King was a famed Morning Star Magus! The disparity in power was too large for any strategies to be of use.

Thus, he was left with no choice but to take a gamble. Fortunately, he had already exterminated the opposite party’s clone, earning him and the Ouroboros Clan some extra time!

Otherwise, if they allowed the Azure Mountain King to continue to stir up trouble, word may leak out to other power-thirsty parties, that the Ouroboros Clan no longer had Morning Star Magi defending it! He could imagine them swimming forward like sharks towards their prey.

For now, since the Azure Mountain King’s matter had been settled by Leylin, he’d presumed Leylin’s strength was why Gilbert and the others chose to lay low.

This was what Leylin was striving for, a little of their apprehension!

“Morning Star realm! I must advance to the Morning Star realm!” Leylin clenched his teeth.

At this moment, Tanasha brought forward a transparent box, “My Lord, this is our harvest.”

Inside the box were some scraps of flesh and hair, and even some blood-stained clothes and other fabrics and such.

“Well done! For your contributions, I shall reward you in the form of contribution points later on. Right now, let’s go home…..” In front of his subordinates, Leylin resumed the attitude of a master.

……

“My Lord!” Back at his own Magus Tower, upon hearing the green tower genie’s greetings, Leylin felt as if he had been away for a lifetime.

His departure had started with a banquet, celebrating Freya advancing to the Crystal Phase.

Who would’ve thought that, within such a short time, so many drastic changes would take place. Even the entire Ouroboros Clan was in a crisis, and was almost destroyed.

The failed mission of Gilbert and the other two was something Leylin could never have predicted.Morning Star Magi’s failed mission on a whole, was something Leylin could have never predicted.

After losing the deterrence of Morning Star Magi, the Ouroboros Clan immediately showed signs of instability.

“Tower genie, backup the entire experimental data to the A.I. Chip. Destroy all original experiments, starting from the natural resources. Prepare to transfer!” Leylin drew a deep breath, and requested.

“Authorization confirmed. Spiritual force connected, data transmission in progress!” Compared to a human Magus, the tower genie’s level of compliance is as good as first class. Immediately, a link was formed between it and the A.I. Chip.

Leylin had always held the habit of backing up his important experimental data to the A.I. Chip. The amount the genie had was only a small part of the whole, and he took the time to patch up the holes in his database.

The most important step was to destroy the experiments themselves. For the past century, Leylin had secretly carried out many bloodline experiments. He had been fortunate to not leave any clues behind, otherwise he would have gotten into deep water.

Following the command of the formation genie, many secret paths and doors started opening up, revealing the concealed spaces and storage facilities.

Inside, bountiful magic crystals and precious objects glowed in brilliant lights and vibrant colours. It was a feast for one’s eyes. Leylin heaved a sigh and picked out many of the stored magic crystals.

He was sure he had provoked the Azure Mountain King to the maximum this time, thus he didn’t have high hopes of being able to preserve the Magus Tower.

Compared with the main headquarters at the Phosphorescence Swamp, his Magus Tower would be the first to be ravaged. Since he had decided to seek refuge at the main headquarters, he didn’t want to be taken advantage of and lose his magic crystals.

With these thoughts in mind, he turned to the experimental room where he absorbed Lamia radiation.

After complicated and meticulous verification, Leylin saw the brilliant milky-white bone in the center of the crystal ball.

“A.I. Chip!” Leylin’s face contorted as he yelped.

“Begin compatibility scan, unscrambling data in progress…” A huge amount of data flowed in the form of blue streaks of light from Leylin’s eyes, and seeped into the crystal ball held by a machine.

After two minutes of data transmission, a clear, distinct sound echoed, as a tiny pin-sized hole appeared on the surface of the crystal ball, slowly enlarging.

“This is what my advancement to Morning Star will depend most upon!” Leylin exclaimed and sighed. He drew out a box made of crystal and carefully kept the Lamia bone.

Prior to this, he didn’t want the Lamia bone to be kept on him for fear of Gilbert finding out. But right now, there wasn’t even a single Morning Star Warlock in the headquarters, so Leylin naturally had nothing to be afraid of.

“Mentor, are we really leaving now?” Before they set off, Snoopy looked at the black tower and Onyx Castle in the distance, his eyes filled with a look of unwillingness to let go.

Having stayed here for more than a thousand years, he had already developed feelings for it, hence his hesitance to leave.

Similarly, Kubler, Parker and the others who were behind Leylin felt the exact same hesitance and unwillingness, even though they had obeyed Leylin’s orders and packed all their belongings.

“We must leave!” Leylin’s reply was resolute and decisive. “You should know the situation and how things are right now. Except for the main headquarters, everywhere else is dangerous….”

Parker and the rest solemnly nodded their heads. They had not found out about the three missing Morning Star Magi yet. However, the chaos that had happened was enough to keep them on the edge for a long time.

Magi who were able to live past three, four or five hundred years were all intelligent, and the recent spate of events had made them realise that something unusual was going on. Hence, their support for Leylin’s decision was unanimous.

Glancing at his rather muddle-headed apprentice, Leylin shook his head and patted his shoulders:”We will be back! I promise!”

“Mmm. I believe you, Mentor!” Snoopy nodded his head passionately. Parker, on the other hand, forced a smile.

…….

Inside Phosphorescence Swamp.

Numerous sulphur-filled bubbles rose from the sludge, becoming green balls of flame as they escaped.

Erected in the center of the swamp, the Warlock City was as busy as always. In fact, the population seemed to have increased.

It wasn’t just one or two families that could feel the oddity in the air. In the early days, when there were instabilities at the border, many Marquises and Counts had reallocated their families and servants over here, blowing up population and city.

As for the issues of their territories and such, they had no worry about that.

To the Warlocks at the top of society, commoners were like wild grass. After trimming them, come spring time and they would tenaciously grow again. So if the taxes were reduced for the people, in less than 10 years, the population would boom again.

Regardless of whether it was the invading troop or the defence troop , they did not need these commoners as resources, thus the commoners were able to lead a rather good life before and after the war with no major changes.

Compared to these commoners, the Warlocks’ regrets would be losing their castles, Magus Towers and such.

Just like Leylin, who had built his Magus Tower in his own territory. He supposed that after the war was over, his tower would be gone too. And it did not matter who the enemy was, they would be ruthless and would helped themselves to the structures. Also, once a tower genie discerned a master, she would never change. Thus, total destruction was the only way.

“Hehe… Leylin, it looks like the bad blood between you and the Oakheart Clan is serious. Looking at this latest intelligence report, your territory had been occupied by him and your Magus Tower has been demolished…” Freya smiled as she handed the intelligence report to Leylin.

“It is serious!” Leylin stroked his nose, ”Even their chief died in my hands!”

In his heart, he silently added ‘and a Morning Star’s clone’ next to it. Under such circumstances, if the opposite party were to be polite to him, it would truly be odd.

After moving to the Ouroboros Clan headquarters, over ten days had passed and within this time, many things had happened.

Every territory had its fair share of unceasing riots, and there were multiple forces would invade these areas. Naturally, Leylin’s territory was not spared .

Freya, too, had lost her territory. Hence, she teased Leylin with a bit of schadenfreude.

However, Leylin could sense the fear and restlessness beneath Freya’s smile. This time, the power of the enemy had surpassed the expectations of many. The Azure Mountain Clan was but one part only, there were other more powerful ones yet to show themselves.

The Ouroboros Clan was strong in appearance but weak in reality, and everyone could see it. Hence the minor skirmishes at the borders had escalated to entire territories being taken over.

Even the outer regions of Phosphorescence Swamp were not spared. From time to time, scouts sent by many different powerful families were discovered. Warlocks from the Ouroboros Clan could only rely on the headquarters’ defensive spells as a core, building an extremely narrow defensive perimeter and guarding it resolutely.

Anyone with a discerning eye could tell that if the Morning Star military strength did not make an appearance soon in the Ouroboros Clan, the entire clan could face imminent destruction.

“Over at the astral gate, how is the progress?” Seeing Freya’s strong and obstinate persona, Leylin couldn’t console her directly, as otherwise, he would have hurt her pride. Instead, he changed the subject and asked her a question.

The truth of the matter was, the root of all the problems were the three elders. If they could appear immediately, even if just one of them could show their face in public, not only would the Warlocks of the entire Ouroboros Clan gain confidence from their pillar of strength, the number of enemy scouts would reduce drastically too.

“Some of the Marquises from the technology department have been working for days in there…” Freya smiled wryly.

“But in the end…. Only someone of at least a Morning Star Magus status, can open an astral gate. Otherwise, no one can support the crossover of the body. Forget rescuing them, we can’t even find someone here qualified to open the astral gate…”

Seeing Freya, Leylin knew deep in her heart that she had some disagreements with the Blood Duchess Emma and the other two Morning Star Warlocks. But since she was a student of theirs, she couldn’t say anything.

“You can’t blame our Mentors, the allure of the Purgatory World is simply too huge…” Leylin sighed.